[SPEAKER_07]: Once upon a time, Sonic was exclusively Sega's darling.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sega's exit from the console wars means that more gamers get to enjoy Sonic in their games.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's mostly a good thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And turnabout is fair play.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll soon be able to race Sonic and others as Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_07]: Prepare your rush jets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you more about this story and the rest of the week's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Starting right now on the show, where every gamer has a voice...
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're back and live once again tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Episode number 1062 for September the 21st, 2025.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you remember the 21st night of September?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's myself, Rob Roberts, and my co-host.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello to the one and only Dark Sakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm okay yeah um you've been doing some streaming this week some fun games playing um I've been playing some different stuff and going back to things but I'll talk about that during my gaming week all right sounds good uh we'll go over and say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki hello hi Loki how are you
[SPEAKER_06]: What is this game you've got playing behind you tonight as we are, of course, taping live as we do every week at 9 o'clock Eastern, 6 o'clock Pacific, The Voice Geeks Network, twitch.tv slash VOG Network, VOG Network, usually right after the Bobby Blackwolf show, except our pal Bobby has the night off.
[SPEAKER_06]: He is listening to polka music as he posted about on Blue Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, that's code for Weird Al Yankovic, which, you know, I can understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird Al's a worthy reason to take a night off.
[SPEAKER_06]: So,
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was an amazing show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a tour, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I feel like he's, I wonder if he's seeing the exact same thing because I feel like it's part of a festival out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could be wrong, but I feel like that was a thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like there's other bands too, but Weird Al's like the highlight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: as far as I know it was always just Al and Puddles the Clown or Puddles Pity Party that would have been a fun show I don't know why I always miss that stuff I liked that a lot more than I thought I would because I normally hate clowns oh yeah, I didn't think about the sort of conflict there not an amazing voice at least Puddles Pity Party makes clowns bearable
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I like sad, angry clowns better.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not even going to ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to mess around with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's say, oh, I was saying with Loki, you have the game playing behind you, and I don't think I recognize it, but is that C-3PO?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a Star Wars game?
[SPEAKER_06]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It is not a Star Wars game.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, this is Borderlands 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, how do I?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I was gonna say, how do I not recognize that?
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, I'm like, well, I haven't really played the other Borderlands games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually know that's a lie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did play quite a bit of Borderlands one, at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: But like one and two were all like Wild West.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this looks sci fi Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there like a tone change that happened in the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I'm just... There's always sci-fi in Borderlands, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but like, not looking like you're in a space station or whatever this is that's playing on the game right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's just a villain, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't villain things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get into some gaming news, which I actually, again, I feel like we've really been in this news drought lately.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what the heck is going on, what's in the air, but we do have some things to talk about, of course, you know, but it's just kind of odd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they terrific things?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, well, there's a couple stories tonight that are fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what we're here for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We let everyone know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We give you the pulse on the gaming world so you don't have to go look all this stuff by yourself and be depressed about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The good, the bad, and the ugly.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think DarkSakura, you have a kickoff topic for us tonight that is kind of bad and ugly.
[SPEAKER_05]: This ain't just ugly, it's fugly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, just when you thought it was safe to spend money again, Microsoft is raising Xbox prices in the US.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Series S 512 is going from $380 to $400.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's a $20 increase for some of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Series X Digital is going up $50.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Series X is going up $150.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the Series X 2TB Galaxy Black Special Edition is going from $730 to $800.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is the second price increase this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the last time they raised prices was in May.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I agree, Brad.
[SPEAKER_05]: JFC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or FFS in my case.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I mean, it's not just Microsoft doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is just like a more recent trend.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, think about our current economic environment.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Sony has raised their prices earlier this year, and we know that the Switch 2 pre-orders were delayed because Nintendo was looking into their options.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it was higher than people expected but now the Switch has a price you know price race too I think that happened what beginning of August end of July and all the accessories too got a hike too I'm glad I got mine free free and it still works but yeah yeah so if you want even the cheapo Xbox
[SPEAKER_05]: 400 bones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the cheaper way to play Xbox right now is to not fucking bother and do the cloud.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, honestly, seems like, I mean, well, you know, it depends on your internet, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if you're getting charged a lot for bandwidth and that's not going to be a cheap option.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it sure looks more and more like the cloud is such an attractive option because no matter what your PC is powered at, as long as you meet that bare minimum to do cloud gaming, which isn't much, you know, you can access Xbox and stuff on Game Pass, which is probably why Microsoft's leaning more and more into the cloud.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got my gigabit ethernet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got my Mac Studio that comes with a gigabit jack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't need no Xbox to make my life happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like Microsoft's adding more to the cloud gaming too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like I just saw a story about things that aren't necessarily in your library you can still stream.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'd have to purchase it one way or the other, I'm sure, but they're trying to open up more and more of the cloud streaming, which makes sense because the obvious question in the room is who's going to buy a fucking Xbox right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who is going to buy an Xbox right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like
[SPEAKER_04]: People to whom money is no object.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to say you're a fool if you buy an Xbox right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are free to spend money how you see fit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if that is the value to you, then go off, sis.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I really feel like the Xbox is set up to fail right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I completely understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is because of the political environment and things going on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not like Microsoft's sole decision or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: The industry is set up to fail.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's another way to look at it for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or they're trying to solve...
[SPEAKER_05]: What they see as a problem with the only way that a corporation knows how, they don't think outside of the box.
[SPEAKER_05]: The last person to truly think outside of the box was Iwata.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, as far as the head of the company.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was reading the other day an interview with the head of Larian who was also just like,
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they're doing it all wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to make sure that your user base is happy and you keep it into something that they want to spend that money on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looking at chat, I feel like this just puts a lot in perspective what PodCulture says here over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: PodCulture says, I paid less and I bought mine from a damn scalper in the pandemic, which that's a whole other can of worms.
[SPEAKER_06]: But whether you agree with PodCulture doing that or not, it sure puts a lot into perspective.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, it's wild.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, I just, I just, like, for me, if I'm Phil Spencer and I'm Xbox, which thank God I'm not, but if I'm there, like, I am just at this point starting to really step away from trying to sell hardware and really pushing how software can carry.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do, how is the cloud lucrative?
[SPEAKER_06]: How is Xbox Game Pass lucrative?
[SPEAKER_06]: How do indie games still run great on Xbox One?
[SPEAKER_06]: And that makes a decent solution.
[SPEAKER_06]: And like, I, I, and it,
[SPEAKER_06]: To Microsoft's credit, they have been leaning into this for a while, certainly more so than their competitors, with the whole every box is an Xbox and that whole thing that they have been doing for several months ahead of anything that happened in the political climate.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I do feel like Microsoft is probably better set up for this kind of crap than anybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: but I mean not that Sony seems to be hurting but I would still argue the same thing and say the exact same thing about PlayStation 5 right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's a smart time to buy a PlayStation 5 either or a PlayStation 5 Pro.
[SPEAKER_06]: I realize the price of those hasn't gone up as much but you still know there is a literal artificial price increase to those systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just so weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what unchecked power by someone who doesn't know what he's doing happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, 100%.
[SPEAKER_06]: 100%.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100, Matt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, not to get too political, but I mean, they already made H1B visas, you know, now a subscription model.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, it's just the way the world's going, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, literally, I don't smoke, but I feel like sitting on the porch and just taking a big drag off a cigarette and just going...
[SPEAKER_06]: What's next?
[SPEAKER_06]: What are the horrors we're going to wake up tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_06]: Damage report!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just... I'm just at this point where nothing... Well, because every day shocks me, nothing shocks me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, here's the latest bit of drama I heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was listening to... It was like some Fox News interview with a constitutional specialist who was like, yeah, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: There will be no third or fourth term because it's in the Constitution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, are you sure?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, dude, I'm a constitutional scholar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people are always like, oh, well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I say no?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me put it this way, because this is really what I'm seeing happening on a wide scale.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've said this a lot about gaming, and yes, this does have to do with video games, because this is the exact same thing I've been saying about video game media and the way we perceive things and the way things go on social media.
[SPEAKER_06]: The truth doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, shocking, but that's the facts.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the perception that guides things at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what some people do politically?
[SPEAKER_06]: They get on there and they push, they push, they talk, they talk, they lie, they lie, and try to shift people's perceptions because then that becomes the truth.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this has been happening ever since it was Barack Obama wasn't born in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: When like literally there is a birth certificate that says Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has literally been that since, what was that, 20 years ago at this point?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not that long.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you didn't want Hawaii to be considered part of the United States, then maybe you shouldn't colonized it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, and you know, if you're pissed that we're getting political on this whole thing, tough titty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this is, this Xbox going up, video games getting expensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is nothing else to blame for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to challenge your perception.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's something we can all do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me, you, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Challenge your perceptions.
[SPEAKER_06]: And look at what is really driving these price increases.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fact check all the things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the way we escape from the harshness of reality is that we play video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's talk about our gaming weeks and the types of video games that we've been playing to take our minds off of the horrors of the real world.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually took a break off of Dead by Daylight for the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I did log in a couple of times just to, you know, check stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I took the week off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had a really awful, gut-wrenching week.
[SPEAKER_05]: and um I've had a lot going on at work so I just have been trying to focus on things that make me happy and so um I uh
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Palia.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Avatar Frontiers of Pandora because shooting the silly, terrible human beings in that game make me really happy because people suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: I put it to a vote on my Discord.
[SPEAKER_05]: for what game I should play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I've played through Dragon Age Inquisition like four times on stream and Mass Effect twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three times, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meaning the whole trilogy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the whole trilogy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I was like, okay, so what should I play?
[SPEAKER_05]: and everyone wanted to see Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, okay, which version?
[SPEAKER_05]: The PlayStation one or this put together edited Saturn one?
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're like, the Saturn one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, okay, play the Saturn one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm like two thirds through the first castle just running around being an idiot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sad I missed that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to see that version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Accidentally using Soulsteel the one time I don't want to use it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and then there's this one uh like sword knight guy that's like a pain in the ass to get through but if you can jump past him and then go behind you get a room with stuff but then you punch the wall and kneel down in the wall and after like a minute or so you go down a platform and right there is the jewel knuckle and you get like amazing attack at a really early level
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like it's been so long since I played Symphony of the Night on any platform.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to experience it on Saturn, but I haven't really played the game forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can hook you up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I'm going to be playing Palia tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just, you know, again, I want to keep some chill vibes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going back, though, to my...
[SPEAKER_05]: Try to get P100 Pig and my Dracula Adept, which is actually kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be honest, it's hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not looking forward to Hellmaster at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I've also just been playing a lot of Avatar Frontiers of Pandora.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also found a translation for the Super Famicom Record of Lodoss War RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: I forgot that it was semi-tactics based.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I played it for a little bit and got all nostalgic for the anime.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm actually reading the first of the books right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: For anyone who doesn't know, Record of Lodoss War, if I recall correctly, was a tabletop RPG first, based off D&D.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it spun anime and video games and all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I played a little bit of that, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to decide if I wanted to do another SNES RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was just trying a few different ones and seeing if it hit any kind of joy in my heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: So far, not really much of anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might start Marvelous, considering that.
[SPEAKER_05]: but I also started playing Minecraft and by started playing I meant I have the game and started downloading mods and I am going to be playing well I played before and then I got bored my account expired so I had to get it again but
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to be doing a bonus stream with Shay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, her delightful boyfriend Ryan is visiting from Scotland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, you two.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I probably won't be able to do that until after TwitchCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I also did promise to do a stream of playing Marvel Rivals.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I am opening that up to whoever wants to play with me and keep me from not dying.
[SPEAKER_05]: because I'll get motion sick I need someone to hold my hair when I throw up maybe it depends on when because I literally have played that game once and it wasn't even against real people it was against bots it's the only way I've played that game I'm thinking about I wanted to wait until Nightcrawler was out in the game because I know it has to happen but I have all this stuff for Invisible Woman I was thinking of either going to Emma or Phoenix I haven't decided
[SPEAKER_06]: I can figure out a healer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember who I was playing that I liked for heals but I can figure it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heals please, heals please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heal, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: As 200 Matt says, Jamie and Loki are playing Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Time for Rob to join in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I have Minecraft and I've played it before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, I don't get sucked in the way Matt does.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I kind of go, oh, for my crafting joy, I'm going to play No Man's Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I sometimes feel a little bit stuck on what to do in Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I have Palia for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I can always give it another go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for the record, Psylocke is in it, but I think it's Quanon Psylocke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But as far as... If I want my crafting, I go to Palia because I've gotten a lot better at some of the glitching.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm actually saving up to buy yet another property because they have new houses out, but I don't want to destroy my old houses to build the new houses.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new houses are infinitely customizable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you can remove walls.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can add, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: different trim and vines to the roof and all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty intense.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Talia is still my happy place.
[SPEAKER_05]: That and the Avatar game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just thinking is that if I find matches that I thought I had fun in, whether or not I won, that I would just, you know, edit out some of the slow parts and put some silly commentary on it and upload it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it took me like two hours to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was watching another Dead by Daylight pig main and was like, you know, I may as well just do this while I'm watching.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I will go ahead and give them a shout out it's Justin Bubba, UK streamer who congratulations on finishing your dissertation get your masters but we pig mains, we gotta stick together
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you mentioned TwitchCon and I kind of had a moment of like, oh crap, that is like right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's less than a month away at this point, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to have to finish fixing my pig cosplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was considering doing a Legion again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's just going to be pig for a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's go over to Loki and check on your gaming week, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just been Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been digging a hole.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very big hole.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you've been streaming Minecraft as well, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, digging a hole.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just digging the hole?
[SPEAKER_08]: Big hole?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's about 4.5 million blocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it for all your enemies?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, I thought that wasn't possible in Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you hit the bottom eventually.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Down into the core.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there is a point where you hit the bottom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, you eventually get to the bedrock layer, and then if you know the way to exploit the game to break the bedrock layer, then you just open it up into the void, and if you jump into the void, then you die.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing lives in the void.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you want to conquer the void.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can dangle mobs into the void.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a little buffer area that you can use entities, but other than that, you can't build down there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, I do love that idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then again, you can also mod the game to have a higher build limit.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could do a couple thousand, then it just really tanks the computer, though, because it has to calculate all those extra blocks and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so digging a big hole actually might end up having to be about 50% bigger, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, because I was looking at it the other day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how big it needs to be, but this is how big I'm starting.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to talk about mods.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's lots of stuff with mods.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I can help you with mods.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, good luck on your hole digging, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, most people I talk to on Blue Sky are looking to get their hole filled, so it's ironic that you're digging a giant hole in your game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I have so much material left from the hole.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I've got 200 plus shulker boxes of stone right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: for comparison a shulker box is basically a chest so it's more than I'll ever need and that was just like the first 10 layers I stopped collecting materials now, I just don't collect anything, I just let it rot maybe copper, that's about it, but everything else I just let it die because I'm like, I cannot store all of this, nor would I ever use all of this and it would actually...
[SPEAKER_08]: It would probably lag out the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can build pig shrines.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt is interested in the void, saying this void sounds pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they allow early voting?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the void might be a better place to live these days.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do not.
[SPEAKER_05]: They built Dead by Daylight and Roblox.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet it could be done in Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think someone did build something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can do some limited stuff with Redstone, or if you decide to go the route I did with Datapacks, you can do quite a bit more with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, you probably could do Dead by Daylight.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would just be tricky.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, Tango did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I found it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dead by Daylight Minecraft maps.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, I bet some maps, especially like Leary's and stuff, I bet some maps are, I don't want to say easy to recreate Minecraft, but relatively versus other things.
[SPEAKER_08]: The maps are probably somewhat easy to create.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Recreating the gameplay would be very difficult.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd probably be able to have something where you could stand on a
[SPEAKER_08]: Pressure Plate 2, Fix, Generator, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone did Dead by Midnight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure you could build some things that mimic the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Someone I knew recently built Clash of Clans.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, at that point that's kind of what you have to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, just because the game making Sands of Time is essentially, it's a random, normally it's a random generated dungeon, and so because I have to make a dungeon that goes out in all different directions, like even the main room I think is like at least
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, at least like 70 blocks by 70 blocks wide and right now the whole I have I think it's like 169 blocks by like 200 and something and then 90 blocks deep is what I was going for but I'm probably going to have to expand it at least another 100 or so blocks out the sides depending on how I end up deciding to lay everything out that's the problem is I don't have any idea how I'm going to lay anything out yet
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Folks in chat are talking about mobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loony Bard says, heck, there's a mob for Quiet Place, and that sounds kind of scary as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it made me think, okay, so speaking of scary mods, you know the thing that I'm seeing all the time now on...
[SPEAKER_06]: TikTok, that is a Roblox thing, like the newest thing in survival horror, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: I found a video of it I can play here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it's a little harder for you guys to see, but I'll show it on our Twitch TV stream.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is called One Night at Rue's, and it's RuPaul's Drag Race, and it's like they have the workroom, and it's like a horror game, and you get chased around by this giant RuPaul that looks scary as fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck, that like chases you around the shadows and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to see a place where maybe this person's getting chased by like Rue or something that is really scary when that thing is following you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it looks like Slenderman, but it's like RuPaul.
[SPEAKER_06]: And obviously we'll do that laugh, that ah-ha-ha-ha, you know, that laugh that RuPaul does.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it just looks so scary.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's another one my kids are telling me about called 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, wait, that's like an Ami game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're like, no, it's like nights as in nighttime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not 99 Nights as in, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: One million troops.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw in chat says, Roblox is scary enough as it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: SGO100Matt says, Rob, did you see that George A. Romero's daughter is coming out with a zombie movie, Queens of the Dead?
[SPEAKER_06]: I did see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That looks like it'll be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to check that out at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: OrangeRite says, you don't just lip sync for your life.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good tagline.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear that they're going to make like a big budget drag race movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like they're actually making a movie to be on the big screen that RuPaul confirmed he's starring in this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to make a movie set in the drag race universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what the fuck that means because they've made other like media like what AJ and the Queen was practically and that got canceled after one season.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was that bitch who stole Christmas movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I...
[SPEAKER_06]: I would, yeah, that's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: When are the queens going to do some actual drag racing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like all this promise of drag race and there's yet no racing going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: The promos for whatever season Sasha Colby won were all like racing themed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say the very, very first season was all racing themed too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But like, you know, now that the budget's bigger, whatever recent one that Sasha Colby won, they actually were posing with cars and shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they do lean into the jokes a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just spin it off into like a Fast and the Furious series, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fast and the fierce.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fast and the fierce?
[SPEAKER_08]: That has potential.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, SC100 Matt says needs a kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_06]: They try to push season two cross worlds, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: They try to push mobile game slop on me.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some type of like match three RuPaul game that they try to push on me all the time and ads.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, no, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's talk about my gaming week, which ironically does involve match three.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, I will mention I'm still playing Final Fantasy 11 on Cat's Eye.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm already like level 40 on Red Mage, like level 30 on Dancer, just because everything's like so hyper powered.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's been fun to like play with some of my friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But believe it or not, I've been playing something else too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, I'm playing other games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually checked out something new that just came out, but it's an old game that's new again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I checked out the Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's called Immortal Edition, but it's basically the new version of Puzzle Quest that's 4K and all the DLC included and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was only, I think, $11.99 on PlayStation right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's on sale the first week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And because PlayStation Stars is going away,
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually had like $15 worth of gifts.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I ended up getting this game for free because I had like $15 worth of credit on PlayStation Store because of everything fading with PlayStation Stars.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I ended up getting the game for free and...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so Puzzle Quest, I mean, that game was out years ago on what, the PSP?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe the DS as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on everything, I think, at one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's essentially a match-three game, but it's a little harder than that because you have to think, you know, you're always going up against some type of opponent.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, you're going up against a spider or an undead rat or, you know, I'm sure later on you actually get to fight people, but I'm still in the early stages of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you have to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you do a match three, then your opponent does a match three.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you have to think about what you're doing to the board and how that's going to affect the board to set up your opponent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the way you damage your opponent is that there's not just the regular colors that represent mana.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's red, yellow, green, blue.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then there's purple asterisks for XP.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's gold for gold.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there are skulls.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Fifth Dream says, Puzzle Quest is underrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And speaking of, the Marvel version has Captain Betsy Britton in it, so it's better than Rivals.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Marvel had a spinoff Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Puzzle Quest was everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was, what, three Puzzle Quest games?
[SPEAKER_06]: They had the Marvel Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then it just went away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like Puzzle Quest has been gone for like...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to say a decade, but at least since COVID.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't seen a new Puzzle Quest game in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't know what happened behind the scenes to let it come back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't been following it that closely, but it's cool that it's back again.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe they'll create more stuff in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seem to remember really liking Puzzle Quest 3 in particular, and I don't remember why, but maybe they'll go through and release the old games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, if you enjoy Match 3 and strategy games, I think Puzzle Quest is worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this would be a really good candidate for the Switch though I do sort of wish I had this one on a more portable type of system it's on my I bought it on PlayStation 5 but um which is fine it looks really good for a puzzle game um but if I don't know if it's on Switch 2 but if it is that's probably the way to go with it to be honest um
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to look really fast do research live to see if it's on yeah it does look like it is on Nintendo platforms it's on the regular Nintendo Switch and so I'm sure runs on Switch 2 as well so that might be the way to do it if you want a puzzle game to go on the go so that was my gaming week we're gonna move on we've got some headlines to cover in the gaming industry including one we brought up earlier and last week Loki some continued updates on this front yeah
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so Borderlands 4 has had a lot of issues with basically just optimization issues.
[SPEAKER_08]: Overall, gameplay-wise, it's been pretty positive as far as the reviews go, but there are still some struggles with...
[SPEAKER_08]: Performance even on high-end hardware and one of the things that people are running into and this is actually on console too so outside of the whole PC realm there consoles have a really bad memory leak bug right now and so unfortunately it's not really something that they they're able to fix right away but they are working on it but in the meantime they're like well if
[SPEAKER_08]: If you run into this bug, which means after playing the game for long enough, it'll start dropping FPS.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just have to save, quit, and restart.
[SPEAKER_08]: And away you go again.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had to know about this bug before releasing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those playtesters test for hours and hours at a time.
[SPEAKER_06]: This had to have come up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would assume so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would assume it did, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, and I want to acknowledge, we all know that testers find bugs that then are discussed in some sort of forum about, is it worth the time to fix this bug or should we release anyway?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can't help but get this feeling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't help but get this feeling that this release date for this game was non-negotiable under any circumstance.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's what these performance issues are leading me to believe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Along with that, you know, so they're running into, like I said, issues with like DLSS and the PC requirements and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though folks have really powerful rigs, they're barely cracking like 60 FPS or, you know, they're still getting slowdowns and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, I think as we were talking before, Randy Pitchford, not helpful in this situation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically just fighting everybody in social media and
[SPEAKER_08]: saying that, no, you're just losers with weak computers and that's why you can't run my perfect game.
[SPEAKER_06]: He needs a babysitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't you guys code your own Unreal 5 engine, you know, and then we'll be your customers.
[SPEAKER_08]: See how hard it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then again, I don't know how far I want to go with this rant, but especially these days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Social Media, and in particularly, X and Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know I've been bitching about Twitter ever since you know who bought it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a problem ever since then.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean just within the last few months.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder what happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, logging onto that site, I can't believe is good for anybody's mental health.
[SPEAKER_06]: anybody's mental health unless you are maybe a somebody who makes their living off adult entertainment and your only focus on that site is the adult side of things maybe but even then the worst of the worst people are on that website and responding to things and stuff and I just I don't see how anybody can get joy
[SPEAKER_08]: Out of a post on that website anymore And this is just Randy Pitchford He just does this Because even before the game was released People were complaining about the price of it And he's like Well, I guess you're just not really true fans then Because you're not paying $80 for our game It's just like He doesn't shut the fuck up About stuff
[SPEAKER_08]: Randy, what happened to all that porn that was on your USB drive that you left at a fucking medieval times?
[SPEAKER_08]: What happened to that shit?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's bring that up since you're being a little asshole on social media.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just delete the account.
[SPEAKER_06]: This isn't like a delete your account, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is delete your account for your mental health and well-being.
[SPEAKER_06]: Delete your account to make you feel better.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm saying to Randy Pitchford.
[SPEAKER_06]: Delete your account because...
[SPEAKER_08]: you won't be so stressed out all the time he could have just it was so easy for him just to take the W on this for people to completely forget all he had to do
[SPEAKER_08]: because the game was getting great reviews already is go hey we hear some of you're struggling with you know optimization issues in the game we're working on it when we hear you we're working on it done there you go everyone's like cool they're on it the game's great let's let's go you know everybody would have been positive about it it would have been a lot of good
[SPEAKER_08]: Press and PR for the company.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, Randy Pitchford has to be correct all the time and just made it completely.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is now overshadowing how good the game is because of his dumbass responses on social media.
[SPEAKER_08]: I unfortunately think he's in a position as far as ownership of the company that no one can really tell him to stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: People should tell him to stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like you could have this, you know, this could have been painted in a completely different light if you would just shut the hell up.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw on chat says social media in general isn't good for anyone's mental health, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to argue with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are correct on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy's been just fine for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blue Sky is fine because I think Blue Sky is extremely curatable.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no algorithm on Blue Sky unless you opt into one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that is crucial for why Blue Sky has a different feel to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you build your experience on Blue Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: You truly do.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is no other entity pushing it at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: It automatically removes my tweet and you don't even see what that person quoted.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just see whatever they said.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I actually didn't block that person because the other thing you can do on Blue Sky is you can simply go to that little post and you can say detach post.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it automatically  it will replace the post with deleted by author.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I looked at this person's timeline.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all they do is quote post.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's like
[SPEAKER_06]: But that is a security measure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot easier to weed out the... It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: For sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Unwantables.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, Facebook has been, and I know, I shouldn't be on it and I shouldn't use it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like in some ways this is a necessary evil for promotion, but I'm sort of able to cross-post from Instagram.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what people say about Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Facebook is...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing that has gotten me to look at Twitter recently is the simple fact that there's a DBD meetup.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's the only place the information is posted.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only thing I've really been seeing on... I go to Facebook for is to read the people complaining in the neighborhood, like the local city chats.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it just makes you realize how people are in the public, which is bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, as Joan Hunter-Matt in chat says, be less like Randy and more like Yoshi P. Well, what a good transition to our next story to talk a little bit about what is going on with Final Fantasy XIV and the fact that, you know, Yoshi P has been, who of course is the producer of that game, Naoki Yoshida, who has worked on other games like Final Fantasy XVI.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's, you know, a pretty popular guy because he did revive Final Fantasy XIV literally from the dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that is fundamental or a minimum requirement that I have because I belong to this company and he says that he's more of a businessman than necessarily a creative in Final Fantasy XIV kind of interesting sort of take on it but I think realistic to like where he's at at this point um
[SPEAKER_06]: He's not bored with the project because there is so much more he still wants to do with the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says,
[SPEAKER_06]: Same.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: you know sort of situation especially Naoki Yoshida who is so popular he gets pulled into these other things like wasn't he I don't remember if that's still the case but he got pulled onto Square's board about Final Fantasy at some point because because of the fact that Final Fantasy 14 is still a money machine for Square Square makes more money off of Final Fantasy 14 than most of their games right now sadly including Final Fantasy 16 which was something that Naoki Yoshida was also a part of but
[SPEAKER_06]: I think also 16 was extremely limited by being a PlayStation 5 exclusive at the time that it came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're trying to get that to more places, but I don't know how many more people still want to play Final Fantasy 16 at this point that haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: SGO100Matt says, Yoshi P seems like he's working too hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe he should take a break on things and work on a fun project like a Chrono Trigger remake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Him and Sakurai should start a club and it should be like, don't call us.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the club.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do not call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please do not.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're busy making a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do not call.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what him and Sakurai should do.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not going to ask us for anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to make the game we want to make and you're going to like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my dream collab right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yoshi P and Sakurai making a game that you have no input on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You, the gamer, have no input on this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are not allowed to say anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're just going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: D'Artencio says, don't forget about Katsuhiro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't ask me for shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Harada from Tekken.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent call-out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should absolutely be an advisor on that game as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sakurai, Yoshida, Harada,
[SPEAKER_06]: Sakurai Yoshida Harada.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we can't really get an acronym out of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But those three get together and you're not going to say shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're just going to buy the game and you don't get to talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sit in the corner until it's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: You sit in the waiting room and we'll call you when it's ready.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sayoha?
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sayoha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's their first syllables.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as it's not like a dirty word I'm not aware of, then great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not to my knowledge.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said there was some good news tonight, and I look at this and go, this is kind of neat to hear about, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Indeed, indeed.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, now you know that a lot of my focus of what I like to look at in the video game industry is the education and spreading of positivity.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what an article I found is about indigenous video game makers who have done games in the Taino and Ojibwe languages.
[SPEAKER_05]: They
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to see if I can find... A woman named Elaine Gomez who owns Midnight Hour Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: She developed a game called The Vegigantes about the Vegigantes masks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's folklore and indigenous roots and was taking language classes in her...
[SPEAKER_05]: The tribe that she belongs to, I'm going to mispronounce this, Higwayagua Taino of the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so they decided to translate the Gigantes into that language.
[SPEAKER_05]: And her chief was like, hey, you got to keep making these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And trying to spread the culture and awareness of her ancestry.
[SPEAKER_06]: These types of stories that make me go, video game is an art form, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about sharing a story.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about sharing a feeling.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about sharing a passion.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I see that all those things are present in this type of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's another game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this one, I'm going to mispronounce her name too, but Anagukwe Hermes Roach.
[SPEAKER_05]: who is a designer and developer and co-director for Reclaim, being developed by Grassroots Indigenous Multimedia and grew up near the La Corte Reservation and made a game dedicated.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm actually trying to see if I just realized I can... You can find the links to it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm actually trying to get a little bit of what the game looks like here.
[SPEAKER_06]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I found a little YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's a pre-alpha, but at least you can see a little bit of what this game looks like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's try to get past the title screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has a really cool art style.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like it's all hand-drawn.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will link what I have as well for the game studios and whatnot in the chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: MidnightHourGames.com and it's G-I-M-O-J-I-B-W-E.org So we have GolfIndigoMike-OscarJulietIndigoBravoWhiskeyEcho.org Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: The art style in this game is really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's really striking to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when I saw that, I was like, I might have to wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a backlog.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I wanted to bring it up and showcase these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's move on from low budget to big budget, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should say indie, not low budget.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds demeaning.
[SPEAKER_06]: Indie to big budget, Loki.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, so Metroid Prime 4 we know is looking pretty impressive, but apparently there's some information that has leaked allegedly saying that it is also the most expensive project Nintendo has undertaken.
[SPEAKER_08]: That it had a $100 million budget.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it says Prime costs about, well, they said $10 million.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Prime 1 costs $10 million to make.
[SPEAKER_08]: Prime 4 is costing about $100 million to make.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game needs to sell between $4.5 to $5 million to break even.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I don't think it's going to have a problem doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's going to be a problem for them to sell that either, to be honest, especially during the holidays.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, when asked about how he obtained the figures, that's what I've been told.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: My uncle works at Nintendo, so he knows Mario personally, and this is the information that Mario gave him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we'll see what ends up being...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I think it also is why, you know, the flip side of that is also why I think there were some people that were surprised when this was announced that it was coming for the original Switch.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think people at some point felt, oh, because it was rebooted, because it's been so long, this is a Switch 2 sort of launch game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to be fair, I think I had that perspective for a hot minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when you kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and or even myself and I don't want to spend all that money on a Switch 2 but I'm going to get him a new game.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is available on the Switch.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I do think Metroid Prime 4 does fine and makes his money back because it is on the original Switch no matter how crappy it runs.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it should be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yes, Tigerclaw says we have Samus riding a motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody rides motorcycle now in Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll tell you right now, as if my anticipation for Tron Ares couldn't get shot in the foot any harder, all I have to tell you is that, reminder, it's a Disney movie and...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I have to say, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Y'all can read between the lines right now, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, I'm more excited about Metroid Prime 4 and its light cycle races than anything else right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I listened to the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was kind of underwhelmed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not as good as the last one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was never going to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand that, but Nine Inch Nails is good as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wendy Carlos could rise from the dead and do the soundtrack and it still wouldn't be.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's not dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought she was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought she was!
[SPEAKER_08]: But she could rise from the dead if she wanted to as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, that's how talented she is.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Wendy Carlos is still alive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Wendy.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's pretty old.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, she was born in 1939.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's 85 years old and still going strong in Rhode Island.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's embarrassing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Wendy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought there was a story that came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'm mixing up with another composer.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do still want to see Tron Ares.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just, I haven't, I just, it's like, I'm going to see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yar.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's, it's, it's, it's just like, I don't know though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see everything Tron that's happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says Jared Leto.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why Jared Leto?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's go back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about another big budget game.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least, you know, especially in other countries, this game is huge.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Football Manager 26, but this is the kind of football that, you know, is real footballers.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actual football.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we call it in the States soccer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Football Manager 26 is going to include the officially licensed Barclays Women's Super League and National Women's Soccer League and other women's competition.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe I'm saying this, but this marks the first time that women's soccer has been featured in the long-running management sim.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's the year 2025, or on the box, 2026, and here we are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, the debut of women's soccer was announced back in 2021.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was supposed to come out in Football Manager 2025, but that game was canceled.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sports Interactive instead switched the attention to Football Manager 26, which is coming out on November 4th.
[SPEAKER_06]: When the developer was kind of asked about this early on, the prospects of adding women's soccer and football to the various game modes, they said they were only going to do so once it was able to offer the same level of depth and authenticity as it does for men's soccer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, the popularity of women's soccer has grown enormously throughout the world.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Sports Interactive has said that for Football Manager 2026, there is one ecosystem and you are not exclusively limited to men or women's soccer on one save.
[SPEAKER_06]: In ensuring that the recreation of women's soccer is realistic, they consulted real life players, clubs, organization, managers, the people involved.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: 14 playable leagues across 11 nations at launch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Leagues in Germany, France, Japan, Australia, and more.
[SPEAKER_06]: England, the US.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently the database for Football Manager 26, 36,000 players.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that takes 40 researchers to make this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why this is a big budget game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But these games are huge.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's not EA, but it's still like, you know, these soccer games worldwide are tremendously popular.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: But congratulations on finally getting on board with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: SGO 100 Matt also points out, you know, kind of the growth in other forms of media.
[SPEAKER_06]: Over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network, SGO 100 Matt says the women's leagues have been getting good amount of TV play internationally.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that has changed in recent time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to all this, I say WNBA next, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before you bring out all the receipts on ways the WNBA has been represented, this is completely stemmed from my sour grapes over the fact that we haven't had the Monarchs here locally in years.
[SPEAKER_06]: So until the Monarchs are back, I'm always going to bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: A while back, they were great and it was really nice talking with them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, back when I was at my old job.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've had so much fun when I went to Monarchs games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were just, it's a different vibe.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, how do I put this?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's less serious, but not in a negative way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like it just feels fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems to me there's more love there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it is wild to me that we had a world championship team here in Sacramento and they got rid of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, maybe some other sport good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we know we are big Kunio fans in this house, and there are more Kunio games that are being localized coming out in the US for the first time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are getting River City Ball and Brawl Bundle.
[SPEAKER_05]: being published by RetroBit which the two games that are there is River City Basketball or Neketsu Koha Ganbare Basket and then there's also River City Fighting Legend Neketsu Kalto Densetsu
[SPEAKER_05]: So the first one, the basketball games, is Kunio gets a trip to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: on a quiz show and goes to play at a basketball tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then in the fighting legend, Kunio has a note on his locker that says there's a fighting tournament, and of course he's going to fight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it is a full set.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get...
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see what we have here.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we have... The whole thing is going to be 109.99, 129.99, and Canadian 154.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it will have... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this first official cartridge release outside of Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: A Zanshin cartridge for 8-bit consoles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number Deluxe Hardcover Cartridge Packaging, Full Colored Instruction Manual, Exclusive Acrylic Cartridge Display Stand.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's if you get... That's just for River City Fighting Legend, and it alone would be $60 US.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then...
[SPEAKER_05]: basketball it would be again $60 US on its own and it comes with again the cartridge release street chalk cartridge for 8-bit consoles number deluxe hardcover cartridge packaging full color instruction manual exclusive acrylic cartridge display stand I just want a poster
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a lot of fun stuff to come with this, and it's kind of neat that this is happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's maybe, you know, 30 years too late, but it's never too late, but you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a lot of hot-blooded action.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it sure is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dang, Kunio gets around.
[SPEAKER_05]: He can play dodgeball, and basketball, and baseball.
[SPEAKER_06]: As Joan Hunter-Matt says, I was wondering why it was so expensive until I realized it was an 8-bit console cart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then also, you know, those things might be a little more expensive right now just because I don't need to explain it to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Y'all know why.
[SPEAKER_06]: So.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on, Loki, from from classics to new stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Microsoft is, of course, shoving Copilot into every goddamn thing you don't want it to be in.
[SPEAKER_08]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Xbox mobile app is not immune to that crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's coming!
[SPEAKER_08]: Your Copilot that you don't want.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love my Mac.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some stupid little child poking and going, hey, you're going the wrong way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you're going the wrong way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Clippy's back.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Clippy being back would be way better than this crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Clippy got melted into a microchip and now he powers Copilot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clippy got melted down into a computer chip that now powers Copilot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clippy's better than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can turn off Apple Intelligence and I can tell Siri to shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_05]: She says she doesn't like when I talk like that, but still.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will throw this out here, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, I don't love this either.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, in the interest of looking at a story from all angles, I know that many people, when they get stuck in a video game, are going to go to Google or they're going to go to Bing, maybe, and they're going to type their question, like, where is the exit in World 3 or, you know, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And oftentimes what's going to generate right off the bat is going to be Gemini or whatever the Google's AI thing is called with the answer to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's wrong half the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a key point.
[SPEAKER_06]: But aren't a lot of people sort of already relying on this, I guess is my point.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the point here?
[SPEAKER_08]: To collect more data on you?
[SPEAKER_08]: If I'm searching for whatever this is, like the question that I have, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: You're gonna have the same data.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, if I'm using Bing or using the Microsoft Search or whatever, like, I just don't see the point of shoving this into every single app.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I know I don't use it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, like, even I had a coworker try to use it for, like, generating AI images for something funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, like, they could not get it to work right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Jamie, I was going to ask when you're telling Siri to shut the hell up, did you go, I don't remember asking you a goddamn thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm just like, I wasn't talking to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or, that's not what I asked, bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please watch your language.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt says physical game manuals and guides died for this actually no they existed so that all of the words inside of them could be stolen I mean it's I know jokes are funny and the truth isn't always funny but that's my honest answer to that
[SPEAKER_08]: and yet with all of that information at its fingertips it can't fucking answer questions correctly or do proper math most of the time so a funny thing to do
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: and I bet most of you don't even know what half these fucking buttons do on this thing it's not using it for math necessarily like using it for like math problems you know people do though I'm sure they do but like it's more of like I've used it for building for me for numbers
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's more of being unable to do simple things like, hey, I am giving you this word.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many letters are in this word?
[SPEAKER_08]: And it gets it wrong every time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or, hey, count the number of times the letter T appears in this word, and it can't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, that's the simple things that it just gets confused on, which I don't understand how it can't count.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you can code something to count, you know, the characters in a string.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I
[SPEAKER_08]: You would think you would know how to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fifth Dream says also you can just type math into Google and it tells you the answer right in the search bar.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to be fair, that is a thing that Google did before AI.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it is useful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like if you're like how many quarts in so many teaspoons or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will do those conversions of things I can never remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to figure out like the mass of this container when it wasn't listed and I needed to measure how much food was in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just put in the, you know, the one thing I do like is that on the sites where it will not just give you the answer, but it will also show you the calculation for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that for me is better because at least if I have the formula and I'm not where I can do anything about it, I have a way to calculate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie to all of her computers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, don't forget to show your work on that math problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, honestly, though, it is good to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, I'm just saying it's what is going to make that be more, I guess, more accurate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Accurate may not be the right word, but it shows that at least the calculation is following actual numbers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Formula and Procedure and isn't just something that was pulled out of a computer ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back in our day, we had legit calculators.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were Texas instruments and you hacked it to play Dope Wars and Snake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell fucking yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We played Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a friend who flat out programmed Pole Position on their graphing calculator.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Pole Position was available when the big thing was running those in assembly so that they would be much higher performance and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I remember Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, essentially with any of the high school stuff, because we just went through the whole back to school night stuff, a lot of the things where there's concerns about AI use and abuse or whatever, they will just...
[SPEAKER_08]: Make them do it on paper in class so that you can't use AI for that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aside from, I think they were still using Grammarly and that type of stuff for proofreading, but not for actual generation of all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or maybe, I think there was another tool that was for citing sources or something that helps you find sources for things.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's at a point where it's extremely useful yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I would want it, like, more personalized and intuitive and not as some, like, sort of backdoor for them to advertise to me, which I have to say, despite the fact that, like,
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, literally every company is stealing all of my data, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, they still can't push accurate ads to me about what my interests are.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I just, it boggles my mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, if you literally have all of my data, you still can't figure that out?
[SPEAKER_08]: What makes you think AI is going to be any better at that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's just, you are already bad at your job if you have all of the data and yet still don't know what I want.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see my Blue Sky post about the Instagram ad I got pushed this week with the holiday sweaters?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was getting pushed holiday sweaters on Instagram and it would be like a pink, I don't even know if I can say, like there's literally one of them, I can't say the word or we might get banned from Twitch, but there was one, I think I can say cunt, there was a sweater that was pink and it said cunt on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's just it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a holiday sweater that I could wear to my aunt's house for a holiday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you imagine me walking to the door with a pink holiday sweater?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't I have this?
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was a neon green one that had the F slur is the one that I don't think I can say.
[SPEAKER_06]: The F slur.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want the one that says the other.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there was two, it looked like pixel art of two rats smoking.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: on a holiday sweater.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like why?
[SPEAKER_06]: I might buy that one because that's the one I could actually probably get away with wearing on a stage somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: But and then there was one that said ketamine and it was all like drawn and like chalk and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just like, what in the world?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, why am I getting pushed these ads?
[SPEAKER_06]: To which Alan replies, oh, that might be my fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, what in the fuck are you looking at?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they'll do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll advertise to other people in your household stuff that they think that you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's always wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is how Alan figured out my Christmas gift last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: He knew to get me the Atari jacket because I was on Atari's site.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to see if they had a new version of the woodgrain hoodie that I really liked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just kind of wanted to see what clothes they had.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I saw that leather jacket and I started looking at it and it started pushing Alan the ad for it because we live together.
[SPEAKER_06]: and he ended up buying it because he's like, oh, Rob would probably like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was like, God damn it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't let them know it's working.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's what I hate.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw says sometimes it's an accident.
[SPEAKER_06]: You open a page or something and then you get recommended stuff from it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the worst.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, my fat finger tapped an Instagram ad and now I am forever getting ads for, like, I don't know, potpourri or something I don't fucking want.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just wild.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't want any potpourri.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't want things to smell like an attic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like grandma's house?
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember when... Do you remember when, like, potpourri became really popular in the 80s?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everywhere you went smelled like...
[SPEAKER_05]: and Old Apothecary.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before we get to the classic game of the week, I want to talk about this as a follow-up to something we talked about last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember the saga of the Sega dev kit that was bought at an auction type of thing or an unloading and then now it became a whole mess?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, an interesting twist in this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's full of cockroaches.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's covered in bees!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there's no B's that I know of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, apparently the company that Sega used to clear the Brentford offices is a registered charity.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the latest twist.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now Sega is now essentially accusing a charity of theft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, there's a lot of on-edge people with this whole conversation and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of allegedlys and maybes and he said, they said, she said thing going on here.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that is the latest twist is that now apparently it was a charity organization, which I actually  there are like
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you hear the commercials on the radio or whatever all the time about donate your car to this charity and then it's a tax write-off for you and they turn around and sell you a car and they make the money, they get people to donate their time to fix up cars.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yes, charities do get involved in this sort of work sometimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's not outside, I mean, I know it's Britain.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, that'd be like if I was...
[SPEAKER_08]: I had my massive estate sale and our fine diamonds got mixed up with the linens and we accidentally donated it to Goodwill.
[SPEAKER_08]: Am I going to go sue Goodwill or try to get my diamonds back because I'm a dumbass that just accidentally threw that stuff out?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but I've seen the girl whose parents in the estate sale or grandparents had the photo album donated to Goodwill found the book and bought it for like a dime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, like, that's fine if you repurchase your stuff, but, like, there should be no expectation that, like, oh, well, you gave this stuff to them and you didn't know what you had, so... Tough beans, like, I don't know, like... Just let it go.
[SPEAKER_08]: No one's gonna be, you know, getting any sort of industry secrets based off this crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean... Ugh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: These people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't...
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to our next segment and look back fondly on something in gaming's history.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time, where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's time for the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, this is an interesting one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excited to hear about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is your pick for the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a game I've been waiting to do just because it's... It was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Drunken Robot Pornography.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's got a great name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Had the best intro song.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, drunken robot pornography.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a bit of a story about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: For a post that was by one of the developers of the game,
[SPEAKER_05]: DejaVon Games
[SPEAKER_05]: This, yeah, some people, there are people who call it DRP, but people just call it drunken robot pornography because that's its name.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, you play Ruben, a bar owner who gave his robot bartender Tim's sentence.
[SPEAKER_05]: And after Tim listened to all the pages at the bar, he said the best way to cure humanity is, you know, suffers from widespread depression, was to build a 30-story tall robot to destroy it, or several of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to save the city of Boston Sky from Tim and his robot centerfolds.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly how it's described.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game...
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It made me really motion sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: To me, there were aspects of jumping flash in it and all kinds of running and gunning craziness and it was wonderful.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, you wear a robot suit and you go around and you fight other robots.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Digibond Games also did one in 2008 called The Wonderful End of the World and one called A Reckless Disregard for Gravity.
[SPEAKER_05]: The thing about this game is that it was announced on April 1st, 2010 as an April Fool's joke, and it came out on February 19th, 2014.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, I mean, people gave it kind of mixed reviews.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people didn't really care for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought this game was hilarious, and I had a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I wasn't very good at it, I will freely admit that, but I had a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you can still get it on Steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_05]: 14 bucks if you pay 30 you can get three copies and share them with friends so that's nice um but yeah you have jetpacks and guns and go around and and stop Tim and his uh and instead of that they burn down your bar how can you let that go but yeah it's also really pretty
[SPEAKER_05]: But it has the best opening song ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's a Kotaku quote that says, I'd play this game even if it wasn't called Drunken Robot Pornography.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's a really smart way to get more of your game, like offer the bulk sales thing, offer the Costco plan on your game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like that's really smart, especially if it's like multiplayer, like 30 bucks for you and two other people to get the game is actually a really smart marketing tactic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and honestly, it looks like there's some other neat games that have come out since.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've kind of fallen off of my radar for a while because they had done some pretty neat games and they're trying to sell sentient ice cream.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this website template allows us to add food items to our page.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not a restaurant, but if we were, here's some of the things we might offer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bison-Bear combo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Natural dancers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew a guy in gaming podcasting that left to go sell ice cream.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: The people at DejaVon are very interesting people.
[SPEAKER_05]: The website's actually pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just like also that they have a game called... Literally.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to say, as much as you talked about this game, I never played it myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I probably need to at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you should get the friend pack and share it with your friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you already have a copy, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then who do I share it with?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess Alan would be an obvious choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: You want a copy of the game, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I probably already have one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are we sure it wasn't in like a... Ooh, it's angry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do like the little captions.
[SPEAKER_05]: OLR giveaway!
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a copy, but I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would just throw it in the pile anyways if I had a copy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'd have to put this in Minecraft in order for you to play it, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nope, I took it back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have it already.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I already have it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny, funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that everything then?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish we could hear some of the opening song, but... We might be able to, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it in the beginning of this video?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the very beginning, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys won't hear it on Discord, but I'm going to play a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just be quiet for me for a moment, and I will play some of it here for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is the theme song to the game that DarkSakura was just speaking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it goes actually really long and this sadly gets cut off.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to hear the rest, you'll just have to buy the game or look it up on YouTube, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drunken Robot Pornography.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that this is another game that I've enjoyed that started off as an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love April Fool's games that become real games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon Go is the one that comes to mind for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's cover some other headlines in gaming rapidly in Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so we got the final Crossworlds DLC promotion, or at least the franchise it's going to be with.
[SPEAKER_08]: This came from an early leaked copy of the game that was out there from retail, and it's Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, it was confirmed by Sonic City Net.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were the ones that posted the
[SPEAKER_08]: The screenshot or the photo of the DLC brochure.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yes, Mega Man is going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also, I think it was also confirmed on X as well by the official account showing that it's going to be, I think, Mega Man base.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or no, Proto Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mega Man and Proto Man were in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think possibly the racers that are going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to make it Mega Man and Minecraft in one game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're speaking my language.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, I will have to check this out when it comes out next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then along with that, we're getting some more roster updates for the new Marvel Cosmic Invasion beat-em-up game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now, of course, their latest trailer, they showed off Black Panther and Cosmic Ghost Rider.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what the difference between Cosmic Ghost Rider and Ghost Rider is, but it is Ghost Rider.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he's got a space helmet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is he a motorcycle hero?
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a space hero.
[SPEAKER_08]: Space motorcycle, maybe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Frank Castle, Brad.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I stopped reading any of the Ghost Rider stuff except for like Helverine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the former Punisher is now Ghost Rider.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good job, Marvel!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well let's go over to DarkSakura with a quick headline.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yas, so Sega has put out a trademark for Arcade Paradise and they have some unannounced games that they're going to reveal at Tokyo Game Show and this could be one of them or it could be a compilation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows what it is, but they've got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wonderful, beautiful, exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Less exciting is the news that some Evercade cartridges are moving into the Legacy program, which means they will no longer be made.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they exist, but they are no longer being actively made.
[SPEAKER_06]: As of December 2025, the four cartridges are the Pico Interactive Collection 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: This collection had Beast Ball, Eliminator Boat Duel, Hulk,
[SPEAKER_06]: Hoops, Shut Up and Jam 1 and 2, Soccer Kids, Summer Challenge, Winter Challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a lot of sports games, so maybe if that isn't your jam, you probably don't really care unless you're a collector about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But also, this one kind of surprises me, the Indie Heroes Collection 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of games in this.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's 14 games, which is a lot for an EverQuest cartridge, which has a variety of different indie games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Indie Heroes Collection 1 Megacat Studios Collection 2 Alter Ego, Romeo and Juliet, Romeo and Julie Cat, and
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just... I can't believe this is real life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yazi, Roniu's Tale.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be honest, not a lot of games I've recognized these names of, but cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless, you know, the fact that if you don't already have this cartridge, you're probably going to have a hard time getting it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the last one, the Sydney Hunter Collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard of these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's three in this collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then a random game, throw them in there as well, called Jester.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is all from Collector Vision Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So these four are now in Legacy status.
[SPEAKER_06]: and are no longer going to be available.
[SPEAKER_06]: Evercade is still cranking out new cartridges though.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have some newer collections they just opened for pre-order.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say a Rare collection is coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's an Activision collection coming too, which actually kind of surprised me because that means Evercade and Microsoft have a deal because Microsoft is...
[SPEAKER_06]: and Microsoft has their own retro thing, but they have an Activision collection coming, which I think sounds pretty cool because I think there might be some games in here that aren't in Microsoft's thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if the Microsoft thing had Star Master or Sky Jinx.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have them all memorized and they do a terrible job of updating us when they have new stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Neo Geo Arcade 2, 3 is coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a lot of stuff on the horizon.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Evercade's far from dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, it seems like it's growing, but those four cartridges will no longer be available.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on and travel around the world and check out some newer games that are coming out this week in world release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, let's start with the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have Baby Steps coming out on PC and PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blippo Plus on PC and Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Forgive Me Father 2 on PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Slime Rancher 2 coming out of Early Access on PC, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wizarddom on Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got Blade and Soul Heroes on PC, iOS, and Android.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jump Plus Jumble Rush on iOS and Android.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aquapazza Aqua Plus Dream Match on PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: AESA Shadows of the Silence on PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hades 2 coming out of Early Access on PC, Mac, Nintendo Switch, and Nintendo Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have...
[SPEAKER_08]: Mamoru Kun Recurse on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Road 59, Yakuza's Last Stand on PC and Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Silent Hill F in chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sonic Racing Cross Worlds on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, no Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's coming out later.
[SPEAKER_08]: SWORN getting out of early access on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Tourist Deluxe on Nintendo Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have Tokyo Extreme Racer out of early access on PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Atelier Res...
[SPEAKER_08]: Why are these names so hard to pronounce?
[SPEAKER_08]: Rezlorania and the Red Alchemist and the White Guardian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too long of a name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gus, get better.
[SPEAKER_08]: On PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have...
[SPEAKER_08]: Clendon X3 on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5 EA Sports FC 26 on PC, Nintendo Switch, Nintendo Switch 2 PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One and Xbox Series that's the biggest video game in the world if I'm not mistaken
[SPEAKER_08]: That is a pretty big one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, that's full of microtransactions and gambling for kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hotel Barcelona on PC, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: And finally, Pac-Man World 2 Repack on PC, Nintendo Switch, Nintendo Switch 2, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, heading over to Japan and checking out the releases there.
[SPEAKER_06]: EA Sports FC 26, of course, is releasing in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, I don't think there is a bigger video game in the world.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that is on its way out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also on the Switch 2, there's a variety of peripherals and things like new cases and things from third parties.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we also have...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no, that's next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so that's it for Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about the PlayStation 5?
[SPEAKER_06]: Silent Hill F, of course, is on its way out for the PlayStation 5, also in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And no, Tigerclaw does not mean Silent Hill fucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if we, do we know the meaning behind the F or is that to be revealed through the story?
[SPEAKER_06]: We might.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also out on the PlayStation 5, Sonic Racing Crossworlds, which that is the game that Tigerclaw fucks with.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that for a fact.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, but I'll be fucking with it too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking forward to Sonic Racing Crossworlds because those games are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mama Rukun Recurse is also out in Japan on the PS5 this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poppy Playtime Triple Pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, gets its own release in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Neon Blood, also releasing in Japan this week on the PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Atelier Resloriana, the Red Alchemist and the White Guardian, which I think Loki also mentioned for the US, that is also out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: That looks like a worldwide one this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in Japan, of course, you can get the regular, you can get the premium box, and you can get the special collection box.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's in the special collection box?
[SPEAKER_06]: A bunch of crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stickers, postcards.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't look like one of the Paltrow's heads in this version.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to probably pre-order a different version for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gold edition, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: EA Sports FC 26, of course, is on that console as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck, they would probably release EA Sports FC 26 on the ZX Spectrum if they thought they'd sell 100 copies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's about it for this week's releases, but still a pretty big week in releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only going to get busier as the weeks continue.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, how about the U.K.?
[SPEAKER_06]: ?
[SPEAKER_05]: on the 22nd we have Deadly Days Road Trip for PC, Atlas Legend 2 for PC, on the 23rd Blibbo Plus for Switch and PC, Aethermancer for PC, Climbrancher 2 for PS5, Xboxes PC, Creepy Redneck Dinosaur Mansion 1 for PC, Baby Steps PS5 PC, Aztec's Last Son for PC, also the House of Tesla um
[SPEAKER_05]: Wizardom on PlayStation, Xbox, Switch for the 25th we have Death on the Nile for pretty much everything Sworn for The Same on the 25th Mamoru Kun Recurse for Damn Near Everything
[SPEAKER_05]: Out of Time for the PC, Consume Me for PC, My Child of Ages for Switch, Silent Hill F, PS5, Xbox's PC, Sonic Racing Crossroads for everything, Unfair Flips for PC, Lost Rift Early Access for PC,
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 26th, Freeride Switch, Clover Pit for PC, Hades 2 Digital for Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, that says the 25th.
[SPEAKER_05]: But on the 26th, FC26 for Switch and Switch 2, Atelier Reslariana, The Red Alchemist and The White Guardian, PS5, Switch PC on the 26th, Hotel Barcelona, Steam, Xbox, PS5,
[SPEAKER_05]: EA Sports FC26 for Damn Near Everything, Pac-Man World 2 Repack for Switch 2 and Switch, and NBA Bounce for Switch.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before we get to the listener roundtable, your emails, your comments, your blue skeets, all that stuff, we will get to one more stories from Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, unfortunately, we live in a world where people are... I mean, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Making light of someone's death is not necessarily a good thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, I think there's varying degrees of gray there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, for example, if I was making fun of the death of Hitler, that might be fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But apparently one of those people was an artist at, of course...
[SPEAKER_08]: Sucker Punch, who got fired because of their comments regarding the death of Charlie Kirk and basically made a comment saying that, you know, something to, oh, I hope the shooter's name is Mario so that Luigi knows his bro got his back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard that.
[SPEAKER_08]: um and then of course uh the artist Drew Harrison is no longer employed at Sucker Punch Productions because they were unhappy with his comments but there's also pressure from like external groups to try to get anybody fired for you know saying anything bad about the the mega MLK or was that 13th Apostle something like that that they want to call this hateful bigot of a person
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the world we live in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have nothing to say on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's the world we live in.
[SPEAKER_06]: SJ100Matt in chat says, anyone who says anything gets in trouble over this.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where we're at in this world.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we'll just all sit and think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's get to the Lister Roundtable and see what you all think.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can send us emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Participate at OrangeLawnRadio.com You can send us posts.
[SPEAKER_06]: BlueSky at OrangeLawnRadio, our domain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, excuse me, OrangeLawnRadio.com or what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought somebody said they were going to send an email, but I didn't see any come in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did we get an email, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, perhaps we just didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I'm going to make a statement real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole thing about not speaking ill of the dead, don't make fun of death and murder, definitely, but it's not speaking ill of the dead if you're speaking the truth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some people laugh at funerals because that's the only way they know how to process.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pointing to a famous Mary Tyler Moore episode that I think explained a lot of these feelings that people have.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not saying it's the same situation, but I am saying you have full license to when I pass away inevitably, which all humans do at some point, you have full license to roast me because I love a good roast.
[SPEAKER_06]: So please make it funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just make sure it's actually funny because there's a lot of jokes out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: They are not responsible for any of this and blaming the complete other side, which has only talked about like, you know, hey, we need to be peaceful about this and all this stuff while they're still stoking things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, just today, still stoking things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's disingenuous, obviously.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to create a bigger rift because they know that when the chaos dies down, they'll come out on top.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Chaos is getting people to not talk about the Epstein files as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's, you know... Oh, I'm not shutting up about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I think it's also... Oh, what else was I going to say this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just lost the train of thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I know what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say that, yeah, yeah, of course we should denounce gun violence.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of us that have been denouncing-
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no, they're not gonna-
[SPEAKER_05]: So I laughed at the irony.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will say that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think many of us are ready to talk about how do we fix the gun problem in this country.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know how we fix the country, but I can't say it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: And no, I'm not talking about violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am talking about dismantling and reorganizing, but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Due process.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: So we don't have emails, but if you want to send us an email for our future week, participate at OrangeLaunchRadio.com is the place to send us emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you have for dinner, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Blue Skies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I haven't eaten dinner yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we got lunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always eat dinner after the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never eat dinner before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sundays are usually the day that Alan and I all do a DoorDash, which, yes, is expensive and we spoil ourselves.
[SPEAKER_05]: I DoorDash Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't even.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not judging.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, also, because my husband is a Costco queen, he found that you can get like $100 worth of DoorDash cards for $90.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, we kind of filled up on the DoorDash cards there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you now the DoorDashians?
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: We DoorDashed ourselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to say it because they didn't pay me to endorse them, but one of those make your own pizza places, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's like...
[SPEAKER_06]: I love balsamic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: What'd you have?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because this is the original studio now I had a togo sandwich I haven't had a togo sandwich in forever They keep closing them Yeah, the one by me closed Yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I did want to mention any Blue Sky mentions that we have.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only mention on our Blue Sky was actually a shout out from our friends over at GameBooey.org video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I mentioned it last week that I'd recorded the episode, but it came out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will shout out our pals over at GameBooey.org.
[SPEAKER_06]: I joined them to talk about music games and rhythm games because I had joined them for a show like 12 years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they are revisiting some of their old topics through like the new lens.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a really interesting look back.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's episode, you want to look for episode 182B but I would encourage you to listen to 182A and other selections from the Game Buoy catalog as well because Game Buoy is an excellent show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spike and Slag Kick are extremely well-spoken individuals and really do their homework when it comes to the, more than I do, when it comes to the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: So shout out for GameBuoy.org.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny, every so often, Psychic and I consider going back to that old WoW comic that we wanted to do ages and ages ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hillsbrad Blues.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta get all the models again.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know where Slykick's name comes from too?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is an interesting story to tell.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Slykick, that name comes from the God Warrior lady on, what was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Swapping Wives or whatever that show was called on Fox years ago where she goes, it's tainted.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark-sided.
[SPEAKER_06]: Slykicks.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's trying to say psychics, but she says Slykick.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's where he gets his name from is that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it had to do with the...
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Condescending calling someone a slag.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might be a double entendre, in which case I fully endorse, because I do like to joke, you know, oh, I'm going on with the slag, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: But yes, because there was an excellent show called Slag Wars that starred the cock destroyers, which sadly, you know, one of them passed away a couple of years ago, which was really, and they had a fight and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Slag Wars is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you remember the Cock Destroyers?
[SPEAKER_06]: They did all those YouTubes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's these two gals that just talk really dirty.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's over-the-top funny to me, but they actually had a reality TV show to find the world's next biggest slag.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was dumb reality TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reality TV ought to be a little stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I love The Traitors, because it's ridiculously over-the-top.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why am I thinking...
[SPEAKER_06]: is one of the most incredible reality show hosts we've ever had because he brings that right, unserious vibe to what otherwise is actually, like, people really get into that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, like, the vibe of the show and the over-the-topness and kind of leaning into the excessiveness I think is what makes that show really fun at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's, yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just thinking of that line from Golden Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's not a slut.
[SPEAKER_05]: She is the slut.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't finish my thought on Slykick's name though.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that lady, no, that lady from Wife Swap or whatever it was, Marguerite Perrin was her name.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's kind of back because of TikTok.
[SPEAKER_06]: So she does a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here's the thing about her.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, she's gone through some terrible loss.
[SPEAKER_06]: She lost her daughter and her husband, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it has something to do with the fact, I don't know all the details, they would be her words, not mine, but the fact that they were kind of there for her when she needed people to lean on through all the tragedy she was going through.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like a really, like she's become one of those like good religious people, the people that actually use their religion to lift up others, to do that sort of thing, as opposed to try to tear people down.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just love that for her and her journey.
[SPEAKER_06]: and all that so look her up she's she's fun so um anyway i guess that's i guess that's it for me i'll i'll end on the god warrior note why not so uh sure let me uh let me go to loki though i do want to see if there's any other last minute stories from loki um not really much in the last minute stories other than um
[SPEAKER_08]: Still more stuff kind of falling out from that whole Visa MasterCard thing where adult games are kind of getting struck on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now they're not allowed to make updates to their game post-launch to add Not Safe for Work content to their game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So apparently that's a new thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: They said Valve isn't the problem here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's still the card processors.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for bubbling that up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't heard on that in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, that's still a debate going on for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't want that to fall off the radar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, still going.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't let all the other news in the world distract you.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't have enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will be back next week in seven days to do it all over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the meantime, we hope to see you here live with us at the Voice Geeks Network as we tape our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we do appreciate those of you that leave a nice review for our show and help us spread the word on a site like Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever it is that you found this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: With that, let's get to some final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mentioned earlier you're going to do some Palio tonight, but do you have a final thought and wrap up for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Resist the regime.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: On that note, we'll see you next time, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later, taters.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll go over to you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have a final thought for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm excited to see we have Minecraft live this next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm curious to see what announcements are going to be made other than the date for the new update, which should be like probably next week or two.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're already in pre-release.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess my final thought would be that we're starting to get into a really exciting game release period.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know this week I'm excited for the Sonic Cross Worlds racing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really excited for Silent Hill F in just a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be in October, and that means Pokemon Legends, probably the game I've been looking forward to most this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: ZA is going to be out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's hard to say because Metroid Prime 4 I'm really excited about as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's just a lot of good shit and gaming coming out in the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: so although the gaming news has been slow the game releases are huge and we're just weeks away kind of stepping into that zone so it's a nice thing to say a nice thing to see so otherwise I will just say don't be assholes to each other I think that's always a nice final thought don't be assholes to each other be nice that's it have a great week everybody bye you've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next week.