[SPEAKER_15]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Our live talk program begins now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio may contain sexual and adult content and many instances of the F-word, which is not safe for children.
[SPEAKER_16]: Goddamn, you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Stop calling here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Isn't it 4215, Pussy Wayne?
[SPEAKER_16]: You bitch!
[SPEAKER_12]: Now let me check the zip code.
[SPEAKER_12]: 212, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_10]: You have no morals, darling.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd also like to add that I have my father's gun and the scorching case of herpes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Kiss my grip, nooch.
[SPEAKER_21]: Mecca lecca hi, mecca hi-dee-ho.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, I hate throwing up in public.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me too!
[SPEAKER_07]: Fucker, yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loser.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_10]: On the side of my face.
[SPEAKER_10]: Breathing, breath, heaving breath, heaving whatever Now you all just sit there and keep your mouths shut While I go listen to my Britney Spears records I am your singing telegram
[SPEAKER_04]: Somewhere inside the state of California, in the great nation of the United States of America, on the planet Earth, Orange Lounge Radio is now on the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're tuned in to the Bomani Scene's newest and greatest radio station of all things Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always is my lovely co-host, Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back!
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I'm back, and I'm sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am 100% glad to be back.
[SPEAKER_11]: The trip was interesting to say the least.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll definitely get into that a little bit more later, right Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is episode number 4 for July the 14th of 2002.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are joined in studio once again by many, many, many guests.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got Matt, Dave, and Paul's here in the house.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be talking to all of them a little bit more later, but first we're going to take a real quick break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other opening thoughts from you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you say I get to break stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just not anything I own.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can break my roommate's stuff, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's on vacation.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think I'll just break this thing over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to start off this first break with a request here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got a couple requests in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you go ahead and join our chat room if you want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just have to join irc.akeheads.org.
[SPEAKER_04]: or any other side IRC chat server.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them would be also karma.othersideirc.net.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're just in Channel Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got a few requests in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to start it off with from 2DX7Style.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Dumond with Never Look Back.
Thanks for watching!
Blow my whistle baby!
[SPEAKER_15]: And now it's time for Erotic Pop Idol, where we will find the next singer for everyone's favorite perverse Bomani band, Erotic.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do it all night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do it with me.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no, that was awful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bloody terrible.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you take vocal lessons?
[SPEAKER_17]: Kill your teacher.
[SPEAKER_17]: In the heat of the night.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, God, I think my ears are bleeding.
[SPEAKER_13]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shut the bloody hell up, Paula.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do you even know why you're here?
[SPEAKER_19]: That was just bloody pathetic.
[SPEAKER_19]: Next!
[SPEAKER_16]: Come on, do it with me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, yes, that's it!
[SPEAKER_16]: We have a winner!
[SPEAKER_15]: A star is born here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, a star is born here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, they were saying that the old promos were getting a little old, so we had to make that new one before the show started tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, now we have new old promos to play the hell out with here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty, a big hello to everybody, by the way, tonight in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got a pretty crowded chatroom there tonight, so thanks everybody for listening in.
[SPEAKER_04]: And those last few songs were for some people that were listening in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had Don't Look Back and The Whistle Song were both requested.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I threw Jet Ningen in there too, because I know a lot of people like that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Paul, for that lovely hooray.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we have a hooray from the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of The Whistle Song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I personally think it's the most interesting song in Max 2 out of anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was the one that probably got the biggest reaction in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: People going, oh yeah, I really want to hear this song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just really kind of gets in your mind and just messes with you to like, I hate this song.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the scrubbiest song on the face of the earth.
[SPEAKER_04]: When people play this in the arcade, they sing along to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want to kill myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it about the whistle song?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was weird because when it first came out, you know, when Max 2 News was first coming out, people said, oh, that song is going to be the most overplayed Max 2 song because it has the word bitch in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we find out they censored bitch and it just says baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, unless, you know, you're looking at the banner, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says baby in the actual song.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people are afraid to play it because they don't want to play it out, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They all play Suguru.
[SPEAKER_21]: They all play Suguru, which is not even as good as the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: So then they, instead they play Suguru and play that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, then it's like all of a sudden somebody actually plays the whistle song and now it's like, oh, people are playing this and it's pretty cool and now the whistle song's a cool song, but now it's getting overplayed again.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's frustratingly catchy, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just infectious.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets in my mind and it never gets out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It feels like burning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other interesting songs that you just kind of totally changed your opinion on in DDR?
[SPEAKER_11]: An old school song, but love that feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: By Changmo?
[SPEAKER_11]: I hated that song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody hated that song.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then it kept coming up on my non-stops on my lovely Dreamcast edition, so I learned to like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I was the only one who did.
[SPEAKER_04]: and right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later on tonight we're going to be doing our very own version of Listless here and we are going to be determining the worst Bomani song in history next to Let Them Move because Let Them Move it's already given that wins it's the worst Bomani song in history we're going to determine the number two second worst Bomani song in history tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was officially the lowest on that list on that old survey that went on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you remember that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that it was Have You Never Been Mellow.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, Have You Never Been Mellow was ranked a good bit higher than Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love Machine wasn't even number one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, see, Have You Never Been Mellow is cool because it was made just to spin around the whole time on the maniac steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can spin the entire thing, and it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then you go try to step off the stage, and you fall on your ass.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was Butterfly, where you just go spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Butterfly has a few chops in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can get a little scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's been done, you know, I don't think anyone can top what's been, it's a classic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think there will ever be a great butterfly routine from here on out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think anybody, do you think anybody has the balls to do butterfly anymore?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's just ask Kyle Snyder.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobody can do butterfly better than Kyle Snyder.
[SPEAKER_04]: I put out a challenge, I want to see a fucking great, either butterfly or boom boom dollar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like somebody needs to just get old school and blow us all away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just saw one video, I don't remember, I believe it was off Music Gaming Zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was these two Korean guys doing Boom Boom Dollar, and it was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I've seen a lot of crappy routines from Boom Boom Dollar, but that was probably the only one that actually stood out in my mind as being good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat room does seem to agree here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Snyder owned Butterfly, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The end.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's two songs he owns, because isn't he the king of Trip Machine Jungle or something like that, too?
[SPEAKER_11]: He is the butterfly, no Kami-sama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, oh, Corey, okay, Corey, we have Virtue in the chat room, and he says at CVGL next Saturday he will do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will totally be there to see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope it's as good as the Burning Heat routine, Gloria.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I'm going to make it to CVGL, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we're hoping, and this is something we want to do in the future, we're going to be taking our little kit out remote.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got some remote tape stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to do some interviews out and about at some different tournaments and things.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll be bringing them back to the show and playing them all for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hopefully Jamie can get out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see who wants to give Jamie a lift.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm taking donations now.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I go, I will definitely take you, but I do have Under Sedation Live on Saturday night, which I committed to, so I'd have to run back early just so I can make that show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't we get into Jamie's FU of the Week, because a lot of what we want to talk about today revolves around Jamie's FU of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I am going to turn it over to Jamie, and she's going to give us, like she does every week, we've had to fill in for her the past few weeks because she's been gone, but she has an FU of the Week every week, and so Jamie, tell us your FU of the Week.
[SPEAKER_11]: My FU of the Week has to do with Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_11]: First of all...
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going expecting to see some new anime, something that I hadn't seen before.
[SPEAKER_11]: They played the same crap that you can buy at Suncoast.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is stuff that I've either already had for months or a couple stuff for years.
[SPEAKER_11]: and it was all just this commercial crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I go in the dealer's room, okay, last year I was so excited, I was going to make Jungle, buy a bunch of laser discs, $5 a game.
[SPEAKER_11]: They had like five laser discs that were $5, all the rest were $30, $40, which is still good for a laser disc, but still, you know, I want my $5 laser disc.
[SPEAKER_11]: I walked out of AX last year with 20 laser discs.
[SPEAKER_11]: This year, not a win.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, I did get this really cool little Initial D racing car thingy that's like the size of my thumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say that is very cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, it's adorable.
[SPEAKER_04]: That almost makes the whole trip worth it right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've decided that I'm officially going to get a 1983 Toyota Corolla hatchback and paint it up like the Initial D car.
[SPEAKER_11]: They had one there, and it was adorable, and I was picturing it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And another thing, this is my other rant.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, the cosplay was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: There were lots of people in really awesome costumes, and I found a massive angel pictuary group.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I was in my Mad Hatter costume, which if anybody wants to see, it looks like I'll find you pictures later.
[SPEAKER_11]: But people kept asking me if I was doing J-Rock cosplay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, no, I'm not from Malice Miser!
[SPEAKER_11]: No, go away, leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I got glomped a lot, so that was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do explain to all of us what a glomp is, for those that don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's when people randomly run up to you and latch on to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you get hugged by screaming fanboys and fangirls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you get glomped when you play DDR, Dave?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I get glomped by beautiful women wearing bikinis.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you wake up!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ladies love the knee drops.
[SPEAKER_11]: He breaks out as no old school A-team.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave, for those that don't know, is the guy that likes to play Demon Road over at Roseville Golf Land, and he likes to do the knee drops on Paranoia while he's trying to do an Oni.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is winner.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's even better is for the people who can do that and actually make it through the course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Freestyling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that's going to be a new trend, is freestyling the Oni courses?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, what's left to do?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I freestyle Waka Laka.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's hard, but you can throw in a few stuff there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, not much, but Paranoia definitely adds more stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, you can spin and hand plant, knee drop, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hey Dave, Virtue's challenging you in the chat room to a freestyle only.
[SPEAKER_21]: You better back that up.
[SPEAKER_21]: You better bring it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know that I definitely could not even do Demon Road at all without freestyling, but with freestyling I'd make it to at most the fifth song if I really did well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I'd like to issue out a challenge of my own, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's challenge night here on Orange Lodge.
[SPEAKER_11]: A few people already know of this challenge.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, my edit is on SoCalCakes' page right now, my DXY edit another.
[SPEAKER_11]: For whoever full combos it or gets a 90% perfect attack, I will take them out to dinner.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what kind of dinner?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who will be on the course for this lovely dinner?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sushi, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or, you know, something, you know, maybe Outback.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I got an idea.
[SPEAKER_21]: How about we go to Hometown Buffet?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hometown Buffet!
[SPEAKER_04]: The true Sacramento Cowtown way.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to go Hometown Buffet!
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: We will go to JJ North.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're a little better.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're tastier.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I live right up... I have cheesecake.
[SPEAKER_04]: The studio here is right up the street from a nice little oriental buffet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see Corey's comment there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will make sure that you get a copy of this one way or another.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, it is available.
[SPEAKER_04]: I figured out finally how to update our website all nicely, so we did update the links page today.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the very last link there leads to one of the listeners of the show, SoCalKicks.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has a nice little page there, and it has edits on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Jamie's edits are downloadable there.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said it might be broken, but I know he'll fix it, especially after I just plugged his site here.
[SPEAKER_04]: He'll figure out a way to fix it now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can also mirror those edits on SackbyMoney.com and on DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: I also have another challenge attached to my Look to the Sky edit for whoever full combos it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll give you a GameCube pin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of edits, actually, I should start posting mine on my website there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I'll post that link next week or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So going back to Anime Expo, there's a question I want to ask, and I think a lot of people want to know the answer to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it that there seems to be this correlation between anime and DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides the obvious that they're both from Japan, I mean, that's the obvious, why is it that a lot of people, not everybody, but I'd say a good 90% of people who love DDR love anime?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I've actually found out that a lot of the people that I used to know online through my anime channels are people that are now like kind of big in the DDR world too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like a few people actually in Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I knew them online before I knew them by DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: And by the way, hi Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo!
Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I also, you know, I think it was really cool that actually this is one of the coolest things about AX is that AI supplied a bunch of machines for an arcade there.
[SPEAKER_11]: They had a Max that was actually in a 1.5 cabinet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_11]: They had Guitar Freaks 5th, Germania 4th, which I absolutely butchered my hands on.
[SPEAKER_11]: They had a Beatmania 3rd there, the 3rd core, Beatmania 3 core.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, maybe I'm wrong here, because the chat room is telling me I've got SoCalKick saying he doesn't watch anime, Joe Mama says he watches maybe three animes, and Virtue says they're the same because it's Japo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I said, besides the obvious, they're both from Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any comments from you guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about the correlation between DDR and anime?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: The last time I watched anything that could be from Japan in cartoons was when I was in 6th grade and watched Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pokemon Ohms!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was real quality.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went to see the very first movie and I was all by myself in the theater with one of my best friends, Amanda, who plays DDR in the Bay Area, some of you might know her.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we had so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's all.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just think that some people who like DDR like anime, because lots of people who like video games are into computer nerd type people, like Matt here.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I'm sure that he likes tons of stuff, because he spends hours and hours on the computer.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was just the most interesting face he just made.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's been, I don't know, 20 hours a day on the computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty close to that, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: The correlation between anime and DDR, I think it's just because when people are into the Japanese pop culture, they're into everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anime, the music, the video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just kind of all one package deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's probably why right there is because you find a lot of crossovers with that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it kind of like similar to the correlation between the Renaissance Faire, Star Trek, and Bondage in S&M?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they all have scantily clad women in them at one point or another, so then, hey, we'll play anything with boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anything else you want to add on that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's time to bring the lusty wench into the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: But no, it's basically, it's just like what Matt said, I think it's the whole fan base there.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, you get into one, you hear about the next.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, my newest obsession is the whole J-Rock visual K thing, because, well, they're pretty men in makeup.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell me about the J-Rock obsession.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it about the J-Rock that's just... Because I notice it's like, you're...
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that don't know, the Bomani Music and More program, which is on this station when we're not live, all the music, we have every week, Jamie picks a song and I pick a song to play that's not in any Bomani game, but we think it should be.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Jamie picked a J-rock song, Luna Sea.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm such a whore for Luna Sea.
[SPEAKER_04]: With Crazy For You for a Guitar Freak song, which would be a pretty damn good Guitar Freak song, I have to agree with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I notice you're becoming obsessed with the J-rock lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of was for a little bit, and then I got really back into it during AX.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually bought a Hide plushie, as in Hide from X-Japan, who killed himself in a very, very controversial whole thing, but that's another story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, I picked up a Luna C set over at AX.
[SPEAKER_11]: There were lots of people.
[SPEAKER_11]: There were the gacked sex kittens.
[SPEAKER_11]: outside of the Hyatt Hotel.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it was all over the place at AX.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lots of people doing Mana from Malice Miser cosplay.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I got back and just went and found all of my old MP3s and was really into it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was visual K-Owns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Corey is challenging you.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says that Glay is better than Lunacy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a whore for lunacy, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love everything they've done.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, Rozier is my favorite song that they've done, and love song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, DarkTetsuya is reminding us that in Guitar Freak's 8th mix, which is being location tested right now, there is going to be a Gak song covered in it, so that would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, DarkTetsuya, he's saying, what's wrong with Renaissance Terror?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing wrong with a Renaissance Terror, just like there's nothing wrong with Star Trek, and there's nothing wrong with Bondage.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever you're into.
[SPEAKER_11]: They all involve leather of some kind.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've got your Klingons for your leather, your blood pie.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a leather correlation.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they are into big time S&M.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, do you think that anime and DDR, maybe it's the shoes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been wearing the same pair of shoes for a year.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the sexy nurses, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it's the whole, you know, because Solo is going to make us all go to hell.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Solo sucks anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anything else on anime?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I would probably have to say that, you know, to each their own.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anime is a pretty, you know, versatile genre, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it encompasses so much you can do anything with animation now, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And DDR, you know, they've actually started having references to DDR, to Beimani in some different anime now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't think of any off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, even Konami is putting their Beimani into their other games, like Tokimeki Memorial, Dancing Summer Vacation, which I have.
[SPEAKER_11]: And other things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, if we're done with the anime topic... Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, many of the songs from Initial D are in Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, there's an anime you might be familiar with that had a promoting reference, King of the Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it counts as anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of more like Scribble May or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd say it's more like Scribble May.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anywho, I'm being fed a lot of news here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Corey Virtue is somehow in the know, and he's giving me all this news here that he wants me to share with you and get your reaction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only in the chat room, but those of you here in the studio that might be hearing some of this news for the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'm presenting to you a little segment we call, Corey Gives Sky the News, and he reports it over the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so we have an eighth mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, if you use auto-bass, or auto-whatever, instead of giving you a perfect, it's now going to give you an auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not going to count as part of your combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think of that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I heard that before, but he didn't say auto-bass.
[SPEAKER_21]: He just said, instead of perfects, you get auto.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_21]: There's no perfects?
[SPEAKER_11]: They better take the short people into account, like... Yeah, there should be a Jamie instead of me if we can get into Jamie's.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, no, it's like, if I'm at Spiegel, the thing is too damn tall for me to reach the damn bass pedal.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should have a chair that comes with it that just boosts up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie Detective.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, for every version of Drum Mania that they put out, they need to send a free stool and a booster seat for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Drum Mania 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I say 6?
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: They need to make the bass pedal higher.
[SPEAKER_11]: They need to have adjustable bass pedals.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the new Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania, they're going to have auto instead of perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll give you incentive to play with the auto bass, but for those of us that are hype challenged in one way or another, we're just going to have to get more magazines or a smaller chair or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also in the news, you're going to be able to set different difficulty levels for one player and two player for Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So one person can do beginner, the other can do extreme or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also change the difficulty of the extra stage before you enter it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can do all your songs on Maniac and then be a chicken and do a basic extra stage or vice versa.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just want the Maniac extra stage, just use a bunch of crappy songs to get to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, there's going to be reverse mode in it too, so you can flip it, just like DDR's reverse mode, and now the notes can come to the bottom, so it can be like Beat Guitar Mania.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be like, you know, rocker mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, in another Bomani Game News, I'm not sure what the source is for this, must be a Japo site or something, he says that Beatmania 3 will be the last one too.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are going to be putting out Beatmania 3, the final as well, to correlate with the final 5 key, regular Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_11]: That really makes sense because they hardly use the pedal anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Paul's throwing his hands up behind me with the music in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's one of our hoochie mamas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thank you very much to... So you're a hoochie mama then?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much to Virtue for providing all that news for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what I was told to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been following through.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one else put their hands up.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're kind of the underdogs there, and it's all about the stupid swim park they have there, and the laser tag, and Beachhead 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, Dave, tell them about your new trick for people when they're playing Beachhead 2000 for little kids.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh yeah, Beachhead.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think Paul might have done this too, but I do it now a lot to little kids.
[SPEAKER_21]: It has a counterweight to balance out the level of the...
[SPEAKER_21]: the controller that goes on your head because it kind of does the VR virtual reality type thing where you place the controller on your head with the little two joysticks coming off the bottom and so the counterweight is behind the screen and it kind of goes and you can kind of fit back behind all the games and if you push down the counterweight then their controller that you know they've got their face
[SPEAKER_21]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is all in theory.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you can give us a shot.
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually tried it several times yesterday.
[SPEAKER_21]: But the only problem is, since I'm behind the machine, I can't see the look on their face when they poke their head out of the VR game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And look around going, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: What we'll do, maybe we'll take the remote out to Roseville Golf Land this Wednesday and we'll try that on some people.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge bloopers and practical jokes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge amazing bloopers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Smile, you're on Orange Lounge camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully we'll get those on the website for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So ways to fuck with people on Beachhead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you guys figured out a way to mess with people in Sumo yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that haven't seen Sumo, it looks like you're climbing into a giant Pokeball and playing these, like on a big screen TV you've got these big plane games and stuff and the ball moves as you fly the plane.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, I still thought it was funny when someone tried to climb on top of one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yes, imagine this big red bubble with somebody piling in it, you know, going all Evangelion on somebody, and then there's somebody on top, and then there's people on the side.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're trying to get you.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're trying to get you!
[SPEAKER_11]: I swear they are!
[SPEAKER_11]: They want your brain!
[SPEAKER_11]: But I wasn't sniffing your spicy brain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other ideas on how to mess with people on other games?
[SPEAKER_21]: No ideas yet, but I'm sure that you can just take a couple of hammers and pound on the game.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, you know, it's like shake it back and forth.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not losing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not getting hit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have someone play Gunblade and then have them try to write something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a keyboard mania.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a rightful punishment.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll strike back for our home.
[SPEAKER_11]: Our poor keyboard manias.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to know how to mess with the Gauntlet Legends players, because those are the ones, they're obsessive over the game as we are with ours.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen people there all day long, you know, Red Valkyrie is about to die, oh, I better put in another 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, don't shoot food.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, see, they play it so much, they pull up the chair, and I know a couple of guys who I just watched them play it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like they accidentally leave it on free play for two minutes, so they punch in 99 credits, and they sit there all day, and then whenever someone comes along, they dictate to them what to do.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like, okay, you go sacrifice yourself in front of the big fire-breathing dragon while I sit back and launch my little attacks.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, but I think that we should go in all dressed up like the characters.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like Red Ogre has entered the building and we should just sit there playing the game.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dressed up, it's like move aside, it's our turn to play.
[SPEAKER_21]: Make them play the old gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, make them play the old school gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That old school gauntlet rules, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they don't have an old school gauntlet machine at RVGL, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need to have them put that in the UltraGate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought of the other game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I noticed?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that when people make fun of you while you're playing DDR, they instantly go and play the WrestleMania game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I want to know how to mess with those people that are playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The WWF game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one that's right in the front as you walk in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go to Slim Jim's, Adam.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think playing that awful WWF game in Gauntlet Legends is just punishment for now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Until Day of Reckoning!
[SPEAKER_21]: It'll burn!
[SPEAKER_21]: Just come up to him.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like wearing a bandana.
[SPEAKER_21]: Snap into a Slim Jim.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_11]: Take it!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's time for a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_11]: I get to break more stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we got lots of things to celebrate in the 2DX world this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have 2DX 6 Style coming out in just four more days.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: For the Japanese PlayStation 2s, so you can order your import machine and then play some 2DX at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I'm being told that after a few weeks of downtime, 2DXStyle.net is back up and running.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you haven't visited them yet, go visit our links page, and they've got a link on it to 2DX Style.
[SPEAKER_04]: and if you don't know our website, it's at orangelounge.skie.cx and visit that one too while you're at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, in honor of these such momentous 2DX events, I'm going to play a whole set of 2DX songs for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you say?
[SPEAKER_11]: I say, okay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we'll be right back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want to be accepted by Hollywood?
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we care what people think of us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we want people to kiss our ass?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Extreme Bobani Radio That's us, Orange Lounge Radio Yes, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio This is episode number four for this July the 14th, 2002 A long break there of all 2DX songs We had Colors from Six Styles A from Seventh Style Cracker from Fifth Style for the home version In My Eyes, Fifth Style, Frozen Ray
[SPEAKER_04]: from Six Style, and an old school one, Shine On, from 2DX Second Style, which the chatroom commented, uh, wanna talk as best, although I don't think it was in reference to that song, that's by Shore Eye, actually, 2DX Second Style, I might be corrected on that, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we took a long break, because we were prepping for this segment that we're gonna do, which we're gonna call Listless.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are going to determine the worst song in Bomani history besides Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let Them Move is already assumed to be the worst song in Bomani history, so that's not a factor.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to determine the second worst song in Bomani history right here, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got everybody on the panel here who's written down their top three choices for worst Bomani song ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've ordered it in the numbers three to one.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to name off what we think the worst Bomani song is ever and why.
[SPEAKER_04]: And after that...
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get to eliminate one choice from the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have a list of 15 choices because there's five of us here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then each of us will get to take one choice off of the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then after that, with the 10 songs that will be remaining, the chatroom gets to vote and determine what is the worst song in Bomani history next to Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're in the chatroom right now, you'll get to participate in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be your vote that determines what the worst song is in Bomani history next to Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's start with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was your number three worst Bomani song in history?
[SPEAKER_11]: I really, really hate Let the Beat Hit Em.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let the Beat Hit Em, all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really care for that version.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number three worst Mamani song in history.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so going to get smacked for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I'm going to get smacked for this, but for some reason I just don't like this song when I hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number three choice is Graduistic Cyber.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Gradiusic Cyber.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Gradius.
[SPEAKER_11]: That song is cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to kick you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, my number
[SPEAKER_21]: Number three pick is Bye Bye Baby Balloon because, well, they already made it like three times and then they put a new name on it and some freeze arrows and so it does not deserve to be Bulani music.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, it kind of does because all the other ones are the same thing, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Paul.
[SPEAKER_03]: Double Trouble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Freaks Number 3 Bus Stop
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: The oldies in Disney's Rave.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did they put all these oldies in Disney's Rave?
[SPEAKER_11]: Mr. Bassman owns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Mr. Bassman does own.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mr. Bassman owns Dropout.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Bus Stop and what's the other one that annoys the hell out of me?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another old school song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Macarena.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, there's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a given.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Johnny B. Goode.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something that you heard in grade school and you did during the Disney review.
[SPEAKER_04]: It works for DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody's number threes picks are out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Let the Beat Hit Em, Graduistic Cyber, Bye Bye Baby Balloon, Double Trouble, and Bus Stops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number two choices.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Number two would be Buell.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate Buell Buell is a good one, that's a good one, very good My number two choice was another 2DX song Oh, you're correcting my spelling on what he says I'm typing these out so we can see the list of what we have so we can eliminate things later
[SPEAKER_04]: My number two choice for worst Bomani song, and I might get smacked for this because it's another 2DX song, but I really just don't like this song.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be Kamikaze from 2DX4Style.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've never actually heard that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: But my number two is, I first heard it on the DDR USA, My Fire, because that song is just terrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't like My Fire.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blasphemer.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's old school.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's enough to be retro.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was my favorite song back then.
[SPEAKER_21]: Butterfly in Boom Boom Dollar Old School.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is just crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is on 1.5.
[SPEAKER_03]: First it was cool, then it was very uncool, and now it's retro-cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gone through the cycle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Retro-cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: My number two is a very generic choice for a song.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just has the diva part, it has the rap part, everything that would be characteristic in a DDR song, and it's all done badly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Detour.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a bad song.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta get that on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh man, I don't know if I can top that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, my second pick would have to go to Chodo, I guess, from DDR Club Mix, and also his second mix, Link Version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even, that was just, it was a Laughin' Pete track, and it was just awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: How in the hell do you even spell that one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even think I've played that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here, C-H-O-T-T-O, and then the second part of it is K-I-I-N-T-E-N-A.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye, laugh, and peace.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting screamed at from the chat room for some of our number two choices, which again were Buell, Kamikaze, My Fire, D2R, and Chotokitene.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people disagree with Kamikaze.
[SPEAKER_04]: Corey is crying because he loves D2R and doesn't understand why none of us seem to like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, number one picks for worst Bomani song ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my vote to Strangle Politary.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Queens, Jamaica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Queens, Jamaica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate Queens, Jamaica.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate Queens, Jamaica because way back when on the old hip-hop mania machine that we had, everybody made me freaking play that song and I hate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's also on my fifth mix non-stop.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it always comes up right after my favorite song.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I hate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number one choice for worst Bomani song in history besides Let Them Move would be Jam Jam Reggae.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yum Yum Ragu.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I just, it's annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No worries.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whoa!
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, um, my least favorite song is, uh, I'm going on Corey's naming because I don't know the name.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's, uh, Under Control, which is the encore stage for long version songs for guitar, seventh mix, uh, uh, drum mania sixth mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the reason why I picked it is because it's just grunge music.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's terrible.
[SPEAKER_21]: It belongs not in Bomani.
[SPEAKER_21]: It belongs in, like, underground crap music that's not even made into CDs.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I avoid playing it by failing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I fail the extra stage, which is One Phrase Blues, which is an awesome song, just so I don't even have to hear the beginning of that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Under Control, worst Pomani song of the day has been in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some really bad songs, you know, have a nice thing about them, like Detour was hilarious, the best worst song ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jem Jem Reggae has some fun steps on Maniac.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this song, I heard about it, heard it before, and it was coming in the DDR, I was like, oh, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I play the song, and the steps are so slow, which is an awful song in the DDR, the steps are tub-thumping, had the worst steps in the DDR, and I was so pissed about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, what a bad song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't think you're going to get much argument there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but it gets, it gets not down, but it gets up again.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're never going to keep it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Matt, you're the final choice on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, there was just, like I said, so many to choose from.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, now, Jam Jam Reggae, and I'm talking about the original one from Beatmania, because that one is damn awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, there was another one from Beatmania that was also very awful, and that would be Love So Groovy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love So Groovy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate that song, it's just awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was originally one of my picks, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so the big list here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is all 15 choices, and we're going to now eliminate one song at a time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Let the Beat Hit Em, Graduistic Cyber, Bye Bye Baby Balloon, Double Trouble, Bus Stop, Fuel, Kamikaze, My Fire, D2R, Choto Katana, Queens, Jamaica, Jam Jam Reggae, Under Control, Tub Thumping, and Love So Groovy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once we get this narrowed down to 10, the chat room will get to vote on what they think is the worst song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think some of these songs are so bad that we never bothered to get them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_11]: And there was much rejoicing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Graduous Exciber has to come off.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is my freaking song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I finally, finally managed to beat and sing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so it gets saved.
[SPEAKER_04]: I, yeah, he would kill me, but he's not here, ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am going to grant a pardon to I'm Sorry Dave, but Under Control is fucking hilarious, and it goes off the list.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song's so bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, well, then I guess I'll just have to take off Jam Jam Reggae off the list, because that song rocks on Doubles Maniac.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's so cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you know, it was from 1.5, and it is a cool, retro-cool song, my fire, and it's taken off the list.
I agree.
[SPEAKER_11]: I totally agree with that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know about the steps in Tump Thumping, I thought it was damn easy, so I had a really cool edit for it, so I'm gonna have to take Tump Thumping off the list there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take it off the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody boo Matt, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so we've taken five songs off the list, and these are the ten that are left.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let the Beat Hit Em, Bye Bye Baby Balloon, Double Trouble, Bus Stop, Beul, Kamikaze, D2R, Chotokatena, Queens, Jamaica, and Love So Groovy.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's too late to add little bits.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's too late to add songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the ten.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just posted them in chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat room, send me a private message, please, with your vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying my vote is whatever for the worst Vamani song ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, we're going to take a really quick break while you guys vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just send me a private message in the channel saying my vote is and whatever you're picking for worst Bomani song.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll tally up the votes and we'll come back and let you know the worst Bomani song in history next to Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have something to say, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't believe you picked Gratis Exciber.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure there's got to be a song you hate that I like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what else were you thinking of putting on your list?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I did have Love So Groovy on there, and I really hate D2R.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like the music, but I hate Politary singing, so I'd have to ask anything with her singing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's play something we talked about being over... We'll do one... Do I have... No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do some of the Max tracks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do some of the Max exclusive tracks.
[SPEAKER_04]: People like these songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to take a quick break here, and we'll be right back with the worst Bomani song in history.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm waiting for your votes in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when she caught his eye, ain't no man can fight the demon He knew he had to try to make love again Mother let him know, she was in the mood for talking So then he began to play the game Before he knew it, he had told her how much he'd been hurt
[SPEAKER_09]: And when you wake up late thinking it's a dream The best thing for you, no, you can count on me, believe me And what this lady, you know what she found in me Is a lady, the kind of lady that can give you what you need Baby, the kind of lady that will never leave you lonely And what this lady, finally she found me, oh, I love you
[SPEAKER_05]: Bitch, get a new song.
[SPEAKER_15]: An open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just after 8 o'clock, a little bit closer to 8.07 here in the middle of our fourth episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live where we are right in the middle of determining the worst song in Bomani history.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next to Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let Them Move is already a given that it's first place, so we're doing the next worst Bomani song ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the votes are in.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've asked everybody in our chatroom to vote on the list which we had, which consisted of Let The Beat Hit Them, Bye Bye Baby Balloon, Double Trouble, Bus Stop, Buell, Kamikaze, D2R, Choto Katana,
[SPEAKER_04]: Queens, Jamaica, and Love So Groovy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we do have a winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: In third place is Let The Beat Hit Them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how that corresponds to Let The Beat Hit Them, but I thought it was a funny sound file.
[SPEAKER_04]: In second place for Worst Bomani Song Ever, Buell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buell.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my goodness, I can't believe it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything's ruined.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything's ruined by Buell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buell, the second worst Bomani song in history.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the worst Bomani song in history, next to Let Them Move, is Bye Bye Baby Balloon.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just going to flush that one down the toilet and pretend it didn't exist.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye Bye Baby Balloon was the winner.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I guess the winner of losing.
[SPEAKER_04]: First place loser.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sucks so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye, Baby Balloon.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so bad, they didn't even put it in Max 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just got taken right off of Max and flushed down the toilet.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wait, you've got to think of it this way.
[SPEAKER_21]: Buell sucks even more because he can't even lose right.
[SPEAKER_21]: He has to come in second at being the worst song ever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good point, good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, unfortunately, I do not have a drumroll sound, but I do have this.
[SPEAKER_04]: For when Paul tells his next joke on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pressure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had this tower of vanilla Coke cans that I was building up that just fell over.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm surprised you guys didn't hear the sound of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: My leaning tower of vanilla Coke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I have to... Yes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, you know, for all of the songs, I think, that are so terrible, we do have to remember that because these songs are so bad, they give value to the songs that are really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we need our bad songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe in a future edition, do you think we'd have the balls to do the best Bomani song ever?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, totally.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we'll do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we have the balls here at this radio station?
[SPEAKER_11]: We've got balls bigger than anybody because they're inflatable, like our egos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Balls of them all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, tournaments.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were some tournaments this weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a tournament up in Reno.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, none of us were able to get up there and go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what the results were yet, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: But are you guys going to be going to any upcoming tournaments?
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems like there's so many tournaments going on lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think it's just because it's summertime or...
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's because people are bored.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they just want to have a tournament?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear about now?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a tournament at SVGL.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're having the... I unfortunately don't recall the right name of it, but I'm sure I'll be correct in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something like the DDR Royal Rumble, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be having a perfect attack tournament that's kind of tied in a little bit to wrestling.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to have a tag team thing, and they're going to have a rumble.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they're going to have...
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think about tournaments on weekdays?
[SPEAKER_04]: It blows because people have jobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't really comment on jobs or responsibilities, but I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I can't really comment on that either, but I've got Summer School, which totally blows even more.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care, Perfect Attack is boring, don't want to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but you have to admit though, you have to admit Matt, even though Perfect Attack is boring, the stuff they're doing with this tournament is going to make it a little more exciting, because they're going to have the music, and the big costumes, and everything, just like Rosalind.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just like watching that 80s show and then the final episode of that 80s show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a little bit better, but it still sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I don't really know what this Royal Rumble they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everyone pile on the machine and stomp on one arrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it doesn't work like that, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although that would be fun, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the way they're doing the Royal Rumble is basically you're going to draw a number randomly from 1 through 30.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the first two people will go up, and whoever wins stays on the machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, to prevent the last person from just coming up there, say the first guy beats 29 people and then loses the last guy, that would really suck for him.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they have this little system they're using called chips, where if you beat so many people, you get a chip, and basically it moves you back to the end of the line.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a very good idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a very good idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still wanting to have, like, you know, Guitar Freaks Drum Mania Visual K. I'm very surprised there hasn't been any kind of Drum Mania Guitar Freaks tournament.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be really simple to do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Rob, if we ever do have another tournament here in Sacramento, that we have to use my idea of PA with answering trivia questions.
[SPEAKER_21]: And whenever you get one wrong, then you get beaten with, like, some object, and the object's continually...
[SPEAKER_11]: The Orange Bat of Doom
[SPEAKER_02]: and, god damn, there wasn't any... That was the most boring thing ever, just waiting for freestyle to come around, just watching all the people get up on the machine, complaining that the buttons aren't working, and they have to stop, and they have to test the buttons, and the buttons were working.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is so boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, oh, and Folsom, when we had our SCAT tournament, I mean, it was even worse, because then you got it... You had the whole thing, you know, just packed, and then...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do have to admit, at the very end of the Perfect Attack and the Folsom Tournament where they had to do the verses, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But like I said, the rest of it sucked.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why this year we're not having a tourney named after feces.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, instead we're going to find another crude word to name it after.
[SPEAKER_04]: I notice you've got some listings here of some upcoming tournaments.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what some other local tournaments... Well, we're not just a local show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk about some of the abroad tournaments.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like there's a pretty popular tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, this is kind of local.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to be a tournament at Mountain Mike's in Concord on August 17th.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Dollar Mendy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And another Chinak Chinak tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is interesting because I believe it's going to be a no-bar machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they were going to take the bars off for Perfect Attack as well, but I know for Freestyle there is going to be no bar on the machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I recall, I do believe that the bar will be removed.
[SPEAKER_03]: For Perfect Attack, if it isn't removed, then if you grab the bar and you don't look like you're falling down, you'll get disqualified.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who uses the bar for Perfect Attack anyway?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's people who rape the bar.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see it in tournaments though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I've ever seen anyone grab the bar in a tournament.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've seen it happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the only time I think I really see people grab the bar would be on fast songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Dropout was first, you know, the new song to beat, everybody, all the cool kids want to beat Dropout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people held the bar for that, and then of course Max and Max Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't say that I've ever really held on to the bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: I... I... When I was learning how to beat Max 300, I was using it for a while, but then I was like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to do this with my feet because it doesn't seem... It doesn't seem right unless I can do it with my feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: At Max Unlimited, I haven't allowed myself to touch the bar at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm really bad at Max 300 and Max Unlimited, but I've gotten further through them without using the bar than I have using it because it just totally throws off my center of balance.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, the bar is there, I think, to catch yourself if you're falling.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, for emergencies.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I...
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know, the original solo machines, the Japanese solo machines, they don't have a bar on them.
[SPEAKER_11]: So... Anyway, we have more tournaments.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, can you go back to that listing of tournaments there that you had up on the screen a minute?
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at some other tournaments that seem to be pretty popular.
[SPEAKER_11]: Use the little... There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're having a moment while we... Okay, we're looking at some other popular looking tournaments that are coming up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, there's the big one at Castro Valley Golf Land on July 20th.
[SPEAKER_04]: The week right after that, they're having one in Rohnert Park, Scandia.
[SPEAKER_04]: The same day as the big Mountain Mikes in Concord, they're going to be having one in SoCal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this one's kind of a controversial tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're having the Rays Game Center tournament, and it's kind of a bit controversial because it's not DDR Drags, which is a little bit...
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a constant controversy on some message boards.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was told in no uncertain terms that when I was in San Diego I was not to go to Rays.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess some interesting things going on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if we want to get into it on the show, but apparently they've decided, the owner of the place decided to make a change with who's going to be running the tournament and not going over well with some people down there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they are still going to be doing a tournament on the 17th, same day as the one in Concord.
[SPEAKER_04]: So unfortunately that's going to split things up a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know Drags 2, I went down to Drags 2, which was about a year ago, and one of the best...
[SPEAKER_04]: Best tournaments I went to.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a great road trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really like road tripping sometimes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had to miss it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was home all by myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we go back to the list?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_21]: When is the 17th of the 8th month?
[SPEAKER_21]: On the 17th!
[SPEAKER_21]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_21]: Of the 8th month of the year.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm like Captain Not Look at Obvious Stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a Saturday, to my knowledge, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Midwest Showdown 2
[SPEAKER_04]: and they've got some other tournaments coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see anything too far off the calendar.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems like August 17th is really the last thing that's planned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are the results for yesterday's tournament in Reno up there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't we go ahead and read those off if we've got them.
[SPEAKER_11]: They might not be up yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to Dollar Mendy's Summer Vacation, no bar, in Concord.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, should you drive farther for a tournament that may not be good or have no bar?
[SPEAKER_11]: And some tasty pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, Paul, it's a national show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually an international show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have listeners in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cool thing is on the Live365 stats, I can see where the listeners are listening from, and I do have listeners listening in from Japan, so that's pretty cool, huh?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're robots.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are robots.
[SPEAKER_04]: All over the place.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have listeners in Canada as well and all sorts of places now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Poppin' Music Poppin' Music 8
[SPEAKER_11]: I like poppin' music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love poppin' music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But why is it that it's kind of forgotten?
[SPEAKER_04]: You never hear it talked about?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, poppin' music is just like, hey, I got an idea, let's take 2DX, lose the turntable, make all the buttons really, really big and colorful.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow, that sounds great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds like some kind of Fruit Roll-Ups, you know, mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, what did we pour on the buttons?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are they getting so big?
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think it's because pop music isn't in a lot of arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more of like a novelty thing that people don't really play that much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Poppin' music is pretty challenging, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought I could get right up and play it, and I totally failed like Cutie Honey on Adamelo 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think it's just because the machines are so scattered amongst the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't really see them in the... There's no pop-in music machines, to my knowledge, anyway, in the Bay Area, which is where, you know, the majority of your board posters come from, because it was the first area that had Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: SoCal has a couple machines, Arcade Infinity.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been there playing... It's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the ones when you have to hit four at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: You kind of have to use your forearms to hit the buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, karate chop!
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I think they have a machine in Seattle, but they're kind of spotty, the location of the machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that's the only reason people look at... Sort of out of sight, out of mind.
[SPEAKER_21]: At AI, why play poppin' music when you can play Mambo-O-Gogo?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's all I... Because Mambo-O-Gogo has like ten songs, and once you've played them all... Personally, I find Mambo-O-Gogo to be kind of easy, personally.
[SPEAKER_21]: Even on the hard mode, it's... You can play it with all nine of the things and get like... You can beat the hardest song on that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I played the hardest song, but I played Hard Mode, and it wasn't, you know, 2DX is harder for me, but I guess that's a given.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's the information on the, what do you want to tell us about Poppin' Music 8, Matt?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, this information comes from BimaniStyle.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got, looks like a couple features here.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, there's going to be a mode called Beat Pop, which is basically, you have instead of the nice little, I guess, stuff they normally have falling down the screen, you have lines just like Beat Mania, that type of thing, kind of makes it look more like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a sort of a dark mode called Soft Discretion Line, and it just turns the indicator a little bit darker, so it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they have one that's really cool that's called Disjointed Speed Mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what that is, is where, for instance, if it were to be applied to DDR, you'd have the left arrow going at 4 speed, you'd have the up arrow going at 2 speed, maybe the right arrow at 1 speed, and then maybe, I don't know, the down arrow or something at another speed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically you have all the arrows going at different speeds.
[SPEAKER_11]: Disjointed Speed sounds like some weird band name.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be really hard to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of pretty much all the new features that are going to be coming out for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as the song list goes, there's a couple of songs coming over from different Bomani.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got Candy, the vocal version from Max 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have, well, let's see here, Boa Boa Lady from Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_02]: Much better than Jam Jam Reggae.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here, Linus, I think that was 2DX, Sixstyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here, we've got...
[SPEAKER_02]: Jet World
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, driving this into the ground here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you think of it, you can let us know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're actually having a request, though, from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want an update.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt, you seem to be our simulator expert here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on in the sim world?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we haven't talked about it yet, this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they want to hear what's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, some stuff going.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now, pretty much two things that we've been waiting for have been the new versions of Step Mania and Dance With Intensity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance With Intensity, we're still waiting for them to actually release a beta of version 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Step Mania has been coming out with new betas.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have beta 4 now, which is alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been trying it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still sticking with Dance With Intensity because it loads up really fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's what I seem to like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll rather have faster loading over all the, you know, kind of bonus features that they've got there.
[SPEAKER_21]: For Step Mania, I don't know if it was just Beta 3 or just the computer that I played it on, but two-thirds of the time or more when you ever hit an up and down jump arrow or whenever you held one of the up and down jump arrows and tried to hit...
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, held up and down arrow, or either one of them tried to hit the other one, it wouldn't register, or it would register just as like a boo or a good or something.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I don't know if that's just on all beta 3 or just on the computer that I use.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really sure about that one but the other thing that's going to be going on is the contest that they had for the DWI contest they had put out by DDR East Coast Invasion is they're actually doing voting right now and it should have been wrapped up today according to their boards but I still haven't seen anything on that yet and the melting pot boards are still messed up
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I am getting a rumor here that DWI2, one of the new features, is going to be a groove meter.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't doubt it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's been looking for a good code for it, you know, some good source code to actually generate those, much like, you know, Stepmania has.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I saw that with Stepmania 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just like, okay, so I don't look at that anyways.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we're going to take another quick break, and when we come back, we'll interact with the chat room a little more, talk about whatever they want us to talk about.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have some other topics here that we can get into if we want.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, God, who knows what else we're going to talk about here on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll just say screw Bomani, and we'll just talk about other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, you're listening to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing over there, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm on the floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're on the floor?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to kick Matt out of the chair?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I just kick him?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or I can get you another chair if you want.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we'll be back in a little bit.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: I am DJ Sender!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Gachon!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_18]: Who's that Pokemon?
Move on now, let somebody feel the beat Come on, wake up, let our energy to beat
and many more.
[SPEAKER_15]: Warning, Orange Lounge Radio's Bonnie Music and More program might be dangerous for you to listen to in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have reported incidents where exposed listening to this program in the kitchen has caused people to bust out a Sharpie pen, draw arrows on the tiles, and start stomping away.
[SPEAKER_15]: A friendly public service announcement from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're here until 9 o'clock tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going to turn it over to Paul.
[SPEAKER_04]: Paul likes to do a little segment every week here, when he's here, where he's going to wrap up what's going on on the local message boards, local and abroad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever message board he wants to talk about, he's giving us the wrap-up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go for it, Paul.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to give you some music, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, on the Sacramento Money Board, there's a little action in, you know, great, being grown up, but you're obese.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: On Sacamani, we've been going over and talking about, after our crazy broken bread, we've been seeing, you know, how much stuff has been broken out in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, since it's been us helping out, and we've decided that we're going to get a letter together.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jessica, the Gwana girl, has gone to play in the drafts with us together, and we're going to go over it, and form a letter together, and I'll send it in, and talk about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um, so the discussion has been going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people still can't post in the right introductory thread and everything else.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just a little concern.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to get that mic a little closer to your mouth, Paul.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like you're going to shove it all in your mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take it all at once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take it all.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just going to blow that whistle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just glad that we've been actually getting something together after complaining for so long.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I thought we'd just note that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyone who's interested should talk to people about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other boards you want to give us a lowdown on?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, not much has been happening too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of boards have slowed down just because people have been divided, and I haven't been on DDR Freak in a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Same old, same old on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so that's a wrap-up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same old shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Paul.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm being given a link here in the chat rooms for us to discuss, so let's just bring it up here live on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rumors, rumors, rumors.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know these have to be... These are all rumors and who knows what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, this is an interesting rumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: This kind of has to go with the message board wrap-up because this has been posted on DDR Free causing quite the stir here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Says, Konami USA has issued a press release saying they will seize all unauthorized 5th, 6th, and 7th mixed games with the help of local law enforcement.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure I know what site they'll be looking at to find out where these machines are located.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thoughts, people?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, first of all, I'd like to actually read that press release.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is there a link on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: There is not.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Makes one think.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, if someone's going to put up a rumor of that magnitude, the only way I would believe it is either, one, seeing the press release, or two, having it posted by KOA on the board.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, until I have, you know, legitimate proof, I call that a big pile of sticky poop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what people are saying about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: BS, BS, BS, BS, BS, BS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much everybody says that's BS.
[SPEAKER_04]: That they're going to be wasting their time and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're claiming that Konami of America is going to make an announcement tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see if there's any truth to that rumor.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see if miracles will ever start.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if you've seen how many people in green shirts are going around Golfland now with the racetrack and stuff, they have an evil army.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no way anything's getting out of there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you tie yourself to the DDR machine if it was going to be taken away?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tyne, you know, I think I'd just stick with the Guitar Breaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: The people would be distracted, no one would be playing, I could get a few games in, it'd be alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to see how they're going to actually pull this off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, how many machines do we have in California alone, let alone the whole United States?
[SPEAKER_11]: Plenty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, where the hell are they, what the hell are they going to do with those tournaments, the USA Mixes?
[SPEAKER_03]: And they can't read the machine locations page on DDR Freak with their tiny Asian eyes, so I don't know how this is going to work out.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: But no, you know, if they're going to do that for Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania, why not do it for DDR2?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not go get all those pop music machines, all five of them that we have in the country?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or, you know, go hunt down Dance Maniacs or the like.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or, you know, go get the Korean machines.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not, you know, hit them too?
[SPEAKER_04]: Quick, they're coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get the Max 2 and run.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had something you wanted to add, Matt?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much, we're being told in the chatroom, they pretty much agree that it seems to sound like a bunch of BS to you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's poopy!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, DarkTetsuya is offering, though, if anybody wants to come play the Max 3 beta at his house before the cops take it away.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dude, I'm there.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is for you, DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sound will never get old for me, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead Air!
[SPEAKER_04]: In two weeks on this show, on the 28th, there's about a 50-50 chance we're going to have a very special guest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two very special guests here that night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't say who because it's not confirmed yet, but you'll definitely want to tune in to that show in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll hopefully have somebody who knows Jamie and I very, very well, who's sure to bring up a lot of dirt on us, and a very famous freestyler also should be here.
[SPEAKER_21]: You sound like you're actually promoting our show.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody knows my email address anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your email address is accessible on the website.
[SPEAKER_11]: All the porn people just love to send me stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: What other topics do I have written down here for things we can do?
[SPEAKER_11]: We have a hold.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait one second.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me pass the mic over.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, I'm just reading this off of Konami America's site, totally unrelated to what we were just talking about here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's talking about that this guy, John Benson and Ward Evans, are DDR fanatics.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're creators of Dance Machine, a short film about the world's biggest DDR fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: The movie won the coveted CLAMD or 2002 CLAMDance Film Festival.
[SPEAKER_02]: The CLAMDance?
[SPEAKER_02]: In Newport, Rhode Island.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully we'll never see that on video.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: If we have a DDR movie, I have a real good idea for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: People have been making DDR players, celebrities and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know Corey's in the chat room and he's been getting some of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know Corey's screen name?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to talk to Corey.
[SPEAKER_03]: People like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I think that as anyone like Mike, people have heard about this movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little kid finds his shoes, becomes like Michael Jordan, starts dunking on everybody, gets in the NBA.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want someone to find maybe like Corey's old underpants.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's say Corey on the name tag.
[SPEAKER_03]: He'll put them on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please make me like Cory, and he'll come to the PA competition, maybe the triple threat, you know, start owning everyone, this little scrub that everyone sees playing USA, and just kills everyone, and it's a whole new phenomenon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then he finds out, you know, the underwear wasn't what it is, it was the magic inside.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that would make a good... Put down the pipe, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember that old business though about DDR Freak the movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: With all the scripts that floated around that made it into this utter, you know, crappy teeny movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would have just been, that would have been boycotting that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say this on the show right now, something I haven't told anybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm writing a screenplay that involves DDR heavily.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'll say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we have another guest who just walked into the room.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bongo demands this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Introduce yourself, new guest.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's your real self.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have a bit of a problem with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The big gay perilous.
[SPEAKER_20]: Our token cross-dresser.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now I'm forever known as the absolutely gay cross-dresser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Matt, bring up the official site for that movie thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you trying to do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a click here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's some, and we're being, one person in the chat room says they did see it and they didn't like it, so your first review is a big thumbs down.
[SPEAKER_04]: The DDR movie about the biggest DDR fan that won the Clamdance award.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's what?
[SPEAKER_04]: www.johnandward.com We'll bring it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm even more alarmed that as opposed to there being a movie, there's a clam dance festival.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's the big news here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that there's a movie out, but there's a clam dance.
[SPEAKER_11]: That just makes me think it's like some big, you know, like, lesbian gathering.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what brings to mind a clam dance festival?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what brings to mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: Was that the sound of a dying mutant clam?
[SPEAKER_04]: A clam opening up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Roar!
[SPEAKER_11]: When you have the signal, beat like a dying camel.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to take a real fast break and we're going to come back and wrap up the show because we don't have much time left.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stay with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to take a real quick break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, everybody!
I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll be your everybody I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll stay to you every night I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll be your celebrity I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll be your everybody I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll be your everybody I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll stay to you every night
Happy New Year, Happy New Year, Happy New Year, Happy Wedding Happy New Year, Happy New Year, I say to you everyday Happy New Year, Happy New Year, Happy Sunset Wedding
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: And now it's time for Erotic Pop Idol, where we will find the next singer for everyone's favorite perverse pomani band, Erotic.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do it all night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do it with me.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no, that was awful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bloody terrible.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you take vocal lessons?
[SPEAKER_17]: Kill your teacher.
[SPEAKER_17]: In the heat of the night.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, God, I think my ears are bleeding.
[SPEAKER_13]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shut the bloody hell up, Paula.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do you even know why you're here?
[SPEAKER_19]: That was just bloody pathetic!
[SPEAKER_19]: Next!
[SPEAKER_16]: Come on, do it with me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, that's it!
[SPEAKER_16]: We have a winner!
[SPEAKER_15]: A star is born here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, a star is born every second.
[SPEAKER_04]: A star being born over there on the other computer in the house.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were watching that short movie that we were referencing earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the name of that, Matt?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Machine is also proof that while every moment a star is born every moment a star explodes too
[SPEAKER_02]: Never have I felt more sorry for mid-age men who think that they're young I've never seen a guy that old playing DDR, that's amazing There's always Kobe Hey, and Nick Nolte owns a DDR machine That's true, that's true Nick Nolte owns one and he takes lots of items too Yeah, but Nick Nolte didn't win, you know, Best Comedy He didn't win the Clam Dance Award In San Francisco, okay
[SPEAKER_11]: The Clam Dance Award is a lesbian award.
[SPEAKER_11]: So is he like, you know... Is it kind of like Flashdance?
[SPEAKER_04]: What a feeling.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's always better with clams.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's the quote of Ryan for the evening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also during that break, I took a chance to look at the newly remodeled 2DX style and I give it my seal of approval.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a little pretty opening movie when you go into the site and it's all nicely remodeled.
[SPEAKER_04]: So do pay that a visit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's linked from our links page if you want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_11]: 2DX style gets the kudos of the evening.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll go buy you a candy bar, Corey.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also 3FeetElite, who is the puppeteer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will go buy a box of Kudos and deliver them to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have some nice forums over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think the DDR community is too saturated with forums?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think there's too many?
[SPEAKER_11]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the uncles you don't talk to much.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the uncles you don't talk to, they're kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't speak good English.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and Sakmamani's just like, Yay, we're happy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't flame on people.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's because we love everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you don't think there's just an overabundance of sites?
[SPEAKER_04]: What about when boards shut down, like DDR spots did?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think they just thought, you know, maybe this is a little much, there is a lot of boards, or, you know, I'm not on the staff, I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's not something I feel that I can really comment on.
[SPEAKER_04]: True, I know, we probably can't really say much about it, but I'm just kind of saying, do you think maybe it was too many boards, or...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, like, as far as for one purpose, okay, you know, it's hard to get used to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even Ryan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, sort of like the alternate board used to be GDCon, and people would talk about that and go on there eventually.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it sort of got split between that and MonkeySpline and other network.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of good to have the big, big city, but then it's also good to have a couple little suburbs too that are fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: My observation with the GDCoon forums is that a lot of people who were booted from DDR Freak ended up there too.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was still another place.
[SPEAKER_11]: The big thing I like about having such a wide selection of forums is that you can see how their community works.
[SPEAKER_11]: Each one of them has their own feel.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have the one that's a little bit more irreverent.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have your other that's more all-encompassing.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Freak I think is more all-encompassing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really, really like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, we have our little, you know, happy inbred family at Sakumai.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, you know, we have, I think we're really getting that good sense of community.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm really at least hoping that, you know, a lot of the good feelings from back in the old days come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we talk about porn there, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we talk about porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have our own hentai thread, thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we're all going to YaoiCon.
[SPEAKER_11]: YaoiCon.
Wee!
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm not going to YaoiCon.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know what you people are smoking with all the gas.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're coming to YaoiCon.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not!
[SPEAKER_11]: We're making you dress up.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're making you cosplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get to wear the frilly black lace.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we like lots of different forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool to have a lot of different forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody has their own different personality, and you just choose to hang out with the people you want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other topic I wanted to bring up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hearing DDR songs in interesting places.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't necessarily mean on the radio, but do you guys ever hear DDR songs in very strange places?
[SPEAKER_04]: Places you didn't expect to hear them at?
[SPEAKER_04]: In the mall.
[SPEAKER_04]: For once, I picked up this CD this week that just happened to have Ordinary World on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was very odd.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like this trans compilation CD, and then all of a sudden there's Ordinary World.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, wow, DDR in my nightmares.
[SPEAKER_03]: This DJ at one of my school dances was playing all this bad techno music, and all of a sudden Stomp To My Beat comes up, and that's where it's taken.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we went over this before, but Stomp To My... Why is everyone shoving two microphones in my face?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, I get one, and Jamie's like, here, here, take it, take it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Get the dual voice effect.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we were all at Brookfield, and I played Stomp To My Beat from the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and, um, but, we went over this a while ago, and yeah, stomped on my beat, I've heard it a while, but I think that I've listened to DDR music so much, that whenever I think I hear something, I have to take, like, a second, listen to it, because I'm not sure if it's just my mind playing tricks on me, because now I've listened to so much, and some of the stuff sounds so similar, I'm listening to Dropout, and it sounds like, yeah, I'm dead around, or something like that, it's, I, it just doesn't compute, I've listened to so much.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think it's getting more annoying on the idea that you listen to the radio and some of this DDR stuff comes on or you have a CD where you're listening to the DDR stuff comes on you don't know which is getting pulled from which because I know Stomp to My Beat was a pretty popular techno song before it got pulled into DDR so I'm wondering if more isn't coming along those lines
[SPEAKER_11]: It's also sad that, you know, with some of us being the ages that we are, that we actually remember the original songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were like, I remember the original Sky High that was redone by DJ Miko.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, even being an anime fan, I will sit and listen to Freckles and the Japanese lyrics, like the opening to Rurouni Kenshin goes in my head, and the original Hot Limit by TM Revolution, which, by the way, everybody should listen to because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I had the weirdest thing happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was watching MTV for, like, the once in, like, the last two years, and I heard Oops, I Did It Again, and it's so weird that they ripped off, like, DDR Fifth Mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I have no idea why.
[SPEAKER_12]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, it's just like, whoa.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Oops, He Did It Again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, that song was cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know... Anyway... It's just, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that not only are our lives, I guess, influenced by Behmany, but, you know, Behmany is influenced by the way that the world has been, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, the music has evolved.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's evolved with, you know, people's tastes.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it evolves with the times.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, that's another really cool thing is that you're more likely now to hear something that's been in a Behmany game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mike Dornan
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the Mattel Chocobot Hour.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other comments?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I think we're going to wrap up the show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks to everybody for listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have got a really good turnout tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, everybody in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you join us every Sunday night from 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: until 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, we're going to start doing rebroadcasts on Monday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to do rebroadcasts Monday night at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can hear all of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then at 9 o'clock, we bring you a classic show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to go ahead and replay the first episode this week for those that missed it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd like to thank all of my friends who said that they'd be listening in tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: And for our two listeners in Japan.
[SPEAKER_20]: We have listeners in Japan?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we have listeners in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would like to thank our listeners on the East Coast, West Coast, South Coast, Gulf Coast.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, whatever coast it happens to be.
[SPEAKER_11]: The coast in your own mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: And again, do join in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Visit our website at orangelounge.skie.cx and get all the information on our station.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when this live talk program isn't on the air, do tune in to our Bomani Music & More program that runs 24 hours a day on this dial-up stream.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got all sorts of music, 2DX, DDR, everything including Dance Mania and other music games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now Rob, are we going to be adding that list of songs we would like to hear in Bimani?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I remember we were talking about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a couple weeks ago we were talking about the songs that we think should be in Bimani that aren't yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, some of those songs do show up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie and I put in a pick a week on the music stuff and we'll be adding some of the stuff that was talked about that show also.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knows, perhaps we can make that a contest for the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, if you guys want to send us email...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all one word.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLoungeRadio at Yahoo.com Your suggestions for music you think should be on the station, even if it's not in a Mamadi game.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it should be, why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let us know and then tell us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Send us a sound clip of your voice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say who you are and what you think should be in.
[SPEAKER_11]: You might find yourself a local celebrity.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks everybody for listening and we'll see you next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody else have any closing words?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks all of you for being here, Ryan, even though you were only here 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks everyone else.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's the important part.
[SPEAKER_11]: Listen to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bongo demands it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think that only one cuss word was said this entire show.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I said it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will you care to remedy that situation then, Dave?
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I can't copy Brad because last time he was just busting out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shitty Poopy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember folks, this show is brought to you by DVDA.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: This show is brought to you by the number...
[SPEAKER_03]: Sponsored by Red Octane.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like everything you own.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everything belongs to Red Octane.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, goodnight everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura, and Rob Roberts, also known as Sky.
[SPEAKER_15]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember kids, say no to crack.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pull up your pants!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.