[SPEAKER_11]: Monkey, Monkey, Monkey, Monkey, Monkey, Monkey, Monkey, Monkey, I'm gonna be a monkey.
[SPEAKER_11]: Monkey, Monkey, Monkey, would you like to be one too?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, if you wanna be a monkey, you gotta learn to act like a monkey.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I've got the know-how, cause I've seen every car and movie ever made.
[SPEAKER_11]: So watch and learn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, everybody.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just made up a song, and I hope you can sing along with me.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's called I'm a Cucumber.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: One, two, three, four.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm a cucumber.
[SPEAKER_15]: Please don't take me to Pickle Farm.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much, everybody.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: The following program is intended for mature audiences.
[SPEAKER_22]: Tonight on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 165, more dick and fart jokes with Bomani.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're going to talk a lot tonight about catching up with Jamie, because it's been a little while, because she's been bogged down by viruses.
[SPEAKER_22]: and hopefully she's not contagious because we don't all want to catch bubonic plague.
[SPEAKER_22]: But we might all catch ferret.
[SPEAKER_22]: We shall see on tonight's episode.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also tonight, your calls and such and more information on DER Strike and Miklatov's in the house for a little bit to talk about his love for something that isn't a video game.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_22]: And God knows what else.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding, Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_22]: We are live, and this is episode number 165 for this November the 27th of 2005 episode.
[SPEAKER_22]: You're tuned into Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want, and this is Orange Lounge Radio Live, your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_22]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_22]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts in this corner.
[SPEAKER_22]: Welcome back, the happiest bunny on the farm, Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_22]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: You don't, you say you're still kind of, you're obviously, you're coughing right now, that's not picking up on the mic, but you don't sound sick.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like the last two weeks you sounded sick, but now it's kind of one of those, you obviously have a virus or something because you don't sound sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a virus, it's bacterial and my voice does on occasion come and go.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I didn't really talk much today.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, but you sound pretty solid tonight, so.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I apparently have whooping cough now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, we're going to play the Wheel of Infection, I think it's what Loki called it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wheel of Infection, turn, turn, turn.
[SPEAKER_22]: Show us which disease Jamie should have.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thing is, is that whooping cough is something you're inoculated against when you're younger, only it apparently has something like some 10, 20% chance of hitting you when you're older.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fun, huh?
[SPEAKER_22]: Exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, diseases.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we'll be talking diseases with Jamie tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, in that corner, we'll be talking hamburgers with Loki!
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm almost done.
[SPEAKER_22]: How is your biggest gainer adventure going?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't had McDonald's, though, in a week, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's an accomplishment, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I had turkey this week, so no time for McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, I actually just kind of wanted something quick, didn't have anything, so I got two cheeseburgers, which is a lot better than having a double quarter pounder, I mean, obviously.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_22]: But you know what would be really good would be like one of those fruit and walnut salads would be a really good choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's a problem here.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually worse.
[SPEAKER_22]: Really?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't eat salad.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you use half the walnuts.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're heavy sugar.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, it's candied walnuts.
[SPEAKER_22]: I only use half the walnuts because I know that they're candied walnuts.
[SPEAKER_08]: And dried fruit is even higher in sugar than... Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_22]: It concentrates the sugar.
[SPEAKER_22]: I hate the regular... I don't like their regular salads.
[SPEAKER_22]: If I'm going to get a regular salad, I want like Fresh Choice, Laboo, a real salad place.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't do McDonald's salads.
[SPEAKER_22]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm eating one of their salads right now and I find it highly tasty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't, bleh, I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate salads.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate the taste of lettuce.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've tried it numerous times.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not like lettuce.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_22]: Lettuce is something I used to hate as a child, but I like it now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care for lettuce, I prefer spinach, and this has spinach in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spinach is good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, we'll talk plenty of food later throughout the show, but also say hello to the one and only Mikotov.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_22]: Are you playing Mario Kart Online right now?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm trying to unlock Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm right here.
[SPEAKER_22]: God, I'm funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's working on the chassis he built.
[SPEAKER_22]: I see.
What?
[SPEAKER_22]: I somehow highly doubt that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: How far are you in Unlocking Rob?
[SPEAKER_22]: You almost there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I have like two more races, and then, yeah, I finished.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, well stop interrupting him then, because he's very zen-like in playing his Mario Kart over there, so we'll leave him alone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've taken a break from Mario Kart today to actually be doing the show, and there's a puzzle with this mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't speak.
[SPEAKER_22]: I refuse to play.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want more information on this when we come back.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're going to take a quick break, though.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I got to play Tent Style this week, so I'm in a very Tent Style-ish mood.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we're going to play some music from Tent Style.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then we'll come back and do our show.
[SPEAKER_22]: So join our chatroom, www.orangelandreo.com.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_22]: After this, we're going to start it off with a song called Strong Woman.
[SPEAKER_22]: One of the CS songs.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hopefully it works.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just got this before the show started, so I hope it works.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lingerie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just ain't got no way to go
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: From StepSquad to OrangeLoud, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_07]: Holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla!
[SPEAKER_22]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're in the middle of episode number 165, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was just kind of thinking about today, you know, 165 doesn't sound like a big number.
[SPEAKER_22]: Would you consider that that's one a week?
[SPEAKER_22]: That is an awfully long time.
[SPEAKER_22]: 165 weeks.
[SPEAKER_22]: That doesn't even count weeks off and stuff, because we're entitled to a week off once in a while, damn it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_22]: Thought.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have your finger up in thought.
[SPEAKER_22]: Your mic's not on, but... Why'd you turn the mic off?
[SPEAKER_22]: Bad you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Is 169 going to be on New Year's Eve?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: We have to decide, and we can worry about this next month if we're going to do shows.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I think, isn't Christmas and New Year's Eve on a Sunday this year?
[SPEAKER_08]: Both are.
[SPEAKER_22]: See, I don't know if we want to do shows then.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know about you, but I'm not going to be here on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, New Year's Eve, definitely not, because there's other things I've got to do.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we might be taking some time off for the holidays.
[SPEAKER_22]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_22]: We earned it.
[SPEAKER_22]: So shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone's going to be listening anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll do a marathon or something special.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're pre-recorded.
[SPEAKER_22]: A little special treat for... Yeah, nobody's going to want to listen to us on New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_22]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_22]: People are going to go out to parties and stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe the dude that records us every week will record the station to see what was here.
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, there's several people that are recording us.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I don't see a big demand for programming on New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now I've got to talk to...
[SPEAKER_22]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, granted, but you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: And me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can get near alcohol poisoning, but I don't get hangovers.
[SPEAKER_22]: Go, Greg.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Lots of good points in the chat.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've seen how the chat was lighting up.
[SPEAKER_22]: What about Jewish people?
[SPEAKER_22]: They want a show on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can do the Hanukkah special.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hanukkah starts today after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want to do like a Kwanzaa special, Orange Lounge Radio Kwanzaa special.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't we do the generic holiday special?
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: The pick your holiday special.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll do Orange Lounge celebrates Hallmark's Christmas.
[SPEAKER_22]: That'll be a Hallmark Presents, the Orange Lawn Trio.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll get Extifer in here to share some stories with the Hallmark Trademark.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see what else they're saying in the chatroom there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, everybody's booing us for not wanting to do a Christmas episode.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, excuse me, maybe we'd like to spend time with our family.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, we want to open up presents.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's a very important part of Christmas.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not Christmas Day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want Christmas nookie, dammit, and I'm not going to be here.
[SPEAKER_22]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want Christmas nookie, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, how was Thanksgiving?
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you get any Thanksgiving, Nookie?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm still too sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ate my food, and then I got such a bad headache trying to watch Dan play Perfect Dark Zero, which was a very pretty, very pretty game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it wasn't Dan who was giving me the headache, it was watching his friend who completely sucks at that game being like an absolute retard playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, uh, I, uh, I mean, he was really making some dumb mistakes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, uh, I just sort of laid back and threw a pillow in Dan's lap and passed out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I actually did fall asleep for something like two hours.
[SPEAKER_22]: But you're sick, so you can't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still feel crappy.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_22]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_22]: How was my month?
[SPEAKER_22]: How was your month?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a little while since I've been here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It involves lung cookies and homework and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I slept 16 hours yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I slept 17 hours last Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had lung spasms at work Friday and had to go home the week before.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been really, really crappy sick and haven't even felt much like playing anything, let alone sitting up and going to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: I opened World of Warcraft and then shut it down.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then last night around 1am I played some We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then started getting really motion sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like my stomach has gone between being ravenously hungry and being very nauseated.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, trying to play Wheel of Katamari while being highly nauseated anyway just spells disaster.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spells don't make any plans because it's all coming up.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's one way of explaining it, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_22]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_02]: My week was good because there was turkey involved.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, you know, it was a very chaotic week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got my car fixed, finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I had turkey.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was also good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then the rest of the week, you know, the last four days was really trying to be productive, but that didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: No, instead I kind of wandered around on Black Friday trying to see if there was any 360s around.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, give me a break.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, did you really think you were going to find a 360 on Black Friday?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I just wanted to get out of the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went and picked up another game for the 360 I don't have yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have Cameo now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luckily, there's a used copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone already put out a used copy.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's probably a review copy or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, not like any of the copies I bring back are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, then I went to Best Buy and wandered around there for about a few seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have quite a few Xboxes and the PS2 Slims.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were blocking off aisles with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, okay, I get the point that you have lots of these systems available.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the one I'm looking for, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kind of fed up with Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, why were people lined up at 10 o'clock Thanksgiving evening outside Best Buy?
[SPEAKER_22]: Like, they were camped out for Black Friday?
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you give a microphone to make it sound... There were, like, computers for, like, $150.
[SPEAKER_22]: Decent ones?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and laptops for, like, $200.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hell, maybe I should have camped out, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had some HP computers or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just didn't really want it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Didn't Walmart do some type of, like...
[SPEAKER_02]: They were talking about it, and I don't know if they did or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a big mess.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I actually went to GameStop that day, thinking, oh, well, the GameStop by my house is normally not crowded at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had like a freaking line of seven people in there at about noon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I wanted to see, first off, where it was on the Xbox 360 pre-orders, and also...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, whether or not they had any accessories and stuff and possibly games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now I'm to the point now I have the four games I kind of wanted and there's really nothing else I want except for maybe DOA 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: But once that comes out, there's nothing I want for at least a few months.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, looking at my list of games coming out, there's nothing coming out for the 360 until February.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like PSP Syndrome all over again or Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's crazy, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, even... I mean, excluding the delay on Dead or Alive 4, you would actually have two months of nothing for the 360, and I mean, that's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: When's that Baldur's Gate coming out?
[SPEAKER_22]: Did that get pushed all the way back to February?
[SPEAKER_02]: Elder Scrolls is coming out in April or March.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why did I say Baldur's Gate?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Elder Scrolls... I think March now.
[SPEAKER_02]: March or April, I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only big games coming out... December is nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only real game worth mentioning is actually...
[SPEAKER_02]: and just Gauntlet Seven Sorrows.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and Dead or Alive because Dead or Alive got pushed back.
[SPEAKER_22]: Gauntlet Seven Sorrows is also coming out on the other systems too, so it doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's not on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just talking games in general.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then for the month of January, 25 to Life, which would be pretty big.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, there's really... January is a very slow period for games, just as it is for movies, because after the holidays, there's really nothing up again until, you know, I don't know, early spring period.
[SPEAKER_22]: Probably, there's going to be a very big lull between the holidays and probably summer.
[SPEAKER_22]: There usually is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it should be... You get a couple big titles in February.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think we're getting Prime Hunters on the DS somewhere in there.
[SPEAKER_22]: March?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, you get a couple big titles, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking now I've got to put down my money for a Revolution and a PS3 if I want them.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS3 I'm not so worried about because they haven't even really announced a date for that yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking it's not going to be until the fall anyways of next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Revolution, though, I'd be wanting to pick up.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think Revolution and PS3 will both be out by next Christmas, I really do.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think they're going to rush them just like Xbox rushed to get out there, but I think they'll be out there by Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Revolution, they've been taking their time on, so.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, but I think, you know, the fact that they haven't said a lot about it, I think is a good sign.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to be like a Nintendo 64 launch.
[SPEAKER_22]: Comment?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just seeing the 360 going the way of the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_22]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot in common.
[SPEAKER_22]: I saw that story on 1up.com that shared what they had in common, but that's the same marketing guys behind them both, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get the commercials.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: I haven't even seen an Xbox 360 commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you probably don't even realize it is an Xbox 360 commercial unless you watch it all the way through because they don't say or show anything about the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: They show kids playing and really cryptic, artistic crap, and then they go, Xbox 360!
[SPEAKER_02]: It reminds me of this commercial we made for our economics class.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically a bunch of kick-ass clips of action sequences during movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like explosions and people getting beat up and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And at the very end, buy bumper stickers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is kind of like the whole 360 thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You show a bunch of kids playing and having a water balloon fight or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: 360, it's like, you look at it and you're like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't say anything about the system, what it does, what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just shows kids playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so the 360 is a watermelon launcher?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, what the hell is it?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: I barely watch TV at all, and even the few shows I do watch, thanks to the lovely DVR we have, I fast forward through all the commercials.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I don't have to watch it.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that's why I'm like, oh, there's a funny commercial?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything else you want to share about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_22]: My week and my day, I went to GameStop on Black Friday as well, but I went to the one near here, and the line was only about one, two people, like it usually is.
[SPEAKER_22]: Nothing...
[SPEAKER_22]: Dragon Quest VIII
[SPEAKER_22]: And it looked pretty cool, so I wanted to pick it up and play it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And also the Final Fantasy XII demo, which is very, very sexy.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to let you borrow it so you can see it, because it's very sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: No need.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you already got it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I found it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You acquired it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I acquired it.
[SPEAKER_22]: You acquired it through your various contacts.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you need it, or do you already have it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I'll let you borrow the Final Fantasy XII demo, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have the trailer.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's a playable demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no I don't.
[SPEAKER_22]: You want to borrow it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_22]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like it was like 11.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just got the Dragon Warrior 9 or whatever one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever the new Dragon Quest is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Quest.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, about the actual game, Dragon Quest VIII.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm the one saying Dragon Warrior.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dragon Quest.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, they went back to Dragon Quest.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because Squeenix is doing this whole mea culpa.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, we did change the names of all your games.
[SPEAKER_22]: We released them in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here, we fix.
[SPEAKER_22]: We fix.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll talk more about Dragon Quest on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, yeah, I like that game.
[SPEAKER_22]: And...
[SPEAKER_22]: I've been playing a little bit of Mario Kart here and there, and World of Warcraft, a little bit, a little bit, not a whole lot though, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm using the crappy mic tonight, so if my voice fades in and out just because I'm on the crappy mic tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't really do anything for Thanksgiving, because I have a small family, so it's just me, my mom, and my dad, so we just went out to eat.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_22]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's just been very nice to have these past few days off of work, because I'm not going to have a vacation like this again until like February, because I'm taking some massive time off in February.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it's just very nice to have a break.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I feel very charged.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm very relaxed tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: I hate this mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm in a pretty decent mood, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_22]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, Miklatov, you're here.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know you're in the middle of a race, but you gotta pause that for a minute.
[SPEAKER_22]: And of course, we have to give the disclaimer that, you know, even though he works for Konami, don't read into too much anything that he says, because he's not here to represent Konami tonight, he's here to represent himself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_10]: As usual.
[SPEAKER_22]: As usual.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_22]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: My week was pretty boring, because all I do is work.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mario Kart has taken over our office every break, almost every lunch.
[SPEAKER_10]: We play eight-player matches.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love hearing that at Konami you'll play games by other people all the time.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sure all the other companies do it too.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's just kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: We even use our DSs that we're not supposed to use for actual gaming to play, because not everybody has a DS there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I saw Rent, which is an amazing movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't say anything, Rob.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's your moment.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll let you have your moment.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a great movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw it twice, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I picked up Brokeback Mountain.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two books of it and the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_22]: How do you buy two books of Brokeback Mountain?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they released a standalone.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really just a short story from a collection of cowboy western stories.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I picked up the book that had all those short stories in it, and then they also released the one for the movie that's coming out, and I picked that one up also, and the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm in love.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the movie comes out when?
[SPEAKER_10]: December 9th.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was next week, and then to my horrible, horrible dismay, it's actually two weeks from now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now next week's going to be depressing, because that's all I was looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything that you've by chance maybe been spinning a turntable or making some arrow-stomping noises to?
[SPEAKER_22]: I refuse to comment.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have to try.
[SPEAKER_22]: The listeners would get angry and say that, you know, we're a farce if I didn't try.
[SPEAKER_22]: The Mario Kart music.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and a lot of random 90s music I've been listening to at work lately, but nothing to do with DDR or anything like that, so don't read into that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just, that's what I play when I'm doing...
[SPEAKER_10]: So I hear Rhythm Is A Dancer a lot.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if I can say it.
[SPEAKER_22]: There was something that happened once that involved work and somebody hearing a song a lot that was really, really funny that happened once.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damien Busters?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, can I say that on the air?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's in the past, so I can say that now, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: I won't say who it was.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll just say somebody.
[SPEAKER_22]: It wasn't in the past.
[SPEAKER_22]: Somebody who also is very close with Konami said... Used to be.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was this song that was playing on the Dave & Buster's radio station, and she said, or he or she said, shit, he or she said, he or she said that, fuck, I don't know if I can do this story now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now our picture is falling down the stairs.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if I can continue this story now because I don't want to get anybody in trouble.
[SPEAKER_22]: They don't work there anymore.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_22]: The person said that, oh man, I can't get this song out of my head because I've been hearing it at work so much lately and I'm like, oh really?
[SPEAKER_22]: Turns out it was an Ultramix 2 license that nobody knew about yet.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the rest of my week was watching that next clip constantly
[SPEAKER_10]: Next Next Next
[SPEAKER_10]: So she's walking out of the van thing, and she's doing her little spiel for the camera, and as she's saying that, she falls down the steps.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really funny because they freeze frame on her falling down, and she has the best expression on her face.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's somewhere between laughing and just shock.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's really great.
[SPEAKER_22]: And she was a stupid whore anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love how he's like, so I just wanted you to walk over here because I wasn't sure if you were okay or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was nice.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, I know what I wanted to ask you about as well.
[SPEAKER_22]: One little work-related thing that I'm okay to say, I think, is that you met LED.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I met LED.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to have dinner with LED.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_22]: Was it a nice dinner?
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you guys go to a fancy restaurant?
[SPEAKER_10]: We went to TGI Fridays, because he wanted American.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, that's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_22]: You probably can't say much about the details of what you guys talked about, but...
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything interesting that you might be able to share?
[SPEAKER_22]: Does he seem to be aware that he has quite a following here in the U.S.? ?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think that was brought up, but I think he would have to be stupid to know that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know what I can really say from the dinner, but there was one funny thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was me and a couple other people from work, and he asked us what types of music we listened to.
[SPEAKER_10]: At the time, it was like I was listening to drum and bass a lot, and I also said Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_10]: and he kind of groaned and said Eurobeat after me.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was rather disgusted with that answer.
[SPEAKER_22]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_22]: You make LED cry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was funny.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you have nothing else to say for now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_22]: Brokeback Mountain's awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's go, okay, since we can't ask these things of Miklatov, we can mention them ourselves if we pick stuff up along the wire.
[SPEAKER_22]: Something about Beatmania getting pushed back again?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: You found this out?
[SPEAKER_22]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, dates changed.
[SPEAKER_02]: We get updates like at least once a week from like all the different companies when stuff's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the tentative date of, what was it, like February 9th is no longer, it's now being pushed back to March something.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what I think is interesting is that finally after this website's been running for about three and a half years now, people are considering us like a legitimate news source.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just for the record, remind our audience where you get your information and why it's pretty reliable.
[SPEAKER_02]: My information comes directly from our buyer because our buyer talks to Konami directly.
[SPEAKER_02]: They give us the dates so we know when product's coming out, so we know when we can sell it, when orders are due, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have to know what the upcoming slate of titles is going to be and that's how I know what movie titles and game titles because...
[SPEAKER_02]: I work at a friggin' distributor, so you have to know what's coming out when.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that's the tentative date.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, like most games, dates shift around, like, weekly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, what might be March today, could be January, could be April, who knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, for example...
[SPEAKER_02]: Tomb Raider, the new one, Tomb Raider Legends or whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_22]: The Tomb Raider, I don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Tomb Raider, trying to reinvent ourselves, Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, that game was originally slated for January, moved to April, moved back to January, moved back to April, moved back to January, and now it's in April.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like they can't figure out when they want to release a stupid game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's a perfect example.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually Konami, though, they don't shift their dates around that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's usually...
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple, and once it gets closer to it, it's set in stone.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA, on the other hand, they like shifting their dates all over the damn place.
[SPEAKER_22]: How about Square?
[SPEAKER_02]: Square?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not so much, but not many Square games come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's what we've had two in the last four months.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, a question from the chat room, Advent Children, what's the status on that?
[SPEAKER_22]: You know when that's slated to come out now?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's to be announced still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was going to be in February.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then it was actually slated for...
[SPEAKER_02]: The end of January, and then now we have it as moratorium in our system, meaning that we don't have a date yet.
[SPEAKER_22]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why are they doing that?
[SPEAKER_22]: That's so crazy, because people are pirating this movie.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe that's why they're doing it, because of the piracy, they're going to have to go back and add all these extras that people are going to want to buy the DVD for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking they're probably trying to, because people bitch and moan about the fact that they don't have good box sets over here or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talk to the Sony guy, I always yell at him every time he comes in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, because I knew more about it than they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I was like, why aren't you releasing the box sets here?
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're like, oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yeah, because I'm sure that one guy who comes to your company makes all the calls on what they're going to be releasing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, a lot of the people that come to our company, though, are senior sales or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they do have somewhat of a say.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, they...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know when it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I know is I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully it'll be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always keep the website updated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I post when it changes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Another comment from our chatroom, from Ranchan, chatroom, by the way, OrangeLaunchRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rumors are leaking out about theatrical release.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's kind of true.
[SPEAKER_22]: This has been something that's kind of been circulating for a while now.
[SPEAKER_22]: We mentioned this on a podcast like months ago because I don't even remember where I picked up this bug.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now, I want to say it was sometime around E3.
[SPEAKER_22]: I picked up a bug, no, it was later than E3.
[SPEAKER_22]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was a friend of a friend kind of thing, so take it with a grain of salt, but...
[SPEAKER_22]: Final Fantasy Advent Children and IMAX
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they have Polar Express running right now on IMAX, but I think it needs to be an IMAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that'd be awesome if it was an IMAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: And if that's the case, it's going to take a long time to, you know, to print digital to, you know, the IMAX film store.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, since the movie's all digital as it is, it won't take that long to enhance, so to speak, for the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's go to break.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio after this.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got to forever The green grass blows and the wind is dancing It would be a much better sight With you, with me If you hadn't met me I'd be fine on my own, baby Never felt so lonely when you came along
[SPEAKER_07]: and many more.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge Radio, Bomani Music, and more.
[SPEAKER_15]: Perfect!
[SPEAKER_22]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and that break you heard Come With Me from Ultramix 3, Final Countdown from 2DX4Style, You're Not Here from Silent Hill, and then it was in DDR Extreme as well, and from Keyboard Mania 2nd Mix, Akumajo Dracula Medley, which is also now in DDR Ultramix 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_22]: By the way, speaking of Castlevania songs and Bomani, I don't know if you saw that early song list for Beatmania...
[SPEAKER_22]: I still want to call it 13th style.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know that's a taboo thing to do.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, it's not 13th style.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's distorted.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it does have 13 in the title this time, so I'm going to call it 13th style until I get yelled at.
[SPEAKER_22]: But no, it's supposed to have bloody tears in it.
[SPEAKER_22]: What is this you just pulled up there?
[SPEAKER_22]: That's Ragnarok Online 2?
[SPEAKER_08]: This means that Jamie's going to be quitting World of Warcraft awfully soon.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's very fluid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's got a 3D fluid sense to it, where you're not warping into fights or anything.
[SPEAKER_22]: Kind of reminds me of the Final Fantasy XII demo, I must say, actually.
[SPEAKER_22]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Except you're by yourself, but of course that would be to be expected in an MMO.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's Ragnarok 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is your customizing for your character.
[SPEAKER_22]: Our chat room is yelling now for a link, so you better link them up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki, you had some interesting observations on eBay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, I was just looking at the... I was checking on there, there was this Beatmania final machine that was on sale for $99 before.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I looked at the guy's other selling... He's selling some other Bomani stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keyboard Mania, third...
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, $280.
[SPEAKER_22]: Holy fuck, I want that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know where I would put that in this little apartment.
[SPEAKER_02]: City of Industry is where it's at if you want to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Does that mean it's AI selling it?
[SPEAKER_22]: But it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's AI.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're selling Dance Maniacs, Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, what, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: It had No Buy It Now on it and it had Many Days Left on the Bed when I looked at it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sorry, go ahead, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a 2DX Red Machine for $5,100.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beat Me at the final right now is only $152.50.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they have a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Initial D3.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a Wang Dan Midnight Maximum Tune 2 Racing Machine for only $2,500.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a bunch of kick-ass stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drum Mania 5th, Guitar Freaks 5th, Dance Maniac 2nd, Extreme, and Boxing Mania.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I wonder if that's AI unloading all that stuff, because you know Arcade Infinity had a lot of, and they're in City of Industry, or at least they're right next to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we don't have a fifth mix, so.
[SPEAKER_22]: They did, though.
[SPEAKER_22]: They did at one point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's probably upgraded, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I kind of want that Keyboard Mania machine.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know why I'm so, like, into Keyboard Mania, but I am.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like, I really want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I had a house, I'd be getting something.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: Speaking of next year, it looks highly, highly probable I'm going to be at, now I haven't signed on the line and everything, but it's very, very probable.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I know we have a lot of listeners on the East Coast who have asked me to hang out with them.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I actually did.
[SPEAKER_22]: When I went to Pennsylvania last time I was out there, I actually hung out with a couple of the listeners.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was a good time.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm down for that again and the time and place to be at is Katsukan which is going to be in February I believe it's the 17th through 19th don't quote me on that but it's around there and in DC and it's looking very very likely I'm going to be there and possibly doing a panel which will be a lot of fun
[SPEAKER_22]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I will let you know absolutely for sure the details as soon as I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I've bought my plane tickets and everything, but it does look very likely I'm going to be there.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I'm pretty excited.
[SPEAKER_22]: I haven't been to D.C.
[SPEAKER_22]: in a long time.
[SPEAKER_22]: The only thing I'm kind of freaked out about is that in February it might be snowing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't they get snow?
[SPEAKER_22]: This is the California side of me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Even though it does snow in some parts of California, I don't live in one of those parts, so I'm so ignorant when it comes to snow.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never been to D.C.,
[SPEAKER_22]: I have before, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh, anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh, moving on.
[SPEAKER_22]: We were going to do Extroverse movie review, but the room cleared out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Did somebody fart or something?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because the room just cleared out.
[SPEAKER_02]: His phone rang.
[SPEAKER_22]: Miklatov ran out, Extroverse phone rang.
[SPEAKER_22]: Miklatov's trying to pack his bags, because they're leaving soon, and DarkSakura had to go to the restroom, so.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, gosh.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um...
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see, what else, what else, what else?
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess let's talk about the 360 for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Some of the horror stories, did you hear about some of the horror stories when it came to the 360?
[SPEAKER_22]: About like the Walmart that had the riot somewhere in Pennsylvania and there was EB games that got robbed?
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard of some funny ones.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was one where there was a big line out in front of this Walmart, I think it was, or Walmart Target, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So a big line of people and they had one cop sitting there making sure nothing's gone wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then this National Guardsman comes up and it's like, holy shit, he's getting everything in order.
[SPEAKER_02]: immediately stands in the front of the line, gets a ticket to buy an Xbox 360, and is like, FIN FOR YOURSELVES, and leaves.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's funny, is what that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be pissed.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want to let Extover do his thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll go back to the 360 in a little bit, but Extover's back in the room.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you have an important phone call you had to take?
[SPEAKER_09]: I did have an important... Was it a hookup call?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was definitely not a hookup call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Booty call?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it a family call?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is everything okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, everything's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: You seem kind of bunned out tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is everything okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just, like, tired.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you need a hug?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't touch me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, I won't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your week, Extover?
[SPEAKER_09]: My week was fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was like Thanksgiving and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Saw my family and went and saw Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Liked it a lot better than the first time that I saw it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to go see that again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to see that four times in the theater?
[SPEAKER_22]: I can.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, and it's the fourth movie, so you'll see it four times in the theater.
[SPEAKER_22]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really retarded.
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't say that again.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I know you've got to get going soon because you and Mickey have to get on the road, but I wanted to allow you a chance to do your movie review.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now, I know you hate your old theme music, so I changed your theme music.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: So what movie are you going to be reviewing today?
[SPEAKER_09]: I am going to be... What is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just do your talking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't worry about what's going on behind you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be reviewing Rent because I went and saw it yesterday with all you folks.
[SPEAKER_09]: And basically it's a movie about late 80s people trying to make it in New York and having problems financially and dying of AIDS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty much like you said yesterday, if you don't get a job, then you'll die of AIDS.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was my summary of the moral I learned from Rant, is that if you don't get a job, you'll die of AIDS.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rob didn't really like it that much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hated Rant.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hated it a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I liked it quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think this may be because I really just am into musicals.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the music in them.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was poignant.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had some really good moments in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that because you're gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: No way, I'm gay and I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't think that liking musicals is a gay or straight thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, you can be a musical lover.
[SPEAKER_09]: My mom's straight and she loves musicals.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bad example, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like musicals.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're very fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like musicals, I just don't like red.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, as I heard many a time.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it was good though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: So two thumbs up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Two cocks up and a limp cock.
[SPEAKER_09]: Use protection, or you might catch something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or else your cocks will die of AIDS.
[SPEAKER_09]: And make sure your cocks get a job.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please get a job.
[SPEAKER_09]: A blowjob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm off.
[SPEAKER_09]: And careful not to sell out to the man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, don't do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't sell out to the man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_09]: Go see Rent.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: You may like it or you may not.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Get Miklatov back in here so he can say his goodbyes too because I know you guys are leaving soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_22]: Is he out there somewhere?
[SPEAKER_22]: Live Radio Kids.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're not in an actual studio, by the way.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is the spare bedroom in the apartment that Extrovert and I live in.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's quite a nifty apartment.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, give that mic back to Loki.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, back to the 360.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: What's the status on your 360 now?
[SPEAKER_22]: You pre-ordered your 360 back in, remind me when this was, like June?
[SPEAKER_02]: August.
[SPEAKER_22]: August.
[SPEAKER_22]: And still no dice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm on the first page, halfway down.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said, though, that I will probably get mine before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm guessing, they're saying, someone said in the chatroom that 14 units are going to each store each week or whatever, so if that's the case, I'll probably get mine probably in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, why would 14 go to the Ma and Pa shop and bumfuck, you know, North Dakota, but then 14 go to Best Buy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well that's... I don't think, no one knows until they get the stupid shipments in, so...
[SPEAKER_22]: Do we know anything about future shipments of Xbox 360s?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's what I think is interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they sold out so that their drive-up hype, they did that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would you drive up hype if you're not going to replenish the market?
[SPEAKER_02]: So it only makes sense.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, I have an interesting story to share real quick.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know you've got to get going soon, so I want to give you a chance to say your final thought and any other things you want to say to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: Brokeback Mountain is the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go buy it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's only like $10.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go buy the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go see the movie if you can.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you like the notion of people buttfucking and spitting on their cocks and having that as a lubricant, then go see Bareback Mountain.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, this is like an Oscar caliber film they're trying to put this out as, and you're turning it into a porno.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a friend on Live Channel.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I know this person doesn't listen to the show, so I'm okay to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it's behind a friend's lockpost anyway, so none of you would know who it is.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I told him I don't know how I feel about this.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is somebody, he's not a gamer in any capacity.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, I think he's like a casual thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know how most people our age have probably played Mario Brothers once in their life?
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But by no means a hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_22]: He rounded up a team of individuals.
[SPEAKER_22]: They got, I think, eight people or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they managed to get nine people.
[SPEAKER_22]: Platinum Xbox systems on launch day because they all camped out at least 24 hours in advance.
[SPEAKER_22]: So they all got nine Platinum Xboxes.
[SPEAKER_22]: They sold all the systems on eBay.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they gave each person that stood out in line and helped them out $1,000 for their help.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they were very happy for $1,000 for their help.
[SPEAKER_22]: and they still had after that left over I think something like $8,000 that they put $5,000 away for the baby's education because they have a new baby on the way and the other $3,000 they just spent on themselves.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know what I think about this because I think you're taking advantage of people but at the same time I blame the people that actually bid that much on eBay and allow you to think that this is a viable option for making money and I'm happy that as kids because they're going to invest the money and I know they will I know they will be smart with their money and invest the money and they will be able to send this baby to a
[SPEAKER_22]: Really great school, all based on these Xbox 360 sales.
[SPEAKER_22]: But as a gamer, I can't help but think, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_22]: I wanted one of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're taking advantage on the desperation and relative stupidity of other people.
[SPEAKER_22]: But who's to blame in that scenario?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: They were well within their rights.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think, you know, it's hard for me to put the blame on them.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think they are within their rights.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are smart.
[SPEAKER_08]: They put the work into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They put it online knowing that there were going to be morons out there who'd bid on them.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I believe the idiot masses should be exploited.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just can't believe somebody would pay like $3,000.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they got it.
[SPEAKER_22]: They got like $3,100 for each of these systems.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Crazy, crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can I say there?
[SPEAKER_02]: People are dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, like I said, I'm just waiting.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if I do find one in a store, you know, if Best Buy is getting, you know, 90 in each shipment or whatever, and there's some sitting there, of course I'm going to buy one because, you know, I can have it now and I still have my, I can get my, you know, money back from my, you know, deposit on it and whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's no big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, no, I'm really, when I look at the games and the four games that I got for it,
[SPEAKER_02]: I looked at, once I got those four games, I still had like $70 in store credit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, what do I buy now?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I looked at the list of everything that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, I don't want any of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's kind of what it is.
[SPEAKER_22]: See, that's what's scaring me away from buying an Xbox 360 right now, is I really don't feel like... I think it's going to be the same thing with regular Xbox.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had no reason to buy a regular Xbox until...
[SPEAKER_22]: Halo, Willy, and even Halo, I wasn't a fan of Halo when I first played it, but I converted.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's a first-person shooter I enjoy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to see Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_22]: I do want to see Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's all about Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, well, I need to be talking to you.
[SPEAKER_22]: As an Xbox 360 owner, which you and the hubby got one of these systems, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I told you we didn't.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, I thought... I told you we decided not to.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know, but then I thought you went back and you did.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we went and played somebody else's.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now we're going to get one next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we are going to get one next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, now it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, so you didn't end up getting one, but you played somebody else's.
[SPEAKER_22]: So what did you think?
[SPEAKER_22]: I've only played the demo kiosk.
[SPEAKER_22]: I haven't played an actual system yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a point where games can be too pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Project Gotham 3 is too pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: The cars look like they float over the ground.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, you do actually start off with performance vehicles as opposed to just eye candy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like one of your first cars you can pick from is the Saleen Mustang or the...
[SPEAKER_08]: New Shelby, which actually isn't even going to be out on the market to purchase until next year.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now, did you play this on like a widescreen HD type setup?
[SPEAKER_08]: I played it on an HD TV, but nowhere near as huge as mine.
[SPEAKER_22]: But still, I bet it was very pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was pretty, but it was too pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, like I said, the cursor, they were floating over the ground.
[SPEAKER_08]: It does have good music in it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some really good original music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perfect Dark Zero was gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_08]: The levels are humongous.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's lots of opportunity to shoot people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait till you see Ghost Recon 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I wasn't too interested in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He had it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was boring.
[SPEAKER_22]: What about Condemned?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I remember you liked it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you get a chance to play Condemned yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't have it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I remember you liked that one at E3.
[SPEAKER_22]: It didn't have it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe that was the Sega fangirl in you that liked it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking forward to it I'm still going to get it I've got Waiting for Perfect Dark and I'm probably going to do maybe Condemned Ridge Racer if they send me a free copy But the other one we also there was another game they had there too No, it was the whatever that war game was Call of Duty Call of Duty, that was it Call of Duty was kind of boring
[SPEAKER_22]: It was pretty, but it's kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, the weird thing is that the two games I want most on the Xbox 360, I can get on another platform.
[SPEAKER_22]: Quake 4 and Gun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Need for Speed Most Wanted, having compared the Xbox version and the 360... Actually, this is coming from Dan.
[SPEAKER_08]: He compared the Xbox version, which he's been playing non-stop, and the 360 version, and said that actually the Xbox version plays better.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 360 version is apparently a slower game.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've already bought Soul Calibur 3 for PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have this bad feeling they're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why are you so sure they're not going to do it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_22]: Milk more money out of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they've said they're not going to.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a rumor that was going around about it, and they said no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_22]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why wouldn't they do it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's exclusive to Sony.
[SPEAKER_22]: So was Resident Evil 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony paid for the rights to have it exclusive for...
[SPEAKER_02]: And if that's the case, it might come out maybe next year or something like that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I didn't say it's going to come out tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_22]: It would come out months after it's announced, but I bet you Soul Calibur 3 would end up getting released for the Xbox 360 outside of Sony's exclusive window, and it's going to have two new characters or something good that's going to make us all want to go buy it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'm going to be pissed, because I already have it on PS2, but it's going to be prettier on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gun, I would recommend getting it on the current-gen systems, because the 360 is not worth the $10 extra you're paying for.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the same damn game.
[SPEAKER_22]: No prettier graphics or anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: The texture resolution is a little bit higher.
[SPEAKER_02]: The character models have a few more polygons.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not like night and day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like, you know, Call of Duty 2 and Big Red 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's major differences between those.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as Quake 4, I heard that there's problems with the frame rate in Quake 4 making it unplayable in parts because it's so slow on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_22]: Why didn't... These kind of mistakes kind of just ruffle my feathers.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, and you hear about the Xboxes crashing and everything, and it's like, if it isn't completely fucking obvious that you rushed to get this out on the market.
[SPEAKER_02]: 360, they said, I've read so many things about why it's crashing and overheating and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them, they said there's vent holes in them that some of them are getting punched out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't get to see the BSOD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the blue screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: The black screen of death.
[SPEAKER_02]: The power supply overheats and you have to put it on something that gets proper ventilation?
[SPEAKER_08]: You have that problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're overheating more commonly when they're kept inside of an entertainment cabinet.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I bet you in a testing environment they don't mimic that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're so big because they have a giant fan inside of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, put this stupid thing on the system and forget about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The hard drive they said is overheating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a lot of heat problems.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then they're also saying, oh, it scratches disks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, when you knock it over, like anything, if you're playing a CD and you knock the damn thing over, obviously it's going to scratch your stupid CD.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's retarded, but that's one other thing that was going wrong with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Problems with the hard drive being able to read stuff, just problems like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's widespread, and I haven't heard issues about live or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of our podcast listeners also stated that you can actually play your iPod in-game.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play music in-game.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it comes out over your TV.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's kind of an interesting little perk.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just can't rip stuff from...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Me personally, Xbox 360, I think I'm going to end up waiting until next year to see some more games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was totally sold on getting one at launch.
[SPEAKER_22]: And had they been readily available everywhere, the impulse firing me probably would have done it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I'm kind of glad they weren't available everywhere.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm buying Gans for his birthday next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's a little different.
[SPEAKER_22]: Birthday, Christmas, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: And my husband.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was staring down some of those core systems and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for example, there's another, there's websites out there where you can still get a 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a guy that's getting in 90 next week and he's an online seller selling them for I think slightly over what retail is or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just wait until next week when the next shipment comes in and see how short they really are on these things.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I bet you anything that's going to be, you're going to see them in stores regularly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I said before, driving the hype up if you're not going to replenish the supply.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no point to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was the whole point.
[SPEAKER_02]: They want to make it the must-have item for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's going to be the must-have item for Christmas, you've got to have some for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: And of course, one of our chatters, Rainy, reminding us of the golden rule of gaming, a system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that fundamentally, I think, is a problem.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, there are some good games for Xbox 360, but for me, my kind of games, the role-playing games and other type of games, there's just not enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I'm waiting to hear is I heard that the 360, some of the games may not be region coded.
[SPEAKER_02]: In which case, they're not sure if they're region coding everything or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if they're not, then you can import like crazy.
[SPEAKER_22]: I heard that rumor as well.
[SPEAKER_22]: That would be, I gotta just do away with that region coding.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS3's doing it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good.
[SPEAKER_22]: If I pay 70 bucks to import a Japanese game, then shit, I should just play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: ESP doesn't have region-coded games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's about time they got rid of the... I mean, I always thought... I understood the reason behind it was to keep games per market and track them and all kinds of other stupid marketing crap.
[SPEAKER_22]: But thanks to the internet, we live in a worldwide market now, and I think people are coming to understand that.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's what I was going to say, actually.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I'm thinking is, the only regions they should have are PAL and, you know, NTSC.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, yeah, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should get rid of PAL altogether.
[SPEAKER_22]: But doesn't, isn't it, when we move into the HDTV age, isn't it all standardized?
[SPEAKER_22]: Or am I wrong?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's still, maybe some tech junkies in chat know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Technically, I've played PAL discs using my DVD player on my laptop, routed through my TV.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it worked just fine.
[SPEAKER_22]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I'm wondering in the HDTVs, with the new HDTVs, because it's a new resolution, like basically the issue between NTSC and PAL is resolution, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: So aren't HDTVs resolutions standardized throughout the world?
[SPEAKER_22]: Or am I wrong?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they are.
[SPEAKER_22]: I do believe so.
[SPEAKER_22]: Then good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like using a computer monitor.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, then good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Then we're moving towards a standardized there too.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, you know, and that would be good news for overseas people as well at some point because that's the reason why it takes them so damn long to get their games usually is because they have to redo all the resolution and stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that's good news for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just do multiple languages from the start.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boom, done.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right, we're going to do one more break.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know we said we'd do Skype Line.
[SPEAKER_22]: We will do that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're also going to do the Cage Match and anything else we feel like.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I have to go potty, so that means, and Loki's going to beat me to it, I have to go potty, so that means we have to break.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_22]: In this break, we'll start it off with a little bit of Superstar.
[SPEAKER_22]: Remember this song, Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_22]: We used to love this song.
[SPEAKER_22]: I still do, but... It used to be my PA song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dancing to this song was wonderful.
[SPEAKER_22]: It used to be my PA song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_22]: If we actually play DDR, it might still be your PNPA song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Launch Radio.
Baby, if you want to come back
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Saturday night?
[SPEAKER_22]: We're back here, boys and girls, on Orange Lounge Radio, and I hope you enjoyed that break.
[SPEAKER_22]: A little, just some potpourri music there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I tried to put in some stuff that I know Jamie likes that we haven't played in a while.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm kind of doing stuff I think Jamie likes tonight because, you know, it's been a while since she's been here and getting to dictate the picks in my ear.
[SPEAKER_22]: But she hasn't really said a lot of songs she wants to hear tonight, so I'm playing stuff I think she'd want to hear.
[SPEAKER_22]: Am I doing good?
[SPEAKER_22]: So far so good.
[SPEAKER_22]: In that break we heard Superstar, The Safari, because I know you love The Safari, Look to the Sky, I don't know how big you are on that song.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was more for the listeners, because I know that's a listener favorite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, screw them.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Era, Taku, which we had to do.
[SPEAKER_22]: We had to do at least one song by him.
[SPEAKER_22]: So maybe some more Jamie-inspired stuff next break.
[SPEAKER_22]: But for now, we're actually going to head on over to the Skype line, and if you would like to call us, please do so.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry, the program was being unruly there for a minute.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had to figure out what's going on.
[SPEAKER_22]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, we're up and ready to go on Skype if you guys want to call in.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, we have a... Oh, the Skype server might be down right now, actually, because it's still showing us it's connecting.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we're going to have to proceed.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, we're not going to take calls on Skype just yet.
[SPEAKER_22]: Live radio can't control when the servers go up and down, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_22]: So let's actually head on over and see what else is going on in the Mimani world.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mentioned earlier in the show I checked out 2DX 10th Style this week.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if either of you guys have gotten a chance to play it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Jamie, have you really picked up 9th or 10th?
[SPEAKER_22]: I thought you got 9th.
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, you never got 9th or 10th?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's one of those things where it's kind of getting old.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can keep in mind, I work full time and go to school part time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really don't have a lot of time left over for BVMD until the end of the semester.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I played a whole lot of 8th style over the summer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I wasn't going to classes.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I figured that I was going to wait and pick up 10th style because I refused to play 9th style.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why 9th style?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because of how crappy the arcade release was.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, you know the timing's fine in the home version.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not... Yeah, but it also didn't really have much in it I liked.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what's funny is I have just the reverse with TenStyle.
[SPEAKER_22]: TenStyle is put together beautifully, and the song list is okay, and it's a really great looking game, especially because they've upped the resolution from the old third, fourth styles, and it's a very sharp looking game, and it's nice, but I find that when I was playing it, I was kind of like, where's all these songs I like from NinthStyle?
[SPEAKER_22]: See, I like NinthStyle an awful lot.
[SPEAKER_22]: I still think Eighth has the best of all of them.
[SPEAKER_22]: Eighth had a really solid song list, especially the arcade release, but...
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know, I just, I do love 9th, so as soon as I get a new controller, because we're pretty confident that the US is getting their own controller that's going to be different, and hopefully better, that's when I'll truly get back into 2DX.
[SPEAKER_22]: But Miklosov was nice, he offered to let me borrow his 10th style and controller, because I'm supposed to be seeing him this weekend too, and he offered to let me borrow it all week so I could really test drive it, but I said, I'm going to be too busy with Dragon Quest VIII.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, my controller still works perfectly fine and it fell off the top of the van.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know how that is.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't, I, I, you, you have the miracle controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been through it three times.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's, that's still something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do have, my controller is indestructible.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, what,
[SPEAKER_22]: I want to ask Loki about this real quick.
[SPEAKER_22]: These are some articles you posted on the site about the portable DDR and Beatmania sim games that are out there.
[SPEAKER_22]: What's going on with this?
[SPEAKER_22]: I know this isn't your sim scene update, but what's going on with these PSP clones?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mentioned last week about the old DDR one, and it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to actually... It's basically Steadmania for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the Beatmania one, not quite so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Beatmania for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's more of a two-button Beatmania because the way the buttons are mapped.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you could actually, I guess, remap everything so that you could play songs using their corresponding keys, but I mean, with a PSP, it's kind of hard to play seven-key Beatmania on it, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually installing that on my PSP right now as...
[SPEAKER_02]: as you caught me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, no, it looks really good, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got quite a setup for DDR and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one looks like it's more of like, I don't know, Delight Delight reduplication or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you can do DDR in the Beatmania setup as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they also have 2DX in normal Beatmania as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really sure how that works, but it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've got really good skins for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And both of them are available on PSP Updates right now, but I think we'll be adding them maybe to the PSP site at some point.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know there was something else I was dying to mention.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, Strike!
[SPEAKER_22]: There's lots of updates on DDR Strike that was going on over on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_22]: Some folks had found some pictures.
[SPEAKER_22]: Damn it, and I wish I'd gotten to this when Mikulatov was here because maybe he could have elaborated a little bit even though I know he can't say a whole lot about work stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: are crossovers from DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: For instance, As the Rush Comes and Block Rockin' Beats, which we had in DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: But here's the weird thing is that they have tied them to Dance Mania releases because As the Rush Comes was on Dance Mania EX7 and Block Rockin' Beats was on Dance Mania Winters.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I'm not sure, it's very interesting how this worked.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if, were these games chosen for the US first, or were they actually chosen for Japan, and we got them anyway because they were easy to license.
[SPEAKER_22]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: But also apparently the scan in the magazine or whatever it is also gives away a couple other songs.
[SPEAKER_22]: Heaven is a Place on Earth, the German election mix from Dance Media Covers 01, and Let's Dance by David Bowie, which I think is a very sexy addition to DDR.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't believe we're getting David Bowie.
[SPEAKER_22]: That is badass.
[SPEAKER_08]: David Bowie is so hot.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Let's Dance is a great song, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's going to be in a movie with Michael Caine.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then You Sexy Thing by Hot Chocolate.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I can't think of what song...
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't think of what song the, uh, You Sexy Thing is, though, but I think that's that old song from, uh, um, You Sexy Thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think I remember hearing that song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know who did it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, I remember, like, the line on it, but I don't remember how the song goes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just must be because I have completely different tastes than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's good to see that this game isn't just going to be a rehash of DDR Extreme 2 like I was thinking it was going to be, but, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: New stuff's always good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I think what's also interesting is that there's some crossovers from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: At least one, which we can kind of infer because there's going to be one.
[SPEAKER_22]: There will be more than one.
[SPEAKER_22]: Baile La Samba, which was a Konami original for Ultramix 2, is crossing over.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that was picked off from one of the Mission Mode screens.
[SPEAKER_22]: A very observant person on DDR Freak noticed that the banners match up.
[SPEAKER_22]: So Baile La Samba is going to be there as well.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that is starting speculation as to...
[SPEAKER_22]: Might we see some of the freebie songs?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because as you know, a different drum sort of gave songs to Konami.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not really had them licensed, but gave them for the exposure.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that's where we got Skulk and Superstar.
[SPEAKER_22]: So it would be very, very interesting if some of these songs showed up in the Japanese mix.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think that would be kind of cool for them.
[SPEAKER_16]: That would be.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think for sure they will get Gyruss and probably the Midi Head mix and some of the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: They'll probably get all that crap for sure.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't see how they couldn't get that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, also, when you think about it, was it Festival had Ultramix One stuff in it, so it only makes sense that they would do that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I think a lot of people, this really isn't surprising anyone, but it's kind of cool, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_22]: And what else we got going on with Strike?
[SPEAKER_22]: Then this came up later in the thread is that somebody actually got a screenshot and knew enough Japanese to kind of translate the little tiny stuff that shows up there on the side and notices that there is no online mode for the Japanese DDR Strike release.
[SPEAKER_22]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if that's because DDR they don't think is popular over there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not sure what to think of this, why they're not doing the online mode.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or maybe it's just an early screenshot.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe because the Extreme 2 online sucked?
[SPEAKER_22]: That's true, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Doesn't it have bugs, too?
[SPEAKER_22]: Aren't people still cheating on there and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucked, apparently.
[SPEAKER_22]: Compared to the Xbox One, it does suck.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's too bad that Extreme 2 came out later, but I realize there's a lot of anti-Microsoft people, for lack of a better term, people that don't have Xboxes for financial, just don't want to, whatever reasons, that haven't gotten to experience the Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'll tell you what, guys.
[SPEAKER_22]: I used to be anti-Microsoft too, and in some circumstances I still am to some extent.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't like some of the things they do, but I've come to accept, embrace some of the things that are really great about Xbox, one of them being they have advanced videos, or the other one being that they
[SPEAKER_22]: have the best online system that kicks PS2's butt.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, Xbox Live kicks anything else's butt, basically, right now that's out there in the console world.
[SPEAKER_22]: And so, to go and play DDR on the Xbox Live, and then go to play it on Extreme 2, you're like, yeah, this sucks.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I bet for people that have never played Xbox Live, they probably don't know that it can be a lot better, so it works out just fine for them.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Still kind of interesting that they left it out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_22]: Of course, more to come still on this game.
[SPEAKER_22]: We will see what happens a little later.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sure there are surprises still left in store.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_22]: Skype is doing some weird stuff with me, guys.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's going to be too bad if we have to do a show without Skype, because I'd love to hear from our listeners.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'd love to hear what they have to say.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's try this one more time here.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're going to try connecting there.
[SPEAKER_22]: And yeah, I got booted again.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, so we're going to go ahead and actually we're going to go into the cage match for right now and try to get some time for Skype to come back up.
[SPEAKER_22]: And we'll go to the Skype line a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'm sorry guys, I don't know what's happening there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm having timeout problems.
[SPEAKER_22]: Some of you might be on it.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're just having some problems here in studio.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I'm going to try some other things here while we go into the cage match.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it is time to get into this week's cage match.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now the nice thing about CageMatch is that we don't need our Skype line for CageMatch, we only need the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_22]: So you gotta be in our chatroom if you want to vote in CageMatch, and that's www.orangeloundtrader.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the way CageMatch works is that we're going to play three songs for you guys, and your favorite song will go into rotation all week long.
[SPEAKER_22]: on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani and Video Game Music program.
[SPEAKER_22]: And we had a winning song last week.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was a brand new winner, and it was something that Loki picked.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the song was by John Sykes, and it was called Cautionary Warning.
[SPEAKER_22]: And anything else you want to say about this song, Loki?
[SPEAKER_22]: Your mic's off.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a really cool song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_22]: A clip of last week's winner, John Sykes, with Cautionary Warning.
[SPEAKER_22]: And here's a clip.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, that was song number one in tonight's cage match, a clip of last week's winner, John Sykes, Cautionary Warning.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wasn't that, now I'm remembering that song, that's the one where the White Snake guitarist or something has something to do with that, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_22]: That's very correct.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: Song number two in tonight's K-Twitch will be my pick.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to go ahead and go.
[SPEAKER_22]: My song is... Too bad Miklatel's not here because he talked this song up for me.
[SPEAKER_22]: But my song is by an artist named Andy Bell.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Andy Bell was half of Razor.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, the great 80s and 90s synth-pop band.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love synth-pop.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Andy Bell has a solo album out now.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like... I had to put in...
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuckin' mic, I hit this mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know I love me some synth pop.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I had to put this in because Andy Bell is one of the granddaddies of synth pop going back to Yaz and all these other great bands.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love this song.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's the latest CD, Electric Blue.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_22]: Crazy, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, that was song number two in tonight's Cage Mesh.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was Andy Bell with Crazy.
[SPEAKER_22]: And we'll go around and see what folks thought of that.
[SPEAKER_22]: If they were crazy for that song or it drove them crazy.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, you're up first.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was... no offense, it was a little repetitive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't write it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't a bad song.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just find it a little repetitive and kind of boring, so it gets a 6.5.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've been blasting this song in my car all week.
[SPEAKER_22]: I really like it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh, 9.
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's so crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll hold 7.5.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, moving on to song number 3 in tonight's Gage Match.
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, what'd you pick for us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, because it's that Saturday, which is usually the day I think about what I'm gonna play, um, I just picked the Blur song, so it's a crazy beat.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, sound of the pre-tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Blur!
[SPEAKER_21]: With Crazy Beat.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
I love my brothers on Saturday night
[SPEAKER_07]: I love my sister and I love her tonight Break out!
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, that was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was Blur with Crazy Beat.
[SPEAKER_22]: Once again, are you crazy about that song or did it drive you crazy?
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually not my favorite Blur song, but I like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, so, uh, give it an 8.5.
[SPEAKER_22]: Kicks and Butts Kicks and Butts
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you listening to tonight's K-Town songs, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I am listening to K-Town.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just thought it would be funny since both songs have crazy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was interesting that both songs have crazy in the title.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just one of those funky coincidences.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, alright, it's time for you guys to vote as soon as we recap.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here we go, the three songs you can vote for tonight, starting off with song number one, which is Cautionary Warning.
[SPEAKER_22]: And song number two you can vote for tonight is Andy Bell with Crazy And song number three you can vote for tonight is Blur with Crazy Beat
[SPEAKER_22]: All right, kids, you know what to do.
[SPEAKER_22]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote, and we will reveal the wiener of the vote as soon as we can.
[SPEAKER_22]: Moving on over to Loki to talk about what else is going on in the sim scene besides the PSP thing, which, by the way, you actually showed me because you downloaded it there during the last little bit.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: That actually looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_22]: The skin's a little fucked because your life bar's in the middle of the screen, but, well, there's four skins.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't tried the other four skins.
[SPEAKER_02]: I walked right into that joke, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, there's supposedly four different skins for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's weird, though, because you can do DDR and stuff, but I haven't actually tried some of the other skins.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been basically using a default one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really know it's the life bar in the middle, so it's not a big problem for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: The keys, though, are a little fucked up, but I probably should have not been trying to play one key P1807.
[SPEAKER_02]: That just didn't work very well.
[SPEAKER_22]: You had one key assigned to all your buttons?
[SPEAKER_22]: What was that about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's the default settings they have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because try doing 7-key on a PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then why point the damn thing to a PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But 5-key, though, works pretty well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I am getting some nice 5-key sim files to try on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, I don't know, it could work for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that, there is some stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know on BomaniStyle right now they are actually doing OSC4, which is another SimFile contest, not to be confused with...
[SPEAKER_02]: Turny Mix, which is not going on anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, anyways, OSC 4, I believe, is available for download right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got some links on their front page there, and they also kind of talk about who's judging and how it's going to go and that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, check it out now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the keyboard division, so these are all going to be the ones that are impossible to play, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Check those out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not you, we're laughing in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: Somebody just joined and we said that they missed the cage match and their response was, and I quote, shit, shit, shitty, shit, shit.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's the little things in life that amuse me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to immortalize that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which, by the way, is what I think about a large part of the Bomani files that are being put out lately as shit, shit, shitty, shit, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And since you mentioned shit, shit, shitty, shit, shit, I have to mention the Mac
[SPEAKER_02]: SimFiles for the week, and starting off with Max Don't Have Sex With Your Ex, not exactly a Max Remix, but still, you know, falls under the Max category, Max 300, the Miss Remix, Max 300 Pack, which means probably more than one Max 300 in there, Max Max, Max Stinks, and Max 340.
[SPEAKER_02]: Max Stinks?
[SPEAKER_02]: Max Stink.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not Max Stinks, as in Max Stink, like Maximum Stink.
[SPEAKER_22]: That sounds like an anti-deodorant.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like instead of, you know, like Right Guard Max, it's Max Stink.
[SPEAKER_22]: When you're going out on a date with an ugly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But to be fair, what I'm going to do is I'm going to download Max Stink to my PSP and play it on the DDR simulator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually, no I'm not, because I'm not going to waste that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Space on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now, the other thing I was kind of curious about with PSP, hypothetically, couldn't you use that little USB adapter to hypothetically use a Kiki Joy to hypothetically put in a PlayStation 2, 2DX controller?
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because the way the USB things works.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, you could, in theory...
[SPEAKER_02]: Put a portable keyboard which uses the infrared port and use that for Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now there's an idea.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or... And then it's like that one game.
[SPEAKER_22]: What was that Beatmania game?
[SPEAKER_22]: Da da da or something that they put out that was a keyboard Beatmania game?
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's interesting, though, is the USB port, people are saying that you can't really put stuff in there, like, you know, peripherals and stuff, but they have that new Talkpad coming out for it, and it looks like, because the problem was they couldn't get power off of the port, there was no power going through it, so that's why it's not working, but I looked at the side of this port here, and there's these two little, like, copper contact points where the power comes through, so apparently you can get power
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess in theory you could hook up a dance pad, but why would you want to?
[SPEAKER_22]: Just imagine for a minute, holding a PSP while you're dancing.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know how stupid you'd look to someone who's coming by?
[SPEAKER_16]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I kind of have an idea what that would look like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've done that with the controller before.
[SPEAKER_22]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_22]: Both would work, though, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because the PlayStation 2 has USB on it, and like you said, the PSP has the little power thing on it, so you could use your PSP to charge your iPod, which is a really stupid idea, if you think about it, but it would work, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the problem is that it's not a standard USB, it's the Mini-B, so you'd have to have some sort of adapter, but yes, I guess it's possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if power's going directly to that all the time, I don't know, but I'd imagine it has to be.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe it'd have to be in USB mode for it to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Like on everything, there's these copper contact points by all the AC adapter and also by the USB.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this is for a cradle, is why they have that there, so you can just sit it down in something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, the other one for the peripherals that go into it, because they have screw points where you can screw something in.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I guess you could do that, but why would you want to, honestly?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because people will do something just because they can.
[SPEAKER_22]: Explain why people install Linux on a Billy Bass, on a toaster, on Hello Kitty watches.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why do people do that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because they can.
[SPEAKER_22]: Seriously, I mean, if you figure out that you can charge your iPod using your PSP or whatever, aren't you going to show that to somebody?
[SPEAKER_22]: Like, dude, I can charge my iPod with my PSP.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never hear me say that because I'll never have an iPod.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here's the status with Skype, you guys.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're trying to get into Skype, but the weird thing is whenever we try, and I realize I hear you guys in the chat room loud and clear saying you see us online, but I've tried calling the back number, the phone number that you can call to get into us too, and it's not working.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's not ringing on our computer.
[SPEAKER_22]: So even if you guys tried to call us, we are not seeing it.
[SPEAKER_22]: So even though you guys are seeing us logged in Skype, we are not actually there.
[SPEAKER_22]: We are trying to log in, but the problem is I'm getting caught in a loop on Skype is that I log in and then it says logging in and then kicks me back out to the login screen.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Usually what I would do is I would just reset Skype or reinstall Skype to get this to work.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_22]: at least we have the chat room if nothing else because we do want to hear what our listeners have to say and I want to hear about your thanksgivings and stuff very sorry about Skype but this is one of those things where it's kind of out of our ballpark right now so we'll keep trying I'm going to keep trying to hammer in there and clear some stuff out and see what I can do
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't wait for Animal Crossing
[SPEAKER_22]: You played it, how?
[SPEAKER_22]: At E3?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, okay, so E3 answers some questions about it, but it doesn't tell us how online is going to work.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's really what I'm curious about.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can I go into DarkSakura's village and cut down all her trees?
[SPEAKER_22]: If you want DarkSakura to go into your village and set fire to it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Am I going to be able to go into DarkSakura's village and teach all of her villagers to say, you smell like butt?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you had Olivia in my village.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was saying something rather foul.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was cunt, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_22]: The word was cunt.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was sophomoric and juvenile, and I thought it was funny to get one of my Animal Crossing villagers to say cunt, but... It's hot at two... One of them moved into my... No, she moved into your village, and then I got her back, because she was my favorite.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she was foul.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was going around foul-mouthed, and then her neighbors started saying it, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember who moved to my town, Big Cock, but it was funny everybody talking about Big Cock all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had Danville.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because of Dan.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_22]: You had Danville.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't even remember what I called my town.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was Sky Place?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Big Cock.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_22]: We have Rob on air saying that he likes it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_22]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow, that was scary.
[SPEAKER_22]: That didn't get all picked up on microphone, but Jamie went from laughing to like, ah!
[SPEAKER_22]: There she goes, sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: You try coughing up balloon cookies.
[SPEAKER_08]: See how loquacious it makes you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here's what I remember about Animal Crossing is that I got that Olivia to say cunt, and she went back to your village.
[SPEAKER_22]: Then she went over to Iguana Girl's village, and those of you that know Iguana Girl knows that she hates cunts.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't remember I had the lesbian in my village too
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, there was lesbians.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember what she was, but she was a lesbian because she lived in the gym teacher house and wore sweats all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I put a big rainbow sign outside of her house.
[SPEAKER_22]: I remember you put the big rainbow sign and then you got her to say something like, you know, Big Dyke.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought we got her to say Real Gay or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_22]: We are thinking now, I am...
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, cool, they're saying in the new Animal Crossing you can teach outright phrases to animals rather than just sentence fragments and words.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can teach my village lesbian to say that, never mind.
[SPEAKER_22]: I eat, never mind.
[SPEAKER_22]: If I say it, somebody's going to YTM and do it, so I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I fear our listener base all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_22]: Although I do love the idea of like an Orange Lounge Radio Village.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know how we're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess it'll just have to be one of our towns.
[SPEAKER_22]: We will open up during the show and just let our listeners randomly come in and harass us during Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll have to recreate ourselves in Animal Crossing form and have our houses.
[SPEAKER_08]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or maybe we'll come to your village.
[SPEAKER_22]: That could be the thing is that Orange Lounge Radio, we could party crash your village.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe like once a week somebody will give us a friend code and we'll go party crash in their village and destroy things.
[SPEAKER_22]: It'll be Orange Lounge Radio, burn and eat your village.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_22]: This could be like a contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: We could have contests, you know, who could hit, you know, Loki with a bug net first, or... We also have them put out welcome signs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we'll have... Make us shirts.
[SPEAKER_22]: Purchase our... Too bad you can't, like, sell stuff to other players.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, on my Mario Kart 64...
[SPEAKER_22]: I used, because I suck at creating emblems, I used the little pre-made t-shirt one and I just wrote OLR on it, it was my first emblem, but I'm like, that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then like when I would get into matches randomly on the internet, I know nobody's going to know what that means.
[SPEAKER_22]: So now mine is a big orange heart and it says in the heart, I can't draw.
[SPEAKER_22]: I wrote, I can't draw.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mine I actually went and did an old logo that I had designed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to do, I wanted to get some skull and crossbones on there too, but I just stuck with Loki.
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you see the VG cat earlier talking about the logo on the car and it says, it's a penis?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to link that to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or, you know, maybe we'll just have to rely on our quick wit to fill some show.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_22]: In this break, I want to do a little bit of bequia, because I need some Korean music.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we're going to do bequia.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Laundry.
I came in from a rainy Thursday on the avenue Thought I heard you talking softly I turned on the lights, the TV, and the radio Still I can't escape the ghost of you What is happening?
and more.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Don't lie on paradise!
Do you like it or hate it?
It's all up to you!
[SPEAKER_07]: The blue one will take you for a clarion!
[SPEAKER_22]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_22]: Is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_22]: Testing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Testing 1-2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does this thing work?
[SPEAKER_08]: This thing reads like stereo instructions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this on?
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Broke down Ghetto Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the?
[SPEAKER_22]: You're telling me, Broke Down, Get Over My Radio, we can't get our Skype tour tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think it's going to be a wash for Skype tonight, because I'm getting the same problem when I get back in there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had one of our listeners try calling us during the break there, trying to get in.
[SPEAKER_22]: No workie.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I think Skype might be down tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: We will keep trying.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not going to lose hope.
[SPEAKER_22]: If we can fit in even one call.
[SPEAKER_22]: It caught your whooping cough or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: If we can fit in even one call before the end of the show, we will do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know, this show existed for like a year and a half before we ever had Skype, so we will...
[SPEAKER_22]: Of course, then again, the show was only two hours then, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: But we'll find a way to get through this somehow.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I realize you guys are seeing us online.
[SPEAKER_22]: I assure you guys, even though we are somehow showing us online, we are not getting the pop-up box that shows us we have a call.
[SPEAKER_22]: Therefore, we cannot take your call.
[SPEAKER_22]: We thought about patching through DarkSakura's laptop, but unfortunately, that is not an option either.
[SPEAKER_22]: I told you I can't go wrong if I pick Damon.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know why you won?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because Roz was rallying the troops in the chat room for you, I think.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was a big part of the reason why I think you got it.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, good job.
[SPEAKER_22]: Blur wins, and we'll go into rotation on our Bomani Video Game Music program, which, by the way, I updated in some capacity this week, and we're going to take a look at the Video Game Music portion very soon, but Bomani got a little bit of a facelift, and that is all based on your scores that come up in the... For those of you that listen through Live 365 and not through iTunes, you get little
[SPEAKER_22]: Little thumbs up and thumbs down icon
[SPEAKER_22]: You can actually, whoa, my stupid microphone.
[SPEAKER_22]: You get a little thumbs up and thumbs down icon where you can actually rate the songs as they play.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we actually took out a couple of the Bomani songs that were very low rated.
[SPEAKER_22]: Some of the stuff from Ultramix 2, some of the old, old songs.
[SPEAKER_22]: We just kind of flushed out of there and put in some of the good Ultramix 3 songs and Happy Sky and some other stuff too.
[SPEAKER_22]: We just kind of filled it out.
[SPEAKER_22]: I threw in a new Castlevania song for good measure just because I was like, oh, this song should be in rotation.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I snuck one new one in there.
[SPEAKER_22]: This microphone is pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, I hate this mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's what we need to use our $25 just to get on as a replacement mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to actually put down some money and get good mics.
[SPEAKER_22]: We should invest it, and then in a year we could have a good mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, a good mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because that microphone that you're using there would be about what we could afford if we invested the $25, because that's one that Angel very kindly donated to us, and that's... You know this, for years that mic's been lasting pretty long.
It's...
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, that one's not bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm about ready to go just buy my own top dollar mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, that's a great mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_22]: The one you're using is a fabulous mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it costs this much times eight.
[SPEAKER_22]: It costs that much times eight is how much that costs, according to Angel.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, and I see some people in the room bitching about my microphone suggestion to turn up the mixing board's mic boost until the microphone works.
[SPEAKER_22]: Unfortunately, that doesn't work right because the problem with this microphone is it's what we call, um, I think they call it unidirectional, which means it only works if the microphone is pointing
[SPEAKER_22]: in one particular direction.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it's really good for reporters who are trying to interview someone who don't want to get all that background noise.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the problem is, usually what you get is a cardio-shaped microphone, which is like a heart-shaped audio pattern.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or you have a, I think, omni-directional microphone, which is you can pick up sound in all directions.
[SPEAKER_22]: And DarkSakura and Loki have omni-directional microphones.
[SPEAKER_22]: So no matter which way they're holding the microphone, it's picking up their sound.
[SPEAKER_22]: Unfortunately, with this microphone, if I turn it just a little bit too far one direction,
[SPEAKER_22]: You suddenly lose the voice and you don't hear me as well.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I have to talk specifically into one part of this microphone or it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the problem is that I'm not necessarily used to this microphone, so that's why you get a lot of weird sound out of this.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, go figure.
[SPEAKER_08]: You still sound more normal than I do.
[SPEAKER_22]: Eh, to some extent.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then people are saying in the chat room, oh, my headset mic only cost me $8.
[SPEAKER_22]: The problem is that we used to use those headsets...
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, and the headsets that I brought were expensive.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they were... They were call center headsets.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, and the problem is they kind of sounded like call center.
[SPEAKER_22]: They didn't... They were good.
[SPEAKER_22]: They worked at the time.
[SPEAKER_22]: They were free.
[SPEAKER_22]: But remember that very, very, very first mic we had?
[SPEAKER_22]: It was the guest microphone.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was this little, tiny $10 microphone that sounded like you were talking out of two Dixie Cups and a string.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish I had... What happened to the boom mic?
[SPEAKER_22]: The boom mic?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, the big... Oh, the boom mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's at Loki's house.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, it's still my house.
[SPEAKER_22]: The boom mic was our idea because we used to have a lot of sidebar conversations.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because in the old place, in the old studio, we would have like 10 people that could fit in the studio.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was an ambient mic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, and the boom mic was supposed to pick up sidebar conversations.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was to kind of encourage people to shut the F up while we're trying to do a show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it was supposed to be so you could hear people yelling in the background.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It worked pretty good for what we had.
[SPEAKER_22]: It worked okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was kind of hit and miss.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was hidden, so no one knew where it was, so they couldn't talk into it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think what we'll do now, because I'm feeling a little angsty about the Skype line not working, is I think now would be a very good time for us to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, why do we do the FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_08]: God, I haven't heard that in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big F you goes toward whatever the disease of the week is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently I went from a cold to a sinus infection to bronchitis to pneumonia to whipping cough.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I kind of miss knowing what my voice sounds like other than listening to our old bumpers on the station.
[SPEAKER_08]: And F you to me getting motion sick from playing We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_08]: and FU goes to me not having any more time off for the rest of the year and also having to put off my trip to London until 2007 and also to whoever that was that double parked in your parking lot because they suck they suck quite a bit and also FU to me not having any hot tea right now good let's go over to Loki and see where his angst is
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, my angst is with, um, games being boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, for example, um, Shadow Colossus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting quite bored with that game really quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so, yeah, I have to sell that back now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, this Microsoft for not saying out quite enough Xbox 360s.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know you want to drive a pipe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not going to do that by really cryptic, um, commercials.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need a commercial that screams, wow, this is kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you got to get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Watching people throw water balloons.
[SPEAKER_02]: does not scream, wow, this is kickass, or watching people jump rope, no, that is not kickass, that tells me, go outside, that's what that says, so, you might be marketing that to the wrong people, um, then finally, um, fuck you McDonald's, because no matter how simple I make my orders, they just can't seem to get them right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't have a problem today.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never have a problem with McDonald's in my order.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do it myself.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have tea bags if you want some hot tea.
[SPEAKER_22]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_08]: I want my herbs from home.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have peppermint.
[SPEAKER_22]: I only have shitty Lipton, sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have shitty Lipton green tea, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been making peppermint and white willow tea.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, that sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: White willow is nasty shit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Egyptian licorice is my favorite.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate licorice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be online playing Mario Kart DS after this show, briefly between show and podcast.
[SPEAKER_21]: You should get some friend codes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have friend codes, but I can never catch anyone online.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just let them know and give them fair warning.
[SPEAKER_22]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you did the fact that I have to go back to work tomorrow after...
[SPEAKER_22]: Four days of not having to work because you kind of get used to not working and then you have to go back to work.
[SPEAKER_22]: Tomorrow's going to kind of be a busy day, too, just because it's like one of those things, you know, especially when you're kind of in the role that I play at my organization.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's kind of like I've got to find my groove.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rob's got to get his groove back, like Stella.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've got to get my groove back, and it's not something that's going to click at 8 o'clock in the morning tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I'm going to be very groggy and bitchy tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_22]: And if you do the fact that I way overslept this weekend, I mean, seriously, I've been sleeping like...
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: I think if I could have just hibernated for the past four days, it would have been great.
[SPEAKER_22]: An F you to the fact that I couldn't get an Xbox 360 even if I wanted one.
[SPEAKER_22]: And an F you to the fact that a lot of video games are $50, like the new ones.
[SPEAKER_22]: $50 is a lot of money. $60.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, yeah, Xbox 360 is like $60, but even like, you know, current-gen platforms are $50.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sometimes, if you're lucky, $30 or $40, but Dragon Quest VIII set me back $50.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's kind of like, boy, oh boy, I better get 100 hours of playtime out of that game or something to make it worth it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Otherwise, I'm going to be pissed.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, so F you to expensive things.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's not fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right, let's go to the chatroom FUs, of which I'm sure there are plenty this week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rene wants to give a big huge FU to Best Buy and McDonald's for making me gather $21, Best Buy dollars, and when I finally get to use them on Ultramix 3, the website, LOL at Loki, the damn game gets on backorder, so I had to buy at full price at GameStop and get a refund.
[SPEAKER_22]: Another FU to the manager at a nearby EB Games, where I was considering buying Ultramix 3 when he hangs up because he thinks I'm a rival manager letting him know that the game is out already.
[SPEAKER_22]: and my last F.U.
[SPEAKER_22]: to a wasp that took four hits with a large towel to take down.
[SPEAKER_22]: My next F.U.
[SPEAKER_22]: comes from Sephiroth1215.
[SPEAKER_22]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_22]: to my teacher giving work over Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_22]: Remember back in the day when we were in high school and those bitches would give us homework over Christmas break?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like, read this book!
[SPEAKER_08]: I really enjoyed reading books.
[SPEAKER_22]: I enjoyed reading books too, but not the crap that our teachers assigned us.
[SPEAKER_22]: I liked reading contemporary stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I remember to this day the book I hated that I had to read in high school was Dandelion Wine.
[SPEAKER_22]: I hated that book.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dandelion Wine, The Inferno, The Odyssey,
[SPEAKER_07]: They had no choice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wrote my book report.
[SPEAKER_07]: And look at the book!
[SPEAKER_22]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: What was the book?
[SPEAKER_22]: 1984, but our class didn't do that one.
[SPEAKER_22]: We did Brave New World, which was just as weird.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, we did Catcher in the Rye, which was cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I enjoyed doing Catcher in the Rye.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hated the Grapes of Wrath.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck the Grapes of Wrath.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, we had to do that one too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, Sephiroth1215 also says, and F you to Tecmo for pushing back DOA4 because I want another 360 game that is actually good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, and Sephiroth1215 would like to say he's actually in college, not... Fuck it, Mike.
[SPEAKER_22]: Same thing with college.
[SPEAKER_22]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dark Knight says, F you to Black Friday, F you to losing my stylist, I had to buy a new one, F you to being single for 18 years.
[SPEAKER_22]: I would buy him a horn.
[SPEAKER_22]: Seriously, I mean, that's why I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hold on to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My stylist got eaten by my couch.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a spare.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan bought me a silver one that matches my DS.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know you can buy those styluses in like the little color packs so you have like a purple stylus?
[SPEAKER_22]: We have the three packs.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the black one, the blue one, and the silver one.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I have a silver one.
[SPEAKER_20]: I want a purple one.
[SPEAKER_20]: God, I hate you like I'm a purple school.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_20]: Roz... Seriously.
[SPEAKER_22]: Roz wants to say an F you to Graham Coxon.
[SPEAKER_22]: That sexy bitch delayed his new album release from Fall 2005 to March 16th, 2006.
[SPEAKER_22]: Nice way to work in that plug, by the way.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ron Chan says, F you to people that drop out of races on Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_22]: Take your beatings like a man.
[SPEAKER_22]: Neo Dude Zero says, F you to crappy Linksys USB Internet adapters.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've been in and out of both show and chat all night.
[SPEAKER_22]: Vander C says, F you to Jamie for slapping me with a trout.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't like trout.
[SPEAKER_22]: Tell him to stay tuned for my response.
[SPEAKER_22]: You need to slap him with a grilled salmon.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or slap him with a chili bass.
[SPEAKER_22]: The macro is for trout.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: Tomo Kun says, Fuck me neglecting this show and the podcast for weeks upon weeks upon weeks.
[SPEAKER_22]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, and fuck you whoever sends me the same piece of spam.
[SPEAKER_22]: ColorOfSakura says, F you to not getting enough hours at work, F you to Mario Kart's DS's lack of good Wi-Fi interface, F you to the Xbox 360, F you to sickness, F you to getting my 2DX controller in the mail and it being broken.
[SPEAKER_22]: Legend of Zaku says, F you to not investing $400 earlier this year, it's like getting Xbox 360 for me to sell on eBay now.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to sake not being as strong as I thought it would be.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to fucking ants that invaded my box of rice-a-roni, thus forging me to ditch that box and use up another.
[SPEAKER_22]: I ought to be in college again.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to all other game stores for trying to offer me pennies for Madden 06 and NBA Live 06.
[SPEAKER_22]: Lucky me, I knew this place around my way that gave me $50 for both of them.
[SPEAKER_22]: and Nintendo Maniac would like to say, or Nintendo Maniac 64, says, F you to the weather for there being lots of snow and a possible snow day on Thanksgiving week.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to my computer for locking up a few minutes ago, preventing me from not knowing it's F you time.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to myself for putting a knot in my last F you when it was supposed to be there.
[SPEAKER_22]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: It wasn't supposed to be there.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to myself for building a DS LEGO charging deck which took up my charger and I had to partially disassemble it to get my charger out so I could play Mario Kart DS without my DS's battery dying.
[SPEAKER_22]: Mine still won't fit together.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I liked your little Lego charger that you had there.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was kind of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: I missed that thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I should get some Legos and build me a Lego base.
[SPEAKER_22]: What I also liked about it is that you can put your games and your styluses in it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I thought that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, except every now and then it's sitting on my cabinet and every now and then I knock into it and it falls over and it breaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, I don't have that many games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it works good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It works good for charging.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you use hot glue and you put it together and it'll never fall apart?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, and then you'll never be able to get that stupid charger thing out of there because you basically hold the wire in place with Legos or something underneath it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's stuck in there pretty good.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like that DS charging station.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was a good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have to find, I have the specs on my computer still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Post those.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, I think what we're going to do is we're going to go to a break and when we come back we might do some Ask Orange Lounge if the Skype line's not working.
[SPEAKER_22]: and some other stories, whatever tickles our fancy when we come back after this break.
[SPEAKER_22]: And in this break, more Bomani Potpourri, because we can.
[SPEAKER_22]: And we'll start it off with an old school Beatmania song.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're going to do Total Recall.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, oh, oh
[SPEAKER_12]: Straight, Indie Record Store, I'm picking something up, I'm picking something more
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I know that you'll be mine
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
[SPEAKER_22]: Gaming Radio, so uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Back, boys and girls, with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: And a broke-ass Skype line, so we have no callers tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: God, thank God we didn't have any interviews or anything scheduled tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'd be really screwed.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, sorry guys, we can't get you guys in on the Skype line, so we're not going to be able to do some calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll try one more time before the end of the show, although I somehow highly doubt it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_22]: And apologize to those of you guys that were waiting to call in, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_22]: Shit happens.
[SPEAKER_22]: Of course, next week we'll be back with another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live, and all of us will be here.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe we'll have some special guests next week, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: We've got to talk some of our buddies into coming on over to the show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't forget, we also have other live programming on Orange Lounge Radio all week long.
[SPEAKER_22]: Monday nights, Extroverse Case of the Mondays, which airs at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, 7.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura is with us with...
[SPEAKER_08]: I pump up the volume which I'm doing every other Tuesday until the end of the semester and then I'll be back on regularly it's a music request show, I play whatever just tune in
[SPEAKER_22]: Wednesday nights on the station, The Rob Roberts Show, which is also on at 7 o'clock Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_22]: And same sort of deal, I do take requests, but that's not really the concept of my show.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just play whatever the hell I feel like.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I also talk about geek stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: I find some geek articles on the web and kind of give you my opinion on them.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm kind of like Rush Limbaugh in that way, except not a fat drug addict, basically.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, on Orange Lounge Radio, we may have some new shows coming soon.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're looking at expanding the station in the future.
[SPEAKER_22]: May happen, may not, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Very likely, though, that you're going to see some exciting stuff in the future at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_22]: But as you'll notice, we've got Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_22]: We've got a couple days we can do some other stuff with, so we will see what happens.
[SPEAKER_22]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shall we do some Ask Orange Lounge, boys and girls?
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, I got the thumbs up from DarkSakura, so here we go!
[SPEAKER_22]: It helped to have the volume up when I bring in the theme music, huh?
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_22]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_22]: Will we find out why this microphone is broken?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I'm about to throw it through a window if it doesn't cooperate.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, apparently all they heard was geek articles and then fat drug addict.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, what I said is geek articles, and I'm kind of like a one-man Rush Limbaugh, because I give my opinions on them, except I'm not a fat drug addict.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was the correct thing that I said.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sakurina wants to know, does Sky like Rizlem the remix?
[SPEAKER_22]: I believe that's a song in Night Style, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: That's over in the 9th style.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let me see if I can get a little clip here of the Rizlem remix.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura is over there in the corner gagging.
[SPEAKER_22]: I take it you do not like the Rizlem remix.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could just be a lung cookie, but it sort of made my stomach turn.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hold on, let me see if we can get a little clip here of the Rizlem remix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the part that doesn't have the singing in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, this is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing where we get in the middle?
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the plot where it ends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: I prefer the original.
[SPEAKER_22]: I definitely prefer the original.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it's okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't hate it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't despise it like DarkSakura does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still gotta work on the other remix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Are you gonna tell us about the samples thing?
[SPEAKER_22]: You gotta tell us.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_22]: After Asporn's launch, we'll get into that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Does anyone know the approximate cost of a 2DX 9th style machine and if they are still in production?
[SPEAKER_08]: 2DX Red on eBay right now, it's in City of Industry, $5,100.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that's probably what you're looking at for a 9-star machine as well.
[SPEAKER_22]: It is not cheap.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Sakurina also wants to know how Xtifer knows how to pronounce 2DX when he doesn't even play it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, cause he's heard me say it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And he, you know, Miklatov spends the weekend here sometimes and we'll both be playing it and he's like, what's that?
[SPEAKER_22]: And we say, it's 2DX.
[SPEAKER_22]: So he knows it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Cause he's Tina, he just sucks at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just teasing.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is a pro at, uh, at Taiko No Tatooine.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's actually very good at Taiko No Tatooine.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh, let's see, moving on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Tomo Kun wants to know, how about that show, The Boondocks?
[SPEAKER_22]: I've never seen this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember reading the comics in my funny papers.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not interested in watching this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a funny show I did hear about, and I want to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be late tonight is when it's on.
[SPEAKER_02]: MTV2, it's called Wondershosen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like an adult version of Sesame Street.
[SPEAKER_22]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: MTV2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna have to... It's late at night.
[SPEAKER_22]: Are Bert and Ernie really gay in this one?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they have, like, different characters, but they have one, it's, uh, what is it, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: D-O-G-Y-N is one of the, you know, like, dog OBGYNs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they also have, like, some weird ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's one, like, they were talking about the letter N, and nobody liked the letter N, so N left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then they had to find the letter S with the track down the letter N, and instead of tracking N down, ended up having sex with N and had babies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is your favorite character in the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: series?
[SPEAKER_22]: Who's your favorite character in the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_22]: series?
[SPEAKER_22]: Um... I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'd say Princess Peach, because Peach is the winner!
[SPEAKER_22]: She's such an arrogant little fuck, I like her.
[SPEAKER_22]: Big Boo!
[SPEAKER_22]: Big Boo's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: You, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Geno.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's from Super Mario RPG.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_20]: Wow, that's obscure.
[SPEAKER_20]: More questions.
[SPEAKER_20]: Rimi asks the following.
[SPEAKER_20]: Consider the following.
[SPEAKER_22]: Medical science advances to the point where a device can seal wounds on the spot.
[SPEAKER_22]: Problem.
[SPEAKER_22]: Your friends use said technology to seal your ass shut as a practical joke.
[SPEAKER_22]: What do you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Go on, jackass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Viva la banja.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fart it open.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think you would die because your colon would explode.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fart it open!
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you would go to the hospital and, I don't know, have them cut it open.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, yeah, I would think if the medical science is far enough along where they could seal your ass shut magically, they could unseal it magically.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it ain't broken, they can't fix it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And what are some pretty underrated songs on DDR?
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, a real question.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's good to know.
[SPEAKER_22]: What are some pretty underrated songs on DDR?
[SPEAKER_22]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Someone's knocking on the door.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, that's me.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm tapping on the table.
[SPEAKER_22]: Moving on from DDR5thMix.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's a cool song.
[SPEAKER_22]: What else?
[SPEAKER_22]: Can you think of anything, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_22]: Underrated songs in DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really easy because I always said Love That Feeling was underrated.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, because a lot of people hate on Love That Feeling.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bass.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_22]: God, most of the songs I like, a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_22]: Xanadu Night in Motion Kongafelin
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm trying to think of some of the more recent mixes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantasy from Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, Fantasy was in Max 1.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was in Max 1 and then didn't come back for Max 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: That one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Max 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantasy was the one that was Eurobeat from Max 1.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that one needs to go away, but the other one, that one's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_22]: That is a good one.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm trying to think of U.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, there's U.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: licenses that I think are incredibly underrated.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think the PlayStation 2 fanboys need to recognize that Xbox has some really good songs on Ultramix 2, such as Skulk.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I don't know if I would call that underrated, because anyone that's played it knows it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I'm trying to think of other U.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: licenses that I think are a little bit underrated.
[SPEAKER_22]: I always liked Dark Black Forest, and I know a lot of people hated it on that song, but I thought it was a great song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just a very random choice for DDR.
[SPEAKER_22]: I thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: and what was the other one?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another one that was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was also O.M.
[SPEAKER_02]: Max.
[SPEAKER_21]: Max USA?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: The Take It To The Morning... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_21]: That one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like that song, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: How about a question from me?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I see our chat room is suddenly singing, My humps, my humps, what would you do if they put my humps in DDR?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because Loki hates that song, by the way.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I would say that's pretty bad, but thank God it hasn't been put in, and I would have to show my fianc and she'd have to laugh at me.
[SPEAKER_22]: I actually like Hey Mama a lot in Ultramix 3, though.
[SPEAKER_22]: I gotta say, that was a good choice.
[SPEAKER_22]: For a Black Eyed Peas song, that was a really good choice.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Black Eyed Peas
I have heard this song.
I heard it in spin.
See?
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard it in spin and I remember hating it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Black Eyed Peas?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, in the Best Buy commercial, the, you know, remix!
Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I friggin' hate this microphone.
[SPEAKER_22]: I hate this microphone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Black Eyed Peas are okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Xander C wants to know, do I suck at DDR if I can't beat Max Unlimited on Heavy?
[SPEAKER_22]: And is it weird that I can't beat that but manage to beat Charlene in the group of an expert?
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't beat Max Unlimited on Heavy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, I used to play doubles and I would play some crazy shit in doubles and I still couldn't beat it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just too fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not really a song that should be played.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just made it really super hard and ooh, I did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not a song to be played for fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I don't think it's odd that you
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think it's odd that you can't beat that, but you can beat Charlene, because I remember, I think it was Charlene, I might be mixing it up with one of the erotic songs, but I think maybe I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_22]: I might be mixing up Charlene with Lemmings on the run, but I remember that one of them on heavy had an awful lot of freezes, was like the big thing, was there was a lot of freezes in the hands.
[SPEAKER_22]: And if I could do hands, unfortunately I'm very tall and my back will go out very easily if I do too much of the hands thing, which is one of the reasons I don't like in the groove because I hate the hands thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: I could almost beat it, though, if it weren't for that.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't remember if it was that or Charlene that I was very close to beating, but yet I haven't come close to beating Max Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I have no problem sharing that.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think you have to necessarily be the bestest DDR player in the world.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, who cares?
[SPEAKER_22]: You play it because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's why I play it.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's why I don't mind when they release a new mix of DDR and there's only one 10-footer in it and a bunch of 7s.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like the game better that way because DDR for me is more of a casual workout type thing and not a...
[SPEAKER_22]: I want to wheeze and throw up, you know, lung chunks after, no offense, lung chunks after one song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I know all about throwing up lung chunks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to get back to the wheezing part.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, the sad thing is I probably wouldn't even be able to beat, like, Breakdown or Stay on Heavy, and I used to be able to do those, no problem.
[SPEAKER_22]: I beat Breakdown.
[SPEAKER_22]: I probably couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Having a fiance really cuts into the 8 hour sessions of DDR that I used to do in arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... I can't do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, it's Queen of Light that's the freezes in hands and Charlene is just a lot of runs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku wants to say...
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm in the market for some good-ass sake.
[SPEAKER_22]: Any suggestions?
[SPEAKER_22]: I've never had sake in my life, believe it or not, so I can't help you.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a brand I like, but for the life of me, I can't remember how to pronounce the name, so give me a sec, I'll look for it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, uh, Loki?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't drink sake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any sake?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I don't drink it either.
[SPEAKER_22]: What's a plum wine that you usually get?
[SPEAKER_22]: I know that's not sake, but speaking of, like, you know, Asian liquor, what was that?
[SPEAKER_22]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_08]: The cheap stuff I buy is the Takara brand.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, let's check out the, uh, uh, sake thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He basically all actually has his own energy drink.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just some random trivia thrown in there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Legend of Zaku wants to know, I wonder if you t-voted last week's episodes of Direct Effect in which yours truly was seen as well as New York City's best DDR player being profiled.
[SPEAKER_22]: I forgot to set the t-vote.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I had it on there and everything, I forgot to do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I know they're going to rerun it to death.
[SPEAKER_22]: It'll be on again, so I'm not too worried.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'm sure Zaku will tell me when it's being rerun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's a good brand for the plum wine.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got the green plums at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ah, yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, you bought that once and we got drunk off that shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can't tell because it doesn't taste like booze.
[SPEAKER_22]: One of the first times me and you got drunk together was off that stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Off that stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: So now look up that sake and let us know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Meanwhile, more questions.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're doing Ask Orange Lounge here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you're just joining us, this is a portion of the show where the listeners can submit questions to us and we answer them because we love our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just joining us.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a bit late, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want to learn Japanese, but I'm poor, so I can't pay anything, and there's nothing or anyone near me that could teach it to me for free.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything good and free on the internet, I'm out of ideas.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have a suggestion, try out podcasts, because there's actually a lot of podcasts out there that try to teach you how to speak a second language, not just Spanish, but I'm sure there's a Japanese one out there too.
[SPEAKER_22]: A lot of good free stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if you can find anything at an elementary level, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, sometimes if you look on some of the sites such as BitTorrent stuff, you can sometimes find and learn how to speak Japanese CD, which, you know, it's better than nothing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Go to college.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, or go to college.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or if you...
[SPEAKER_02]: BOOM BOOM Satellites BOOM BOOM Satellites
[SPEAKER_22]: NintendoManiac64 says, did anyone make a YTMND out of your I Like Big Dick quote yet?
[SPEAKER_22]: No, they haven't, and I hope they don't.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also wants to know, how was my Firefox Mario Kart DS decal?
[SPEAKER_22]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I imagine you probably used that same thing that a lot of people use to turn a graphic into an emblem.
[SPEAKER_22]: But what I want to know is, what was that thing...
[SPEAKER_22]: Where you were going back and forth, because I remember playing you, you were going back and forth on the track a lot, like, I don't know if you were trying to do like a bunch of drifts, but you were going really fast, and I know you weren't getting that many mushrooms, so, I don't know, were you trying to do a bunch of drifts or something?
[SPEAKER_22]: Snaking?
[SPEAKER_22]: Snaking, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the things I've seen people doing wasn't snaking, because it looks like they're spasming on the track.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand what snaking is, where you drift back and forth really quick to do the little boost so you go faster that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hard to do, you have to have the right cart for it, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do it, but the thing is, they used to do that actually in, remember back in F-Zero GX, except that was done differently, that was with the break boosting or whatever, and you can do that with Mario Kart Double Dash, you can do it with the drifts the same way, but this is something different though, and I don't know why, because when I've seen these players...
[SPEAKER_02]: Is anyone there really gay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm ignorant and gullible so I usually can't tell if you guys are joking or not
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura has a husband, so obviously she is, you know, dansexual, I believe, as she calls it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dansexual.
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki has a fianc and does not like any of the cock, as far as I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not that he has a problem with that.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's completely straight, yes?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: I am gay.
[SPEAKER_22]: I am literally gay, and it's fine.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's not a joke.
[SPEAKER_22]: We joke about it because, you know, it's kind of like how, you know, gay people can call each other fag and that's okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just like how black people always call... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_22]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, I'm gay and so is Xtifer, but we are not together.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's a very common misconception I think people think because Xtifer and I live together and we're both gay, we must be fucking, but that's not true.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, Xtifer and I are just buds, we're like brothers, nothing like that.
[SPEAKER_22]: However, I date, I've been seeing someone, and I've kind of brought that up a couple times on the show, but...
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think he'd be used to the idea of me talking about him on the air yet, and he could be listening, so I don't say a whole lot about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But he's cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's a gamer, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: He plays Mario Kart DS with me, so he rocks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who else?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think he's cute, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: He is cute.
[SPEAKER_22]: He is a cutie.
[SPEAKER_22]: A little quiet sometimes, but a cutie, I like him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though the one time I met him, I was highly intoxicated.
[SPEAKER_22]: You were very intoxicated, but he's a nice guy.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I don't think Miklatov would mind me sharing that he's gay, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that's cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, yes, there are really gay people that do this.
[SPEAKER_22]: But we don't talk a whole lot about... Well, we do talk about the sexuality thing, and I think it might be hard to tell that we're joking sometimes.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_22]: Not just her, but other girl presenters on podcasts, game podcasts, get targeted.
[SPEAKER_22]: They do.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because some guys don't know how to deal with that.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_22]: They assume that she's a giggling girl.
[SPEAKER_22]: To quote one site, put down the controller and get back in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excuse me, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, that's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, okay, he's got too many questions, so I'm jumping right to his last question.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why did you say I used the decal generator?
[SPEAKER_22]: I made my Firefox decal myself.
[SPEAKER_22]: Took two hours.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry, I made an assumption.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shoot me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to make a penis decal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to play the game just to do that.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like in our chat room there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm just now reading all the chat room is that everybody is like gasping and saying that they're so surprised at the fact that I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Zaku says that Sky can't say nigga.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just saw him.
[SPEAKER_22]: Man, I screwed up.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then, of course, my favorite term ever, gamer.
[SPEAKER_22]: Color of Sakura says I'm a gamer with a G-A-Y capital.
[SPEAKER_22]: Get it, gamer?
[SPEAKER_22]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Color of Sakura wants to know, any suggestions on what 2DX song track I should buy?
[SPEAKER_22]: I have 2DX Red and Happy Sky, so other than those two.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love, love, love Fifth Style.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love Fifth Style's soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I suggest that.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you're going to go old school, go for Fifth Style.
[SPEAKER_22]: I used to wake up to that every morning.
[SPEAKER_22]: Eight.
[SPEAKER_21]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_22]: NeoDude0 says, what good dance pads are there besides Red Octane that don't cost $500?
[SPEAKER_22]: There's the kind you build yourself.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's the one that DDR Game puts out, but I'm going to be honest, we played it at E3, not impressed by their product.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it injured.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's right, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, so honestly, I suppose if you want something that is cheap and effective and you don't play a lot of katas, just go for the $20 Madcatz ones.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know a lot of people knock on the Mad Catz ones, but honestly, for the casual DDR player, it'll work.
[SPEAKER_22]: It'll get you through the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or if you take a softpad and you mount it on a wood, and you do the... That's a good idea, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, just basically mounting something on a board makes a softpad even better.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if she came up again here, but she used to have that at her old apartment.
[SPEAKER_22]: They worked very, very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was the first 9-footer I ever passed was on those.
[SPEAKER_22]: Me too, I think.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, second 9-footer I ever did was on those.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I passed Electro-Tuned.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it wasn't Electro-Tuned.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Lupin.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hypnotic Crisis?
[SPEAKER_08]: Lupin.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that was right before I passed Lupin because I had actually passed Hypnotic Crisis before.
[SPEAKER_08]: I let you change with my second one.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was Orion 7-8.
[SPEAKER_22]: I remember I did this at her place.
[SPEAKER_22]: I slowed it down and I listened.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because you remember how Orion 7-8 has this very distinct pattern.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you remember back when you had a Bomani party and stuff and we debuted Kakumei on the sim because the game hadn't even come out yet but the sim file for the test location came out?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_22]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was so stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: But good.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, it was good.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it was so easy.
[SPEAKER_22]: I miss Bomani parties.
[SPEAKER_22]: We need to have another one.
[SPEAKER_22]: We do.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's just get drunk and call it a Bomani party.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think once I get my house in order, I'm planning on having one.
[SPEAKER_22]: Badass.
[SPEAKER_22]: If Dan doesn't like it.
[SPEAKER_22]: We should broadcast live from it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would rock.
[SPEAKER_22]: Legend of Zaku says, how come game chain stores and some small time mom and pop stores treat new sealed games like beater copies when trying to get money for them?
[SPEAKER_22]: because they assume you stole them.
[SPEAKER_22]: Honestly, I think that's why a lot of people have policies against sealed games is because it's assumed that they're stolen.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I know what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know you didn't steal them.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know you're trying to sell back promo copies, but you're not supposed to sell back promo copies either.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's actually...
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know so much about giveaways.
[SPEAKER_22]: Giveaways is kind of a gray area, but at least promo copies.
[SPEAKER_22]: Usually when they do giveaways, they give away promo copies and it's part of the deal with promo copies.
[SPEAKER_22]: You're not supposed to sell them.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's why with motion pictures and stuff, big deal.
[SPEAKER_22]: They put the tracking numbers on the screeners and all that shit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: What can I use to convert WMV3 encoded media to anything that isn't WMV3?
[SPEAKER_22]: AVI, MPEG, DivX, etc.
[SPEAKER_22]: on a PC.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know enough about video encoding, I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_22]: Google and look it up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or VCD Helper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I haven't heard of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a website.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have tutorials for converting everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this is Windows Media file.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm guessing probably Windows Media.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe a program like TMG Encoder or whatever.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm hoping someone in our chat knows.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just had a link posted to JetAudio.com.
[SPEAKER_22]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_22]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, kids, it's about 9.30.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's about time for us to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I appreciate you guys participating tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry we didn't get to all the questions.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it was a very popular segment.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry about Skype, you guys.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: I will reinstall Skype so we have it again.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's the show.
[SPEAKER_22]: And thanks to Miklatov and Ekstafor for being here in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_22]: But otherwise, for just the three of us and no Skype, not too bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: So good job.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_22]: And final thought time.
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going into Mario Kart Online right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to play me, that's where I'll be.
[SPEAKER_22]: My final thought is Loki should be preparing for the podcast.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've already done that.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Reject false icons and thanks to everyone who sent me those emails with the Wellicious.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, that's sweet.
[SPEAKER_22]: Our listeners rock, don't they?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Love you guys!
[SPEAKER_22]: and we just love it if you guys would help us out and don't forget in your live 365 player vote us a 5 as well I really appreciate the help you guys and that's it until next week this is Rob and Jamie and Matt saying bye bye
[SPEAKER_18]: More information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_22]: And now back to your regularly scheduled fortune cookie.
[SPEAKER_00]: Soon to be released on world famous Cheese Factory Records.
[SPEAKER_01]: The obnoxious model beating lead vocalist of a certain char-topping heavy metal glam rock band.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sing a medley of all your favorite mid-80s television theme songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Including Small Wonder, Gimme a Break, Silver Spoons, and this irresistible ditty.
[SPEAKER_00]: Available only on World Famous Cheese Factory Records, which is part of Underdog Entertainment, which is part of Columbia Records, which is part of Sony Music International.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you for watching!