[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of November 21st, 2005.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody, once again, welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio To Go, that podcast dedicated to what you gamers really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know, we like to talk about video games that don't suck on this show, although sometimes we will talk about games that do suck, but only to tell you to stay far, far away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Avoid like the plague.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to... Oh, my name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should introduce myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I'll introduce the co-hosts we have over there sitting next to me, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and joining us on Skype line tonight, say hello to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, what happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you catch something from Adam Curry at the podcast awards, or what happened?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I was already sick when I was there, apparently.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a cold, turned into a sinus infection, LA made it worse, and now I have a pretty nasty case of bronchitis.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like God doesn't want you to be on this show or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the hell's going on, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_00]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_00]: Every time this year, I tend to get some type of respiratory illness, but last year I didn't get it, and I think it was just because I lost all that weight the year before, and I
[SPEAKER_00]: This year it's like, hi, you remember me?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's give you pneumonia now.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just a healthy... They x-rayed me for pneumonia.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a healthy LA air.
[SPEAKER_00]: I swear it had to have been that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, real quick, how was the podcast awards?
[SPEAKER_00]: It was... We weren't there for very long.
[SPEAKER_00]: Julie went with me.
[SPEAKER_00]: I said, you know, she helps us out sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, let me real quick, let me say, there are a lot of folks behind the scenes that help us out with a lot of things that sometimes don't get their due credit, especially Jason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, we'd be dead in the water without Jason, so thank you to Jason, and Julie, and Jess over at DDR Freak, and just everybody who helps us out behind the scenes and doesn't get their credit sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Julie kept my road rage down to a minimum on the trip.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which, there was plenty of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was the awards themselves?
[SPEAKER_00]: The ceremony itself, it was sort of like, let's give it everybody on stage, give them their thing, get off.
[SPEAKER_00]: Only the people who win the big prizes get to talk.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I got to see Adam Curry, who looks a lot more handsome now than he did in his MTV days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Met some cool people.
[SPEAKER_00]: I met Frank from The Overnightscape.
[SPEAKER_00]: Haven't had a chance yet to check out his podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, I came back to homework
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I came back to homework and then getting sick again.
[SPEAKER_00]: I went to the doctor soon after I got back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, leading into our next topic, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I imagine you probably haven't gotten a lot of gaming done.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I can say that the last weekend was pretty much taken up by Phantasy Star Online for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was a lot of that going around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are there still a lot of people on there?
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the guy that we stayed with, he was busy playing that, and then Julie was showing him Blueburst, so we had some Blueburst going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I was kind of glad I didn't uninstall it off my laptop, because they used that version.
[SPEAKER_00]: And actually, the theme for my house has been Need for Speed Underground Most Wanted, which...
[SPEAKER_00]: Looks kind of pretty.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm reserving my judgment for the Xbox 360 version when it's out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, right now, it just looks kind of... It's got lots of prettiness going on and lots of destructiveness going on, but I've kind of had my fill of watching that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, the 360 version is only a port, so it's only a little bit better, and I hear that they've got some really bad loading, like, choppiness in it, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: Like I said, I'm going to reserve my judgment for actually seeing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so is that all you pretty much have for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've had this copy of Mario Kart DS sitting on my computer desk now for a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to open that thing soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, no, it's open.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's sitting there.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just hasn't been in my DS yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get some use out of that this Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: My week was filled with Shadow Colossus, which is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Haven't really got any.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haven't you beaten that yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I haven't really been playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mainly Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been pounding out trying to get Rob unlocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to beat the entire game for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not me, Rob, but Rob the Robot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob the Robot, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's pretty cool, and the online stuff's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does take a little time to get
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: You're still convinced you're getting it Tuesday, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if I'm getting it Tuesday, but I know I'm not getting it after Christmas, like they say.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't believe that they're going to be that long.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the big deal if you hype this system up as the big thing for Christmas and you don't ship anymore?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: We're getting one.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, you have that lucky thing of being very close with a GameStop employee that can manage to get you one, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I had something else about my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_00]: My extreme amounts of giddiness after finding out that Kingdom Hearts 2 is having a Tron thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked about that briefly on last week's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes me all kinds of happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the new trailers show Steamboat Willie is going to be another level that's in that, as well as Lilo and Stitch.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep, I saw that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I knew that because they had it at the E3 demo.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've got Stitch there.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I also played a good bit of it at E3, too, because I have all my pictures up.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game just looks sexy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's out on Japanese sites.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's the...
[SPEAKER_04]: the demo reel for Final Fantasy 12 which is looking pretty hot some folks here have that now because Dragon Quest 8 I haven't gotten to check it out myself yet but I've heard it's pretty darn good too bad the game might be getting delayed again you know that's a rumor going around right now that the game's getting delayed again not surprising they said for sure March 2006 in Japan but now they're saying maybe not we'll see well
[SPEAKER_00]: The thing about the Final Fantasy games I've noticed though is that the US versions are almost always worth waiting for because they add more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then it gets re-released as an international version and blah blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I'm kind of waiting for, you know, and this is really, every time I see Kingdom Hearts 2, I keep thinking, you know, back to Super Mario RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was one of the coolest things where you have Square teaming up with Nintendo to make a really kick-ass RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really need to do that again, just with all their franchises, kind of make a new RPG and make it really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Paper Mario is no excuse for an RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is not a sequel to the Super Mario RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a poor excuse, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, that's what I'm waiting for.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll keep waiting, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: We need Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: Final Fantasy Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys have some crazy combinations.
[SPEAKER_04]: We already got Urgot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, no, that's just Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_00]: We need full-on Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: style with different lock and line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rydia.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, I also have been playing an awful lot of Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really is that good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been into a Mario Kart game probably since maybe the 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really so much though, the Super Nintendo one is really where the old schoolness is at.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I love this new one for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, for some reason the GameCube one, the formula was just off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't care for the GameCube one.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Boy One that they had previous, it wasn't the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what to say, but it wasn't the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this one is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It controls pretty good considering it's got the D-pad and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game runs great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very simple engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It plays much like it was the old Super Nintendo One, and I love that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the fact that they included the retro tracks.
[SPEAKER_04]: The wireless features are great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the fact that it goes online...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: We're hearing, at least we kind of got word this week, that Nintendo is banning you from sharing your friend code on their forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not allowed on Nintendo's forums to actually share your own friend code.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think the reason why they're trying to do that is they're wanting to make sure that people on your friends list are actually your friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not that they could stop me from posting on another forum, but I think that's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are really, really being careful with this online stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, they don't want to have that story in the news about, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Little Girl meets Old Pervert on Nintendo Game and on Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I was going to say, well, in Mario Kart, they can't really communicate anyway, so it's like retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I thought was weird, because you can't really communicate in Mario Kart anyway, which is kind of one of its downfalls, is that you can't do anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't use the microphone to chat, you can't write, talk, or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, that would be so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll see that front end for the Wi-Fi be a little better.
[SPEAKER_05]: My peeve with that game is the whole battle mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get it at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love the battle mode in the Super Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the battle mode in the Nintendo 64 game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just... I didn't get it with GameCube.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their battle mode was crap because their arenas were crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't even think the Game Boy Advance version had battle mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, this one's pretty cool, I just don't get how they blow up the other balloons.
[SPEAKER_04]: My other minor minor bitch besides that would be maybe some of the other mechanics in the actual racing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does seem like it favors, and I know that Mario Kart is supposed to do this, where like if you're in last place you get the really good items, and when you're in first place you get the not so great items.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems to really favor...
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, last place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, over first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, almost too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's kind of skewed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, though, that's a real minor, minor complaint.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still highly, highly recommend Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a great title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially if you've loved any of the other Mario Kart titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I give it my highest recommendation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, what I got to play this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, Orange Lines Radio started all about music video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, of course, I have to check out all the new ones when they come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: My only...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a solid game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do recommend it for fans of DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: For people that are just getting into it, I can only give it about a borderline recommendation because I think DDR Ultramix 2 was better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the formula for how they were picking the songs was better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's kind of one of those things where it's like, if it ain't broke, don't fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Konami kind of really went crazy with some of their song picks.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have some like
[SPEAKER_04]: Stuff that sounds like... I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to do homages to these bands, but does that mean that they're good stuff to dance to?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I think they made some really odd picks, like Ray Charles and The Clash and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, although those are great songs, I don't think they make for good DDR songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that kind of ruins the game for me in that aspect.
[SPEAKER_04]: And plus, just the fact that the song packs that you bought on Ultramix 2 do not function correctly, not all the songs work right...
[SPEAKER_04]: Ultramix 3
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, let's get to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll go ahead and let DarkSakura start off.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, we love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I understand you got some news about the next creation of Katamari.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, it's called Me and My Katamari.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that's a cute name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Looking at the pictures that are online right now, the game looks actually very fabulous.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it looks top-notch for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, the control, from what I understand, though, is supposed to be pretty much crappy.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I can understand that without having both analog on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, imagine you're going from a game where basically you've got two-handed control to trying to control it with one hand.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: So are they going to do it with the one analog and the buttons, or what are they going to do?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've seen too much into it.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, there are some good features that I think might make up for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_00]: Wireless play for up to four people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've got the prince and the cousins.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's old and new.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've got customization options, more masks, more headgear, the ability to wear them various places.
[SPEAKER_00]: A new island interface that highlights players, your options and different stages represented by animals, needs, and new homes.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually, the information for it is up at katamari.namco.com Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: But there's also photos up on this, actually quite a number of photos at worthplaying.com
[SPEAKER_00]: Which actually was, this particular link was also emailed to us by one of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thank you, listener, for sharing the alias developments on me and my Kamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me and my Katamari, now we know what they're officially going to call it here in the U.S., because previously we just knew My My Katamari was like the Japanese translation, so it's kind of nice to hear that it's going to have a name here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: that actually makes a little more sense, so that's nice to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, moving on, I got another story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, and this has to do with, um, World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, as you know, um, it's released into other countries now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just recently went over into, uh, Asia, other parts of there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, what's interesting, the game rolled out in China not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unfortunately, they've had a bit of an incident there.
[SPEAKER_04]: A 13-year-old Chinese boy actually jumped to their death from a 24-story building from playing too much World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, that's not the new thing, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That happened after it rolled out last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: That actually happened last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the new part.
[SPEAKER_04]: The parents of the boy are now suing Blizzard, saying they actually got a lawyer and, quote, internet game addiction researcher.
[SPEAKER_04]: and they are filing the suits upon the whole game industry on behalf of parents.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: The question is, how liable should game companies be when their kids OD on the gaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does World of Warcraft feature jumping out of buildings?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that's what they're saying so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is how it forced some kid to jump out of a building?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because he was addicted to a game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I don't see how that works.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I'm addicted to alcohol, I don't jump out of a window.
[SPEAKER_05]: I go drink more alcohol.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, just kind of, I don't know, it's too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's interesting to hear that the lawsuit crazy stuff doesn't just happen in the US, because that story is coming out of China.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, go figure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you got something for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Those crazy Chinese and their games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're always killing somebody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you have something related to that?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sort of, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this year's Spike Awards, or their video game awards, the results have been posted because we like to spoil everybody's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Game of the Year, Resident Evil 4 Best Action Game, God of War
[SPEAKER_05]: No surprise there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, best sports title, of course, Tony Hawk's American Wasteland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and then they have some really strange stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best cyber vixen of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, some chick from 007 from Russia with Love.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, one that I thought was pretty cool, um, was best, um, soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they have Guitar Hero as best soundtrack, but best original score, We Love Katamari, which is really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um,
[SPEAKER_05]: What's kind of interesting is they have a whole bunch of games winning awards that aren't even out yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Peter Jackson's King Kong, the official game of the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did it win?
[SPEAKER_05]: It won, let's see here, Best Performance by a Human Male, Debbie Jack Black in Peter Jackson's King Kong.
[SPEAKER_05]: It also won, let's see here, Best Cast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best handheld game, Luminous
[SPEAKER_04]: which I thought was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well deserved.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Resident Evil 4 being the game of the year there, I think I could see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it may not be my favorite game this year, but damn, it was a real sharp looking game, really innovated and just the graphics were amazing and I could see Resident Evil 4 walking away with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes more sense to me than some of the other awards that I see shows give for game of the year sometimes, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What were some of the other nominees?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they list the nominees?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I forget.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who were the other nominees for Game of the Year?
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have some other Best Supporting Male Performance, Christopher Walken in True Crime, New York City.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, also Best Supporting Female Performance, also won by Tracy Lourdes in True Crime, New York City.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, what were the other nominees for Game of the Year?
[SPEAKER_05]: Game of the Year, the other nominees, we had God of War, definitely deserving.
[SPEAKER_05]: Call of Duty 2, also a very deserving game.
[SPEAKER_05]: World of Warcraft, also very deserving.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Fear.
[SPEAKER_05]: All very good games.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I'm kind of surprised World of Warcraft didn't walk away with it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just with all the people that are just sickly obsessed with that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Resident Evil 4, I'm not going to say that I necessarily think World of Warcraft is a better game, but Resident Evil 4, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a pretty solid list.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got a good list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot better than, say, GeForce.
[SPEAKER_00]: I disagree with Resident Evil 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you have put?
[SPEAKER_00]: I honestly would have gone with World of Warcraft or God of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why were you not so big on Resident Evil 4?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, if you've followed the series, it's actually such a departure from the rest of the series that, I don't know, as a game it was great, but it wasn't Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if they'd called it something else, would you have been okay with it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_00]: It would have been like, hi, we're pretending to be a zombie game without zombies, then yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you heard me talking earlier in the show about DDR Ultramix 3, which was released last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the biggest gambles that Konami took was in shaking up the song list with a variety and eclectic mix of music, everything from rap to rock to synth to classic Spanish music.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't neglect some of the things that worked for them in last year's DDR Ultramix 2, however.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the songs in DDR Ultramix 2 that got a great reception from the fans was In My Eyes, as remixed by Midihead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Midihead is back in this year's DDR Ultramix 3,
[SPEAKER_04]: I am sorry, I'm so sorry, it was a...
[SPEAKER_04]: Downing some Pepsi One at the moment Suddenly I thought I was reintroducing DarkSakura Because that's usually how she introduces herself Oh no, you mean this has already been done?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you two are going to have to have a contest someday I don't know what's up with that Oh jeez Alright, well, first thing I want to know about You know, your song in Ultramix 2 was so well received by the fans How long did it take Konami to say Hey, we've got to bring him back for Ultramix 3 It took him a couple of months to see the light, man
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a couple of months.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that's one of the reasons why you got brought back is because the fans, do you think they noticed that, that the fans had such a great feedback to the last time?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was all the fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they would have called me back if the fans hadn't demanded the MIDI head.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great to go from one song to three songs that you contributed to.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, now next time, now this is a total secret, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next time, this is for your listeners only.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the next game, it's going to be MidiHeads Dance Dance Revolution Ultra Mix 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be Dance Dance Revolution MidiHeads Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would rather dance to a mix made up completely of MidiHeads songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you what, some of the songs they picked for this last mix, because they picked some really weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're making me blush.
[SPEAKER_04]: This time, one of your original songs, because most people know you for your remixes, but now one of your original tracks, Raise Your Hands, actually shows up in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you get to suggest this, or did Konami actually listen to your album and pick something, or how did that happen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, I just sent them a CD full of stuff after I did the In My Eyes remix.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I said, you know, guys, I also have
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of my own music.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so they were surprised to get it and listen to it and actually hear that I have some talent in me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they decided that that was the song that was going in the next game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It works really well for the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you've had a chance to see it in the game yet, but the cut and everything works really well, and the video's kind of cool, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it should, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do crunches and sit-ups to that thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I don't think they put you in the video.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they hired some dancers to be in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm a little too overweight for their taste.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So are most of the people playing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to get the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is what's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've done all this work for Konami, and I have yet to get the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They haven't hooked me up with the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't sent you a copy of the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to make me go out and buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know people from Konami listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami, send him the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: He earned it.
[SPEAKER_04]: People.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, I need an Xbox, too, then, at that time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they should send you all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, well, here's another thing I'm curious about is that, okay, your music did so well that you're in DR Ultramix 3 three times.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know if you know about this yet, but did you know that one of your songs is crossing over into a game that Konami is putting out in Japan?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my goodness!
[SPEAKER_02]: You're kidding me!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I would hope... I knew, I knew, I knew.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, I hope you got paid for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys announced it on your website.
[SPEAKER_04]: David Hasselhoff
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be the next David Hasselhoff of Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did that happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they tell you they were interested in doing this?
[SPEAKER_04]: How did that all go down?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they don't tell me anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you kidding me?
[SPEAKER_02]: They just do what they want.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've paid me and done away with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have full right to circulate that as they please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, a lot of the fans were saying that you should be in Beatmania as well, and now that's happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, they're definitely listening to the fans over on some of the boards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think that's one thing I've got to give to Konami Hawaii is the fact that they do listen to their fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is to be well-respected.
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't happen a lot in this industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: So kudos to Konami for actually reading and getting a pulse for what's going on on the message boards out there and giving us what we want, usually.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're lucky enough to actually have a copy of Jelly Kiss Midi Head Smack Mix, so we're going to go ahead and play it for you guys right now.
I'll keep my voice alive
My boy, I just gotta let you know that I know that I'm not gonna die
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that was Midihead's smack mix of Jelly Kiss here on Orange Lounge Radio To Go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're joined still with the remixer himself, Midihead.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little later in the program, we'll be bringing you one of his original tunes from DDR Ultramix 3, Raise Your Hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to check out more information on Midihead's music, check out his website, www.midihead.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not meaty head.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, not meaty head or...
[SPEAKER_04]: One other thing you've actually been doing on MidiHead.com, you actually, for the past couple months, you put out a couple podcasts of your own that were available on your website, and they were kind of teasing Dance Dance Revolution, Ultra Mix 3, and kind of playing, hey, here's some of my songs that are going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's some of the other artists that are going to be in the game, kind of teasing us with what was going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to continue to do this, even though the game's out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you thinking that podcasting is something you want to keep doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, to be quite honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a lot of time, as you know, to put those things together.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I continue to get...
[SPEAKER_02]: The feedback that I've been getting from all the fans, then I don't really see any reason to discontinue it.
[SPEAKER_02]: After all, we've got to give them what they want, right, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to make those fans happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, one thing I think they'd want is to keep knowing what's going on in the world of Konami with all their games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think Konami would be good to you and let you be their voice?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, it's one of those concepts that certainly we're trying out right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I can't tell you how much dialogue I've had with Konami about it, but it's gone all the way up to corporate and we've discussed the benefits of having an artist kind of mingle a little bit more with the fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: So in this form, it seems to be doing just fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just need to find the time to do more podcasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if I continue doing them at the rate that I've been doing them, which is like every other month, it won't burn people out, and it won't burn me out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck to you in whatever you decide to do with future podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you know I've got to ask you this, because we're a video gaming-related show, and I know you said earlier in the program you haven't gotten a chance to play DDR Ultimate 3 yet, but I'm curious, are there any other video games that you're into?
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of video games do you like to play?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I gotta say I have this really sick habit of firing up Urban Terror.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know I've mentioned that before.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Quake 3 mod.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I play it a little more than I really should.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you looking forward to Quake 4?
[SPEAKER_02]: Quake 4?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Rob, I have to say that although I used to play a lot more video games in my time, I don't find a lot of time to dive into...
[SPEAKER_02]: as much first-person shooterism as I'd like to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's good, though, to remind our listeners that there is a real world out there outside of video games that sometimes involves work, working two or three jobs, kids and life and house and payments, and I think I've pretty much summed it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy youth while it lasts, kiddies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, you bet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You better enjoy youth while it lasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that one spawned off of the remix of In My Eyes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spawned off a phone call and there I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I just tell him this exciting story about how I was laying dying in my
[SPEAKER_02]: Hospital bed after knee surgery and they cut a main artery and I was bleeding to death and overcame D.M.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ashera.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it D.M.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ashera?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he's the one that actually contacted you behind this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know much about the game, so we're trying to figure out little bits and pieces wherever we can.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if hospital bed, leg amputee, be it, then that's all we know so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was getting out of control now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, back to a more serious story.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet probably a year and a half ago you probably didn't think that you would be so involved with video games as you are now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that true?
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course I knew I was going to be involved in video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you kidding me?
[SPEAKER_02]: I paint my entire destiny for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I actually...
[SPEAKER_02]: Video games was something that I had planned on doing eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just didn't know when it was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything I do in my musical avenues, I always try to leave as many doors open when I'm doing stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: So do you have future plans to continue working with video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if the money's there, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you kidding me?
[SPEAKER_04]: That sums it up, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll go where the money's at, won't we?
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta pay for my house, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I live in Southern California.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, Middyhead, that's about all the time we have, but thanks so much for being on the show today.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, guys, check it out, www.mittyhead.com if you're interested in Middyhead and he's got his own music there that you can download and the forums and his podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just an action-packed site, so check it out, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks so much, Middyhead, for being on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you're welcome, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yay, Middyhead!
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a rumor that's out right now is that a Zelda movie is on the way out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about this, but this came out of Club Nintendo, which is a Mexican publication that's very similar to Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was...
[SPEAKER_04]: Reggie Phil's Aim was the guy at Nintendo that actually talked to this magazine about it, saying that they want to do Metroid, and then Zelda would be next in line.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the weird thing about this is that I thought that John Woo got the rights to Metroid, but this is indicating that Nintendo actually somehow bought this back, and I didn't know that that had happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't trust it unless it's official Nintendo
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, because the games are so freaking phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, Metroid's great too, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zelda seems like one of those things where it's already a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't need another movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: If they did, they would have to do it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would hope they would.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you had another story for us about one of the Xbox 360 launch games might be kind of buggy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on with this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, Rare has stated that they took a very big risk with Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_00]: so that it would be released on launch day.
[SPEAKER_00]: They said typically it goes through a certification process to finish it up and then it's released to be manufactured, but they've gone ahead and released it to manufacturing without it going through their certification process.
[SPEAKER_00]: They actually said they gave the go-ahead five days before the game certification.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if their certification doesn't pass, it's actually quoted here that they would have hundreds of thousands of discs on their hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a huge risk because that's a big penalty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know Microsoft is huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the game companies really are is huge on those.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, everything's got to be right and certified.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a huge risk you're taking there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess Rare kind of working directly with Microsoft can get away with it a little more.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope the game makes it or we're all in trouble.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's also stated on there, though, that Rare puts a lot of work into polishing the game, so they're sure that it's going to be okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they've produced 700,000 copies for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that every person who has an Xbox 360 will also have that title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now we know how many are coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's their estimate.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the estimate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I would think that they would know what they're talking about as soon as they have to communicate directly with Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, wait, Microsoft, you said that we're only getting... But that doesn't mean we're getting 700,000 of them on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: That just means they're making 700,000 of them for the first run.
[SPEAKER_04]: First run, first launch.
[SPEAKER_00]: That also, though, explains why the game hasn't been available for review by some place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of which, by the way, not only that, we've got more problems with Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was supposed to be out on Friday, but apparently they're having trouble getting it to the United States because it has to ship from China now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're running way behind schedule to delay it to launch day instead of before launch day, which was interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're not even sure if it's going to be there on launch day either.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's probably why you can't find it in stores right now either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, if anything, then if it's having to go from...
[SPEAKER_00]: Joanna Dark does not feature jumping.
[SPEAKER_05]: She cannot jump.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, what good is she then?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, as long as she's got boobs.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of the Xbox 360, now, the other week we were talking about the backwards compatibility and how there's like 200 games that are going to be backwards compatible here in the U.S., and people are saying, that's not enough, that's not enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what, kids?
[SPEAKER_04]: Be thankful you don't live in Japan, because guess how many games are going to be backwards compatible at launch in Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: 12.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it, 12.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they promised they'll be adding more and more, but all you're getting the first run through is 12.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now granted, these are probably some of the biggest games, Halo, Halo 2, Ninja Gaiden, Rainbow Six, Crimson Skies, Fable, and then of course, Simpsons Hit and Run is just randomly in there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_05]: and they have a ton of stuff out there going to be available for you to download.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they've actually released what they're going to be releasing initially.
[SPEAKER_05]: For old retro games, they've got Gauntlet, Robotron, as well as Joust, which will be really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Smash TV, which I thought was really neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then, of course, my favorite, which is going to be...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hectix, Bejeweled 2
[SPEAKER_05]: and then, of course, my favorite, Geometry Wars Retro Evolved, which seems to be everybody's favorite out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are going to be available.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most of the games are actually going to be available for either $5 to $10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Geometry Wars and some of the better ones are actually going to be $5.
[SPEAKER_05]: A few of them are going to be $10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some Billiards game is $15 for download.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, it's a top-shelf game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all about Smash TV, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Smash TV, though, I think that was one of the ones that's $5, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has the best quotes in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But considering you can buy it as part of a $20 pack with 20 games, it's really only worth a dollar.
[SPEAKER_00]: Considering I already owe three copies of it and the meme, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the cool thing, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least they do have free demos you can try out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can try these games before you buy them.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have free demos for other games, like Need for Speed and Most Wanted are going to be on there, as well as some of the other EA games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, more gamer tags you can purchase and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of ways to waste your money.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: We are all about wasting time and money.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't want to waste all your money on video games, though, because, you know, if you spent all your days playing video games, you'd have no time to go out and spend your money on strippers, like Loki did this past week, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, anyway, so here to always remind us that there is a real life outside of gaming is the one and only DarkSakura, and it's been a couple weeks since she's been able to give you a piece of her advice, so here it is, DarkSakura's advice column, and DarkSakura, what are you going to be talking to us about tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Today's bit of advice is how to leap from a motorcycle to a car.
1.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make sure the vehicles are moving at the same speed.
2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait for a long straight section of road before positioning the vehicles as close as possible to each other.
[SPEAKER_00]: You will be on the passenger side of the car, so you will be very close to the edge of the roadway.
3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Crouch with both of your feet on the running board or the seat and hold the throttle until the last instant.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember, as soon as you release the throttle, the bike speed will decrease.
4.
[SPEAKER_00]: If the car has an inside handle above the door, grab it.
[SPEAKER_00]: If not, simply time the leap so your torso lands in the car.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you miss the window, tuck and roll away from the vehicles.
5.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have the driver swerve away from the bike as soon as you re inside.
[SPEAKER_00]: The bike may slip under the rear passenger side wheel of the car.
[SPEAKER_00]: But my final piece of advice?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't try jumping into a car while it's moving.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or at least tell the guy to stop.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just shoot him first.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why you shoot the tires and then throw the guy out of the car and then drive off somewhere where you can change the tire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's much easier.
[SPEAKER_00]: Much easier.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the love of God, don't tell him you saw it in a video game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, don't tell... No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tell them that you saw it on the edited GTA 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of which, Pursuit Force is available for purchase for the PSP coming this spring.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't want to say the words Jack Thompson, but what you said kind of made me think of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard he got, like, booted off that case in Alabama or something, and the judge yelled at him or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might be kind of... He didn't get booted.
[SPEAKER_04]: He quit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not what I read.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's a big loser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'm just amused by his Amazon rating.
[SPEAKER_00]: What is it, 37,000 on Amazon's list?
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't give him a free plug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, speaking of which, people that like the Jack Thompson book also recommend gay porno books as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Really.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an insult.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just making fun of him because he's a loser.
[SPEAKER_00]: He does nothing but embarrass himself, so I think he's a good point of humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gay pornography can at least be artistic sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jack Thompson's work, never artistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about The Matrix Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, this was a game you played for about, what, three days?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought this game was shut down!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's saying that the Matrix Online is still going.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did a server consolidation, I think, but they didn't shut it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, they are doing another update, it's update number 38, and they're going to be doing in-game advertising, courtesy of Massive.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be doing the in-game advertising using the billboards.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kind of already do some real world product advertising, but now they're going to do stuff, you know, that's bought advertising because the advertising they had before was for like, let's say the clothing was used in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'd give that clothing company free advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now they're going to do, I guess, selling for the advertising, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that those ads will be refreshing and updating with pretty good frequency in the game there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kind of surprised that the game still has such a large following.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seeing as they killed off all the characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't want to bash on Matrix Online, because it seemed alright, and I can see where people get into it, because it does continue the Matrix story, but I don't know, it doesn't have that same play me, play me, over and over again like some of the other MMOs do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoy the Matrix games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ragnarok Online!
[SPEAKER_04]: Not just Ragnarok, but Final Fantasy, Warcraft, hell anything!
[SPEAKER_00]: For all those people who are willing to play the sort of mindless rounds of PSO, and yes, I was one of them.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has its addictions.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you have considering release dates in the UK?
[SPEAKER_00]: I have quite a few.
[SPEAKER_00]: What we're looking at so far, we have Call of Cthulhu, Dark Corners of the Earth, which I'm interested in.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bubble Bobble Revolution on the DS Crash Tag Team Racing for the PSP Is this all this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: The 25th Dr. Mario and Puzzle League on the GBA Dragon Ball Z Super Sonic Warriors 2 Gun Kirby Canvas Curse on the DS Mario Kart DS also on the 25th Need for Speed Most Wanted Pro Evolution Soccer 5 Psychonauts Rugby Challenge 2006
[SPEAKER_00]: Sega Classics Collection, Ski Racing 2006, Tales of Eternia, The Incredibles Rise of the Underminer, and Touch Golf.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also to be announced, we have Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire, and Pac-Man World 3, a few other things coming out, Snowboard Kids DS, those are all scheduled to be out sometime this month, we just don't have a date on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That for our friends over in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here in the US, I don't have a calendar in front of me for the US, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything's all about the 360 this next week, and that's what a lot of people have been talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's been a lot of great games released for other systems here this past week, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we had Mario Kart DS, we had the Ultramix, we had Call of Duty on other systems as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Duty, Big Red One, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just lots of games coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week was, or last week I should say, was one of the biggest launch weeks of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It always is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait, this is the Big Red One?
[SPEAKER_00]: I need somebody who was in that.
[SPEAKER_00]: PSP Advanced
[SPEAKER_05]: but for the PSP so it allows you to put on video and mp3s and stuff very simple like and you can also play a lot of different formats that you couldn't play before like DivX files and whatnot and basically this program goes on your PSP runs on homebrew so it's you know made by an actual you know commercial company that's you know doing this and what's really cool is they were talking about selling it at first but they've decided to go ahead and release a
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, that's really neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other thing which, of course, I'm excited about because, you know, Orange Laundry is all about the Bomani games is PSP Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to go over to our mailbag because it's been a little while since... Well, actually, I snuck into the mailbag when you weren't here last week, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you don't mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I snuck in there and stole some letters.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're allowed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, but DarkSakura is going to read us some letters that are in our mailbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to send us an email, it's togo, T-O-G-O, at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send your letters.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do we have this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: My email I'd like to read is from our good buddy, Asian Buddy Paul.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I couldn't get the article to pull up because it says you have to be a member of that site, and I was like, meh.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I'll go ahead and read the email.
[SPEAKER_00]: It said, hey LLR, I just encountered an article talking about current developments on educational video games and how professors are continuing to take them seriously as fundamental learning tools.
[SPEAKER_00]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_00]: Will we see real great educational and fun video games popping up in schools in several years?
[SPEAKER_00]: Not just like the classics in elementary school like Word Muncher, but like some similar ones to the ones stated in the article.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, I couldn't get the article to pull up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe games that teach English to non-native speakers or foreign languages.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just sort of skipping around now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Japanese, French, Spanish, Chinese, to name a few.
[SPEAKER_00]: As for real life scenario games involving ethics in real life situations like firing someone in tough decisions, I'm slightly skeptical, but I could see them put into intriguing action adventure games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sex Education the Video Game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, just asking what you guys think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of surprised that this is news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I kind of thought we were using computers and games for education type scenarios for a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: In my profession, actually, I'm not sure, you know, my day job, what I do is I actually teach people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a corporate trainer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I like to use computer-based things all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And sometimes that might be a scenario where, you know, they actually choose, like, multiple choice questions that will alter the scenario of events.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't want to give away too much of what it is I do, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: There might be like a multiple choice thing and it changes the events and they watch what happens to their character.
[SPEAKER_04]: In some aspects, and of course, you know, naming back to the classics there, we've all been using that game element in teaching for a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Jeopardy, that's an old classic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I use that for review all the time in my class.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it would help me to know, like, I'm assuming the article is talking a little more about console games and what the rest of us kind of think of as game games.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need a return to Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego Where's Mario?
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of times the games are easy to use for younger people
[SPEAKER_00]: Photoshop 3D
[SPEAKER_04]: A class is only as good as the games that are taught in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got one more quick email for us?
[SPEAKER_00]: One more from Rini.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just to sort of paraphrase a bit, basically stating that one particular reason not everyone should run out to buy a 360 or PS3 or whatever on its launch date is possible problems with faults in the console.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rini,
[SPEAKER_00]: Just stating again, I am reminded of the PS2 launch when the thing erased memory cards and something else.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, we did not encounter this, but then you'd have to go out to your nearest retailer and get an append disc or mentioning of an upgrade station.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another reason is dealing with, I guess, the quality of the systems, holding off for something that might be better down the line, and also wanting to know where the ferrets are.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ferrets were around here somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: They might have died from starvation because you haven't been here, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been there to keep them warm with my love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're still here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's my baby?
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course I say that and my cat looks up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now she's not in here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now she left.
[SPEAKER_00]: She's offended.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, but it depends on how much you use them, too, because you don't game all day long, nor do I.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true, and we hear that they were not good for DVD players, the first few.
[SPEAKER_00]: With any of those systems, especially with the PS2, the more you use it as a dedicated DVD player, the more chance you have of ruining the system itself by that motor drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: My PS2 got it at launch date, and I'm using it as my dedicated DVD player.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perfectly fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you have a satanic curse in your house that keeps that thing running, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've actually known plenty of people who use theirs as their primary DVD player and have had nothing but problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: I use my Xbox as my primary DVD player, but I don't play games on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the Xbox was made quite a bit better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the Xbox was made quite a bit better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And since I paid extra for that DVD kit, you better believe it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, Loki, we're running out of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you got another story for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, we got to still talk about the 360 launch being that it is on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had some craziness on Friday when Circuit City started taking pre-orders for what 360s they were going to have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember what we mentioned last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they're going to sell them in the stores on Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure enough, the day after our podcast rolled out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, that was all a big lie.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Circus City's... So they were being sold on their website.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually did have the units out of the bundle, so that was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you could pre-order the bundle and delete the additional stuff on there, which is also interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that was if you're lucky enough to be able to actually get through.
[SPEAKER_05]: The site was hammered so much it went down as well as their entire technical support line was just jammed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's actually people now camping for their 360 right now, but you can always assure that the celebrities are going to have one.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had an LA launch party for the 360, and Paris Hilton has a bag with the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is so fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think Paris Hilton is going to play on her 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: She doesn't know what a 360 is, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's basically that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then finally, my favorite store in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes me mad that you won't get a 360, but Paris Hilton will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know she's a big gamer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: My personal favorite is the ad for Best Buy showing the 360 and stating that it's the absolute latest in gaming that burns CDs and DVDs too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Best Buy, for lying and not even knowing what the hell you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will not be going to Best Buy to buy anything for my 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just one mistake.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a printing mistake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't blame the whole business.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's not why I'm...
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys are vicious!
[SPEAKER_00]: We sue you!
[SPEAKER_00]: Gotta be vicious to keep up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh man, I hate to be in line with you people on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guess who's not going to be in line?
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, don't rub it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop rubbing it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll come to your house and take it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Real quick mentions.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you pre-order Dirge of Service right now, you can actually get a
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura has our last story tonight regarding gaming in another country We've got one actually published by Eurogamer
[SPEAKER_00]: A group of German politicians proposed a ban on all video games that show lethal violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much simply it?
[SPEAKER_00]: They're actually... It's basically already looking at... I'm trying to find the group that was calling for this.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Christian Social Union saying that killing games have no place in Germany's bedrooms.
[SPEAKER_00]: There already, though, are having some folks against that.
[SPEAKER_04]: If only you people knew what went on in my bedroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: The gaming happens in the living room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I shouldn't have said that on the radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, the head of Germany's Interactive Software Association, Olaf Wolters, basically was quoted in Der Spiegel saying, as far as we're concerned, there are no such things as killer games, but adult games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they're willing to work with the governments to resolve the issue.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's stated also that Germany has some of the strictest censorship laws in the world, but they needed revision, especially after in 2002 a 19-year-old shot and killed 16 people in Erfurt before turning the gun on himself as he was also an avid player of Counter-Strike.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're saying the new legislation, if approved, will go into effect March 2008.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a bunch of crazy people trying to ban things because they can't watch their kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's going to happen, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: The only way we're going to be able to solve violent games in Germany is to make more David Hasselhoff games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew you were going to make a David Hasselhoff joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was trying to think of a good Shiza porn joke, but I want to keep this a family show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know,
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really hard because you know how I feel about this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Parents should be doing their jobs, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: The manufacturer should also be taking responsibility to label their games correctly, yes?
[SPEAKER_00]: But I don't think that the government has any business poking their nose into it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It should be left up to the consumer and up to the manufacturer to keep the consumer informed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially with a statement as subjective as any violent game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that could be anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what's violent?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is Tom and Jerry with a big cartoon hammer, is that violent?
[SPEAKER_00]: You whack-a-mole the game, that's pretty violent.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I hate, I hate, hate, hate, and it's what I hated about the California law.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate these subjective things that leave too much open to interpretation.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, that is going to do it for tonight's program.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, your final thought, and then we're going to say goodbye to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Reject false icons and keep gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we're going to go ahead and click the Hang Up button now, DarkSakura, but thanks so much for sitting with us on Skype tonight, and we'll see you next time, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I'm going to beat this stupid Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to get robbed, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my final thought is Tuesday, when you're all fighting those lines...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be sitting back playing some World of Warcraft and Mario Kart DS and I'll just take my sweet ass time and buying that Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we promised one more Midi Head song tonight before we close out so we're going to leave you guys with this tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is also from DDR Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is another Midi Head track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember to check out his music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to www.midihead.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Raise Your Hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great night everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_01]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next update.