[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of November 14th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody, once again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome to another episode of Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're home from the latest gaming news about video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the news you really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, once in a while, though, we do have to talk about games that do suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: But just to remind you to avoid them.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me tonight, the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, it's me.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, and DarkSakura, as we mentioned last week, she's been representing us at the Podcast Awards this weekend, so she is not able to be here with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'll be back next week for sure, but she did pass along a special message for everyone, and we'll be reading that a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're going to start off tonight's show, and usually we start off with a little bit of How Was Your Gaming Week, but I want to change that a little bit tonight because I want to get this off my chest because I've kind of been thinking about this quite a bit this week, and I think I've decided that
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to get an Xbox 360 on launch day anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I was all hyped up about getting the Xbox 360 the day it was coming out on launch day, and I was ready to fight those lines at Best Buy and Target or wherever I decided to end up going.
[SPEAKER_02]: Toys R Us, which I think will probably be one of the best places.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm just like...
[SPEAKER_02]: After reading about all these horrible, horrible delays and reading about... Now, Loki, didn't your system get delayed, in fact?
[SPEAKER_02]: You were supposed to get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You reserved it months ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I have my theories on this, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's my theory.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before I continue to rant.
[SPEAKER_01]: My theory is that they're not going to be as shorthanded as they think they are.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Microsoft purposefully told them they're getting less than they actually are.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, okay, you pre-ordered 200 for your store.
[SPEAKER_01]: They said, oh, well, you're only going to get 50.
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually ship you 100 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So those people that thought that they weren't going to get them, they got lucky and they got some.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Microsoft looks like the hero now, but still they're still cutting them short and they still sell out and there's still the media hype about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's backfiring because I was interested, but after hearing about all the shortages, I'm like, do I really want to deal with this crap?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do I really want the system that badly at launch?
[SPEAKER_02]: And it kind of made me reevaluate what games are coming out at launch and after playing the kiosk and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not being anti-Microsoft with this statement.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will get an Xbox 360 eventually, but I'm just going, do I really want to buy into this launch hype?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there any game that's coming out on launch day I really, really want?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm thinking to myself, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, there isn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I can wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can wait until January or later.
[SPEAKER_02]: And come to think of it, there's very few systems that I bought on launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last one was the Nintendo DS, but before that, I can't really think of what system I probably bought on launch day.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it can wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I know I've been kind of going back and forth on that for a while, so who knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: I reserve the right to change my mind before...
[SPEAKER_02]: Before the official D-Day in what, like nine days or so?
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it depends on what day you're listening to this podcast, but, you know, we're very little time left.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm just like, you know what, for all that money, especially if they're going to be pushing me to buy, you know, two games out the door and everything, and all this, you know, all this other accessory crap, I'm just like, you know what, man?
[SPEAKER_01]: They may be pushing you, but they're not going to require it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: I have my own qualms with I've read about how they're going to be doing this whole thing at Best Buy and how they like want you to buy all this stuff and they're hoping they spend $600 at their store well the hell with them I had the remember those free Best Buy bucks they had the money for from McDonald's and all that wonderful stuff well I like about $31 of this stuff so I was going to go buy a shot of Colossus there and just say hey okay cool I get the game for like three bucks or whatever
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_01]: You can only use $3 on a game, DVD, or CD.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, where does it say that on this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it doesn't say on this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's on the giant paper.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, what giant paper?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do they want to see the giant paper?
[SPEAKER_01]: It almost made me think I was going to go see The Wizard of Oz or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he wants to see the giant paper?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not the giant paper!
[SPEAKER_01]: No one has to see the giant paper!
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_01]: So I basically went and got a spool of blank DVDs instead and I'm all, is this good enough for ya?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, shit, god.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then I went and spent my money elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I did pick up shallow classes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, don't derail my Xbox 360, dog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I know, that's probably what every gaming podcast is going to talk about this week is Xbox 360, but I'm going to say I'm probably not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've pretty much decided in my mind that my money is better spent on current Xbox, PlayStation 2, and GameCube games, and the 360 thing can wait until January.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have tons of games pre-ordered.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have four games pre-ordered right now with a possible fifth being pre-ordered later this week because I have store credit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm gonna be getting the games.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the system, I have a feeling I'm not gonna be waiting that much longer, even if it is not launch day, which I still think it probably is gonna be launch day.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still gonna get one probably pretty soon, you know, whenever they decide to ship more.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm not really that concerned about, you know, not being, you know, there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't wanna wait in line, you know, in the morning and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: If I...
[SPEAKER_02]: I let some kid who really wants the Xbox 360 for some game they've got to freaking have on the day when, you know what, I'm being nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm stepping aside because you don't want to see me with my claws out in the line waiting to get one of these systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm being nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm stepping aside.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will wait so one of you more eager kids can go get your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I'm doing a nice thing here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, what GameStop told me is I have their pre-ordered mine back in May in order to get one.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's before...
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do want to mention this before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is a little bit of a news story, but it's kind of some late-breaking news that's coming in as we are taping, as we tape on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're getting this story.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually coming off of JoystickWithACue.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're saying that Circuit City is advertising on their website.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can actually see this on their website, CircuitCity.com, that they will be selling 360s on Friday at 2 p.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eastern Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, of course, the initial thought when you see this is, okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: they're gonna sell it on their website and you know you order it on the website and they'll ship it to you by Tuesday or something right so it's not like they're really breaking the launch day but the weird thing is that this article says they actually called the customer service line and they spoke to a customer service rep and they're saying that every physical Circuit City location will be selling the console this Friday at 2 p.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eastern and just to be sure they called back
[SPEAKER_02]: and Double Checked just to make sure that they indeed were selling this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they said, yes, it will be available this Friday at 2 p.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eastern Time online as well as at our stores.
[SPEAKER_02]: So our thought was we'll call our local Circuit City and check, but unfortunately since we taped Sunday night and it's about 8.40 now, we missed the boat because they close at 8, so we didn't get a chance to call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did people still shop at Circuit City?
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought my video card there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still a fine store, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Last thing I bought at Circuit City was your GameCube
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I have a feeling this might change by Monday, Tuesday when you guys are actually hearing this podcast, but this is something that's late-breaking, so keep an eye on CircuitCity.com if you want to try and beat the rush, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, you know, with every gaming site reporting this, who knows, everybody and their sister is probably going to be lining up to get an Xbox 360 on Friday from Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be a lot of interesting phone calls, if it isn't true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's do a little bit of how is your gaming week, what games you've been playing this week, and what you're up to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you mentioned Shadow of the Colossus?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I was playing that today.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've gotten through already six of the Colossuses, and I think
[SPEAKER_01]: The Colossus and The Camera
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the camera does not want to freaking focus on anything correctly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to constantly, you know, control it with the right analog stick while trying to fight this thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's a button to focus in on the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kind of like... It reminds me of Mega Man Legends where you can target stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that works really well.
[SPEAKER_01]: This does not work very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, I get lost quite a bit trying to figure out where the hell I'm supposed to be going in this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's really nothing else, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, it was a really fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it sounds like it's a game you can really get into then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes yelling at the TV makes it a really good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was frustrated.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, you know, because I'm trying to grab a hold of this one part of it, and it keeps grabbing some other part of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm like, son of a bitch, do what I want you to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so, it was kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then, I don't know, I'll probably play through it and be done with it, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm tempted to check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've not been that into Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand why it does so well critically and commercially, but for me personally, it's not really my kind of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I am kind of tempted to check out this PSP one, if for no other reason than I need more games for my PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: The multiplayer is the best part.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_01]: This should have been something that they really had in all of them, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: and just have it online and be able to play that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it'd be really fun, and you can get some really good tournaments and stuff going along.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm hopefully, in the next reiteration of this, which is coming out exclusively on the PS3, we'll have something multiplayer on it, because I think it really needs it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or even two-player co-op would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anything else you've been playing besides those two?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got a lot of stuff lined up for this week, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got Gun and Matrix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Path of Neo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard some good things about that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then there's more stuff coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, or it'll be Need for Speed Most Wanted's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can already tell you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultra Mix 3 is out this week and Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm getting DS'd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh hell yes, we'll see, we'll see, I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is, you know, this is a very interesting week if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a huge week in that, this is almost epic in that this is where Nintendo is finally embracing online.
[SPEAKER_02]: And granted, I mean, you could, you know, get me on little loopholes like, you know, okay, Phantasy Star Online for the GameCube, but let's face it, that was a Sega game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was established before the GameCube
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still waiting for their announcement on December 9th.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll get there in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish I knew about this when it was the arcades, but it was probably a small game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So some little gems in there as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're into the retro collection thing, a lot of good games for $20, I would recommend it for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're not into the retro collections, nothing here is going to win you over.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, Arcade Perfect Bubble Bobble on your console, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, unless you're already into the MAME thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But come on, support these guys a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's $20.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I know, that was a little short review of Tidal Legends, but what else can I really say about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: And another game I got to check out, I went to a little party yesterday for a web forum I'm on, and got to check out some new games at this party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Party 7 being one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't even know if I can really review Mario Party 7, I mean, what the hell can I say about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You've seen 4, 5, 6 on the GameCube, and 3, 2, 1 before that on the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it is eight players.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the first, because we actually played an eight-player game, and you used half the controller in the eight-player game, like you and a friend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, so you have to get, you know, in close quarters.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you and a friend each hold half the controller, and one of you uses the C-stick, the little yellow C-stick, and the right trigger, and then the other person uses the left analog controller and the left trigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it works out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do an eight-player, and you can do teams around the board.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we even did an eight-player game around the board, and myself and Miklatov won, of
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, but those guys are probably pissed off at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, no, we had a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, honestly, I don't know what else I can say about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, if you like these kind of Mario Party games, I don't think they make very good single player games at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're the type of person that games by yourself, I don't think there's a whole lot here for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although there are single player modes, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there are, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some pretty cool mini games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a couple of cool puzzle mini games.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one where there were these balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of reminded me of this old-ass arcade game I used to play at Golf Land called Battle Balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever remember this game?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like a Japanese import game where it had these marbles that were falling and you had to stack them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of like...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't even explain.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a Tetris-type game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they have something like that in this, except it's a rotating sphere that you let the balls fall into.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's some kind of cool minigames.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there would be some cool stuff in here if you are a single player, you know, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: To get the full potential of this game, you've got to be the type of person that has friends over a lot, or you've got a big family, so there's always somebody there to play the game with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you'd get more value out of it that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it does seem to be a better Mario Party game than the last couple I played.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't particularly enjoy 5 or 6 as much as 4, although most other people I've talked to say that 4 is the weakest.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wasn't my personal opinion, but 7's a pretty solid entry.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you've kind of been lagging on the Mario Party series, 7's a good one to come back to, and it does have the microphone support again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other game I checked out was Karaoke Revolution Party Which I played a little bit at E3 But I got to see the full release of the game
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: The version I played was on Xbox, and you can actually use your Xbox Live headset as a microphone, but the game also has a bundle that comes with a holding microphone if you want, but it actually gauges your pitch as a little arrow, so you can see exactly if you're tone deaf, the game will tell you honestly how you're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of how it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I could see maybe a little bit of single player value and that you want to be a better singer, but
[SPEAKER_02]: This is really more the kind of thing where, you know, again, if you have people around a lot, you're an entertainer type with your video games, you'd probably get a lot of value out of Karaoke Revolution Party because I'll tell you, at this party, it was a hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody got on there and was doing the random medley because you can do little medleys of five songs and just do random.
[SPEAKER_02]: So random songs would come up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the interesting thing about Karaoke Revolution Party is that the song list is very eclectic.
[SPEAKER_02]: There really is something for everyone, which is a strong point and a weak point
[SPEAKER_02]: The fact that there's something for everyone means that you really only really, really like like five or six songs on the list and then the rest you're kind of like, oh, I know that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I know that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It didn't really focus on one genre.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I think is interesting about the Xbox version is that you can expand the song list via Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are 100 songs available on Xbox Live for download and you can either download a block of five songs in a genre for $5 each or you can download the whole shebang, all 100 songs for $80.
[SPEAKER_01]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know who'd want to spend $80.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, there's a lot of expansiveness to this game, so certainly the song list will not grow stale, but you're going to have to spend $80, maybe $100 to really expand it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, if you're willing to spend $5 here, $5 there, you can at least buy the genres, because at least it breaks it out into genres.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could buy, like, okay, if I want to buy all the rock packs, that would be like $10, you know, if you're more of a rock music fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would recommend Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, this is one of those games where you already know if this game is for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is definitely the strongest Karaoke Revolution title to date because there's been three other volumes released.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one has Create a Character, this one has the Sing and Dance mode, and both of those just really add to what was already a really unique game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, definitely the strongest entry in the series so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out if you're a fan of the music games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so,
[SPEAKER_02]: XBOX 360 Dominating the News
[SPEAKER_02]: Compatibility list finally released over at Xbox.com Exactly which games they will be backwards compatible supporting And yes, it is apparently going to be using an emulator type thing Because only about 200 titles or so are emulatable Well, so far So far, and they say they are going to expand to it But you do notice a couple things that are missing right off the bat Such as Dance Dance Revolution Ultra Mix Some of the other things such as I noticed Midway Arcade Treasures wasn't on there
[SPEAKER_02]: and some of the other, like, older Xbox titles.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's some weird stuff on that list, that's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_02]: But most, you know what, and I know a lot of people are saying this, like, why is Barbie on the list and, you know, these Aliens vs. Predator and some of these games that weren't standards, you know, and you have this alongside Halo 2, Halo, Fable, you know, all the games...
[SPEAKER_02]: Ninja Gaiden, and all the games you would expect Xbox 360 to be emulating.
[SPEAKER_02]: My thought is, is like, if you are familiar with emulating of games at all, like, for instance, take Nintendo emulation.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's like
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: A game like Ultramix or something will probably take a little more effort.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's why I'm not freaking out about the stuff that they picked to be on this list because obviously they went for their standards and they just haven't gotten around to the rest of it yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But another question was answered and that was if I bought premium content on the Xbox will I be able to transfer it over to the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you will not be able to transfer it to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So don't shelve your Xbox console or sell it back just yet if you use your premium content that's on there because you will have to rebuy it on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least that's what we're hearing right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So far.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that might change later if they figure out a way to do certain things.
[SPEAKER_01]: I somehow don't think it will.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although, if you are a dance game fan, I did see on the list, Pump It Up, Exceed was on there, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: That is one game you'll at least be able to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't think that was Microsoft saying we prefer Pump It Up to DDR or any of that crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's just, again, you get one game to work and Pump It Up worked as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's the problem, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you going to plug in the dance pad?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, good thought, good thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it not the same controller ports?
[SPEAKER_02]: I assumed it was the same controller ports.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really research some of these things.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are no controller ports.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about... No, there's a wired controller that you get in one pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm...
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes too much sense for my feeble brain.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, what they could do is a USB adapter, since the actual Xbox controllers are modified USB.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's probably already an Xbox to USB, so people could use those things on their computer.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure, though, the game would recognize, and that's a problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure this stuff will come out later, but at least it's available.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can play it on the controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woohoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beatmania USA February 8th That's what Konami sent over to us so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, you know, with the dates shuffling like crazy, that could move.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's what they've given us so far, and we actually have a solid date for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: But Tentative should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And speaking of Beatmania, if you are the type that imports your Beatmania from Japan, like I did for a long time, Tentstyle is on its way out very, very soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's next week as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tentstyle has the song list up, and
[SPEAKER_02]: What's very interesting is that there's a very interesting crossover in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jelly Kiss, MidiHead's smack mix from Ultramix 3 is crossing over into 2DX10 style, which is interesting because if you follow the music gaming forums, people have been saying that MidiHead needs to be in 2DX for a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know the other footnote I have to this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: MidiHead's going to be on the show next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to have an interview with him, so I'm going to ask him exactly what he thinks about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have MidiHead on next week's show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, what else is going on here in the gaming world?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about this, because this made me squee like a little fanboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I shed a tear over this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgave Squeenix over this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to sound like such a nerd, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see those pictures coming out of Famitsu Magazine?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, not Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jump Magazine was the magazine that released this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kingdom Hearts 2 characters in Tron outfits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meaning that Tron is a level in Kingdom Hearts 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgive them for the delay.
[SPEAKER_01]: They show stuff from Tron.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they show screenshots and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do like seeing them cross over into these other non-animated movie genres and stuff like that, like the Pirates of the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear about Steamboat Willie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody at the party yesterday was telling me about Steamboat Willie.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's one of the stages, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Retro Mickey or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, old, old style.
[SPEAKER_01]: Square Enix needs to get back with Nintendo
[SPEAKER_01]: and the Nintendo characters and stuff and just make it like Nintendo RPG or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to give another plea over to Squeenix because I'm sure Kingdom Hearts 3 is inevitable and I would just like to issue a friendly reminder to Squeenix that Disney now has the license to the Muppets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could be disastrous but it could be the greatest thing ever as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I'm asking.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: She just sent this over to me over text messenger, so I'm going to read this to you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Her little report from LA.
[SPEAKER_02]: She says, "...the drive to LA was a pain in the arse.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had a nasty cold and it's proceeded to get worse during the trip."
[SPEAKER_02]: The next day was spent on homework in the two-hour drive to Ontario from Anaheim.
[SPEAKER_02]: An hour of that was spent on the five alone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Her friend Julie, Kasumi19, went with me on the adventure.
[SPEAKER_02]: We arrived and met up with Frank of The Overnightscape, a podcast out of New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a big gamer too, apparently, so we sat with him during the ceremony.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also met someone from Madpod.com, sat with us too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The issue when we tried to get in was that we didn't have badges.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, we're Orange Lounge Radio, we won an award.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said, will you be here tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_02]: She said, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they said, fine, just go in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Julie and her DarkSakura helped themselves to the free food.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they sat there mesmerized by Adam Curry, who apparently was standing just a foot away from their table.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I remember when I talked to Jamie on the phone, she didn't shut up about Adam Curry's hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she would also like to say, for the record, he still looks fabulous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, they let the first three awards winners talk, one being Mr. Curry himself, and then the People's Choice winners went up, had picks taken, and got shooed off.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a $25 Visa gift card and plastic trophy, pictures of which will be on the site soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woohoo!
$25!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a higher budget than we've ever had for this show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought we wanted some web design package or blog design.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they chip us?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they jack our pride?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, DarkSakura continues.
[SPEAKER_02]: After that, I mostly hung around talking to Frank and was interviewed for his podcast, so I feel inclined to give his podcast a plug.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Overnightscape.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.theovernightscape.com
[SPEAKER_02]: He's awesome and his podcast was one of the nominees in the political social talk, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: At any rate, that's it for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have one bit of advice for the column tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't try to park on a hill in Julian, California, because it is friggin' impossible.
[SPEAKER_02]: And never trust directions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a map.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: That from our very own DarkSakura, who will be back next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Industry Insider Gaming, Steve, and his podcast over there, as well as RPG MP3, World's Largest Dungeon Audio Review, because they do awesome jobs on their podcasts as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are all independent, and this is probably the only year where the nominees are going to read like that, because I bet you next year, with all the built-in audience that some of those corporate podcasts have, not to knock on the corporate podcasts, you know, they're doing a good thing for the community, 1UP and GameSpot and all them, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably us indies are going to have a harder time standing out next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So guys, we're going to have to enjoy this while it lasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: So congratulations to you guys as well for being nominated.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know, how much Mountain Dew do you think it takes to get through the world's largest dungeon?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm curious about.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, but they have that new energy drink now.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone that we knew was up 48 hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, VX... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was up like 48 hours?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, 48 hours with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure they drink a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tease because I love.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is something about Nintendo that's pissed me off for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this plays into something you were talking about last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how I've been pissed off that Nintendo's not going to support the rev- er, not- Nintendo's not going to support the revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo's not going to support HD with the revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: And as somebody who recently bought an HD TV, that kind of pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I wanted to see Nintendo kind of embrace the HD technology like everyone's doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was kind of this, they said this a long time ago, but there were rumors just very recently that they were going back on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was an interview on CNN Money, and they chatted with Nintendo of America Executive VP of Sales and Marketing, Reggie Fils-Aime.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he said that what we'll offer in terms of gameplay and approachability will more than make up for the lack of HD.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm thinking, shit, this just buys into what Loki said last week about the stereoscope in 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: It all makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can't do it on an HD TV, that's why they're not going to support it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because then it goes on to say that when you have the HD support, you have really long loading times as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I kind of noticed that Halo kind of seems to load a little longer than it used to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, maybe it's just I'm insane, but it seems to have a slightly longer load time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't mind waiting a little bit longer for pretty games, but maybe this all buys into what you were saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll find out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll find out early December.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what do you have for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: A couple things.
[SPEAKER_01]: First thing will be kind of... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_01]: My favorite topic of discussion is how hackers have broken the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Sony's really having trouble with their copy protection stuff this week with the whole CD...
[SPEAKER_01]: DRM Rootkit
[SPEAKER_01]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: PSP3D.com PSP3D.com PSP3D.com
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually had a version of that exploit that they converted into a save file.
[SPEAKER_01]: So basically, you load this save file either in a game or just in their save file browser thing there to actually be able to launch this.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's a bootbin file where you can launch your own code.
[SPEAKER_01]: So in theory, this should work to be able to run a downgrader later on or...
[SPEAKER_01]: Something to that effect.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, a new firmware update is expected.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I believe the new thing that they're adding with the new firmware is going to be e-book reader.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually saw the story on this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's kind of pointless.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe a web browser with, I don't know, Java support would be nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that's that.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other thing that was kind of cool is they were showing some screenshots of the Gradius...
[SPEAKER_01]: Grotius Collection that's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that looks really sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's definitely a PSP game I've got to check out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's going to be nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: They showed both the kind of pan and scan version of the old games and then the widescreen version, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, bow down to the DDR King.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey guys, love the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Helps to make my workday fly by like I am high on drugs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I know you are all addicted to the Bomani games as much as me, and here is where you can flaunt your geekness and help me out all at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance Dance Documentary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where or where do I find it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Help a honky out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I googled it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I couldn't find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea where you can get this movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm telling you, I was interviewed for some movie that they were doing on DDR, and I don't know if this is the same one or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was, and it never came to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, if you go to Internet Movie Database...
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one thing I like.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually see Dance Dance Documentary on Internet Movie Database.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is what I really wanted to talk about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry buddy, I don't know where you can get this movie because I cannot find a website where they are selling this movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was drawn to this entry on Internet Movie Database because it actually has like a full entry here and a review.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's like, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't show your name as one of the actors.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but it shows other people that we know very well, like Mel B and some of the other people in the community.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're all listed here, and they have internet movie database entries.
[SPEAKER_02]: How cool is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you could click on Mel here and get to his whole page, almost like he's a card-carrying member of the Screen Actors Guild now or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a longtime member of the Bomani community, this cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though we've been doing this for, you know, what, three and a half years?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go on to another email.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have another email.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's our buddy Deakman saying, Hi, I'm back from Canada and have just finished catching up on the last month or so worth of shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard you guys read out some release lists for the US and the UK, but nothing for Australia.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he sent us a link.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, checking out the Frapper, you know, we were plugging the Frapper last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't realize, like, every freaking podcast out there has a Frapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, like, now this week I'm looking at other sites and, like, put yourself on the Frapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put yourself on the Frapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: We apparently jumped on this bandwagon way late.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's still cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So put yourself on the Frapper for Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: But looking at the Frapper, we have some pins in Australia.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we got to recognize our Aussie fan base.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only thing I don't like about the Frapper is I can't actually put myself where I live.
[SPEAKER_01]: Instead, it's just...
[SPEAKER_02]: Matrix, Pathineo
[SPEAKER_02]: Also same day, Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming out on 25th November, Shadow the Hedgehog and the Capcom Classics Collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we go into the December.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have 1st of December, you guys are getting WWE Smackdown vs. Raw, which honestly I never really got into the wrestling games, but I know some folks are into them, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Prince of Persia 3, Two Thrones on 8th of December.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, that'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega Classics Collection, you guys are finally getting on 10th of December.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then on into 2006, you guys will be getting Oz, which I don't even think we're getting here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are getting that on 28th of February, so feel lucky about that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then on March 13th, you guys are getting Godfather.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, that all being on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to go to some other systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over in Australia, you guys are getting King Kong for the Xbox on 17th of November.
[SPEAKER_02]: Half-Life 2 on 21st of November.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you go to some other systems such as the GameCube, Pokemon XD this week on 15th of November.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Fire Emblem Path of Radiance on 1st of December.
[SPEAKER_02]: And over on the DS, you guys are getting Burnout Legends on the 12th of December.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Phoenix Wright, Ace Attorney, 28th of February.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like how sometimes they get games before us like King Kong isn't here until the week of the 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just interesting the way it works out sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: He actually got to go to the show in Vancouver, so he wants to share what was going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said the show was great, great sound, great lighting.
[SPEAKER_02]: The production values were great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Each piece was accompanied by game footage.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was an incredible combination.
[SPEAKER_02]: The show started with what they called classic arcade medley.
[SPEAKER_02]: This segment started with the primitive beeps and boops from games like Pong, Space Invaders, and Defender, and then transitioned into the games with some sorts of music in it like Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't sound as hokey as I thought that was going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm really glad that that was the way they opened.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, they played music from the classics with true orchestration like Dragon's Lair and Outrun.
[SPEAKER_02]: They proceeded to play music from games like Metal Gear Solid, Zelda, God of War, Beyond Good and Evil, Castlevania, Myst, Warcraft, Advent Rising, Halo, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: The show was an astounding orchestral experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe that both gamers and non-gamers would enjoy it equally.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's too bad that they had to cancel most of their shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, a positive review of this show coming to us from Edmund.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, if you want to send us an email, 2go at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we hope we'll be reading your email on a future podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: For now, back to the news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other things I was going to be mentioning.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a ton of stuff, of course, with the 360 launch going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some things I found really funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first one being, of course...
[SPEAKER_01]: The golden tickets that are being given out at Walmart, I think those are just hilarious.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently, this is one of those things, you know, they're going to be handling theirs, you know, first-come, first-served type line thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you get a ticket.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's great about the thing, though, is the tickets are a little bit confusing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are for the opposite of the, you know, colored box that they're supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: So the green tickets are for the white box, and the white tickets are for the... Oh, that won't cause any confusion at all, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, actually, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're for the same boxes.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, their little form tells them what...
[SPEAKER_01]: and ones which.
[SPEAKER_01]: The white box is going to be the $2.99 and the green box being $3.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, for all those who are pre-ordering those, those are completely opposite.
[SPEAKER_01]: So some people hopefully will be getting their systems for $100 less than they would have to be paying, which I think is quite funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other thing which is interesting, and this is completely on a different subject here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, same subject.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox 360 Zero Hour.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's an event that's going on in the Mojave Desert.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to see if we could go to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Real work calls.
[SPEAKER_01]: In order to get a ticket, they were doing this Blitz thing on Thursday where you would have
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe there's like 12 sites participating, all the major gaming sites.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, they were giving out... What do you mean all the major gaming sites?
[SPEAKER_02]: We weren't in on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but we don't have an actual huge budget like they do, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we have $25 now, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have a $25 budget now.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, anyways, so they were giving out... I believe each site was giving out about 360 tickets, and then the rest of them were going to be randomly drawn...
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, Monday.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, we'll find out who gets to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: 3,000 people, including VIPs, which will be contest winners from the Origin website and, of course, the Hex168 site.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll be going there, and you'll be greeted with 48 hours of pure gaming fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, is this like Burning Man with more games and less nudity?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And celebrities who really have no point being there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But...
[SPEAKER_01]: And you'll also get to buy your Xbox 360 a whole couple hours earlier than everybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: This just feeds into what I was talking about at the beginning of the cast, why I'm not doing this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why I'm just not going to do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's why.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes sense when you find out why they're trying to force games on you.
[SPEAKER_01]: In order to be able to have Xboxes at launch, you have to promise Microsoft you're going to do $10 million in business by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or else what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or else...
[SPEAKER_02]: Or else what, they're going to slap you on the wrist?
[SPEAKER_02]: What, you're going to give a severe penalty to a big company like Best Buy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Crap, if I were a company like that, I'd pull your crap off my shelves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck selling your damn system under these rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just some gaming fan with a little podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I don't understand the bigger scope of things, so I'm sure I'll get emails on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to understand, they don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're nobody to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: My money, damn it!
[SPEAKER_02]: I should be somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: The customer is always right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anywho, in other news, I will file air the... It was bound to happen sooner or later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo is talking about possibly redesigning the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, so I can buy it again?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, just like how there's like 50 different Game Boys out there I could buy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, what a shock.
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, Reggie fills, I mean, dropped a hint that the DS may be due for a redesign.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, yeah, it's not a surprise.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to make it sleeker, I guess, and smaller, and yadda yadda yadda yadda.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I got a story over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: NCSoft, you know NCSoft, they make Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: NCSoft is saying that they are going to be working on a console game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chief Executive Tak Jin Kim mentioned that they were developing for the next generation consoles, but they're not saying exactly what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you think about it, well, they do MMOs, so that would seem like the most logical thing they're going to put out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything is possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would think if they're going to put out an MMO, Xbox 360 is probably going to be where they gravitate to.
[SPEAKER_02]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything is possible at this juncture.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we do know NCSofts will be developing something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought they'd launch this port Guild Wars to the console.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet a lot of people might get a kick out of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what do I know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, I'm just some guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: for those people who like to play games on their computer that they shouldn't be playing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shame, shame, shame.
[SPEAKER_01]: What, emulators?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there was a long-awaited mod that takes Legends of the Ocarina of Time
[SPEAKER_01]: and updates the graphics with high res textures.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's finally out, folks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, you will need the raw man emulator to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, you can definitely find this link at 4colorrebellion.com and it's one of the posts that they put on there from today, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: November 13th.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I personally didn't get to play Ocarina of Time, even though I had the disc for the GameCube, you know, the
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that Ocarina of Time is a treasured game.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you ask people, what is your favorite game of all time, Ocarina of Time almost always comes near the top of the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not get as into this Zelda.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm in some category by myself sometimes, I feel like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not get into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if it's the 3D thing that really just threw me that I never was able to get over, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I just keep going back to the Super Nintendo Zelda, you know, and how freaking wonderful that game was linked to the past.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just to me, nothing compares to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know if this new Zelda will compare to linked to the past to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, the new Zelda looks very, very sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe all will be forgiven, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, yeah, a couple more things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, first, of course, the game I've been, um, watching closely, Project Gotham Reason 3, I actually watched, they had this 25 minute video discussing, like, all the details that went into the graphics, the physics, and everything, and the game looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, apparently, it might not truly be high def.
[SPEAKER_01]: Big freaking whoop.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, but, apparently, um, there was a test version of the game that was shipped out to, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: A reviewer, and they actually did a screen cap of it straight from the machine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, dumping the graphic buffer or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's 1024x600 instead of 1024x720.
[SPEAKER_01]: Big friggin' whoop.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's not that, you know, the exact same detail.
[SPEAKER_01]: The game looks amazing, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, of course, it's controversy, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: or actually I should say Activision signed a deal with Marvel extending their partnership for another 12 years or so basically allowing them to make games until 2017 using the licenses of Marvel and it's going to be exclusive with them so
[SPEAKER_01]: You'll see wonderful games such as more Spider-Man and more X-Men games coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to say that they don't do bad games, because the Ultimate Spider-Man was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard very, very good things about that Spider-Man game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't play it myself.
[SPEAKER_01]: And X-Men Legends 2 was supposed to be pretty good, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, X-Men Legends 1 disappointed the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was not a big fan of it, but I have heard that 2 is much better, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: 2 is much better because you don't have to unlock multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was retarded.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember when we got that game, we were just like, oh, yeah, let's play multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, wait, we can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of Activision, I just wanted to drop this out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quake 4 is going to be a 360 launch title.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is coming out in time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And with all the news about all these games getting pushed back, I suppose it would be refreshing for a change if you're an Xbox 360 fan to hear that Quake 4 will be dropping at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was going to be dropping at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was originally the case.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was supposed to be on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_01]: I heard now it's going to be the 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to say that it has been confirmed by the studio it is happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eight player support over Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just an FYI.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it also has been reported that DOA 4 is actually pushed back to December now.
[SPEAKER_02]: See?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the game I was looking forward to more than any other.
[SPEAKER_01]: But for now, before we all jump the gun here, it was only pushed back a week.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's December 1st.
[SPEAKER_01]: Big whoop.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's like
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: There's tons of stuff, and I can wait seven days for a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you're going to be picking up launch games anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't need to have six games at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I do, but, you know, that's just me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll still be playing Mario Kart DS for the next three weeks, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, hell yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to dominate the rankings for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some sick, sick, sick Nintendo fanboys that will beat you up really bad online, and some of them are probably listening and can't wait to kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: All will be answered very soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's still going to be all drama this entire week is basically it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, that's pretty much what I've got.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Quake 3 for the Pocket PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: But who owns a Pocket PC?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who really wants to play Quake 3 on a Pocket PC anyway?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, who wants to run Linux on a DS?
[SPEAKER_02]: But they do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, okay, it does make homebrew possible.
[SPEAKER_01]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_01]: And in the story of it's really been a slow news week...
[SPEAKER_01]: People have been reporting on numerous websites.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you pop in Cameo on your Xbox, it says put in Xbox 360, dumbass.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not really, but it basically says this is meant to be played on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's what people do with their games that they buy before the console is out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wondered why people did that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, all is answered.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: All other things, you know, from, you know, instruction manuals being online for the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, people are just dying to get anything, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sick of the hype.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not trying to be anti-Xbox here, but I am sick of the hype.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know if you want the damn system or not by now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have fun if you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have fun waiting if you don't or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got one more story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: One last story for tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kata Takahashi, who created Katamari Damacy, gave an interview with the BBC this week and said that he probably doesn't really want to be doing gaming for the rest of his life.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's actually imagining developing a playground for children.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's not really into doing video games for the rest of his life.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm just reminded of how Kojima always says he's not going to do another Metal Gear Solid and then the next year, oh, just kidding, here's another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we should be forcing him to stay on video games because I'm kind of afraid this will kind of plague around equipment he's going to come up with.
[SPEAKER_01]: God damn, I mean, we don't actually need a physical Katamari out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's
[SPEAKER_01]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all from me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Any last minute stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: I got nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be more of the same next week, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: More games, more fun, more drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got a fun month ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: The next six weeks are going to be a blast because we got the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, it's going to be insane.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually signed on to Final Fantasy XI to update it, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I looked at the date that I last played it five months ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you've been paying, let's see, five times.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much do you pay him on?
[SPEAKER_02]: $12.95 or do you have another character?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have another character.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so you paid $13.95, $14.95.
[SPEAKER_02]: You paid $70 for nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure the fianc is very pleased.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will play.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will play by the end of this month.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mark my words.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played World of Warcraft yesterday.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just don't have time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have certain games I have to play during the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to play like everything comes out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, you poor thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Having to play video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't played that yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe we'll hear a review on that next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: For now, that's the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're pushing an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it for tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next week, we'll have MiniHead on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to ask him questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thoughts, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope Mario Kart DS is going to friggin' rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's my exact same final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Kart DS, please, dear Nintendo, please do not screw up your online capabilities.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have faith it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to be an exciting era for the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then Animal Crossing DS in a few weeks after that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you so much for listening to and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, if you like us, please check out our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com and check out the forums, which are getting more and more active.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're loving that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got some great people, some just intelligent, intelligent posters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep it up with the forums over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, tell a friend because that's really the way the word gets out about us because we're independent and that's how folks are going to find out about us is if you tell them.
[SPEAKER_02]: So spread the word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Until next week, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.