and more.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
Now I see what I gotta do
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: Can't hold on much longer But I will never let go I know it's a one-way track Tell me now how long this will last I'm not gonna think this way Nor will I count on others Close my eyes and feel it burn Now I see what I've gotta do Open your heart and you will see
Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_21]: I will never let go I know it's a one-way track Tell me now how long this will last I'm not gonna think this way Nor will I count on others Close my eyes and feel it burn Now I see what I've gotta go for
[SPEAKER_03]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is episode number...
[SPEAKER_09]: 132 for this February the 20th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're tuned in to the B-Mani Scene's most homely station of all things B-Mani.
[SPEAKER_09]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yes, I'm futzing with the volume levels as we speak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: The volume levels were a little off when we started tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our whole pre-show was kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nobody said anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_09]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say hello to DarkSakura, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm caffeinated today.
[SPEAKER_17]: God, that's loud.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, your mic is loud today.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that's too loud for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if we had to turn it up last week because somebody else was there last week.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't see how.
[SPEAKER_17]: I hate sounding echoey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder what's going on with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll change that.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: She sounds echoey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Turn down her gain a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's just her gain's up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gain?
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, say hello to Techmaster Loki while we're at it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, I'm fixing stuff.
[SPEAKER_33]: I can't tell what microphone this is.
[SPEAKER_09]: In beautiful Orange Lounge fashion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't tell which wire's which in this place.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what's on move.
[SPEAKER_09]: Play with all of them until it changes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh wait, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think this is it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: It does sound echo-y, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds better now.
[SPEAKER_33]: Stop speaking with an echo, then.
[SPEAKER_17]: Apparently I'm an orange chef.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say hello also to frequent guests of our program.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's here again tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um... I just gave something to Robin.
[SPEAKER_16]: All of a sudden he goes, ooh!
[SPEAKER_16]: And I just completely lost my train of thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: Wonderful!
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR Angel knows how to kiss some ass around here.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's brought me a bunch of Pepsi bottle caps that have the iTunes songs on them because she knows I'm like one of the only people that actually uses iTunes and actually purchases songs legally through iTunes.
[SPEAKER_09]: So she's giving me free songs!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then she's also brought me candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is the best way to my heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Music and candy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have meat and caffeine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that works for you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Meat and caffeine.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm music and candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: What would Loki be?
[SPEAKER_17]: Blood and guts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_17]: And porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: And cooking, because that's what he's doing right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, he's got our webcam in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_09]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on... Actually, you don't have to click on anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: The webcam's right there on the front page.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can watch Loki cook, as exciting as that must be.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no idea why.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why is the webcam in the kitchen?
[SPEAKER_14]: Is this in response to the people always saying, You guys never have anything interesting on your webcam.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your webcam is so boring.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why do you even bother?
[SPEAKER_33]: It's because there's, I mean, we only have one guest, Angel, I mean, and she's not even sitting on the couch, and so, you know, figured, what the hell.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll bring another old school game next weekend to showcase.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that'll work.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll bring like the SNES and play Punch Out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, we broke out the PS1 today because we found that Nan's been playing Tempest X all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: As in the kind of crappy version of Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tempest is Tempest, my friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although Tempest 2000 on the Jag was the best.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tempest on the Jag was the only game worth getting a Jag for.
[SPEAKER_17]: What about Defender 2000?
[SPEAKER_17]: Bah.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, there was another.
[SPEAKER_17]: There was Alien vs. Predator.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's about the only Aliens vs. Predator thing worth even remotely wasting your time with.
[SPEAKER_21]: The arcade game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Any arcade game.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But not the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not the movie.
[SPEAKER_17]: The comics were okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're here for the next three hours, you know, to talk about, you know, stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_09]: And all your favorite segments, Cage Match, and maybe some Bomani news too, and if we run out of Bomani stuff, I guess we'll talk about other video game stuff, because we're dorks.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to start off this break with a potpourri of Bomani music.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is no theme this break.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're just going to play whatever the hell we want.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll start off with a song I want to hear, Shiny Disco Balls.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio, episode 132.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for tuning in.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because Bongo demands it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are back here with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, boys and girls, on this happy 220-2005.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a lot of twos and a lot of zeros.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm out of clever things to say.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's a lot of zeros in the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you're not so echoey anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're echoing away.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, but I'm still sniffy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, there's been like disease going around.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, it's called, someone decided to clean the upstairs room while I was in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there was like a thick layer of dust?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: It needed doing, I just was upset at the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm scared of moving out of this place.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know the Orange Lounge Radio studio is moving in April.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, hopefully you'll have less of a drive to get to the Orange Lounge studio, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't even remember what I did last weekend.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know I had to do something.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, it was celebrating Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm so bad.
[SPEAKER_29]: Didn't you say the man was listening tonight too?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I did.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whoops!
[SPEAKER_17]: Seriously though, we went to Claim Jumper for dinner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And ate like everything in sight.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I had chocolate cream cheese pie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish I was in a relationship so I could go to Claim Jumper.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can go to Claim Jumper anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, but.
[SPEAKER_09]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_17]: I was a fool.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they gave me a free cup of soup.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dan got, like, for his appetizer, he got, like, chili in the bread bowl.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm sitting here with my little cup of soup going, huh, soup.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sitting there staring at his bowl and eating part of it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And it's like, there's no point you should be sitting there staring at his food here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Have another cup.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was like, thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: You get a good tip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Claim Jumper has the best potato cheddar soup in the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the world.
[SPEAKER_17]: It has pieces of...
[SPEAKER_17]: of slightly overcooked potato skin in it.
[SPEAKER_17]: So it's crunchy.
[SPEAKER_09]: For those who don't know what Claim Jumper is, because they don't have it everywhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they only have it... I think it's only in California.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I think it's in other states, too, but mostly on the West Coast.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I know they don't have it everywhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: But basically, it's this giant log cabin-themed restaurant.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the portions are like they kill the buffalo out back and put it on your plate.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how big it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: I didn't really do anything too Bimani-related.
[SPEAKER_17]: I played some Silent Hill 3.
[SPEAKER_17]: Silent Hill 4 is sort of, eh, creepy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just sort of annoying creepy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Silent Hill 3 starts off like shit your pants creepy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I screamed like a girl at one part of Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a different kind of scare, I think.
[SPEAKER_17]: Silent Hill 3, I only got as far as the first part of it, the dream part.
[SPEAKER_17]: But it was like, you know what, the Uzi in that game is so ridiculously not useful.
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: but in Silent Hill you don't have enough ammo to kill everything you have to be all Metal Gear Solid about it and you gotta sneak by zombies and just run like hell but that is so not the way I usually play adventure games I want to explore every little corner I want to kill everything because I might drop something I need but that's not the same mindset you can approach I wasn't spoiling shit stop saying I spoiled anything don't listen to that Sharon anyway Dan bought me roses
[SPEAKER_17]: I came home from work the other day, and there were roses.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, now, I believe, and I could find this, too, in an earlier podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: You said something, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember in one of the podcasts, you said, I don't need roses, not flowery girl shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: My man buys me Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I'm really not very, you know, girly-girly when it comes to relationships.
[SPEAKER_17]: But every so often, you know, I want something sweet.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, I have to have my dose of sugar in the relationship, or else I start, you know...
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm getting lethargic, you know, without something to keep my, I guess, relationship blood sugar up or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't use Splenda for that.
[SPEAKER_17]: No Splenda.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, he came home and gave me this box, this really long box, and I'm thinking, oh, well, it's got like a poster in it or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: And there were, there's a dozen pink roses in it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_17]: Aww, I know.
[SPEAKER_17]: I feel all spoiled and special.
[SPEAKER_09]: You are spoiled.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you weren't spoiled, you wouldn't bring that same charm to this show, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, you would.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'd be charming either way.
[SPEAKER_16]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can stop shutting up now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_17]: But that's really it.
[SPEAKER_17]: We've been going through the old system stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dan found my copy of Cotton for the PC Engine Duo.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I have this feeling that tomorrow I'm going to be breaking out the TurboGrafx and playing a lot of Cotton.
[SPEAKER_17]: It came out actually on the Neo Geo Pocket Color in the States, I think.
[SPEAKER_17]: But it's a game where you play as a little witch riding her broom and she's addicted to this candy that makes her throw up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Called Willow.
[SPEAKER_17]: And it's funny in the game she goes, WELO!
[SPEAKER_17]: So anyway, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_16]: Monday was... Monday.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: I got chocolate and stuff.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that new?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, that's new.
[SPEAKER_16]: He's pointing at my necklace.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel's got a heart around her neck.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little gold heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder where that came from.
[SPEAKER_16]: He he.
[SPEAKER_16]: He he, he he.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, Magus' fault.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, jeez, I don't remember what really happened this week, aside from that, and then, you know, school and work and stuff, and Rob's looking at his caps and playing with them, eek!
[SPEAKER_16]: Actually, yeah, he's got a couple songs to get now, yay!
[SPEAKER_16]: And, uh, by the way, I drank way too much soda this week for that, so, like, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Contrary to popular belief, as much as I like people to do things for me, you don't have to drink all that Pepsi to win me free songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moderation, honey.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll just take what you have extra.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Who said it was all regular soda?
[SPEAKER_09]: Still.
[SPEAKER_09]: Water's good, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can do the water once in a while.
[SPEAKER_16]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_16]: God, not much went on, really.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, I played some games, but...
[SPEAKER_16]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh yeah, and then the internet went out.
[SPEAKER_16]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Two days later.
[SPEAKER_16]: Two days later and some phone calls.
[SPEAKER_16]: We finally have internet back, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I don't know what else happened this week.
[SPEAKER_16]: It just went by way too quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, then I guess you're done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Loki looks like he's cooking, so I guess I'll talk about my week.
[SPEAKER_09]: My Valentine's Day, now I'm the single bitch in here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody else is in a relationship, but I'm the single bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You did, but for Valentine's Day, actually one of my buddies had a little cookover thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like he cooked dinner for a bunch of single people.
[SPEAKER_09]: He had like a singles dinner, which I think is really nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a very good idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was very nice and very sweet, so I was happy that he did that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he gave me something to do on Valentine's Day where I didn't feel lonely.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I didn't even have to put out, and I didn't have to buy flowers for anybody, so it was great.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I got steak on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: How great is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I got homemade steak on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because beef is love.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: And no, you perverts, not that kind of meat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, what else did I do this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: I played a lot of WarioWare Touched, because I bought it on the DS on Tuesday, the day it came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, you know, I was all excited for a new WarioWare game.
[SPEAKER_09]: and there was a side of me where I was kind of like what if they do the Nintendo thing and just recycle the same garbage and I have to play the same damn indie games but they're all new and that made me so happy so I'll gush about that more on this week's podcast so definitely check that out if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: WarioWare is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm very happy with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are some downsides to it though so I'll talk about it later.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I was doing a little bit of retro gaming too as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing a little more with the emulator.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why I've been getting so back into that lately.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's because I've been trying to
[SPEAKER_09]: Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_09]: And I got killed so, so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I came in last place, and like seventh place, which is next to last place, had like twice as many kills as I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is how sad it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just not meant to play Halo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or any first person shooter for that matter, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, what did I end up doing in real life?
[SPEAKER_09]: Last night I went out to the casino, and I lost $60.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, that's okay, because I'm going to win it all back next time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to win it all back.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I went to the buffet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Biggest buffets are awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know, when I went out to lunch with an old friend of mine today, I went out to lunch with Julie today, and she was saying, you know, when people say that they're going to the casino to go to the buffet, that's just code words for gambling.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm like, yeah, sadly it is.
[SPEAKER_33]: I go before the buffet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I only gambled a dollar.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you gambled.
[SPEAKER_33]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: The chat room is saying you suck at gambling.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do suck at gambling.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should stop.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really need to stop.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's so addicting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_09]: He's getting his food finished up before he can talk in the microphone here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that still on cam?
[SPEAKER_09]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Our amazing Orange Lounge kitchen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, we can't hear you, bud.
[SPEAKER_09]: Turn on the mic.
[SPEAKER_33]: Yes, it has a shot of the empty walk at the moment.
[SPEAKER_33]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_33]: Which will be full.
[SPEAKER_33]: Well, had a cold this week.
[SPEAKER_33]: That sucked.
[SPEAKER_33]: Saw Constantine.
[SPEAKER_33]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_33]: Played lots of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_33]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_33]: And then to top it all off in the final nail in the coffin, my power supply goes out of my computer.
[SPEAKER_33]: That sucked.
[SPEAKER_33]: And, so yeah, so pretty much today was, I was being very lethargic, just like, slept for ten hours, got up, ate some waffles, watched Ghost in the Shell 2 Innocence, I actually watched one of my movies I got, surprisingly enough, and then slept for another three hours, or, I don't even know, slept for an hour or so.
[SPEAKER_33]: And I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_33]: And now because I just realized I haven't had any actual protein in my body for a while, and I kind of feel faint, so I had to cook food.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my week.
[SPEAKER_09]: When was the last time you ate?
[SPEAKER_09]: This morning, I had waffles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, waffles.
[SPEAKER_09]: But no protein.
[SPEAKER_09]: No protein in waffles.
[SPEAKER_33]: Unfortunately not, there's... Just waffle goodness.
[SPEAKER_33]: Waffle and Aunt Jemima.
[SPEAKER_09]: No protein in Aunt Jemima either.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or her syrup, anyway.
[SPEAKER_33]: No...
[SPEAKER_33]: Her syrup has no protein in it.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's not very tangy either.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aunt Jemima might have protein in her though, but... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, and then we have another person who's knocking on the door, so... It's explicit!
[SPEAKER_33]: You know that knocker's just for decorative purposes, actually.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dude, I just found a neat link on somebody's digital... Alright, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_33]: Tell us about it.
[SPEAKER_33]: Alright, thanks, Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: The online entomology dictionary.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: and I guess just because I'm the only real nerd here that only I really would find that to be a cool thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, our listeners might be nerdy too.
[SPEAKER_09]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll link it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Explicit, since you just walked in, why not tell us about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_32]: This week has been good and bad.
[SPEAKER_32]: I've been busy throughout the whole time doing nothing but homework.
[SPEAKER_32]: Of course, I'm taking like 15 units of class and I have two jobs, so it's pretty hectic.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, I heard you ran into Magus this week in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_32]: Uh, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_16]: At school.
[SPEAKER_16]: ARC, you guys are playing Initial D or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, I don't play Initial D. This Dead Air was brought to you by a DDR Angel story.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, that's what I heard.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, jeez.
[SPEAKER_32]: We were talking about the future, but not...
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_32]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_32]: I did not get a chance to go to that tournament this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was another DDR tournament I didn't go to.
[SPEAKER_32]: I heard about it, though.
[SPEAKER_32]: I heard about what happened at the tournament, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, what happened, Drama?
[SPEAKER_32]: Well, there's some good and bad stuff.
[SPEAKER_32]: Good was... It was a decent tournament and stuff, as far as I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_32]: They've actually broadcasted a commercial for March Madness.
[SPEAKER_09]: They did a commercial for...
[SPEAKER_32]: No, they did an intermission to talk about March Madness 2K3 with a combination of Freestyle Revolution Plus.
[SPEAKER_32]: March Madness 2003?
[SPEAKER_32]: 2005, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think, oh damn, I think we're a couple years late.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_32]: The Manager, Paul, and MilpitasGolfland
[SPEAKER_32]: Screwed the pads over.
[SPEAKER_32]: I heard there's people who are getting 10 misses in a song or 12.
[SPEAKER_32]: There was no full combo throughout the whole tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_32]: That's how bad the freaking pads were.
[SPEAKER_32]: Which also concerns me about March Madness 2K5.
[SPEAKER_32]: If the same result would happen again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are they going to do DDR Idol and March Madness 2K5?
[SPEAKER_32]: Not this time.
[SPEAKER_32]: We're doing Freestyle Revolution Plus.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: As in Mike.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: You listening?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want DDR Idol.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_32]: I'm not the one organizing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why I was putting out that special message.
[SPEAKER_32]: Or the upcoming Sacramento tournament in April.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need another DDR Idol.
[SPEAKER_32]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_32]: Oh, speaking of tournament in April, somebody is actually in the process of organizing a tournament at that month in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not you?
[SPEAKER_32]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's doing it?
[SPEAKER_32]: A friend of mine named DJ Arrow.
[SPEAKER_32]: He's on the forums.
[SPEAKER_32]: Yeah, he wanted to go through the process of tournament organizing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_32]: Good luck!
[SPEAKER_32]: Good luck, kid!
[SPEAKER_32]: Have fun!
[SPEAKER_32]: It's not an easy path, but I have faith in him.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really not easy.
[SPEAKER_09]: If he puts the time and effort into it, it'll be a good tourney.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't doubt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember when we did tourneys, Janie?
[SPEAKER_09]: Janie?
[SPEAKER_09]: I said Janie.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_17]: And this is as long as people can accept criticism without taking it personally.
[SPEAKER_32]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_32]: Well, I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_32]: That was an issue back then, but...
[SPEAKER_17]: That was an issue a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_32]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_32]: But there was a lot of heat and drama.
[SPEAKER_32]: There was so much heat and drama at the time.
[SPEAKER_32]: That I hope does not happen in July.
[SPEAKER_32]: Yeah, I made mistakes.
[SPEAKER_32]: I admit I made mistakes.
[SPEAKER_32]: But I admit my mistakes and learned from it.
[SPEAKER_32]: Hopefully it doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good for you that you can admit that we've all made mistakes.
[SPEAKER_32]: I mean, a lot of things went through tournament organizing itself.
[SPEAKER_32]: There's always going to be a conflict, an unexpected conflict that you may not be able to do because it could be the pad issue, but sometimes the place may restrict you from doing certain things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I say next time there's a clause written into the contract that says, or the gaming thing that says, if the pads break down during the tournament...
[SPEAKER_09]: The tournament will instantly become a whack-a-mole competition, and we'll just all play whack-a-mole.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because whack-a-mole is awesome.
[SPEAKER_32]: Well, if there's really a big bad error on one side, you can try doing it on the other.
[SPEAKER_32]: Unless if both sides are messed up.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what happened at our first SACTO tourney, is that one of the sides was screwing up, so we ended up having to do PA all on one side.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: It made things go a little longer, but at the same time, we were on schedule, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, this was years ago, but I think it ended up being on schedule anyway, so we weren't too bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it was just kind of a bummer that that had to happen, you know?
[SPEAKER_32]: I mean, it happens.
[SPEAKER_32]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_32]: But if both pads, like I said, if both pads don't function, then you can't really run a tournament.
[SPEAKER_32]: Or I don't even know what's going to happen right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: What does Milpitas have, like, 50 machines, DDR machines they can use?
[SPEAKER_32]: Unfortunately, it's under Paul or MGL's management, manager itself.
[SPEAKER_32]: I mean, this is what the reason why I'm hearing why they did not switch the pads to inter-groove pads, which is almost in good condition.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unlike anyone plays inter-groove.
[SPEAKER_32]: According to what I'm hearing... Kidding, kidding kids, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_32]: According from the sources I'm hearing, Indigroup makes a lot more money than DDR in Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm not surprised, because there's no new DDR game.
[SPEAKER_32]: And the fact that they did not use the Indigroup pads for that tournament makes me wonder what happened.
[SPEAKER_32]: I mean, they're extreme in 4th Plus with the messed up pads, so... Right, anyways, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_32]: Sorry if I...
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't listen to the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here you go, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's some Advil.
[SPEAKER_32]: Or you can watch Loki cook.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can learn from tournament drama.
[SPEAKER_32]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_32]: Is anybody going to E3?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know that Jamie and Matt are, but I have to do the business stuff for Orange Lounge still, which I need to get up off my ass and do this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I want to go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why are you asking?
[SPEAKER_32]: Nah, I'm just wondering, because I was thinking more like having a group of people going to E3 and stuff, if possible.
[SPEAKER_32]: I'll be at E3, but I'm going with DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'll be at E3, but, I mean, I have no, it's too early to plan.
[SPEAKER_32]: Hey, who never knows?
[SPEAKER_32]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_32]: I think, who knows if the tickets will cost more, like, later on, I'm not really sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you can pay to get in if you've got a couple hundred bucks sitting around, but, you know, you're supposed to...
[SPEAKER_09]: Get the hookup by having some game companies.
[SPEAKER_32]: I know places like GameStop, EB, and various other gaming companies.
[SPEAKER_32]: As long as you have access to gaming or any interest of gaming itself.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had friends that went under EB Games and GameStop.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_32]: I know people too.
[SPEAKER_32]: You can even say that you have a website dedicated to games even though you don't have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is kind of hard to get in on a website, trust me, I know from experience, because we have a problem proving Orange Lounge Radio is a legit gaming thing, even though, God, we promote the hell out of certain video games, and our podcast is more popular than what we're doing here right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, and it's listened to by quite a few people, but we're still just a hobby, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_32]: because I know of someone I knew who had a fake website and went into E3 somehow.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you know what to do, I guess it's possible, but I'm not good with that stuff, like bargaining and dealing my way in.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, anyway, what we're going to do is we're going to go to a break, we're going to come back, and then we're going to talk about some more Bomani news, I guess, if we have any to talk about this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll find something.
[SPEAKER_09]: and all your favorite Orange Lounge Radio segments when we come back after this little break featuring another mix of various songs from various CDR mixes.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_26]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_33]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_26]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_14]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Episode 132, In Progress
[SPEAKER_09]: We decided during the break that we're going to play some match game tonight, so be ready for that a little later on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We haven't done match game in a little while, so we're going to do that tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: You will have to be on the Skype line if you want to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, we always take one person from the Skype line and one person from our chat room that doesn't have Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you want to sign up to play, just be ready for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want more information on getting in on the Skype line, www.orangeandre.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, while you're on our website, check out the podcast, which by the way,
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, before we get into what's going on with the match game, I thought we could talk about what's going on in the Bomani world, and a little bit of maybe the general gaming world as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, you heard something about what's going on with DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, there is a new DDR game out in arcades.
[SPEAKER_09]: But don't get excited just yet, kids.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's another bootleg.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_33]: Well, give us some detail.
[SPEAKER_33]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_33]: Well...
[SPEAKER_33]: Coming to a Namco arcade near you.
[SPEAKER_33]: And it's basically a PlayStation 2 inside of cabinet with some special hardware and it's running, I kid you not, the DDR Extreme, the US version.
[SPEAKER_33]: So you've got that running in there.
[SPEAKER_33]: And, well, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_33]: The pads aren't even normal pads.
[SPEAKER_33]: They're just these shitty internet, like the ones you can get off of eBay.
[SPEAKER_33]: So they break really quick.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's just shit.
[SPEAKER_33]: That's all that needs to be said.
[SPEAKER_29]: So basically, is it the same?
[SPEAKER_29]: It's just DDR Extreme on PS2?
[SPEAKER_33]: It's running straight off of PS2.
[SPEAKER_09]: How does that work with the quarters and all the different modes and stuff?
[SPEAKER_33]: You can actually buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_33]: They have them for Dreamcast and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_33]: You can actually get where it has a whole quarter system and it'll lock the game out.
[SPEAKER_33]: I don't really know how that would work, though, as far as, you know...
[SPEAKER_33]: I think it might have something to do with pushing the start button, and that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_33]: I'm not really sure, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_33]: But I've seen them out there.
[SPEAKER_33]: They do exist.
[SPEAKER_33]: But yeah, there's been pictures circling around the internet, and it's literally a PS2 inside of a cabinet.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_33]: The US version.
[SPEAKER_33]: Does it have the webcam?
[SPEAKER_33]: With the iToy web, you know, iToy type interface.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does it actually have an iToy hooked up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's lame.
[SPEAKER_33]: And the thing is, is I think people are trying, they're trying to push it off as like DDR9th mix or whatever, and it's pretty lame.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I found that post.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's over here on AaronInJapan.com if you want to check this out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Threads called Namco once again outdoes itself in stupidity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Posted by Windu, Windo, I think it's supposed to be Windo, D-E-U, 32.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey kids, it's the new DDR Mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not Mega Mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not even Extreme Plus.
[SPEAKER_09]: This time we're really lower the bar by putting the PS2 US Extreme in the 2A DDR cabinet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not only that, but we've also changed the pads.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're now Cobalt Flux wannabes, included with sheet metal on metal contact, but with a springy, cushiony feel to them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the layout.
[SPEAKER_09]: When you insert a coin, a big ugly number appears at the bottom center of the screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: The thing looks like it came straight out of Atari.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now when you insert enough coins for a credit and press start, you go to the main menu of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't select anything though, it just goes straight into game mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here you have the option of selecting single, versus, or double, regardless of how many credits you put in.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you go to Versus with one credit, you are stuck at the character selection screen until you put another credit to activate the other side.
[SPEAKER_09]: Same goes for Double, only you can actually go into the Song Select screen and pick a song.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, one of the sides will not be active at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: On to the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you've ever played DDR Extreme USCS or DDR Festival, you know what to expect.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, you pick the song, but what's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: No mod menu?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: No possible way to get into the modifier menu.
[SPEAKER_09]: All you can really do is pick your difficulty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've noticed, though, messing around, that you can hit the left-right select buttons in place of the left-right arrows.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if an LR jump freeze is coming up, no problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: Step off the pad and hit both the buttons at the same time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've also noticed that if you're holding a freeze and hit the start button, the freeze drops, even though you're still on the arrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, if you're playing single player, a credit is in the machine, and someone decides to press the other side's start button during song select, then bam, instant verses, also known as the third mix effect.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, if you're one song away from completing your set and suddenly decide to play non-stop or challenge, no problem!
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, in Extreme US Consumer, you can go into non-stop challenge even on your final song.
[SPEAKER_09]: And hey, if you really want to piss people off, go for the 20-song custom-only course.
[SPEAKER_09]: With a possible 22 songs per game, there's no way you can lose!
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually, you've already lost if you've put your money into this piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: That post, again, coming from Window32 at AaronInJapan.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for letting me plagiarize your post without your permission.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, as my theory went, it is pretty much, you know, you have to put in so many credits, and after a while, it will let you use the start button.
[SPEAKER_33]: That's why you can't get into the mods, because the mods use the start button.
[SPEAKER_33]: And, obviously, it's wired for the, you know, select screen stuff.
[SPEAKER_33]: That's why the left and right work on that.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, yeah, it's just a hack job.
[SPEAKER_29]: Refresh my memory here for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't there some type of disclaimer?
[SPEAKER_09]: When you boot up DDR Extreme US, it says something about, this game is licensed for personal and home use only.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any, oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every game has that type of warning.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the FBI warning.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's on everything.
[SPEAKER_33]: I just know it's licensed for use within the United States or whatever, or North America, however that works.
[SPEAKER_33]: I'm sure I've already sent an email to Konami and I'm sure other people have too.
[SPEAKER_29]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_29]: You sent an email to Konami to tell on them?
[SPEAKER_29]: Did you tell?
[SPEAKER_29]: Are you a tattletale?
[SPEAKER_33]: I just wanted to see what they'd say.
[SPEAKER_29]: Did they reply?
[SPEAKER_33]: Yeah, they did.
[SPEAKER_33]: They said that they were forwarding it to their... Because I did... It was to Konami of Hawaii and they were forwarding it to Konami of America or something.
[SPEAKER_33]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_33]: Some other Konami division.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because Konami's got like 50 different divisions and we can't tell.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're all Konami to us.
[SPEAKER_33]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, interesting.
[SPEAKER_33]: This is the same day that I also wrote the email to Pia.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki's been a big tattletale this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is that website, Savetoby.com?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's this website where they're threatening to kill a bunny.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I was joking in Loki's live journal, I said, ha ha, you should send that to PETA, I bet they'd have a field day with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he did!
[SPEAKER_09]: He sent it to them, and they wrote back this huge old email that said, people like to play pranks on the internet, and that's just sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_33]: I hate PETA.
[SPEAKER_33]: I so hate them, but I just wanted to see that website get shut down, because he's making lots of money.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like 15 grand off of it so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: Explicit, your thoughts on this?
[SPEAKER_09]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_32]: First we have the 20% speed up DDR Extreme Plus, and now we have this type of crap that doesn't even work at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, oh my gods, you can play Go West in the arcade and everything, and your reign.
[SPEAKER_32]: But the sides don't work, so what's the point?
[SPEAKER_32]: The pads are going to be broken within the next day.
[SPEAKER_32]: Would there be an actual point of playing the game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it looks like... Actually, I'm getting a private message from...
[SPEAKER_09]: One of our buddies in chat, and he's actually sending me a link to a picture that shows you can actually get the modifiers in this crappy game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me post this picture.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope they don't mind, but I'm going to post it in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so you can take a look at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You actually can access the modifiers in this somehow.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like somebody figured it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you know how they did it?
[SPEAKER_33]: They said they stomped on a bunch of the buttons.
[SPEAKER_33]: That's honestly what they did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, maybe?
[SPEAKER_33]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_33]: But they have some videos.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe what they're trying to do is just inspire the... They're getting their inspiration from the old mixes of DDR.
[SPEAKER_33]: Remember back when kids... They're trying to make a buck off Namco.
[SPEAKER_33]: Honestly, I could take a shit in a box, put it in a DDR cabinet and sell it to Namco and they'd fucking buy it because they're retarded.
[SPEAKER_29]: No left down...
[SPEAKER_29]: Remember when left, down, right, down, left was little?
[SPEAKER_29]: Little!
[SPEAKER_33]: You know, honestly, um, I should, you know, just create some stupid mix right now of Step Mania and Cellotome.
[SPEAKER_33]: I can make money.
[SPEAKER_33]: They're gonna buy it.
[SPEAKER_33]: I'll say, it's DDR9th mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: And wouldn't that be ironic if Konami came after you because somebody tattled on you just like you tattled on these guys?
[SPEAKER_33]: Well, obviously they haven't come after these people since they keep making them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, explicit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of selling a Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_32]: Speaking of that, does anybody remember about some guy in eBay selling an actual bootlegged CD of Step Mania and saying DDR Complete?
[SPEAKER_33]: You can sell Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_33]: You can.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's in the license agreement.
[SPEAKER_33]: You just can't include songs with it.
[SPEAKER_32]: Yeah, and one of the songs says banner.png.
[SPEAKER_32]: Our first, second, third, fourth, fifth, and et cetera, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what happened with this on eBay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did something happen?
[SPEAKER_32]: Six people bought it.
[SPEAKER_32]: Six people actually bought it.
[SPEAKER_32]: For ten bucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: The average Joe gamer doesn't know though.
[SPEAKER_09]: The average parent that sees DDR on Good Morning America and wants to get it for their kids doesn't know crap about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: These people are just preying off the week.
[SPEAKER_32]: Okay, it does not include any of the MP3s.
[SPEAKER_32]: Two, the way everything is organized in terms of folder-wise, you get Hides Off You in 6th, 7th, and 8th mix, so you have duplicates of the same song.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like those 64-in-1 Taiwanese bootlegs that you used to be able to get for the NES.
[SPEAKER_32]: Exactly, just like those.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where it would have Contra in it eight times, but maybe the player was a different color.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought that for my friend for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where the zapper gun looked like a normal gun.
[SPEAKER_33]: And the controller was an old Nintendo 64 controller that had the analog stick glued in there.
[SPEAKER_33]: And then the other controller was a Genesis controller that they wired up.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's funny, because after Christmas or whatever, they never came back to their kiosk in the mall.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm surprised people don't put this show up on eBay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll sue your ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, we won't.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should put copies of this show on eBay and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to buy them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, we're probably violating all sorts of copyright laws by doing that, but hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's going on in the sim scene right now, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything going on in the sim scene?
[SPEAKER_09]: Even though all the sites are down?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um... No.
[SPEAKER_33]: Really, I don't think there's anything going on.
[SPEAKER_33]: I can't confirm that since my computer's broken, but...
[SPEAKER_33]: MaxVagina
[SPEAKER_09]: On that note, I think we're going to go to another break.
[SPEAKER_09]: When we come back, boys and girls, we're going to get into tonight's match game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And after the match game, we're going to do the cage match and all those other segments you've come to know and love here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we will be back after this.
[SPEAKER_09]: In this break, hmm, how about we're going to do some Smile DK to start it off because we haven't played Smile DK in a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for watching!
Stand by your friends!
Wow!
[SPEAKER_21]: Stand by your friends who's wild!
Stand by your friends who's wild!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you for watching!
I, I, I, I, I, boom, boom, boom, boom Y, I, I, I, boom, boom, boom, boom And all the bottom more time Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually have a prize for our winner tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not with me, but I will send it to them.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a Resident Evil 4 music sampler.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very cool!
[SPEAKER_09]: An actual prize!
[SPEAKER_17]: And I have an ESPN Sports one, too, if they want a whole pack of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: So tonight, you don't get hung up on if you win, or you get your window closed, I suppose, if you're the chatroom contestant.
[SPEAKER_09]: You win an actual prize!
[SPEAKER_09]: Amazing!
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, the winner, going to the winner, will be the company Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to see if I... I don't have my match game theme music anymore, and I don't have Loki's computer to leech it from, so I suppose we'll have to fill in with our listless music tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or I could just cough in the microphone.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be a lovely way to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about we just play Genocide and that'll be the match game music?
[SPEAKER_33]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_33]: How is Resident Evil 4?
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't really played it yet.
[SPEAKER_32]: I haven't really played it yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen it, and it looks very rad.
[SPEAKER_32]: It's very good.
[SPEAKER_32]: It's practically, if you're one of the casual games, it's probably one of the best, or by far the best Resident Evil out there.
[SPEAKER_33]: Wow, more dogs jumping through windows than you can ever imagine.
[SPEAKER_32]: I mean, it's like an actual 3D game, rather than just a side, like a camera view that was in 1, 2, and 3.
[SPEAKER_32]: You actually get to see everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nobody's calling in right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, what the mobasses?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, we got that buffer, so it kind of makes things difficult, because we have a slight delay between the time I say, call now, and the time that they actually hear me say, call now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know what else is interesting is that a lot of our regulars who call in on the skypline are not here tonight, which is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, what is going on tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: What makes tonight so special?
[SPEAKER_17]: 3 Day Weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I don't have a 3 Day Weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why do these people get a 3 Day Weekend?
[SPEAKER_17]: Some of us work for a bank.
[SPEAKER_17]: Guess who doesn't have to work tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_09]: That didn't really work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'd think by giving away a prize we'd have more people calling in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just have them do it through the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we have people that are in chat going, Oh, I've played before so I can't play again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure you can play again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: We actually have a prize to give away tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: That makes everybody eligible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, if nobody calls in the first week, because I know we've got a ton of people who are in chat, because we have quite a few people in chat tonight, but they just aren't on the Skype line, because, you know, you have to download Skype, and then you have to set it up, and da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll just sit here and wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll just sit here for the next two hours.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'll just wait!
[SPEAKER_10]: We can do that!
[SPEAKER_10]: Tick-tock, tick-tock!
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: How stupid do we look right now?
[SPEAKER_33]: I see Paris Hilton's gonna be in a new horror movie coming up, and it's called The Wax House.
[SPEAKER_33]: It looks decent.
[SPEAKER_33]: Except Paris Hilton's in it, and she doesn't get naked, probably.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have something to add to that, that you could probably make fun of.
[SPEAKER_16]: I heard her sidekick got hacked.
[SPEAKER_16]: Her T-Mobile sidekick got hacked.
[SPEAKER_09]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_09]: We will be doing Paris Hilton chat until somebody calls in the Skype line, so I suggest somebody start downloading it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fucking call already.
[SPEAKER_33]: She did all Skype in if I... No, wait, no, I can't because my computer's down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, you guys, did you see The Simple Life this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, it was so funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys, Paris Hilton was so funny on The Civil Life this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know that one part when she said, That's hot?
[SPEAKER_09]: That was so hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, I love The Civil Life.
[SPEAKER_33]: And she was working at a morgue I hear.
[SPEAKER_33]: And with her and the dead bodies, and that was so creepy.
[SPEAKER_33]: Like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then she totally needed to have a makeover.
[SPEAKER_33]: She's like so my idol.
[SPEAKER_33]: Like, I just want to be her one of these days.
[SPEAKER_33]: I wish I could be so rich and have all those clothes and the shoes.
[SPEAKER_33]: Oh my gods.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, sorry, my mic was off for a minute there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, you guys, did you see that episode where they were at the airport and they had to be the airport people and they were like waving and it looked like they were dancing and they were just playing around and then they had to empty the poo out of the plane as punishment.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Paris Hilton was so funny.
[SPEAKER_33]: And then the poo fell on them and then she's like, wow, I haven't done this since last year.
[SPEAKER_33]: Usually they pay extra the shit on me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I was just about to spit seven up through my nose there.
[SPEAKER_33]: Then that one time where she was working at a fast food joint, and she's like, wow, there's more cock in here than I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_33]: And it was funny because it's... Oh, we're getting a call, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yo, Sky, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have saved everybody from Paris Hilton chat, and now we can finally play match game.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now the Skype line is lighting up with calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got like four people hammering in all at once now.
[SPEAKER_09]: You ever hear that saying, you snooze, you lose?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, apply it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You automatically win my eternal gratefulness.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have my gratitude forever.
[SPEAKER_17]: And the ferret loves you, too.
[SPEAKER_30]: And I love the ferrets, too.
[SPEAKER_30]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, finally.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to know who you're playing against tonight, Siggy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you're playing for Resident Evil 4 sampler CD.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that exciting?
[SPEAKER_30]: Even though I don't play Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's Resident Evil 4, so that's alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's no way in hell I'm ever getting rid of my Silent Hill 4 sampler.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think you just lost right there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I am lost.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to play against MPQ in our chat room tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: MPQ is going to bring it.
[SPEAKER_09]: He was the guy who got our trivia question right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I feel better.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get into tonight's match game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know how the match game works, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to ask you a question.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it has a blank in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then your job is to fill in the blank, and for every celebrity in the chatroom, or I'm sorry, every celebrity in the studio that you match, you get a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now here's the thing, I'm going to be asking for an answer from MPQ as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for every answer that he matches, he gets a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he might walk away with that Resident Evil 4 sampler.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, don't let him do that, or you'll never understand the difference between Resident Evil and Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, repeat after me, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_22]: Resident Evil, yeah, I got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Capcom.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_22]: Konami.
[SPEAKER_22]: Konami, there you go.
[SPEAKER_33]: Good.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know.
[SPEAKER_33]: Yo, yo, turn down the Nature's Oxide.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe we should send him a box of milk bones, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe we should send him another prize.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see if he's worth it.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll send you a rawhide bone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see how he does.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: First question.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, hey that's me, was all excited to start a brand new blogger this week all about his video game addictions.
[SPEAKER_09]: The staff and regulars of Orange Lounge Radio, though, were shocked when they visited the blog to find that the first entry wasn't about games at all, but about blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, don't answer just yet, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll let celebrities have a chance to answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio staff was surprised to visit the blogger
[SPEAKER_09]: to find that it wasn't about video games at all, but the first entry was all about blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody's writing down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, MPQ's locked in an answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie's dinged in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: We got it?
[SPEAKER_30]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: How you doing, Explicit?
[SPEAKER_09]: Got an answer?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Staff and regulars of Horne's Lounge, though, were shocked when they visited the blog to find that the first entry wasn't about games at all, but about blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel, you got one?
[SPEAKER_09]: Still thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel's still thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the first thing that comes to your mind, Angel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob was all excited to start a brand new blogger this week, all about his video game addictions.
[SPEAKER_09]: The staff and regulars of Orange Launch Radio, though, were shocked when they visited the blog to find that the first entry wasn't about games at all, but about blank.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, looks like she's written something down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Explicit, you good to go, too?
[SPEAKER_09]: Boobies Boobies Not a match, sorry
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I totally forgot the other person.
[SPEAKER_09]: MPQ put all about ham.
[SPEAKER_09]: All about ham.
[SPEAKER_09]: So boobies is not a match with ham or random prawn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gay porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gay porn, I do believe that would be a match with Siggy.
[SPEAKER_09]: So one point for Siggy, zero for MPQ.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, shocked to find it was all about Paris Hilton and her wonderful shoes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Paris Hilton!
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're going to give me a look from now.
[SPEAKER_15]: I said Kylie.
[SPEAKER_09]: All about Kylie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very good answer, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: My answer was it was all about how he needed a date.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the part where you feel pity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Feel pity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Siggy's up by a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go, question number two.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's MPQ's chance to catch up here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki was very sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, where's my music?
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's my music?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki was very sad that his computer broke down.
[SPEAKER_09]: It seemed like the power supply just didn't want to cooperate anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: He tried to fix it himself, but couldn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he had his friend look at the PC, who explained moments after opening it that...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Loki, maybe it wouldn't have broken down so fast if you hadn't downloaded so much blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Loki, maybe it wouldn't have broke if you hadn't downloaded so much blank.
[SPEAKER_30]: Very funny allusion.
[SPEAKER_30]: Very funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see our chat room there, huh?
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_30]: Hey, laughter is my life, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't this great?
[SPEAKER_09]: When you call in the Skype line to the show, the chat room feels the need to make fun of you as well as the rest of us here in studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: One more time, I'll read this for the folks still thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki was very sad that his computer broke down.
[SPEAKER_09]: It seemed like the power supply just didn't want to cooperate anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: He tried to fix it himself, but couldn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he had his friend look at the PC, who explained moments after opening it that, Well, Loki, maybe it wouldn't have broken down so fast if you hadn't downloaded so much blank.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still waiting on the answer from MPQ as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh no, there it is.
[SPEAKER_33]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: How you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are we ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: Looks like Angel's ready.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, everybody else is ready.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think... Alright, we got MPQ's answer too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: This time we'll go with MPQ first.
[SPEAKER_09]: MPQ says, Well, Loki, maybe it wouldn't have broken down so fast if you hadn't downloaded so much... PORN!
[SPEAKER_09]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Going for the obvious one there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wouldn't have broken down so fast if you hadn't downloaded so much... That mania sim files!
[SPEAKER_09]: Step Mania Sim Files.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, good answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie, wouldn't have broken so fast if you hadn't downloaded so much.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, I have to make this grammatically correct.
[SPEAKER_17]: So many.
[SPEAKER_17]: Final Fantasy XI porn patches.
[SPEAKER_09]: Final Fantasy XI porn patches.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that a point for MPQ?
[SPEAKER_17]: Half a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Half a point for MPQ.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's so many of those online.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's half a point to one point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remixes of girls Remixes of girls
[SPEAKER_09]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I said, it wouldn't have broken so fast if you hadn't downloaded so many crappy remixes of Max 300.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, now, Max Vagina has its special place in everyone's heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, MPQ has half a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Siggy has one point.
[SPEAKER_09]: It all comes down to this question.
[SPEAKER_09]: One point for MPQ could win it if Siggy doesn't get any.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we will see.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's good he got half a point because this way we're not going to have a tie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless we get a half a point on this next one.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we've had a question about me, a question about Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you know who this next one's about.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shermie.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura decided that she was going to head out to RVGL to play some DER.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, the pads were broken.
[SPEAKER_09]: And even more unfortunately for the parents and children present, they were shocked to hear DarkSakura call the RVGL pads a blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were shocked to hear DarkSakura call the Roseville Golf Land pads a blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can play with the grammar on that one a little bit if you need to.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll make this a little harder.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can play with the grammar.
[SPEAKER_09]: So she called the RVGL pads blank, or she called them a blank.
[SPEAKER_33]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_33]: You know, if we go this year, we need to go see The Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_33]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_33]: He isn't going to be living much longer.
[SPEAKER_33]: I mean, that hair can't turn much whiter.
[SPEAKER_33]: He'll be transparent soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were shocked to hear DarkSakura call the RVGL pads a blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops, I didn't copy that question for MPQ.
[SPEAKER_09]: He might want to answer that.
[SPEAKER_09]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now MPQ can answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing, I'm just laughing at one of the answers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody ready in studio?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the last question.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is going to determine who walks away with a Resident Evil 4 music sampler.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura decided that she was going to head out to RVGL and play some DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, the pads were broken, and even more unfortunately for the parents and children present, they were shocked to hear DarkSakura call the RVGL pads a... Siggy?
[SPEAKER_30]: Piece of shit pad!
[SPEAKER_09]: Piece of shit pad!
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a piece of shit car, but a piece of shit pad.
[SPEAKER_09]: MPQ's answer says...
[SPEAKER_09]: was shocked to hear DarkSakura call the Roseville Golf Land pads a, and I quote, fucking fuck shit fucker.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we will see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Piece of shit pad and fucking fuck shit fucker.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your answer, please.
[SPEAKER_17]: Metallic equivalent of fetid regurgitated dog shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because they were all too stupid to know what fetid means.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_09]: Explicit, your answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: A motherfucking bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: A motherfucking bitch!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of close, but I'm not going to count it as a match.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Called them a... The loos.
[SPEAKER_09]: The loos.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are to loos.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_16]: Called the pads a... Let's just say she dropped the C-bomb.
[SPEAKER_09]: She dropped the C-bomb.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rhymes with punt or shunt.
[SPEAKER_17]: I couldn't think of anything else to quote Bette Midler.
[SPEAKER_17]: It starts with a C and ends with a T and it spells cunt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now that would have been a good answer.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's a direct quote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It all comes down to this.
[SPEAKER_09]: If MPQ matches me on this one, he's walking away with a CD.
[SPEAKER_09]: If nobody matches me or Siggy matches it, Siggy's walking away with that CD.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were shocked to hear DarkSakura call the Roseville Golf Land pads a...
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry your time than staying at home watching the Paris Hilton porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Making Siggy our winner!
[SPEAKER_09]: By a half point.
[SPEAKER_17]: So if you want the CD, send me an email.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or actually, PM me your address and I will mail it to you.
[SPEAKER_33]: Now, now, watching the Paris Hilton video is not that sorry of a time.
[SPEAKER_33]: It is rather entertaining.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Siggy, you're our winner and you're going to win that Resident Evil 4 sampler.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm actually kind of glad you won it because now you'll be able to tell the difference between Resident Evil and Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_09]: So thanks for playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any victory speech you want to give?
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, not much, but I got some latest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, some actual news on this show?
[SPEAKER_30]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: The hell?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up, Siggy?
[SPEAKER_30]: The last unlocked one was for the Scorpion Fire.
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, that's the only one confirmed, number 13.
[SPEAKER_29]: Any response to the chat room?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're teasing you on your laugh.
[SPEAKER_30]: Do you have anything you want to say in response to that?
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, I don't care what these people say.
[SPEAKER_30]: I just like to laugh the way I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_09]: You preach on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't give a crap what our chatroom says.
[SPEAKER_09]: We sure don't, alright?
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_30]: The song A and AA, they're actually pronounced as ace and double ace.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ace and double ace.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, like a deck of cards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ace and double ace.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like A and AA.
[SPEAKER_09]: I...
[SPEAKER_09]: Screw that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to call a member.
[SPEAKER_09]: EDR is the 13th step.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or A and A. Ah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for the call, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Congratulations on your win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Email.
[SPEAKER_09]: You got Jamie's email, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, I'll just send a private message.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: He'll send a private message.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I'm in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Congratulations, man.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you, Sky.
[SPEAKER_09]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just wanted to be accurate.
[SPEAKER_17]: According to Dennis, Larry Nyquil is the 13th step.
[SPEAKER_33]: When I hear the word ace, I can't help but think of... Of, um... What was that?
[SPEAKER_33]: Wild Zero?
[SPEAKER_33]: Or whatever?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_33]: Or, not Wild Zero, um... That stupid zombie movie.
[SPEAKER_33]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no idea what you're talking about right now.
[SPEAKER_33]: That was Wild Zero.
[SPEAKER_33]: Yeah, it was Wild Zero.
[SPEAKER_17]: I got you the soundtrack, the record for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have that still.
[SPEAKER_17]: Who was it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Guitar... Guitar Wolf.
[SPEAKER_17]: Guitar Wolf, that was it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ace!
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm lost.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Every time I hear Ace, I start thinking of this line from Red Dwarf.
[SPEAKER_17]: Your nickname was never Ace, maybe Ace Hole.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're an Ace Hole.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know if anybody in here watched a lot of Red Dwarf, but Rimmer always called himself Ace, and finally Lister told him off and said that his nickname was Ace Hole.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to go to break, and in this break we're going to hear... I decide we'll play some number 13, and we'll play some Ace as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or as I like to say it, Ah!
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll play that, and then we're going to do the cage match when we come back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio
Thanks for watching!
From the steps by the Orange Lab, this DDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_09]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio and Jamie's spreading the inside joke love here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is an old joke from Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, wasn't that reunion show supposed to happen like soon?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's supposed to eventually.
[SPEAKER_29]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: But this was back when Mint Skittles came out
[SPEAKER_17]: and Travis was joking about them making mint scattles to make your butt be minty fresh.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I made a label for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You actually made the label in PaintShop Pro.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, I forgot you're not a Photoshop girl.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have to use Photoshop and I hate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway,
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: EverQuest 2
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they're going to add a new command line feature into EverQuest 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know how you can slash say, slash fight, you type in the little command slash whatever?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they're putting a new one into EverQuest 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called slash pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you type slash pizza, it'll actually open up a little web browser right on top of your EverQuest 2 screen and take you directly to PizzaHut.com where you can order a pizza and have it delivered immediately.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right to your home so that you can play EverQuest all night long.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's fucking sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is exactly why I wanted to bring this up for Jamie's reaction.
[SPEAKER_31]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_09]: Slash pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: If they incorporated this into Final Fantasy XI, Jamie, do you see this as a feature you'd ever use?
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: And why not?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because if I'm hungry, I can go into the kitchen and cook some food.
[SPEAKER_17]: If I wanted to go out to eat, my ass would log out and go out to eat.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_17]: There's real people out in the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you've had pizza delivered to you before, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe once in a while?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, but not like because I was too lazy to log my ass off the damn game and go get it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Right, you order pizza because, you know, you want... I was too lazy to go get away from my movie and go get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: The sad thing is, I know people that will use, I would probably use this quite a bit if they put this in Final Fantasy XI, but at the same time, that would probably be the point where I'd have to say, oh my god, Rob, look at yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Should I be happy if we had a Pizza Hut near us?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's true, we don't even have a Pizza Hut in town.
[SPEAKER_17]: The pizza place closest to my house is actually Roundtable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, so even if they built this into Final Fantasy XI, we wouldn't be able to use it.
[SPEAKER_09]: If we could only pay for those pizzas in Gil.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the next thing we're moving to.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if you could pay for the pizza using the online game currency?
[SPEAKER_09]: How sad would that be?
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be really sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or like, if you order the pizza, then your character gets a vitality up or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maximum hit points have increased because you ordered Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this where advertising is going?
[SPEAKER_09]: Order Taco Bell and receive bio effect.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, and if you, like, order from Del Taco, you get the dia one.
[SPEAKER_17]: You mean diarrhea?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that what you... Okay.
[SPEAKER_31]: Or anything...
[SPEAKER_31]: Order any hot sauce to cast fire.
[SPEAKER_31]: Actually, Faraga, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your ass begins casting fire on little goblin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, that's amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: What other slash features do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: First, slash pizza, what's next?
[SPEAKER_09]: Slash blowjob?
[SPEAKER_09]: Get a hooker to come to your house and have sex with you because nobody else will because you play EverQuest all day?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, you'd order an in-game prostitute.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I would like to just kind of humor that question.
[SPEAKER_09]: What other type of slash features would you like to see in EverQuest?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, this might make a good list list later on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would think a good one would be slash exercise, where when you type it in, the game shuts down and your computer shuts off and it won't let you turn it on for 50 minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you have to go out and exercise.
[SPEAKER_33]: Yes, you can see my computer has gone into that feature right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently you typed it in earlier, Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, you actually have this bodysuit that you wear.
[SPEAKER_17]: And if you type in slash exercise, then these little things stimulate your muscles to contract.
[SPEAKER_09]: They actually do have those.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like those ab things that they put on your abs?
[SPEAKER_17]: You want to know what that is?
[SPEAKER_17]: And this is a story.
[SPEAKER_17]: A long time ago when I worked at GNC, I hurt my butt.
[SPEAKER_17]: I actually strained the muscle that sits on top of my sciatic nerve.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I had to have that done to my butt.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so they would make the muscles contract and expand to the point that it gets tired out as though you had exercised it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And that's all that that ab thing is.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it just makes you feel like you've exercised it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just to wear out the muscles to the point it would relax.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because for me it was hitting the nerve.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds painful.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could never put one of those things on.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's light electricity.
[SPEAKER_17]: But they also do that for patients who have...
[SPEAKER_17]: to keep the muscles from atrophy.
[SPEAKER_29]: Isn't that like how Spider-Man became Spider-Man?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, he got bitten by a damn radioactive spider.
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, radioactive spider, radioactive ab belt, same thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not radioactive, it's electricity.
[SPEAKER_17]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess we'll get into the Orange Lounge Radio cage match since all those jokes are...
[SPEAKER_17]: I agree with Elmo.
[SPEAKER_17]: There needs to be a slash slash.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, except they said, for me, what are you implying?
[SPEAKER_09]: That I can't write my own erotic stories offline?
[SPEAKER_09]: Please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's get into tonight's cage match, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: The way the cage match works, you have to be in our chat room if you want to participate.
[SPEAKER_09]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Click on Chat and you can participate.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the way the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match works, we put three songs in for your listening pleasure or displeasure, whatever the case may be, and you vote for your favorite.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music & More program, which plays 24 hours a day, 7 days a week on this station when we're not doing something live.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so last week in the Orange Launch Radio Cage Match, this song won for the second time in a row, so it's going for its third win this week, we shall see.
[SPEAKER_09]: You only get to hear a clip of it though, because you've already heard it before.
[SPEAKER_09]: So here it is, a clip of song number one that you can vote for tonight, Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know the band from Amplitude and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Freeze Pop was Stakeout.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_20]: The feeling is elating, biding my time Yeah, I know that you'll soon be mine Soon to mine Can't let you see me Can't let you see me
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's our returning champion, Freeze Pop with Stakeout.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is up against two new songs this week, starting off with a song that Jamie picked, and it actually looks like one I've heard before, but not in this.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't remember the name of the song, I just picked it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's the filter in Crystal Method.
[SPEAKER_17]: and I don't remember the name of the song.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called Can't You Trip Like I Do.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was actually a popular song several years ago, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spawn soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was on the Spawn soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_17]: See, I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just like the song.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, there's nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, I put Gwen Stefani in and it ended up getting retired.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing wrong with putting a popular song in.
[SPEAKER_33]: That's why they picked this song as a cadence like way earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, you picked Crystal Method before, but never this one.
[SPEAKER_33]: Who the hell cares anyways?
[SPEAKER_33]: We can't remember it.
[SPEAKER_33]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: If we don't remember, then it wasn't in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Song number two of tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_09]: Filter and Crystal Method.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't you trip like I do?
[SPEAKER_20]: Just like I do
Just like that Just like that Just like that
Thanks for watching!
We can't you trip like me We can't you trip like me
[SPEAKER_32]: I like the drums in the actual song.
[SPEAKER_32]: I mean, it's a pretty good song, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_32]: The voice is kind of, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_32]: I'd say 8.5.
8.5.
[SPEAKER_33]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_33]: This song is old.
[SPEAKER_33]: I used to play this song while playing Cusar.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, it gets the 9.
[SPEAKER_33]: The spontaneous record is good.
[SPEAKER_33]: I like Satan on there.
[SPEAKER_33]: That was my favorite one.
[SPEAKER_09]: You would.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel.
9.
[SPEAKER_16]: Junker Cover Pants.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, 9. 9.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I give, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I give it, um, it's like one of those songs, like it starts off really, really cool, and then as it goes on, I'm kind of like, alright, time to end.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I still like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's groovy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I give it like a 7.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your turn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Song number three tonight is by you.
[SPEAKER_09]: What'd you pick?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's not by you, but you picked it.
[SPEAKER_33]: Uh, well, um, this song, um, I don't really know how to describe this song, this song is just different, it's one of those things I found on Amazon when searching for free music, um, and it's just catchy, I, I don't know, a lot of people aren't gonna like it, but, you know, I like, I've been listening to my car, it's just catchy, and apparently it's, it was, it's a
[SPEAKER_33]: I guess on the charts over in India, because that's, you know, it's an Indian artist, DJ Siddharth did the remix of it, and it's from a movie, I can't remember what the movie's called though, I think it's like Tamil or something like that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_33]: But yeah, it's a very, it's an interesting song.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's trancy, dancey, it's got a little bit of guitar in the background.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you pronounce this name?
[SPEAKER_33]: I think it's pronounced like Keka Keka or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's the artist, Keka Keka.
[SPEAKER_33]: Keka Keka is the artist.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's the Tamil song is the name of the actual song.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says in the title, it says, and I apologize profusely to everybody.
[SPEAKER_33]: That's the movie it's from, actually.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's the movie that it's from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yuri and Yuri.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yuri and Yuri, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yuri and Yuri, that's the movie that it's from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_33]: Tamil is the language that I think it's spoken in, and...
[SPEAKER_33]: It's the title song for that movie and it's remixed by this guy DJ Siddharth and the artist was Keka Keka.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, DJ Siddharth remixing Keka Keka.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
S.T.A.R.S
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we are back, and that was Kika Kika, DJ Siddharth remixing that, a song we, I believe, and I apologize again for butchering, absolutely butchering the pronunciation of this, Yurian Yuri.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see what you guys think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was pretty good, 8.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: 8.5 from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exquisite.
[SPEAKER_32]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_32]: For some reason, I didn't like the beginning too much, but once I started getting to the actual music, I liked it.
8.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: 8.5 from Miss Blissett.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_33]: I love the backbeat to that song.
[SPEAKER_33]: That was one of the things about DJ Siddharth, even his other stuff that he has, he has really good beats to all of it.
[SPEAKER_33]: Why he chose, I mean, I understand why he chose to remix that song, because he's, you know, an Indian DJ, so, I mean, it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_33]: But, um, it was, I don't know, I...
[SPEAKER_33]: If I understood the vocals, I'm sure it'd make more sense, or if I heard the original song, it'd make more sense to me, but since I didn't, you know, I give it a 9, though.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's decent, but it probably is annoying to a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Angel!
[SPEAKER_16]: I liked it a lot, just like another, well, Indian artist that I heard.
[SPEAKER_16]: It kind of just reminded me of that, so, um, I'll be nice.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_29]: I actually surprisingly like that song quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think it needed some of the fat trimmed from it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like the beginning was a little slow and there's some parts that could have been cut.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that song was just about over six minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think it could have been cut down a little bit, a little more compact, about four minutes probably would have been good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, though, I do like the beat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like kind of what they remixed there.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand, though, why it has the big beginning, because it's probably meant for mixing in to your normal... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as far as, you know, playing it by itself, it kind of hurts it for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I give it an 8.5, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was still a good song.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is surprising that I liked yet another Loki's Caveman song.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know the one you put in a couple weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been listening to it a ton in my car.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which song was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: The Echoing Green one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I actually downloaded, you know the funny thing about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Echo Image, because you said it sounded like them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Echo Image actually remixed that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's available on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually used one of my free songs for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: It really sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was so sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, good song, good band, this is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, anyway, back to the issue at hand here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's recap the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Song number one, last week's winner, Freeze Pop, Stakeout.
[SPEAKER_09]: And song number two you can vote for tonight, Filter and the Crystal Method.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't you trip like I do?
[SPEAKER_21]: I do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just like I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to pick the quietest part of that song by random there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keka Keka, remixed by DJ Sidarth, is song number three, Urine Uri.
Urine Uri.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that ever going to come out?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm starting to worry.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's still not out.
[SPEAKER_09]: What in the hell is going on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody needs to get bitch slapped, and I don't think it's Konami, I think it's somebody at Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess they're too busy concerning themselves with the Xboxes that caught on fire, or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you heard about this, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: The Microsoft had to recall the power cords for Xboxes that were made prior to October 2003, because I guess if you leave it on for a prolonged period of time, it will catch fire!
[SPEAKER_09]: They say it's only a 1 in 10,000 chance, but those types of lawsuits are still a pretty big deal, so they've got to recall, and they'll send you a free power cord.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got an email on it, although I believe my particular Xbox is immune because it's a Halo Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got the Halo Limited Edition.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think it affects these.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still got an email on it because they suspect it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got to check it out at least.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any comments on this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything you guys have heard extra on this?
[SPEAKER_17]: Our first Xbox already died, so it's kinda moot for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess that's what I hear is that the Xboxes don't last too long usually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the email I got.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says, Microsoft has chosen to replace the power cords on Xbox consoles manufactured before October 23, 2003.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our records indicate that you may own one of these consoles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, that's me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Check the manufacture date on the bottom of your console.
[SPEAKER_09]: No action is necessary if your console is manufactured on or after October 23, 2003.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now I'm all curious.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki's going to look.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki's going to go look at that manufacture date.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought I bought mine after that, but I guess that doesn't mean it was manufactured after that date, necessarily.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what's sad?
[SPEAKER_09]: That must have actually happened for them to realize it.
[SPEAKER_32]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_32]: April 16th?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, my Xbox was made April 16th, 2004.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am immune, motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_32]: That's my birthday.
[SPEAKER_32]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_32]: Yeah, that's the exact date of my birthday.
[SPEAKER_32]: I was like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_32]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I haven't had my Xbox that long.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because those Halo ones just came out, so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should get a new cord anyway, just because they're really expensive otherwise.
[SPEAKER_32]: Oh, yeah, just get it for free since they're...
[SPEAKER_32]: You know, fixing the problem, according to what they're saying.
[SPEAKER_32]: When did this happen, though?
[SPEAKER_32]: I didn't hear about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, it's just this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox sent out all the emails to people this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, check your Xboxes, kids.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have an Xbox that was manufactured before October 23rd, 2003, you better get a new power cord, or there might be a fire!
[SPEAKER_09]: A bad fire!
[SPEAKER_32]: Fry-cro-soft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fry-cro-soft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: Mario Kart Arcade
[SPEAKER_09]: Discuss.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bitches, you all going down.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's going to have Pac-Man and Ms.
[SPEAKER_17]: Pac-Man in it, and it's put up by Namco.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, because Namco and Nintendo teamed up for this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the thing I'm wondering, and it's the thing that I've been wondering a while.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's on Triforce hardware.
[SPEAKER_33]: Triforce, three companies.
[SPEAKER_33]: Namco, Nintendo, and Sega.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Sega being the one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where are the Sega characters?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's a good question.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, Sega has better things they could be doing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like putting out another Knights game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sonic does not get a car.
[SPEAKER_09]: How much do you want to bet?
[SPEAKER_33]: This is going to be tied in with either another Mario Kart game that's going to be released for the GameCube or the new console.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, because it looks like... Because that was the way F-Zero worked, is that it kind of teamed up with one of the home versions there.
[SPEAKER_17]: It should be a card game.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can save your progress.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, it does have the card.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Mario Kart is supposed to have the card system with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like F-Zero did.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's very interesting that they're using so many card games now.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, back when the Neo Geos were first kind of big... God, I remember those.
[SPEAKER_17]: They were supposed to have it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I remember watching this back on... What was the show?
[SPEAKER_17]: It was GamePro...
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know the GamePro show was filmed locally here in this area?
[SPEAKER_17]: I lived in Alabama at the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, yeah, it was filmed at the Channel 3 studios.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that weird?
[SPEAKER_17]: But I remember where you were supposed to have a memory card that worked from your Neo Geo home system to the arcade systems.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: Between the MVS and the AVS.
[SPEAKER_17]: I never... And I actually saw the machine... You know, you can look on the old Neo Geo machines and actually see the card readers on them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would it be maybe that that didn't catch on because nobody owned a Neo Geo because of the price?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, granted, I know you own a Neo Geo, but you are an exception to the rule.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's because me and Dan are cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I mean, you got, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was like cheaper to buy the arcade system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, you might as well have bought the arcade system for how much that thing cost.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know, he'll have to correct me on this one, but I think he traded a Sega CD for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's the thing, is that really that's why it was so damn much, because in a way you were getting the arcade system on your TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it was like the same system.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was the same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we're going to go to a break, boys and girls, so we can tally up the cage match votes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when we come back, we're going to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please don't send in your FUs of the week just yet, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got to get the cage match out of the way and then we'll accept those.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll let you know when.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, whoa, excuse me, we will be back after this with more, excuse me, how unprofessional, but when was this show ever professional?
[SPEAKER_09]: More Orange Entredo.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to start off this break with something Jamie wanted to hear, and I think this is an appropriate song considering the Xbox news we just talked about.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll be back after this.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Mr. Random Person on the Street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think of the Orange Lounge mainlining music in more shows?
[SPEAKER_23]: The music is like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's unearthly.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's like being at a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: and we're going to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But first, boys and girls, I bet you are dying to know who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chirp!
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, we're all dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight's cage match was so close that only one vote separated a tie between
[SPEAKER_09]: You look so sweet and clueless You've been moving on my brain for too long
[SPEAKER_09]: Song number two being one vote behind.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, in the Orange Lounge rules, it states that the host whose song did not tie gets to break the tie.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, Jamie, is it going to be Freeze Pop or Keka Keka?
[SPEAKER_09]: Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Freeze Pop is the winner once again!
[SPEAKER_21]: Just because I want to irritate the people who don't like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Freeze Pop wins for the third week in a row.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guess what, boys and girls?
[SPEAKER_09]: If it wins next week, it will be the third song in Orange Lounge history to get retired from the Orange Lounge Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other ones being Gwen Stefani, Whatcha Waitin' For, and Echo Image, Come Back are the two other songs that have been retired.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't believe that Gwen Stefani went those whole four weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you heard her new single, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's totally hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to put it in the cage match later.
[SPEAKER_29]: If I was a rich girl... Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's from Fiddler on the Roof.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: It is, but it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And in the video, they're all dressed up like pirates.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why should they be dressed up as pirates for a song that's from... Because it's MTV.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's from...
[SPEAKER_17]: and a play about Russian Jews.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: That's... Has anybody ever seen... I was going to say, is that your girlfriend, Loki?
[SPEAKER_21]: Fiddler on the Roof?
[SPEAKER_33]: She would qualify the Russian Jew part, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to start calling your girlfriend Fiddler on the Roof.
[SPEAKER_17]: Gwen Stefani now has dropped in my esteem.
[SPEAKER_17]: But she's cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: But she's being an idiot.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I don't appreciate idiots.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: We need to do the FUs now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And why is it that we do these FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because of Gwen Stefani.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck musicians who think they can get away with taking something that was perfectly fine the way it was and completely misinterpreting it in such a horrible way.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck you, Gwen Stefani, right in your ear.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because your ass isn't good enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: In fact, your ass is probably... Never mind, I won't say anything else about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what's ironic?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that she's dating a guy from a band named Bush.
[SPEAKER_17]: And fuck you, Gavin, for dating her.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody just got told.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's exactly what your fianc in the chatroom just said.
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody just got told.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: And FU goes to...
[SPEAKER_17]: See, I drove past an accident yesterday that was caused by an old person driving a car.
[SPEAKER_17]: They need to make people, once they hit a certain age, take a very strict driving test.
[SPEAKER_17]: Another SU goes towards idiots who drive SUVs.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can understand driving an SUV if you have a legitimate need for it, but... Like you go camping every week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, you go camping.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Back in the 80s,
[SPEAKER_17]: Bad Rob Bad Rob Bad Rob Bad Rob
[SPEAKER_17]: I cannot wait until this is made illegal because it is proven that people in general do not pay as much attention to the road as you would if you were not talking on your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, first of all, do you drive with your laptop on?
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, never mind, there are people who do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: If I could.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because people are fucking retards, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: If we're going to ban cell phone usage, can we ban people who put on makeup while driving then too?
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_32]: I almost got hit with someone driving with a laptop on their lap.
[SPEAKER_17]: Another thing is just people who think that they need to be one car ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that I hate.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god, you're a car... And I can understand if the person is actually going 20 miles into the speed limit in front of you, because then they are a safety hazard.
[SPEAKER_17]: But...
[SPEAKER_17]: If I'm going, normally I tend to speed a little bit, I drive about 5 to 10 miles over the speed limit sometimes.
[SPEAKER_17]: But when someone passes me, no, that's just inexcusable.
[SPEAKER_17]: Nothing is, you don't need to be somewhere in so much of a hurry that you should endanger your lives and the lives of everybody else on the road.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't really care about the person driving, because you know what, if they die, that's Darwinism at work.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, but when they hurt other people in the process because of their stupidity, that's where I draw the line.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, if they decide to run off the overpass into the river and they're the only ones hurt, fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know?
[SPEAKER_17]: Another thing is, I am bad at this, I am getting better, but I don't ride right up on people's asses.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, I do have an issue with my following distance, but I don't drive all the way up on somebody's bumper where it's, you know...
[SPEAKER_17]: The person in front of me stopped.
[SPEAKER_17]: I wouldn't have any time.
[SPEAKER_17]: There was this person who was right on my ass driving home from work the other day.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm just glad that I had good brakes because I actually did have to stop very quickly to avoid hitting an animal.
[SPEAKER_17]: And the person came very close to running into my rear end.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I kind of wish that they had so I could, you know,
[SPEAKER_17]: Make him go through all the hassle of getting worse and, you know, having their insurance rate go up.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, you know, I had better things to do with my time.
[SPEAKER_17]: But that's really it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's mostly about drivers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go on to Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have one more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, let's not go on to Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: People who think that diet pills are the ways to lose weight, you know how to lose weight?
[SPEAKER_17]: Get off your ass and work it off.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_17]: You're dust!
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck you, dust!
[SPEAKER_33]: Fuck you, too, my cold.
[SPEAKER_33]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_33]: Still stuffed up.
[SPEAKER_33]: Been all tired.
[SPEAKER_33]: No tired.
[SPEAKER_33]: Tired bad.
[SPEAKER_33]: And, uh, fuck you to my computer for being broken, cause I'm gonna have withdrawals.
[SPEAKER_33]: Especially now that I think I've realized that Brad hasn't returned Rantheft Auto's San Andreas yet.
[SPEAKER_33]: So I don't know what I'm going to do now.
[SPEAKER_33]: Does that mean I have to finish playing Wind Waker?
[SPEAKER_33]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_33]: And then, finally, the most important one of them all.
[SPEAKER_33]: Fuck you, Golfland.
[SPEAKER_33]: Fuck you and your ugly asses.
[SPEAKER_33]: Fuck you, Keith.
[SPEAKER_33]: Fuck you, management of Golfland and Roseville Golfland.
[SPEAKER_33]: Thank you, because, you know, I love to be taxed on my own fucking money.
[SPEAKER_33]: Let's flashback here to the summer when I got to build a brand new Step Mania cabinet for Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_33]: I did this as purely as a favor because their sales had sucked, no one was coming to the arcade, the scene had basically died.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, what was my deal with them?
[SPEAKER_33]: I would charge them for parts, they would reimburse me the end.
[SPEAKER_33]: Okay, they would have a wonderful cabinet, I would do all the labor for free, that's it.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, a thousand dollars later, you know, I have this cabinet that's built here, they go to pay me...
[SPEAKER_33]: And they're dragging their feet.
[SPEAKER_33]: They don't want to, you know, they're just like, oh, Keith's never there, oh, the check's on its way, da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_33]: So it's been dragging and dragging, and finally I get paid, and then they have the audacity to send me a 1099 for it.
[SPEAKER_33]: A 1099 for my own money that they were supposed to be reimbursing me for.
[SPEAKER_33]: Why am I getting taxed on my own money?
[SPEAKER_33]: Fuck them.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, a 1099 is the one that you pay taxes on.
[SPEAKER_33]: No, 1099s are the ones they get taxed on.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's misleading as income.
[SPEAKER_09]: And... Actually, I think you're meaning a W-2.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's a 1099.
[SPEAKER_17]: Nobody's writing this a 1099.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: W-2s are for wages, I guess.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because they also put out 1099s.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1099, 1098, and 5498s.
[SPEAKER_09]: And W-2Gs.
[SPEAKER_09]: They put out 1099s for return funds for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: I work in mortgage.
[SPEAKER_17]: 1099 for foreclosures and bankruptcies
[SPEAKER_33]: So, taxes.
[SPEAKER_33]: You know how much that's going to cost me, Golfland?
[SPEAKER_33]: That's going to cost me $150 out of my pocket for your stupid shit.
[SPEAKER_33]: Take them to Smokland's court.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's really not worth it, you know?
[SPEAKER_33]: It's really not.
[SPEAKER_09]: A machine, by the way, which no longer operates.
[SPEAKER_33]: Yeah, the machine's been stolen, it's been converted back, or, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Take the check to Golfland and make them pay it.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's not worth it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_33]: Because it was hard enough to get them to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's not worth my time.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: I always say it's worth time to prove somebody wrong.
[SPEAKER_33]: I didn't think to make copies because I didn't think it was going to be a problem.
[SPEAKER_33]: So anyway, so then, um, so they figured out a way what they were going to do is they were going to make this fake invoice, okay, and make it look like I'm some computer company, and then they were going to give invoices to that so I wouldn't get, you know, charged a 1099 for it, and that was the deal, that was, you know, they made it clear that I wasn't going to get a 1099 for it, and that everything was all good, and I was done.
[SPEAKER_33]: Well, guess what, they gave me a 1099 anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you should go into the machine and take back $150 in parts out of the machine.
[SPEAKER_33]: I can't really do that.
[SPEAKER_33]: Well, that'd be theft.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'd pursue it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, they fucked me over again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just go in there with a chocolate gun and wave it around.
[SPEAKER_33]: I sent an email to Keith.
[SPEAKER_33]: It wasn't very nice.
[SPEAKER_33]: And, you know, he hasn't responded.
[SPEAKER_33]: Surprise.
[SPEAKER_33]: Never ever responds.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_33]: Fuck him.
[SPEAKER_33]: And I'm officially, you know, I'm boycotting Golfland.
[SPEAKER_33]: I'm not going back there ever again.
[SPEAKER_33]: And I would urge everyone else to do the same.
[SPEAKER_33]: Because they're just going to fuck everyone over.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, just enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_33]: I lost, actually, on that cabinet over $230.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, thank you, Golfland.
[SPEAKER_33]: You know, this is what I get for doing you guys a favor.
[SPEAKER_33]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: All righty, moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: How can I follow that one up?
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to myself because I have a whole stack of tests to correct and I haven't started yet and I have to have them done by tomorrow morning.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, I got better things to do like play Final Fantasy and WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_09]: And an F you to WarioWare for being too short.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm already like all the way through it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really don't have a lot interesting to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to put the parrots.
[SPEAKER_09]: The parrot was cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the last unlock I got was a soundtrack thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now I can get Ashley's theme song uninterrupted.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the theme song for Ashley is cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm going to rip the theme song because it's rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to our guest FUs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess we'll start it off with Explicit.
[SPEAKER_32]: Well, now that I found out that everybody was talking about the FUs already, Jamie was talking about the SCPs, I was supposed to say the same thing, so my FU goes to that section.
[SPEAKER_32]: And FU to RVGL, I think Loki explained some of that already.
[SPEAKER_32]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_32]: Oh yeah, big FU goes to fucking parents who blame it on the media.
[SPEAKER_32]: Sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_32]: Okay, an F you goes to parents accusing the media for actions that kids commit all for their own, what they think is a bad influence to kids.
[SPEAKER_32]: First of all, if you're going to let your kids play stuff like Halo 2 or Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, you should know what the consequences are and tell your kids how...
[SPEAKER_32]: Don't blame it on the kids, blame it on their parents.
[SPEAKER_32]: I was about to get there too.
[SPEAKER_32]: Parents are the most responsible ones for the issues.
[SPEAKER_32]: My aunt just had a lawsuit with some games.
[SPEAKER_32]: For some reason, I told her that it's not really worth the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_32]: They treat their kids the wrong way.
[SPEAKER_32]: That's all I'm about to say.
[SPEAKER_32]: FPU goes to, of course, I've already discussed this before, the Milpius Golf Line issue with pads.
[SPEAKER_32]: They should have switched it to within the groove pads, and hopefully they make sure that the pads are going to be well for March Madness 2K5.
[SPEAKER_32]: But to make sure everything calms down, I'll say to be continued for now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright then, Angel's turn to get ranty.
[SPEAKER_16]: uh, FU to no internet for two days, that sucked, um, yeah, um, and uh, FU to Final Fantasy XI not working, cause that sucks, it black screens right after the play online stuff's over, and I think it might have to do with the last update we just had, so, I don't know what's up with that, so, dammit I wanna play!
[SPEAKER_09]: Call Squeenix and call him a bunch of fucking fuckers.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, maybe.
[SPEAKER_16]: And, uh, if you had a, like, a, you know, the holiday weekend, because it went too fast again, so, you know, tomorrow's the last day of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Be glad you get a holiday weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sit down, sit down.
[SPEAKER_16]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: One F you for tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to the chatroom for teasing me about the way I laugh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't give a flying fuck what you guys say about my laugh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I laugh the way I wanted to, so in the words of Yoda, up the shut fuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Preach on, brother.
[SPEAKER_09]: RPG King 7 says, first, thanks for reading my FU last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually think it would be up the shut fuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: RPG King 7 says, thanks for reading my FU last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_09]: This week, FU to kill stealers in MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Elmullet would like to give a playful FU.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to Siggy for telling me to call into Orange Lounge Radio now, only to take the spot himself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now I feel the need to pwn him at Guilty Gear X to reload again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call Squeenix?
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to EB for not giving me cash back for the game not working so I had to buy something else.
[SPEAKER_09]: And F you to iTunes for not having real good music available.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, do a search for an iMix called Dance Dance Revolution and it says Orange Lounge Radio's name in the description and it's all a whole bunch of Dance Dance Revolution songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I put it together and it's on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll find a link.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I can find a link.
[SPEAKER_09]: Miklatov says, first FU of the week goes to gaming expenses.
[SPEAKER_09]: E3 plus PSP plus Night Style equals poorness.
[SPEAKER_09]: Second FU goes to my Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have two games and they are the only two games I want for the next several months.
[SPEAKER_09]: Therefore, I may trade it in towards my PSP purchase.
[SPEAKER_09]: Final FU goes to my car smelling like burning every time I drive it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bugged says, FU to no naked hot tubbing this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a demubass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sephiroth 1215 or 1215 or 1215 says F you to all the snow that is falling right now and an F you for the difficulty being raised all the way up on the DDR machine Illusion says F you to Shakey's not having the regular I got you babe to do karaoke to they had some lame remix with bad synth in it
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, it was totally lame and not gay enough for the incredibly homoerotic I Got You Babe karaoke that I was doing with Larry, a big burly construction worker from the bay that whispers sweet nothings into my ear at night.
[SPEAKER_19]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just a wake up call if you guys are falling asleep there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, F you to this week for going by so slow but that it was only four days long.
[SPEAKER_09]: Illusion says, F you to Gwen Stefani for selling out and her crappy new song that makes me cry.
[SPEAKER_09]: John Fields says, huge F you to NCSX.
[SPEAKER_09]: I waited 12 days and you still haven't gotten PlayStation, or PlayStation, Phantasy Star Online Episode 4 in.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to go with Hamea.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also F you to not having enough hours in a week.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S says, F you to a friend of mine for being a dick to this girl I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Payback's a bitch, cause I'm gonna go for it while you waller in your own self-pity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's have tea!
[SPEAKER_09]: I love that name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's have tea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like tea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need tea right now, cause my voice has been hoarse.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a very pleasant name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which so doesn't work for this segment.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm renaming this person, Let's Have Evil Tea.
[SPEAKER_33]: You know what would be funny?
[SPEAKER_33]: What?
[SPEAKER_33]: Um, well, it's kind of random.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, um,
[SPEAKER_33]: But you know how we were talking about earlier how they have those slash whatevers?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_33]: Okay, well, if you're, like, constipated, you can have slash logout.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was nasty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's Have Tea says, F you to the guy who hit my stepdad's SUV earlier today.
[SPEAKER_09]: It got flipped and totaled.
[SPEAKER_33]: That's what you get for having an SUV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, hey, hey, that's not nice.
[SPEAKER_33]: He has a...
[SPEAKER_09]: or it might be a she, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a pleasant name.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think it was Julie who drove by a wreck where an SUV and like a minivan ran into each other and the SUV rolled and landed on the minivan.
[SPEAKER_09]: No matter what kind of car you drive, people should... I think about two birds with one stone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, SUVs are so big in the first place.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has to take a lot of talent to crash into one.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Tell your dad to like get a real car now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stepdad.
[SPEAKER_09]: One that's got a...
[SPEAKER_09]: Lower Center of Gravity Legend of Zaku says F you to elements of my school's student body aka the elitists for dropping emo bombs last week over the N word being used in a play in my school that illustrates the horrors of slavery America has a way of driving the point across that slavery was really fucked up back then which is, in my humble opinion, the best way to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I know I'm old, okay, but what the hell is an emo bomb?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know what emo is?
[SPEAKER_22]: Emo is that, you know, I'm so sad.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to slash my wrist because I'm so sad.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's basically modern goth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, kind of.
[SPEAKER_17]: Modern goth in happy colors.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So basically it's like the people who bag on movies without seeing them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like they bag on dogma for being a satanic movie without realizing that it's actually a pretty religious movie at heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's kind of the point Zach was trying to make here.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to FreezePop, infecting the ears of Orange Lounge Radio listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: And F you to tonight's internet connection at my campus, causing major skipping in... And then he got cut off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Knight says, one F you to Squeenix for making the cutscenes in Star Ocean too darn long.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have to add another one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: F you to the burning sensation of Liquid Dayquil.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Let's Have Tea would just like to follow up the ever pleasant Let's Have Tea.
[SPEAKER_09]: He did get a real car, a Corvette.
[SPEAKER_17]: Forgiven.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to do a quickie break and when we come back we'll do a little bit of Ask Orange Lounge and then we're going to do the wrap up of the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: So send questions now for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_09]: And in this break, gotcha! ...
If you can't say goodbye
Baby, tell me why You don't wanna love me Just like I do You can't say goodbye Tell me what I've got to do If you can't say goodbye Baby, tell me why You don't wanna love me Just like I do You can't say goodbye Tell me
[SPEAKER_06]: Rock over London, rock over Chicago, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good place to listen to the music.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and we're about ready to wrap up tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_09]: But darn it, it's time for you guys to contribute a little something to this train wreck of a show.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're going to do a little bit of Ask Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're playing on the webcam right now, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope you guys are watching over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Anyway, let's get into this week's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_09]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there a point to this segment?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's only here to fill a little time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Question from RPGKing7.
[SPEAKER_09]: Question is, what is everyone in the lounge's opinions of us Canadians?
[SPEAKER_09]: What do we think of Canadians?
[SPEAKER_17]: They're from Canada.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know Loki's thinking of something horrible to say here.
[SPEAKER_33]: I'm not thinking of anything horrible.
[SPEAKER_33]: No, honestly, Canadians are cool.
[SPEAKER_33]: They've got, you know...
[SPEAKER_33]: Lacks their laws up there, it seems like, you know, and it's just, you know, it's a little cold for my taste, but... It's just cold.
[SPEAKER_33]: It's just, you know, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_33]: I mean, I don't have anything wrong against Canadians.
[SPEAKER_09]: They got the gay marriage thing up there.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're ahead of the game as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_33]: They got that stuff going for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's my problem with Canada.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I went to Canada, I'd be out of a job because I work in the healthcare industry, and they got the nationalized healthcare thing going on, so I'd be out of a job.
[SPEAKER_33]: Well...
[SPEAKER_33]: The only thing I don't like is French Canadians, but, you know, but that's just because I don't like French.
[SPEAKER_33]: No one likes French Canadians.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_33]: So, I mean, there's, there's, hey, you know, Canada gave us Jim Carrey, you know.
[SPEAKER_29]: And Alanis Morissette, my favorite.
[SPEAKER_33]: Yeah, well, okay, they gave us Jim Carrey, and, um.
[SPEAKER_33]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_33]: And, and, and they also gave us Tom, oh, wait, no, no, Tom Green, you can have Tom Green back, actually, um.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dan says, too nice, too close, and too quiet.
[SPEAKER_09]: The weird thing is they all live in Toronto, which is, I guess Toronto's where it's at.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go Leafs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, yeah, they have good musicians.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's all I've got to say.
[SPEAKER_33]: Shatner's Canadian?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_16]: Rob already said Alanis Morissette, so I've got to say Very Naked Ladies, because, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or Celine Dion?
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_33]: Well, the game is Jim Carrey.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_33]: What about Bryan Adams?
[SPEAKER_09]: Legend of Zaku says, Seeing that you guys are the drinking type, have you ever thought of creating some Bomani-themed cocktail drinks?
[SPEAKER_09]: My fire, like Goldschlager and... Max 300, Goldschlager, Jgermeister, and 151 all mixed together.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I...
[SPEAKER_32]: Murdoch Survivor
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I imagine some dork out there has thought of something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe that's a thread we should start on the forums.
[SPEAKER_09]: See what people can come up with.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I have a friend who's going to bartending school.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what I'll do is I will ask him to come up with some new drinks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe he's even listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's starting bartending school this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll ask him to try and come up with some new drinks.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when he tells me what's in it, I will give them names.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we will come up with a Bomani drink.
[SPEAKER_17]: We could use the one that I made with the orange juice and the Malibu.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_17]: That can be...
[SPEAKER_09]: My Summer Love I was thinking the same thing Mikla Tav Dear Ask Orange Lounge Please make some E3 plans Alright, stop bugging me And Boom Boom Dollar was not on DER First Mix Meaning it had no basic step rating Hey buddy It was on US First Mix Which was basically just the Japanese First Mix imported Or 1.5 Mix
[SPEAKER_09]: MPQ says, why do laptops make shitty gaming PCs?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, who has the laptop in her lap?
[SPEAKER_09]: Care to answer?
[SPEAKER_17]: I haven't actually tried to run any games on this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Although I could install the Sims.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, my laptop would probably be very good for gaming because I've got a GeForce in here and I've got a 3.06 processor.
[SPEAKER_33]: Simple.
[SPEAKER_17]: And a bunch of RAM.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mine would run Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to download the benchmark and see if my laptop would run Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think you should.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just so I can laugh.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what, I think part of the problem, at least with older laptops, newer ones don't do this so much, but the older ones, like if you change the way you're looking at the screen, it gets lighter and darker, like it's just the way the display works.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's this LCD screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly, and that annoyed the shit out of me, but new ones don't really have that problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mine really won't be running many games though, because it's for school.
[SPEAKER_33]: The problem is that laptops are generation behind usually, and they're also very expensive.
[SPEAKER_33]: Also, it says they're passively cooled, they don't have any actual fans inside of them.
[SPEAKER_33]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: For the money.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Al Mullet wants to ask, As a future newbie to Beatmania 2DX, there are quite a few songs I haven't heard yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: What would be your favorites to play?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe one favorite song to play in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mine would be Deadline.
[SPEAKER_09]: As horrid as that song is, I absolutely love that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Deadline, Fistyle.
[SPEAKER_17]: I used to be really fond of playing Sync.
[SPEAKER_17]: But now it would probably have to be... I actually really dig Holic.
[SPEAKER_09]: On both levels, so... When you're first getting started and you're still playing 1-stars, Five Fathoms on 3rd style is pretty rad, and it has a random video.
[SPEAKER_17]: Five Fathoms, that would be the one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Five Fathoms is like the best song to learn on for 1-star.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's the one with the DDR in the video, like the old-ass DDR that had Boom Boom Dollar in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mikhail Tov.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, we got a lot of questions in a little time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to try and get through as many of these as we can.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can still submit some, though, if you want.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking through some.
[SPEAKER_09]: John Fields says, Hey Sky, why isn't this show or station listed on the Wikipedia?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm somewhat familiar with Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that like the user-created encyclopedia?
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of like, what do they call that Mozilla database of all the sites?
[SPEAKER_09]: Free web or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Freezilla or something?
[SPEAKER_17]: I found Mobile Alabama on the Wikipedia page.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just have no idea how to hook something like that up.
[SPEAKER_09]: If somebody wants to send me an email and tell me how to do it, rob at orangeloungeradio.com or if you just want to submit it, as long as you don't talk shit about us, you have my blessings.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I imagine DarkSakura and Loki feel the same way, yes?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, don't fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's Have Tea would like to know, what is the highest score in Orange Lounge Radio Pinball?
[SPEAKER_09]: Little known fact, before I got into DDR, I was a pinball whore.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really loved pinball.
[SPEAKER_17]: Rob was the pinball wizard.
[SPEAKER_17]: He was blind and used to be called Tommy.
[SPEAKER_09]: House of Magic
[SPEAKER_09]: House of Magic's awesome too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are probably two of the top tables out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another one that I always liked was Pinbot, which is kind of a running joke on Outside the Box when it's actually on the air.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Pinbot's a really cool one too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I always liked that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the NES version, not the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, it's very much not the same.
[SPEAKER_33]: What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_33]: My favorite time playing, what was it, Invasion of Mars or whatever that one was called, Return to Mars.
[SPEAKER_33]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_17]: Because I was always really good at hitting the goal.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dan and I, a little after I first moved out here, we used to go to Godfather's Pizza in Tomas and play Last Action Hero Pinball.
[SPEAKER_17]: All the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, VXJSXV brings up a good point in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some PC pinball games that were actually really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Epic Pinball.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Epic Pinball games were awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can get Pin Mame.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pin Mame's not the same to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would rather play Epic Pinball than Pin Mame.
[SPEAKER_33]: Epic Pinball I bet's in a band and wear probably right now.
[SPEAKER_33]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: As much as I think Pin Mame is an awesome idea and I totally support the project, it just, I don't know, it doesn't work for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's because I prefer the tables that were created for the PC, on a PC, if that makes any sense.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know, there's some really good virtual tables there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I used to have, and if anybody can think of this and private message me the pinball game that this was, I would love you forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a pinball game I used to have on my old ass PC, my 100 megahertz PC, and it had four tables in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of them was like a haunted house, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other one was a raceway.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of them was a circus.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I remember the circus table was a demo you could download on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then there was another one called like Billion Dollar Game Show or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a game and it had four tables.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't Epic, it was some other pinball game.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I could find that again, I would be so happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did Sierra make a pinball game?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think it was Sierra either.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was some other unknown company.
[SPEAKER_17]: I talked to one of the people at E3 last year who said that they were working on a pinball game for the PS2 that was supposed to emulate a bunch of the old tables.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want them to actually go to Capcom and produce the... It was when I had brought up on the show before that Dan showed me there's only like, I think, 16 of them in existence.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dr. Dude
[SPEAKER_09]: It was awful.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody in the chatroom is posting a suggestion for the game that they think it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was Big Bang.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hyper 3D Pinball I'm posting pictures of this table in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_17]: But that's the one.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they only made a few of them because this was in production right before Capcom's pinball division went out.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want a pinball table.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want a Black Knight 2000 machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody's suggesting that maybe it's extreme pinball?
[SPEAKER_09]: And yes, I will... Oh my gosh, I think this is it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I have that game too, but that's not the one I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't tell.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so upset because I really want this.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys don't understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want this game again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Grr.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's not it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Darn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: What we're going to do now is we're going to go around and get everybody's... Oh, I'll do one more question really quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry to those guys we didn't get to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Illusion asks, Hey guys, I have a question.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you do for Valentine's Day?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you get shagged vigorously?
[SPEAKER_17]: I had chocolate cheese pie.
[SPEAKER_17]: I had dinner with my boy.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then I went to school on actual Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, I made pasta, and then it got shagged vigorously.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did not get shagged vigorously this Valentine's Day, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can deal with rejection.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's time to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys for tuning in to Orange Lounge Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's start it off with Explicit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your final thought, please.
[SPEAKER_32]: Jamie, get well soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: Final Fantasy must workie, dang it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_33]: I'm only down to two PCs now.
[SPEAKER_33]: What am I to do?
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is when will Outside the Box return?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nobody knows.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want a Black Knight 2000 pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Check out our podcast, dammit.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, you can have tonight's final word.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, final word.
[SPEAKER_05]: The final word of the evening is... That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_05]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_05]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now, the six merry murderesses of the Cook County Jail in their rendition of The Cell.Tales
[SPEAKER_21]: Popsic Wishes Popsic Wishes He had it coming, he had it coming He only had himself to blame If you'd have been there, if you'd have seen it I bet you you would have done the same Popsic Wishes Popsic Wishes
[SPEAKER_11]: You know how people have these little habits that get you down?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, Bernie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bernie likes to chew gum.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not chew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ha.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I came home this one day and I'm really irritated and I'm looking for a little bit of sympathy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's Bernie, lying on the couch, drinking a beer and chewing.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not chewing.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he did.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I took the shotgun off the wall and I fired two warning shots into his head.
[SPEAKER_11]: He had it coming.
[SPEAKER_24]: I met Ezekiel Young from Salt Lake City about two years ago.
[SPEAKER_24]: And he told me he was single.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we hit it off right away.
[SPEAKER_24]: So we started living together.
[SPEAKER_24]: He'd go to work, he'd come home.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'd fix him a drink, we'd have dinner.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then I found out.
[SPEAKER_24]: Single, he told me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Single, my ass.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not only was he married.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_24]: He had six wives.
[SPEAKER_24]: One of those Mormons, you know.
[SPEAKER_24]: So that night when he came home from work, I fixed him his drink, as usual.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, some guys just can't hold their arsenic.
[SPEAKER_21]: He had it coming, he had it coming, he took the power and it was right.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then he used it, and he abused it, it was a murder, another microchip.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now I'm standing in the kitchen, carving up the chicken for dinner, minding my own business.
[SPEAKER_28]: In storms my husband, Wilbur, in a jealous rage.
[SPEAKER_28]: You've been screwing the milkman, he said.
[SPEAKER_28]: He was crazy.
[SPEAKER_28]: And he kept on screaming, you've been screwing the milkman.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then he ran into my knife.
[SPEAKER_28]: He ran into my knife ten times.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, but did you do it?
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_25]: Not guilty.
[SPEAKER_12]: My sister Veronica and I had this double act.
[SPEAKER_12]: And my husband Charlie traveled around with us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now for the last number in our act, we did these 20 acrobatic tricks in a row.
[SPEAKER_12]: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, splits, spread eagles, backflips, flip flops, one right after the other.
[SPEAKER_12]: So this one night before the show, we're down at the Hotel Cicero, the three of us boozing, having a few laughs.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we run out of ice, so I go out to get some.
[SPEAKER_12]: I come back, open the door.
[SPEAKER_12]: and there is Veronica and Charlie doing number 17, the Sporad Eagle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I was in such a state of shock.
[SPEAKER_12]: I completely blacked out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't remember a thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It wasn't until later when I was washing the blood off my hands, I even knew they were dead.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had it coming.
[SPEAKER_21]: They had it coming.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: I loved Al Lipschitz more than I could possibly say.
[SPEAKER_27]: He was a real artistic guy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sensitive.
[SPEAKER_27]: A painter.
[SPEAKER_27]: But he was always trying to find himself.
[SPEAKER_27]: He'd go out every night looking for himself, and on the way, he found Ruth, Gladys, Rosemary, and Irvings.
[SPEAKER_27]: I guess you could say we broke up because of artistic differences.
[SPEAKER_27]: He saw himself as alive, and I saw him dead.
[SPEAKER_21]: You popped that gum one more time.
[SPEAKER_21]: Number 17, the spread eagle.
[SPEAKER_21]: Pop.
[SPEAKER_21]: Six.
[SPEAKER_21]: Squish.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Cicero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, we figured it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's either Pinball Dreams or Pinball Fantasies.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're both made by the same developer.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're very similar.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm going to check them both out.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was it, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: When I do the image search in Google, I get the images of the game I remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, thank you, Jason, for helping me find that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm very happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's either Pinball Dreams or Pinball Fantasies.
[SPEAKER_09]: One is the sequel to the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, that was it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now people can help me find Konami World.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the cool thing about Pinball Dreams and Pinball Fantasies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Excuse me, I choked on a peanut.
[SPEAKER_09]: They use mod music.
[SPEAKER_09]: The music is all mod files, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, good luck finding Konami World.
[SPEAKER_09]: Miss Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's gonna do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're gonna log off now so we can take care of that podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys.