If we took some time apart, you would find me no more I'm here and waiting for you, where are you?
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_00]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_15]: And this is episode number 133 for this, February the 27th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're tuned in to the B-Money Scene's most Oscar-worthy radio station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_15]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_15]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's right, that's tonight's theme tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Oscar goes to me for being so great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also joining us... I'm sorry, you can't win the Oscar because you didn't get naked.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did not get naked this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: I might tonight, however.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm getting the old thumbs up from our special guest.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who we will get to momentarily after we introduce... Loki, TechMassa.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have corn on one side and rice on the other.
[SPEAKER_15]: That sounds like a very interesting porno I want.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to our very special guest, who, believe it or not, in 133 weeks of Orange Lounge Radio, has never been to a live show, I do not believe.
[SPEAKER_15]: No?
[SPEAKER_15]: Was there one other time?
[SPEAKER_11]: There was the tournament, and then there was when I did it at the house.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, but that's never been here at the Orange Lounge Studios.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: So make sure the mic's on, bud.
[SPEAKER_15]: Make sure it's in the on position.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Into the microphone.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to Dan!
[SPEAKER_15]: And why is Dan so special, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, because we're getting married one day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I rock.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan is DarkSakura's hetero life mate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, my head went like this.
[SPEAKER_15]: So this should be a very interesting show because now I have someone to gang up on Jamie with.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is going to be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but when we get home, Dan's ass is going to be kicked.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'd like to think that, wouldn't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: He got second five.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll school you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, you're too busy eating on this show always to make fun of Jamie with me.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't make fun of Jamie because she kicks my ass and makes me cry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, we will be back shortly after a quick break to kick things off in tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_15]: During tonight's show, by the way, we're going to have a brand new song premiere for you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those of you guys with Xboxes, I'm sure you already heard this one.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the brand new In My Eyes mix from Song Pack 8.
[SPEAKER_15]: But if you haven't had a chance to hear it yet, you're going to.
[SPEAKER_15]: In about 20 minutes, we'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Join us in the chat room, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back.
DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move Marathon.
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Crap-free Bavani Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: We are back here on the lovely Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd like to accept this award.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'd like to thank my mother and my father.
[SPEAKER_11]: This world is shit!
[SPEAKER_15]: That was the best acceptance speech of all time.
[SPEAKER_15]: When Fiona Apple got up there and said, she was drunk off her ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is like what the MTV Awards, what, like 10 years ago almost at this point?
[SPEAKER_15]: She gets up there, oh my god, was that really 10 years ago?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so old!
[SPEAKER_11]: I was living here when it happened.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, okay, good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Phew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, maybe...
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamey
[SPEAKER_15]: Start us off.
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I'm just... We need to fix this.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is why I can't watch the Oscars, even though they call it the Gay Man Super Bowl, and if you hadn't heard the little rumor going around about me, even though they call it the Gay Man Super Bowl, I can't watch this program because I don't see any of the movies, like ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think this year I've seen two of the movies, which is like more than ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would have to second that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really go to the movies that much anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: And when I do go to the movies, I usually see like foreign shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I usually pick a movie and then see it a bajillion times.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I saw Phantom of the Opera twice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, see, I saw Rocky Horror Picture Show like 200 and something times.
[SPEAKER_21]: If I have to see another period piece starring Leonardo DiCaprio, I am going to scream.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or fucking Dame Judi Dench.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dame Judi Dench in every period piece there ever was.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's Dame Judi Dench.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't get me wrong, Dame Judi Dench is a great actress, but damn.
[SPEAKER_11]: My week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: My week was spent in a coma.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, more like being half in a coma and half playing Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I did not have the energy to move out of my chair.
[SPEAKER_21]: It'll do that to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I, um, I basically ran a fever.
[SPEAKER_11]: The highest it was when I checked was 103.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, uh, it's like Friday, like Saturday, I stopped running a fever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I went to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_11]: She said, your ass ain't going to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: And basically I had some type of viral infection that almost became, she said that it was leaving me very open to bacteria and that it was basically settled in my sinuses and the head.
[SPEAKER_11]: Microphone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, and, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, and, uh, what else did I do?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah, yesterday we cleaned our room and found the floor.
[SPEAKER_11]: We threw away, like, two years worth of crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, I got disconnected from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, but I also, uh,
[SPEAKER_11]: What else did I do?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, today we went and bought like lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: And had dinner.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that was it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it got second five!
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is, even though I haven't played the home version yet, the most awesome game in the world.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Loki!
[SPEAKER_15]: I know you're trying to eat, but it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_21]: So anyways... I was chewing...
[SPEAKER_21]: and then stuff happened.
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right now, since I had sort of like lunch for breakfast, I'm having breakfast for dinner.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, just to kind of balance things out.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're having a dyslexic meal day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm having, you know, it's actually pretty good for me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Crispix.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's damn good.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, I've already eaten half the box.
[SPEAKER_13]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's not much in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyways, um,
[SPEAKER_21]: So, yeah, this week, what did I do?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, to start things off, first off, computer was out of commission.
[SPEAKER_13]: We do remember that on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was gone.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was like, you know, I can wait a week until I get paid next to fix it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: The next day... So, I watched Robot Chicken.
[SPEAKER_13]: Robot Chicken is fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't normally endorse television programs.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, I will endorse Robot Chicken.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tonight, 11.30.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fucking comedy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cartoon Network, Best 15 Minutes of Your Life
[SPEAKER_21]: I honestly, I'm glad it was only 15 minutes long, because I was laughing so hard, I probably would have passed out if it was any longer.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, it was great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then, because remember, you have organic internal organs, and you can get cancer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody who saw Robot Chicken is kind of chuckling.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're not really laughing because it wasn't that funny, but they're chuckling a little bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anybody who didn't see it is going, Loki, shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't get you.
[SPEAKER_21]: So anyway, the rest of the week was filled with watching... Well, actually just playing Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I tried actually playing Final Fantasy XII, but then I realized that for some reason...
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually played the guy game last night with Loki and his girlfriend and one of Loki's other friends.
[SPEAKER_15]: And my friend Christopher was just kind of sitting in the corner playing DS going, what's wrong with you people?
[SPEAKER_15]: But I was playing the guy game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I owned at the guy game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd just like to point out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you get boobies?
[SPEAKER_15]: I got my girl to give me a lap dance at the end.
[SPEAKER_15]: Except my girl looked like a dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was right.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, I mean, she looked okay when it wasn't like a still photo of her.
[SPEAKER_15]: When she was kind of in motion, she looked alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: But the still photos did not do that girl justice.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was like somewhere between Tori Spelling and Bea Arthur.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously, there was this one picture of her.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was the name of the model in the game?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_17]: She's the one that looks like a horse.
[SPEAKER_17]: We didn't know Chyna was in the guy game.
[SPEAKER_17]: So anyways, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we did that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I went and played some horse crack because I had to get rid of some of my tokens left over from that horrible place called Golfland.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I still, you know, my boycott still exists.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just have to get rid of these tokens so that I'm rid of their evil.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I have to say, I eat children, my horse, in derby crack.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kickin' ass.
[SPEAKER_21]: And what else did I do?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just kind of
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I retired a horse, like, in two days.
[SPEAKER_11]: When they got Doc over there.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is so weird.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't really been to Golf Land in, like, I don't know, four months.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hear Country Club Lanes has In The Groove, but I'm too lazy to go over there and play it.
[SPEAKER_15]: What the hell am I doing this show for?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, honestly, they had a new Sega shooter there.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: That game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't actually get to see it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That game is really fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dan and I played it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't really get to play anything else.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm really just, you know, DDR is kind of getting old as far as, you know, there's not been really new coming out.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm starting to, like, take interest in the other arcade games again.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, back, you know, where...
[SPEAKER_13]: When I was in the DDRs, kind of like, other arcade games, eh, fuck them, you know, I'm just playing DDR, you know, where now... DDR's got a line.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that was it, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: There was a ton of people standing around the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is DDR going through a renaissance right now?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because, like, there's fucking tons of people always playing it.
[SPEAKER_15]: When I'm actually, when I am at an arcade... No one's playing Derby Owners Club at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe one other person, that's why I came in second and third.
[SPEAKER_15]: Extreme is what, like, two and a half years old now, and it's still...
[SPEAKER_15]: Getting these huge crowds.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Max too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: There is more people on Max too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Probably that's because the extreme pads are fucked up.
[SPEAKER_13]: I went and played Guitar Freaks yesterday.
[SPEAKER_13]: One, my left hand hurt like a bitch because I'm just not used to playing it anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess I gotta start masturbating with my left hand now, you know, to get it used to that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: But their fucking green button on there was messed up.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was like...
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn that fucking green button!
[SPEAKER_13]: Seriously, I was failing songs because of it!
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck them!
[SPEAKER_13]: And their crappy stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I guess, you know, they got tired of... They wanted to save money, apparently, because, you know, after all, they ripped me off on money, so why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's just not fix anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hear they're actually gonna get a fourth DDR machine, which'll be in the groove, so... That's rumored.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck them, anyways.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's another machine they won't maintain I'm done Well
[SPEAKER_15]: My week and my day was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, gosh, Loki already kind of hit on some of the stuff I wanted to talk about, like the guy game thing going on last night.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, you know, just kind of went out earlier this week, and I've been busy with work, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's had me really exhausted, so I've been just napping a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Been playing a lot of Final Fantasy XI, of course, and boy, did I just hit my point of frustration today.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want to quit that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: Final Fantasy II Final Fantasy II
[SPEAKER_15]: But I got sick of Final Fantasy 1, so I want to get back into Final Fantasy 2 and see what it's really all about.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I know very little about the game and the story.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I know bits and pieces here and there.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I recognized the song in the beginning, because everybody knows that Imperial March song that's in Final Fantasy 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: So that was cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, gosh, outside of that, not really a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not that exciting this week, or any week, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dan, would you like to share with us how your week is and how your day is going and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_17]: I had to deal with a sick Jamie all week.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sure you can all relate with how much fun that is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you give her a bell when she's sick?
[SPEAKER_17]: Like she can ring a bell?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that's all she needs.
[SPEAKER_20]: Another way to make more noise.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, actually, it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_18]: I took a bunch of days off this week, which turned out to be good timing, because even though she was sick, it let me spend a lot of time at home with Jamie, and we had fun.
[SPEAKER_20]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, you know, I managed to get her to clean the bedroom, which, you know, five years.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not two years, five years.
[SPEAKER_18]: We unpacked stuff I hadn't seen since I packed it before we moved into that apartment.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to be moving in April and I'm very much dreading it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh god, it's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_15]: I swear to god I'm going to call 1-800-JUNK.
[SPEAKER_15]: 1-800-GARBAGE.
[SPEAKER_15]: 1-800-GET-JUNK or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: GOT-JUNK.
[SPEAKER_18]: 1-800-GOT-TOLD.
[SPEAKER_18]: Haven't had a lot of chance to do a lot of gaming, which is kind of bizarre since I've been at home all week.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sucks, but hey, what are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, it's cool, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: GameStop, Marconi, buy all your Dance Dance stuff from us.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have like 15 ignition pads, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: I need somebody to buy them.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm coming on this show because I need you guys to buy ignition pads from the GameStop on Marconi.
[SPEAKER_18]: You go to any other GameStop, it doesn't fucking help me.
[SPEAKER_18]: You gotta buy them from me, please.
[SPEAKER_18]: I sold five in one week.
[SPEAKER_18]: The company said, oh, fuck, these things are hot.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sent me like seven cases of them.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's two per case.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't get rid of them.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're $100 a piece.
[SPEAKER_18]: I saw the $20 ones, like, they're going out of style.
[SPEAKER_18]: Someone buy an ignition pad, please.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, I went to GameStop to buy an ignition pad once.
[SPEAKER_17]: It wasn't yours.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, but... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: You see how that works?
[SPEAKER_15]: Fucker.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are you doing another GameStop to buy an ignition pad?
[SPEAKER_18]: Now I'm taking over your show.
[SPEAKER_15]: I needed an ignition pad now.
[SPEAKER_15]: At least I went to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because that really helps me.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought there was this whole corporate synergy thing going on.
[SPEAKER_18]: At least I supported your opposition.
[SPEAKER_18]: You see, they make us compete.
[SPEAKER_18]: We fight to the death.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I usually win because, let's be honest, the rest of the GameStop managers in this area, posers.
[SPEAKER_18]: But really, by Ignition Pad, GameStop, Marconi and Fulton.
[SPEAKER_15]: Marconi and Fulton, yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: So if you disagree with Dan's comments, come see him in person.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on by.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I'm already on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what I look like.
[SPEAKER_18]: You ain't going to miss me.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you're in the Sacramento area, you are hereby obligated to shop at my store.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get all this Dance Dance crap out of my store.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll get new Dance Dance crap and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I went into your competing game stop once and I went and bought a new ignition pad.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they were like, Whoa, you're actually buying an ignition pad?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think I've ever seen anyone buy one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you sure that's what you want?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm like, way to sell it, buddy, way to sell it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Aren't you supposed to ask me if I want to pre-order the next fucking pad or something?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, it's because of my involvement with you guys and with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know how shit-hot the ignition pad is supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've never used one, but I know it's supposed to be frickin' unbelievable.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you're going to play DDR at home, seriously, at all, you should spend the money and get one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because the $20 pads ain't worth your time.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, no, they suck.
[SPEAKER_18]: But yeah, so I pimped a bunch of them one week and we were feeling real good about that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Boom rang around, bit me in the ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: Come buy ignition pads.
[SPEAKER_18]: From me, please.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have these pads over here that I don't even use.
[SPEAKER_21]: So sad.
[SPEAKER_18]: Use them with your sick ass arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_21]: I do use them with my sick-ass arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_13]: My problem is the sick-ass static electricity that's created by the sick-ass Lexin that's in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: It kind of fries my sick-ass keyboard encoder board, and that doesn't work very well.
[SPEAKER_18]: Static.
[SPEAKER_18]: It'll stop you.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I need to ground those pads, and then we'll be all good.
[SPEAKER_13]: God damn it, they were expensive enough to build.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't need to be buying anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: No more.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_13]: And besides, the whole reason I built the cabinet and these pads is so I didn't have to go back to Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now they've just, you know, finalized that by trying to rip me off.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, perfect.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's all coming to play.
[SPEAKER_11]: The purpose of GameStop is to rip people off and kill their soul.
[SPEAKER_15]: We sell the GameStop or MovieStop.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's actually a company called MovieStop now?
[SPEAKER_18]: I saw them in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're kicking the idea around for out here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, and they're buying games, or not games, but they're movies for their GameStops also from us.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have a person that works in my key accounts department that doesn't know shit about anything, and he sells to them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ironically, when I was in Mobile, there was one right next door to an EB.
[SPEAKER_15]: GameStop, on one hand, is an evil empire, but on the other hand, you need to get rid of those ignition pads, so come to the GameStop.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, they're an evil empire, but...
[SPEAKER_18]: They pay our bills.
[SPEAKER_18]: At least they're not Walmart.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, now that's an evil empire.
[SPEAKER_18]: A giant evil empire.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what, Starbucks is an evil empire too, but that doesn't make Frappuccino's taste any less, you know, yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, Starbucks, actually, from what I understand, Starbucks treats its employees pretty well.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know people that work at Starbucks and they have nice things to say about it.
[SPEAKER_18]: My understanding is that Starbucks managers make bank.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, so Starbucks... Stock options.
[SPEAKER_15]: But yet people hate Starbucks because it's killing all the independent coffee shops or whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, did you ever go to an independent coffee shop?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, I did.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're screwing up my argument.
[SPEAKER_18]: I did.
[SPEAKER_18]: I did, but... Okay, did you go to it a lot?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I didn't go to it a lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: Have you gone to Starbucks more?
[SPEAKER_15]: The independent coffee shop did not have a drive-thru.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's really the clincher for Starbucks, is that if I can drive home and pick up a mocha latte frappalotta coffee chocino thing... They didn't have drive-thrus, and they weren't in the mall.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you work at the mall, you drink Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's because they pump something through the air.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't drink Starbucks, but when I worked at the mall, I drank Starbucks like a fucking fiend.
[SPEAKER_15]: Could it be the smell of coffee in the air?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_18]: The mall doesn't smell like... You go to the mall, does it smell like coffee?
[SPEAKER_11]: Subliminal messages in the music.
[SPEAKER_18]: It is funny, though.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you get ice water from Starbucks and you drink it, it tastes like coffee.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm friggin' serious, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: Try it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just try it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And they won't turn you down because it's like a corporate mandate from Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you ask for water, they gotta give you water.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate it when I go into places and you ask for water, and this is especially bad at places that have a DDR machine, i.e.
[SPEAKER_15]: Roseville Golf Land.
Sucks!
[SPEAKER_15]: You want to go and you go to play DDR and then you work up a sweat and you want to go get a nice glass of ice water.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be 25 cents for the cup.
[SPEAKER_15]: What if you bring your own cup?
[SPEAKER_15]: Then they won't do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, probably not, because they'll claim it's unsanitary.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't tried it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just end up going off in a huff to the drinking fountain.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm like, you bastards, I'm pumping it up.
[SPEAKER_18]: That drinking fountain is scary.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's got, like, gum and, like, tobacco.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like, what the crap?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's no way in hell I'm going to win my Oscar pool.
[SPEAKER_21]: I, like, lost, like, the last three or four or five.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ah, damn it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyways, sorry to derail that whole train.
[SPEAKER_15]: You poor, poor bastard.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, back to me.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's go to break.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do we get to break things on break?
[SPEAKER_15]: Possibly, because the music that we're going to play might be something that you want to break some stuff to.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it's solitary.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, actually it's going to be athletics.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_15]: And some folks wanted to hear War Game, so I was going to indulge that request.
[SPEAKER_11]: I vote for Disco Dog.
[SPEAKER_15]: We will get Disco Dog in there as well, and some other athletic favorite songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then we're going to come back, and we're going to talk a little bit about Bomani.
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, we got news.
[SPEAKER_15]: We got big Guitadora news.
[SPEAKER_15]: Big news!
[SPEAKER_15]: And we also have big Ultramix 2 stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even more woo.
[SPEAKER_11]: That earns a squeeze.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, are the ignition pads the PlayStation 2 and Xbox kind that have both?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, they're the dual compatibilities.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you know what's funny is that when this DDR... I don't think they make the single ones anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't think they do either, but you know what's funny is that if this Dance Dance Revolution with Mario comes out in the US, which we all expect it will, they'll have to have new ignition pads that have all three.
[SPEAKER_18]: Incidentally, while we're on the subject of Dance Dance Revolution with Mario, which needs to come out because the videos are hilarious, has anybody here played that
[SPEAKER_18]: MC Groove's Dance Beat I have never sold a copy They sent me some, we put a box out, we had them sitting around People look at it, they see the box, they run away screaming
[SPEAKER_18]: Who released it?
[SPEAKER_17]: THQ or something?
[SPEAKER_17]: All I can say is send it back.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't send it back.
[SPEAKER_18]: The company store, they send me the shit they want in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then you need to go put it on their doorstep and ring the doorbell and run.
[SPEAKER_17]: And light it on fire.
[SPEAKER_18]: Then when they step in it like the burning Coleco plastic, they'll be like, no!
[SPEAKER_15]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's actually by Mad Catz, the same company.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's right, Mad Catz.
[SPEAKER_15]: The same company that makes those $20 dance pads.
[SPEAKER_15]: The beat pad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because after you play with them, you want to beat yourself with a stick, honestly.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: It has the full versions of songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you'd think that would be a good thing because I was like, parents just don't understand and stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: But there's really nothing else to it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, besides the somewhat interesting music, the steps don't make any sense at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the visuals leave a lot to be desired.
[SPEAKER_15]: The entire game without the music is probably about the size where it would fit on a three and a half inch floppy disk.
[SPEAKER_15]: to use in your GameCube floppy drive.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, let's go to break.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to start it off with some more game.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: How many people can think about it?
No matter who you are, however you want to be.
This is the end of a galaxy, no one but an enemy.
Brought to you guys from the gods who are in this.
Everybody who I have to kill.
Thanks for watching!
S.T.V, Darius, TikTok
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: and Drewie.
and more.
I love you, active, don't tell this to my family I love you, bubba, bubba, don't make a scene Bye-bye Bye-bye Bye-bye Bye-bye Bye-bye Bye-bye
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: During the break there, Dan was talking to me about a little bit of the celebrity that he gets from being the dude from GameStop.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was some of the stuff you were telling me?
[SPEAKER_15]: You get harassed in restaurants and things?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, it was
[SPEAKER_18]: We just got an IM, or a message, from someone who thought that they knew who I was.
[SPEAKER_18]: Right.
[SPEAKER_18]: You don't know me.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it's like, you manage a video game store, and you're shocked because you see all these people come through your store.
[SPEAKER_18]: And some of them you get to know because they come in lots.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some of them you start to dread seeing.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you know who I'm talking to if you're listening.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're not listening, I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: And sometimes, it's like you can be, I was a thousand miles from home.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was at E3.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some guy walks up to me and he's like, I know you from somewhere.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm like, you should know me, I'm famous.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do you know me?
[SPEAKER_15]: I am so famous.
[SPEAKER_18]: But he figured out who I was and he ran into me again and he's like, you're the guy from GameStop.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm thinking, wow, this guy's probably been sitting here that whole goddamn show, three days of video games, thinking, why the hell did I know that guy first?
[SPEAKER_15]: You've been in that position, though, haven't you, before, where you swear to God you recognize somebody and you can't think of where you know them from, and it just preys on your mind.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's obvious, and like I said, it's just I thought it was pathetic.
[SPEAKER_18]: It wasn't like I was trying to think of someone who might have been a childhood friend or a grade school buddy.
[SPEAKER_18]: This was the guy who came to me and bought Final Fantasy two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dude, you delivered my pizza once.
[SPEAKER_17]: Damn, you didn't bring me any peppers.
[SPEAKER_18]: You bastard.
[SPEAKER_18]: So yeah, it's freaky freaky.
[SPEAKER_15]: I used to get that sometimes back when I did Rocky Horror Picture Show and I was still around and I was emceeing and I would do the big beginning where we had like the virgin sacrifice, you know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Everyone knows who Rob is anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Big dumb fun, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've had people walk up to me and be like, you know Rob, don't you?
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, but I would be at the mall or something and these girls would walk by me and go like, you're the guy who took my virginity.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm like, don't say that with your mother there!
[SPEAKER_17]: Trust me, it wasn't me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_20]: That's no good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've had that happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell your mother you mean you're Rocky.
[SPEAKER_15]: What were you doing after midnight?
[SPEAKER_15]: Mom probably thought that was worse.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: You were at Rocky?
[SPEAKER_15]: You were at Rocky?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why did you do that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, years ago, years upon years ago, I used to have a public access show, which actually kind of leads back to the week and day stuff, because we were so bored.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was this, last night or Friday night?
[SPEAKER_15]: It must have been Friday night.
[SPEAKER_15]: We were so bored, and I was in one of those moods where I actually dug up a copy of my old public access show, and I put it on, and I let my friends watch it that were here.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would have been awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry I missed that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was I letting myself be subjected to with that?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki actually caught some of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any thoughts?
[SPEAKER_21]: It was strange.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, you know, I used to, because it used to be on public access in this area, so, you know, when I'd be out at the mall, people would kind of be looking at me like, isn't that that gay guy from TV?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're like, I don't want to admit that I watch it, but I want to approach it.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what you do as they're approaching.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're like, didn't I see you on TV?
[SPEAKER_18]: And you just start pointing at them, just laughing.
[SPEAKER_18]: What, you watch that?
[SPEAKER_18]: You got a problem?
[SPEAKER_18]: You need to go do something.
[SPEAKER_15]: They don't want to admit they watch public access.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, of course, they don't want to, you know, boomerangs back around.
[SPEAKER_15]: And a show that I was a part of, nonetheless, on public access.
[SPEAKER_18]: See, you're missing, don't implicate yourself.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry, my twin.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd like to think that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: We had the songpacks be made available in Canada, and I believe it's seven bucks, Canadian, that they want for the songpacks, which are five songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: But this is huge news for those folks that live in Canada.
[SPEAKER_15]: And if you live in Canada and you weren't aware of this, well, you know now, you can actually download all the songpacks, one through, what, eight now.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think you can at least get one through seven.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm pretty sure you can get eight at this point now.
[SPEAKER_15]: So...
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, definitely check that out if you're in Canada and you've been wanting to get those.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's definitely worth it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But for us here in America, we've just been waiting and waiting and waiting for Song Pack 8 to come out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it has some new songs that are new to DDR and haven't been in DDR before.
[SPEAKER_15]: Such as Cosmic Cowgirl, that song from DDR Freak... Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Guitar Freaks, not DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a different thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is a whole ton of fun to play on Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know what's funny about the steps to Cosmic Cowgirl?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's very similar to kind of how you play it on basic on the guitar, so I thought that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then, let's see, what else is there?
[SPEAKER_15]: By LaLakia, Carried With The Wind was another one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then we have, that's also from Guitar Freaks, and it's kind of a very pop-ish sort of song, like one of those lute songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: and then also Kind Lady Interlude, which is cool, because Kind Lady is cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then we have More Deep, which is coming over from Max USA too, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then we have another brand new one,
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's a remix of In My Eyes, and it's done by the folks in the band Neuropa, who did the song Standing Still in Time for Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so what we're going to do, we're going to go ahead and play that for you guys, because we know not all you guys have an Xbox out there.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you probably want to check out this song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe you're thinking about buying the pack.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here it is, a remix of In My Eyes.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the Neuropa mix, premiere here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Enjoy.
and many more.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, that was a premiere here of In My Eyes, the Naropa mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: That being said, what did y'all think?
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, I know you have an opinion.
[SPEAKER_11]: It starts with an A, and it ends with an S, and it spells ass!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's another one of those... I've made this argument before where they try too hard to put too much in it, and do too many things at once.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only ever good mix that I've heard that was not the original was the Midi Head one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Midi Head one is superior.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which was also good because there wasn't any man singing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what did you think of that one?
[SPEAKER_21]: Eh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have the same opinions on the I Feel remixes.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're just like, eh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan, I know you don't really play much DDR, but did you have an opinion on that song at all?
[SPEAKER_20]: It sounded like four other crappy songs sort of jammed together.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's exactly my opinion on it, is that I think it's too much.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's too many things going on there.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like I would recognize part of it, well, I guess it wasn't mixed, but I'd recognize part of it from something that I totally didn't expect it to be from, and I'd be thinking, hey, I like that, but I don't like it here.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's awful.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I feel bad because I really like Naropa and I really, really, really like their other song and Ultramix too.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it's awesome, but I just don't know where that mix came from, honestly.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, we knew in the chatroom we just took a shot at the Sega Master System.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Back on track, back on track.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hold on, we can hate on people who hate Sega later.
[SPEAKER_15]: But the remix itself is just, it's so busy and there's so much going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: The MIDI head one I thought was way better.
[SPEAKER_15]: That one, I hate to say it, I don't really care for it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But the weird thing about it is, is that when you actually play it in the game, the steps I actually like a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which is kind of weird because...
[SPEAKER_15]: The steps are kind of odd, and they don't really go with the beat at all, but I think that's the reason why I like it so much, is because it's very different.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, they're different, and you'd think there's only so many different patterns you could do with four arrows, and everything you can do, everything that can be done has been done, but I think that the steps to the song when I played it, it was the first song I played in a long, long time where I went, huh, these steps are kind of unique.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, for that reason, it kind of made it a fun one to dance to, but the song itself, it's like, could I take those steps and put them on a different song, and I'd be much happier, because that song doesn't really do it for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't really see getting down to that, so.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, maybe you guys have a different thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: We will open up the Skype line later if you guys have a thought on that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can definitely share your opinion there with us.
[SPEAKER_15]: www.
[SPEAKER_15]: dot orange launch radio dot com click on interact with us and you can learn all sorts of detail about the skype line alright speaking of the skype line we're going to go to the skype line pretty quick and we're going to talk to one of our buddies on the skype line who sent us some news this week on Gita Dora the brand new incarnation of Gita Dora it's going to be a little different so let's see if we can get him on the skype line I just sent him a message that says we're calling so hopefully he's there
[SPEAKER_15]: And hopefully we don't have lag issues or any of that stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we're going to talk about Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania V. Like the song, V. Like peace.
[SPEAKER_15]: And now it doesn't want to call.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's very odd.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just saying connecting, dot dot dot, connecting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh no, and it says user not online.
[SPEAKER_15]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: What we'll do is we'll go here.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to go to the list.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm actually very excited to be seeing at least some type of new incarnation of Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania because it seems like that series was getting very stale.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was kind of like, oh, here comes 9th mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, here comes 10th mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, here comes 11th mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just the same thing over and over.
[SPEAKER_15]: But now it sounds like that there's actually something new
[SPEAKER_15]: Skyplane isn't open for general calls just yet, but we'll be taking those calls a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_15]: So don't get too impatient.
[SPEAKER_15]: We will get those calls a little later.
[SPEAKER_15]: But first I want to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_15]: So what's going on right now with this is... I guess it's location testing right now, or something weird's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we have a little bit of a song list.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have some song lists going on right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we're going to post this a little later.
[SPEAKER_15]: A Romanized song list.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much to DarkLionXVI.
[SPEAKER_15]: They gave us a Romanized song list of Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania V. And we're going to post that on our website a little later, the Romanized list.
[SPEAKER_15]: But let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me point out some highlights through the list here.
[SPEAKER_15]: A brand new Thomas Howard Lichtenstein song, You'll Be a Man.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what they call it.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's a band called Pooh.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they have a song called Mushroom Boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Best name ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Desro featuring Shige with Endless Cruising.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Brad Holmes, After a Hard Day.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then we have some licensed songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're actually covers by various folks.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we have...
[SPEAKER_15]: Sakunabo by Otsuka Ai, and then we have Friends by Rebecca, NGS by Asian Kung Fu Generation, Nocturne No.
[SPEAKER_15]: 9 by Hotei Tomoyasu, Wild Challenger by Jindu, and this is the best right here in my opinion, Misery Lou by the Spaghetti Surfers.
[SPEAKER_15]: You remember Misery Lou?
[SPEAKER_15]: Misery Lou is the song from Pulp Fiction.
[SPEAKER_15]: Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh.
[SPEAKER_15]: That song was awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then there's going to be some licensed songs as performed by the original musician that go on in this as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: And let's see, we're going to try getting our buddy back on the line here again.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to tell him to call us, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_15]: Something weird's going on there.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we have some licensed songs that's being performed by the original artists.
[SPEAKER_15]: And what I thought was interesting about this is that there's a Vanilla Ninja song in there.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know Vanilla Ninja was a girl group that did Tough Enough in Ultra Mix 2?
[SPEAKER_15]: Vanilla Ninja is on the list, and they are doing the song Liar, which I think is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, there's our buddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_15]: Siggy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey guys, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Finally, we got you on the line.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know what the heck happened.
[SPEAKER_15]: Skype's acting funny tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so we've been talking a little bit about Guitar Freaks, Drug Mania, V. We were talking about the original songs, the licensed cover songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was just getting into the licensed songs performed by the original artists, and I was kind of going, Vanilla Ninja, WTF!
[SPEAKER_15]: They're the girly band from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: What the hell are they doing here?
[SPEAKER_15]: Any thoughts?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've never heard of Vanilla Ninja.
[SPEAKER_15]: Vanilla Ninja is the group that did Tough Enough in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's also in the groove.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not into DDR Ultramix and stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, do you do the in the groove thing at all?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, I never, never.
[SPEAKER_24]: I never go for in the groove.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not my thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'd play a little clip, but I just don't feel like it right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell me about some of the other stuff we can expect with Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania V. Stuff that you've heard about.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, uh...
[SPEAKER_24]: Not really much to expect, but on the official website of Gita Dora V right now, the Gita Dora team is apologizing because they did not include the hidden option.
[SPEAKER_15]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_24]: The hidden option.
[SPEAKER_15]: Isn't this game location testing right now, or did it actually... They're actually playing right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, the official website of Gita Dora V is open.
[SPEAKER_15]: But sometimes those websites just go up when they're location testing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is this game actually out and about now?
[SPEAKER_24]: There wasn't anything said about the location test, so that means they're already playing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll be damned.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you wanted to introduce a little song here, something that we can actually expect to hear in Guitar Freaks Drum Media V, yes?
[SPEAKER_24]: It is the exact licensed song performed by the original artist.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: So Bimani Metalheads, Rejoice.
[SPEAKER_15]: We won't be sad
We had none, we had none, we had none, we had none We had none, we had none, we had none
[SPEAKER_06]: We've come to an understanding You are a prophet While I'm new to the race of secrets No more excuses
[SPEAKER_06]: And all the time we try to tear the street down
[SPEAKER_15]: Certainly a diverse reaction to that song in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: And hold on a minute because my head's still ringing a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Metalhead Haters
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what, okay, I guess the metalhead folks, because some folks in the chatroom are just cheering at this, and some people are just absolutely saying, I don't even want to play Guitar Freaks Drum Mania V right now if this song's on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But some folks are just saying this is awesome, so certainly a diverse selection of music to be in the next Guitar Freaks Drum Mania incarnation.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd totally play that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's just great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Except my hand would hurt like a bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'd play that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would play that song.
[SPEAKER_18]: You get the wailing bonus for, like, whacking the guitar against the machine when you're done?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the kind of song where I would wail and then swing the guitar around and smack a Roseville, Golfland child in the face.
[SPEAKER_15]: In front of his mother.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have any tokens for you, you little shit!
[SPEAKER_21]: Can you imagine the drum mania part of that song?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's not going to be an easy song, whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Some folks in the chat room are saying, here are the lyrics to that song, and then just banging on the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you really can't understand.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me take a little clip.
[SPEAKER_15]: Siggy, help me understand here, because you seem to be in the middle.
[SPEAKER_15]: Help me understand what they're saying in this song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me get you to the part where they're actually singing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds like Lords of Dishwasher Scabies is what I heard.
[SPEAKER_24]: Honestly, I haven't checked out the lyrics to Panasonic Youth yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is a thrash metal.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, yeah, it's kind of really hard to understand.
[SPEAKER_15]: It certainly does make me want to break things.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, well, it's certainly a sign of diversity to come in the next Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any other news on this new mix you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, let me just help you out pronouncing the songs right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Please do, because I have issues, apparently.
[SPEAKER_24]: The Carried by the Wind song, it's actually pronounced Balalaika.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ancient Breeze by Ono Hideyuki and White Tornado by Trek Trap
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, you get to pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because usually, like in the older Guitar Freaks, you don't get to pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I noticed, I think in the newer one, like some of the newer ones, you get to start picking a little later on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just remember, what was it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fifth note was fourth mix with Carnival Day.
[SPEAKER_11]: And going, what the hell song is this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it kicked my ass the first time around.
[SPEAKER_15]: I remember Fireball.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fireball.
[SPEAKER_15]: From like 6 and 5.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now I can beat Carnival Day easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: All the songs now are a lot harder than they used to be.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, on the Gita Dora V, there are two special stages, which is Encore, Fairy Tales by Izumi Mitsushiko, and the Premium Encore stage.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here's a little bit interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: The Zabu Fluta by Wanyan Panic.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, the song The Zabu Fluta is a Mozart song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'm sure they've made it very difficult to play and rock out because it's a premium encore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any idea what the differences are between an encore and a premium encore at this point?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, it's kind of like Guitadora 10-9.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, you know, if you have a double ass on an extra stage, you get to access premium encore stage, which was a timepiece phase 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you don't get, you know, if you don't get an, if you got an S, you get to access Unscore Stage, which is, you know, which is a Model DD5 on a Guita Dora 9.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, okay, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, you had a comment?
[SPEAKER_15]: You wanted to say something?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I thought you did.
[SPEAKER_15]: You were like reaching for the mic, I thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any other comments you want to tell us about Guitadora V until we start seeing some machines here in the States and we start getting some news around here?
[SPEAKER_24]: There are revival songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not sure whether it's going to be an e-amusement access or not.
[SPEAKER_24]: But here are the songs that are going to be revived.
[SPEAKER_24]: Model DD2, Herring Row, Staff, Smile For You, High...
[SPEAKER_24]: Sweet Illusion, Potpourri d'Orange, Heaven Inside, and Depend on Me Long Version.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on, everybody knows that song is Potpourri d'Orange.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_24]: Potpourri d'Orange.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Paul Sanderson.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I hate the French.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, merde.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody knows that song is Potpourri d'Orange.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't give me that d'orange stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Da Orange.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's much better when it's pronounced in French, Monsieur.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just like you're listening to Da Orange Lounge Radio, alright?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Da Orange.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not Da Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: And yeah, and the other Orange Lounge song is pronounced Putori de Marmalade.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, well now I've heard Marmalade, but that's only because I know this song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Criole de Marmalade.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Siggy, thanks for the updates on Guitadora V. We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even if that song gave us all a headache, we do appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Always helping us out there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Helping me out with my pronunciation because I have issues pronouncing things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I've given up.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: At some point, we're going to roll you over here to this screen so you can see this list and you're going to start reading all this stuff so they can make fun of me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or they can make fun of you instead of me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: I found the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_15]: You found the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, these are the lyrics to that song, Panasonic.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to give you a little taste of the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_15]: Should I do it in their style?
[SPEAKER_18]: The idea is we want to know what they are.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: We wrote these plans, took the order, the architecture, and followed them to the end until the gears ground cold and relentless.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was no remorse.
[SPEAKER_15]: We had none.
[SPEAKER_15]: We kept on with no trace of a regret.
[SPEAKER_15]: I never saw any blood, no soul for the body.
[SPEAKER_15]: Watched them turn, her scab-covered skin.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, that's the part that I thought was dishwasher scabies, because of the skin.
[SPEAKER_15]: Her scab-covered skin into a stone like a coal in the sky Searching for the dawn for the last time Bloated with wide eyes wide We've come to an understanding You lose, I profit, high noon And there ain't no secrets no more The song is called what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'm not going to read the whole damn song.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's one giant run-on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, the whole thing is one giant run-on sentence, which is not much of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's the song called again?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's called Panasonic Youth.
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought it was going to be about, like, VCRs and...
[SPEAKER_15]: When I first read it, I only heard, I don't know, somehow my eyes only caught the Sonic Youth part.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I was like, cool, we're getting a Sonic Youth song in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I was disappointed.
[SPEAKER_18]: Especially once you heard it.
[SPEAKER_11]: There is a Sonic Youth song that I would want in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's 100%.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want way more songs in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_18]: And more home versions.
[SPEAKER_15]: We definitely need more home versions.
[SPEAKER_15]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need to put my Drum Mania controller to use.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, I've been session moding it all the time.
[SPEAKER_18]: You just won't come down and play.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you can hear the breathing in the background, that's because we did pick up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even though I didn't say it was open, eh, hell, people were calling in anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, hell, let's take a call.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who dis?
[SPEAKER_15]: This is El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello, El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_15]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm doing good, Skye.
[SPEAKER_23]: How about yourself?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm trying to get over the Dishwater Scabies song, but otherwise I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I have recently taken the plunge into 2DX.
[SPEAKER_15]: Congratulations!
[SPEAKER_15]: How does one take the plunge, so to speak, into 2DX?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, you spend $250 on games in the controller.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's quite a plunge.
[SPEAKER_23]: Been there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Been there, done that, yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so how are you enjoying the water now that you've taken the plunge?
[SPEAKER_23]: I am enjoying the water very much.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, how is it going for you?
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, how are you warming up into the game?
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you jump right into hard stuff, or did you just start on beginner mode or drill mode?
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you getting into this game?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I wanted to start on Light 7, but I was forced into beginner mode because, well, two stars on Light 7 kicked my ass, and that couldn't have been right.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a tough game.
[SPEAKER_23]: Have you ever played the arcade version at all?
[SPEAKER_23]: Actually, I have a total of two times.
[SPEAKER_23]: Once in 2003 when I went to Vegas, and once in 2004 when the machine in Vegas moved to a different place.
[SPEAKER_23]: So you at least had some idea of what to expect?
[SPEAKER_23]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, I had more experience in the original Beatmania, actually.
[SPEAKER_23]: I played it a few more times.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, right on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, usually there's that big question that always goes around out there is that, you know, I'm new to 2DX, what style should I buy?
[SPEAKER_23]: So what styles did you end up buying?
[SPEAKER_23]: I ended up getting 7th and 8th style being as they are the most current ones.
[SPEAKER_23]: So far I like 7th style the best because it has the more fleshed out beginner's mode and it has more of the songs that I like.
[SPEAKER_15]: Interesting, because I kind of preferred 8th style when I played them both.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's kind of interesting, but okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, of course, but we have a different perspective.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, we're not new anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I spent three hours playing 8th style one night.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: On New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which one has burning heat?
[SPEAKER_15]: 7th.
[SPEAKER_15]: 7th, yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Then 7th style rocks.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's not that I don't like 8th style, it's that 7th style is much better for me to get into.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can play more songs on beginner.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's much easier for me to go through.
[SPEAKER_23]: Then I go to 8th style, play a few songs, and go back to 7th style and cower in the corner of beginner's mode again.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, is your goal to become a 2DX master?
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you going to pick up the other styles at some point, or do you think this is going to be it for you, or what
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm looking into purchasing Ninth Style eventually when it comes out, but I'm leaning toward waiting for it rather than pre-ordering for it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'd rather get good on the two games that I have before jumping into a third one and spreading myself even further.
[SPEAKER_15]: NightStyleSongList
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's the one thing that's holding me back from playing a lot of 2DX.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I don't get is why my controller, which is a good two years older than yours, is still in perfect condition.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mine took a lot of abuse, especially when... Mine fell off of the van.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really don't know what to tell you on that one.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd like to tell that story, but we don't have that kind of time.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, we do have quite a bit of time.
[SPEAKER_18]: Told her, don't take the fucking controller.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're not going to use it.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to a convention.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to have other things to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used it.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's like, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got to take it.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's brand new.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, we just got it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Beautiful shape.
[SPEAKER_18]: I said, no, it's going to get abused.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're going to throw it in the back of the van.
[SPEAKER_18]: Something's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_18]: We get there.
[SPEAKER_18]: We pull in the parking garage.
[SPEAKER_18]: We pop open the back of the van.
[SPEAKER_18]: The controller doesn't just fall out.
[SPEAKER_18]: It like gets propelled out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Flies across the parking garage and just clatters in the pavement.
[SPEAKER_18]: Jamie's got a look on her face like... And I'm like, see?
[SPEAKER_18]: I fucking told you that was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's probably the sound she made, too, huh?
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, she looked shocked.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that thing had been broken.
[SPEAKER_18]: I would have never, ever let her forget it.
[SPEAKER_18]: But she got off lucky.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it worked just fine.
[SPEAKER_18]: And we took it apart and gave it a little service.
[SPEAKER_18]: We didn't take it apart that day.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, we took it all apart.
[SPEAKER_18]: We cleaned every button.
[SPEAKER_18]: and it works a lot better now.
[SPEAKER_11]: We did that recently.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, no, we didn't do it that day.
[SPEAKER_18]: We didn't do any of that bizarre shaving the buttons like some idiots that we know advise us to do.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which I refuse to.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't shave the buttons.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's because you're smart.
[SPEAKER_18]: You should have the mad scientist here build you a real controller.
[SPEAKER_18]: Take the circuit board out of that old controller.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because he'll never finish it.
[SPEAKER_15]: He doesn't finish any of his projects.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only one he's ever finished is the orange Xbox thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, now, I finished those pads
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, look.
[SPEAKER_15]: The pads are done.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they broke after like a week.
[SPEAKER_13]: They did not break.
[SPEAKER_13]: They work perfectly fine.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just they build up a lot of static electricity.
[SPEAKER_18]: The trick is to get it done cosmetically before you get it done functionally.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because it's like your arcade cap.
[SPEAKER_18]: The thing works.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it's like, damn, why should I work on it more?
[SPEAKER_18]: It works.
[SPEAKER_18]: It doesn't look so great.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got our caller online, our poor caller sitting there just listening to us yell at each other.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_15]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will get to that 7th style break at some point because I know you wanted to hear some 7th style music to celebrate your 2DX goodness.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything that you think the home versions are lacking versus the arcade version, having played both?
[SPEAKER_23]: I've had such little experience with the arcade version, I wouldn't know what to say, what to do.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can't really comment on arcade song list versus home song list because these are the only songs that I know
[SPEAKER_23]: So politically correct.
[SPEAKER_23]: I guess if I could say that my controller is a little unresponsive in some portions.
[SPEAKER_23]: The turntable right now is the bane of my existence.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm so tempted to turn on auto-scratch, but then I don't learn anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: Out of curiosity, what kind of controller did you pick up?
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you pick up an official Konami one?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: The official Konami one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those are the ones you want to get.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, and just take very, very good care of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, seriously, the next one I get, I'm going to put it back in the box every time I play.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to, like, wrap it back up so that a damn piece of dust does not get into that thing because I don't know how my current controller got ruined, but it's just screwed beyond belief and it makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anything else you want to share with us today, O'Mullet?
[SPEAKER_23]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm in 2DX and I'm not off the DDR bandwagon yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, a lot of people when they go over to 2DX, they start adopting that DDR sucks attitude.
[SPEAKER_23]: Believe it or not, I can kind of see where they're coming from because 2DX is a hell of a lot more challenging than DDR is.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a different game.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Comparing apples to oranges.
[SPEAKER_15]: With DDR, you're moving your whole body.
[SPEAKER_15]: With 2DX, you're moving your fingers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, granted, it may take longer to get better at this or whatever, but it's certainly a different type of challenge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Definitely, one of them is challenging your physical ability, while one of them is challenging a little more your musical and rhythmic ability.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, it's very different.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_18]: and it was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_18]: It can't be that much harder.
[SPEAKER_18]: You see like these, what?
[SPEAKER_18]: What's the biggest song?
[SPEAKER_18]: Is it like a 10-foot these days?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, on DDR?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, 10-foot.
[SPEAKER_18]: You could go over to... It's called like Nuclear-tastic or something?
[SPEAKER_15]: You could go over to In The Groove and they have like 13s, Pandemonium or something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like a super tough song.
[SPEAKER_18]: I remember watching these people play like, you know, like the 8-foot songs, like in the day.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm watching these songs, like, I don't know, what was the one, Dropout or something like that?
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm watching you guys play this and I'm like, oh dear God!
[SPEAKER_18]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_18]: You can't move that fast.
[SPEAKER_15]: The person that does the 2DX one-handed would go over to DDR and probably... After playing a song.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the person that plays DDR and plays the 14-footers or whatever would probably go over to 2DX and go, Too many lines!
[SPEAKER_18]: Too many lines!
[SPEAKER_23]: That's pretty much how I went into it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Looks can be deceiving, my friend.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's the cartoon bunnies.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's where they get you.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is all about keyboard mania.
[SPEAKER_15]: God bless keyboard mania.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rest your soul in peace.
[SPEAKER_15]: I miss ye.
[SPEAKER_20]: Did they kill it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, well, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it's on indefinite hiatus, basically.
[SPEAKER_20]: That means it's dead.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, basically.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, we're going to let you go because I've got other people that are hammering the lines that want to get in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yes, please, work in your plug.
[SPEAKER_23]: InsidePulse.com My column's on Fridays.
[SPEAKER_23]: Read it, please.
[SPEAKER_23]: It pays the bills.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, I don't get paid shit for this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you going to get to go to E3 because of it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you have a column on the intro?
[SPEAKER_23]: I have final exams.
[SPEAKER_23]: You poor bastard!
[SPEAKER_23]: They always organize final exams when E3 is.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hate my college.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hate it to death.
[SPEAKER_15]: How many more years is college?
[SPEAKER_23]: At the end of this year, I should be out, finally.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then we'll see you next year.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, my computer was down for a couple of weeks, and then my anime cosplay club, we were getting ready for Capcom, and we were taking Sundays for rehearsals.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: So we got that together, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, people like to use Sunday nights for other things, even though they should understand that this program is on.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: They should all be in church.
[SPEAKER_15]: Worshipping us.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, this is my church right here.
[SPEAKER_26]: This is my church.
[SPEAKER_26]: Church of Orange Lines Radio.
[SPEAKER_26]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_26]: Can I get an amen?
[SPEAKER_15]: Testify, my brother.
[SPEAKER_15]: God, that's a scary notion.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is a scary-ass notion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't praise us.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_15]: You being the head of a church?
[SPEAKER_15]: We're just big, stupid kids like the rest of you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, you can't deny the financial opportunities in being the head of a church.
[SPEAKER_18]: Plus, when you get tired of it being a church, it can become a cult.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then you can be a cult leader.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I'd be one of those churches that would be like on the Daily Show because we have the topless preachers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, that would be... What church is this?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, if you guys were a church, it'd be a tax write-off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my God, he's got a point.
[SPEAKER_15]: If we were a church, we could write this shit off on our taxes.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what I was telling you.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can't deny the financial opportunity.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can I get an amen?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a guy I met at Coast Con eight years ago who has the Church of the Great Green Frog.
[SPEAKER_11]: He did it just so he could have the tax write-off.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he was going around passing Get Out of Hell free cards.
[SPEAKER_18]: There is a first church of Pac-Man as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's also the Partridge Family Cult.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kid you not, the Partridge Family Cult exists.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: It fully looked like the Monopoly card, except it had a frog with wings, wearing a tuxedo, and it was the Church of the Great Green Frog.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to see if he has a website.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, before we got off on that tangent, how was the convention that you went to?
[SPEAKER_26]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_26]: Some people complained it was in two different hotels, but
[SPEAKER_26]: I had a great time overall.
[SPEAKER_26]: It was packed as hell and it was tons of Naruto cosplayers.
[SPEAKER_26]: Gee, I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_15]: Could it be because it was NarutoCon?
[SPEAKER_26]: That and it was licensed just that week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: I heard that news.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, we got together for the giant photo shoot.
[SPEAKER_26]: There was about 200 of us.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're all in front of the hotel.
[SPEAKER_26]: People that want to take our pictures are going into the streets.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're telling people to drive around us.
[SPEAKER_26]: Security's coming out settling us out.
[SPEAKER_26]: You gotta move.
[SPEAKER_26]: There's 200 of us.
[SPEAKER_26]: Where are we going to move to?
[SPEAKER_15]: Were they taking pictures, like, for promotional purposes as well?
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, are you gonna be famous?
[SPEAKER_26]: No, it was a giant Naruto cosplay photo shoot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Everybody wanted to jump in on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's still pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I can post links to some pictures if you'd like later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Post them in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let our chatters check it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: That I will in just a bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_26]: Any video gaming going on at the convention?
[SPEAKER_26]: I couldn't even make it over to the gaming section.
[SPEAKER_26]: All I know is that if it was the same setup like last year, it was like maybe...
[SPEAKER_26]: There's probably one American Idol set up, two Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: American Idol?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: At one of these conventions?
[SPEAKER_15]: What the heck?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's not Japanese.
[SPEAKER_15]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's crap.
[SPEAKER_26]: After Gwen Stefani's CD, I'm calling.
[SPEAKER_26]: They're going to try to get her to come to a con to sing any of those songs.
[SPEAKER_26]: And I'm done.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's when I'll retire.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think you were breaking up a little bit there, but I picked up most of that, I think, about the Gwen Stefani CD and after her latest inspirations and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything else you wanted to share with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_15]: What are you calling?
[SPEAKER_26]: The skit that we did.
[SPEAKER_26]: We did Naruto 2 Ninja Rap.
[SPEAKER_26]: We won Best Technical Job.
[SPEAKER_15]: Best Technical Job.
[SPEAKER_15]: What exactly is the technical component of a skit at an anime convention?
[SPEAKER_26]: The fact that the tech group loved the fact that they were able to post GoNinjaGo on the big screens while we were dancing.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well congratulations on the award.
[SPEAKER_15]: What did you get for that?
[SPEAKER_26]: We just got a trophy, that was it.
[SPEAKER_26]: It seems that cons are getting cheaper and cheaper.
[SPEAKER_26]: I remember when you won, they gave you like a box set and a stack of music and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: Now it's just a certificate.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, you got a NarutoCon trophy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who needs a fucking Oscar, right?
[SPEAKER_26]: True.
[SPEAKER_26]: I have my fandom.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, before I let you go, can I get an amen?
[SPEAKER_26]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_15]: You too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later.
[SPEAKER_18]: Laters.
[SPEAKER_18]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd like it to be said that that whole phone call is like why I don't go to anime conventions anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_18]: Have you been to an anime convention?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not in a long time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, hold on there, caller.
[SPEAKER_18]: The skit
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_18]: All this jive about Dillager
[SPEAKER_15]: Liz, waiting for us to shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry, Zach, I will shut up now so you can talk.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_17]: It needs to be the legend of hang-ups.
[SPEAKER_22]: All this jive about Dillinger's skate plan song on Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_22]: The fact that it was basically shunned upon in this chatroom, no offense.
[SPEAKER_22]: And, you know, I as a metalhead, I mean, what's the deal with the rest of the chatroom?
[SPEAKER_22]: Why is, like, you know, it's almost split, let alone almost, you know, leaning towards hatred towards this song.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_22]: I sense a bunch of haters about this.
[SPEAKER_15]: But think about it Skye
[SPEAKER_22]: Think about it, I mean, you have a song, you have Konami right here, who's basically has the balls to even license a song in the first place, so that way they could attract a newer, you know, newer type of group.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're being very eclectic with the songs that they have so far.
[SPEAKER_22]: And so, you know, in this, if they were to go stateside with Good Adoram...
[SPEAKER_22]: They'll pick up the metalheads like that if they have that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, here's my thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: If they have the balls to license that song, I mean, as interesting of a selection as it is or whatever, why don't they have the balls to put out a new DDR?
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, let's go ahead and stop right there, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, that's a different story, but... No self-respecting metalhead will ever play Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, that's a different story, but regarding this one... Ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, that's a pretty controversial point, Dan.
[SPEAKER_15]: What makes you say that no metalhead would ever play Guitar Freaks?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because let's be honest, Guitar Freaks is silly.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're playing this plastic guitar.
[SPEAKER_22]: How about Drum Mania?
[SPEAKER_18]: Now Drum Mania is a lot cooler than Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Drum Mania is actually hammered on a drum.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can see somebody being like, you know, Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_18]: I play Guitar Freaks at home, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: And I got my little plastic ukulele.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm wailing out hard to whatever song I can play on the home version.
[SPEAKER_18]: and I'm like, dude, I look stupid.
[SPEAKER_18]: But in my mind, you know, I'm like...
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, a god of rock.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it's like, you're going to get a metalhead, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: A real metalhead, which there aren't any more real metalheads.
[SPEAKER_22]: People who play the guitars are metalheads.
[SPEAKER_22]: People who play in a band are metalheads.
[SPEAKER_18]: The people who are real metalheads play the guitar.
[SPEAKER_18]: They don't play the guitar for you.
[SPEAKER_22]: They play the real drums.
[SPEAKER_22]: They play bass.
[SPEAKER_22]: They play all that.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're in a band.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've seen guys with mullets playing guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, but no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_18]: Bullet and Metalhead, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_22]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Think about the metalheads that play not only DDR, but Bomani games in general.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like me.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, it started off with DDR, and then it moved on to other games, like 2DX.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you never see a metalhead playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: But Zaku is saying he is a metalhead who's playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_17]: Zaku's a faker.
[SPEAKER_18]: Metalheads do two things, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: They smoke weed, and they listen to metal.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_22]: That is a stereotype.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, man.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's bull, man.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's just a stereotype.
[SPEAKER_22]: It wouldn't be a stereotype if it wasn't true.
[SPEAKER_22]: You'd be surprised at the number of people that play DDR, not just regular... No, no, I wouldn't be... Trust me, I wouldn't be surprised at the number of people who play DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd be surprised at the number of Metalheads who play DDR, because as far as I'm concerned, that number is zero.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, no, you got one right here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, Zaku, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_18]: You are the exception that proves the rule.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_18]: Metalheads are rushing to arcades right now to throw down the Mad Dance Dance action.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because, you know, the brand of electronic hip-hop, or not even hip-hop, electronic pop music inside of it, really appeals to the rocker and their soul.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, but we're different.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, we play DDR, remember that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, nothing like B4U, the fucking J-pop metalhead rockers.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what I'm talking about!
[SPEAKER_18]: You know it's true.
[SPEAKER_18]: There is no self-respecting metalhead who would hear the music from a B-Mani machine and not run over and kill it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now maybe that one song we just heard might be the beginning of the metalhead B-Mani renaissance.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not happening.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need to clarify something for Zaku.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've made careers out of taking things out of context, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Politicians do it every day.
[SPEAKER_18]: And incidentally, the opinions of my fucked up self are in no way, shape, or form the opinions of Orange Lounge Radio or anybody else in the whole damn world.
[SPEAKER_18]: But they're pretty damn funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly, I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Quit fucking on my program.
[SPEAKER_22]: The fact of the matter is this, you know, there's not only two metalheads or any other type of people playing EDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're taking off his headset.
[SPEAKER_22]: People who listen to rap music, yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, no, rap people playing DDR, you know, punks, scots, metalheads, as I said before.
[SPEAKER_22]: Almost everyone plays DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: Don't forget bags.
[SPEAKER_22]: You might not know it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_18]: That too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_18]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just killing it, man.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's just killing it.
[SPEAKER_22]: You just killed it right there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: Konami has the balls to go that far.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, you know, live with it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, that's what they did.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's already been done.
[SPEAKER_22]: The license has already been acquired and it's going to be in there no matter what you say.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Seriously, I've been arguing for years that there needs to be more metal music in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because it would appeal to me.
[SPEAKER_18]: But again, I can't really see a real metalhead going out there playing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, but you don't know that for sure.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sorry if I'm talking over you, Rob's computer's crossing around.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have to think of, you know, take for a second and think of, you know, Konami's rationale.
[SPEAKER_22]: What do they want out of, you know, out of Guitar Freaks and any other Bomani game?
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, more people.
[SPEAKER_22]: They would sure, in most cases, they would love to pick up, you know, many types of people.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not just, you know, the typical, you know, typical regular person who probably doesn't listen to metal, but just, you know, a new type.
[SPEAKER_22]: Spread out their bass a little.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that way they get everyone.
[SPEAKER_22]: and they get more, you know, and that's more, you know, more sales than that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: The bottom line is, and we gotta move on soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: As much as I enjoy it when you call into the show, Saku, because damn, I haven't laughed this hard in months.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think the Gita Dora mix is promising to be a very diverse selection of music.
[SPEAKER_15]: And if we win over some metalheads...
[SPEAKER_15]: Then, hey, great.
[SPEAKER_15]: And if we don't, well, we always have the fags, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: It wins for everyone.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because, you know, the more it's eclectic, the more everyone will join in.
[SPEAKER_18]: Incidentally, since the games aren't meant for America anyway, they're just appealing to the Japanese metalhead.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the Japanese metalhead is stuck in 1988.
[SPEAKER_18]: When metal was metal.
[SPEAKER_17]: That is a very good observation.
[SPEAKER_18]: Before it was... On that note... More 80s rock.
[SPEAKER_17]: On that note, Zach... Guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_18]: and I'm putting up the horns.
[SPEAKER_18]: Watch the webcam.
[SPEAKER_18]: The horns are up.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think we should bury the hatchet right now.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think it's done.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think I flamed and ranted long enough.
[SPEAKER_22]: I made my point clear.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have a good one, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for your... Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can hear that a little bit, by the way.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn, you need to come visit us more often.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was good stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need a break after that, I need to breathe a little bit
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll open up the Skype line later for more of you guys who want to call in.
[SPEAKER_15]: In the meantime, though, we've got a cage match to get to.
[SPEAKER_15]: We want to get to the FUs of the week as well and some other news.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe we'll have time for a DDR Freak post of the week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Speaking of DDR Freak, Friday nights, check it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio Rewind.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe you are checking us out right now on the Rewind over there.
[SPEAKER_15]: We appreciate their support in helping us out and their efforts to help us convert people to the Church of Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_26]: Can I get an amen?
[SPEAKER_26]: Amen!
Thank you for watching!
DarkSakura DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Baby it's on, let's go
[SPEAKER_03]: Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music
[SPEAKER_15]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: After, oh man, I had to catch my breath.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was just laughing so hard.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan, you crack me up.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm glad you're here.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what I do.
[SPEAKER_15]: You want to laugh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Go buy an ignition pad at the Marconi GameStop.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll be the first in line to be berated by Dan.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan will berate you and your taste in music in person.
[SPEAKER_18]: Only if you step up saying, I'm the DDR playing metal freak.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: At the next DDR tournament, I'm going to find a bunch of metalheads to, you know, send you a special FU.
[SPEAKER_18]: Zaku's already proven that he's the exception to the rule.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we can find at least one other.
[SPEAKER_18]: There was another guy in the chatroom saying that he was... I'm saying my argument is now null and void.
[SPEAKER_18]: I said no metalheads are Bimani fans, and he said I'm a metalhead, I don't want to be a metalhead.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't have a way to disprove his metalness.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't say that his Bimaniness makes him less of a metalhead.
[SPEAKER_18]: The truth is the guy might eat, sleep, and breathe metal and then go out and play DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe he puts on a Walkman and listens to metal while he's playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: So basically you got pwned.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got told.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what I said.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, you said, I'm metalhead.
[SPEAKER_18]: I said, oh, I guess I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got told.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, you were wanting to mention something there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Crap, I don't even remember now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just tried to blank I was, I'm sure I was I appreciate it I don't want to alienate the listeners I cannot remember what the hell I was thinking It just like, poof, went away Oh, now I remember, now I remember I was just going to say, yeah, Metalhead's playing DDR That was like the black people watching the films nominated for the Oscars As Chris Rock was pointing out in the beginning of the Oscars That was great
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, he was going around at what was the theater, the Magic Johnson Theater, asking the people if they'd seen Sideways or Million Dollar Baby.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're like, no.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he says, what was your favorite movie of the last year?
[SPEAKER_15]: And some of them are like, Chronicles of Riddick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, what are you laughing at there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell the listeners what's up.
[SPEAKER_11]: The link that DJ Ranma S posted in the chat room of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not for real though, is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a fake, but it's funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nobody knows what the PlayStation 3 is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you know, we just got a new submission for Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm having to turn it down because it's not citing a source for more information.
[SPEAKER_15]: But somebody did send us a new submission that says, coming to us from SummerDog, says, Nintendo will debut the Nintendo Revolution in May at E3.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we'll find out when we're at E3.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's old news.
[SPEAKER_15]: All three console makers were going to be debuting their new consoles at E3.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be lucky to get a tech demo on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's not surprising.
[SPEAKER_19]: I knew that was coming.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be lucky to get a tech demo on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what people don't know is the connectivity with the DS, which will be with the new system, because it will be also wireless, Bluetooth, or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think Sony will be downplaying the PS3 at E3.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think they'll be really trying to push the PSP.
[SPEAKER_18]: and I don't think they have enough of a system together yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: All they've said is sell processor rocks and it's finished and that we're using an upgraded emotion engine as the I.O.
[SPEAKER_19]: All I know is we're selling UMD movies now.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're distributing them.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't really want to see that format take off at all.
[SPEAKER_18]: It won't.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's going to flop just like DVHS.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's DVHS you may ask?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Digital VHS.
[SPEAKER_15]: We were talking about this briefly on the podcast, which by the way, if you haven't checked out the podcast, check it out, www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on Orange Lounge Radio to go for more information on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_15]: Check it out, bitches.
[SPEAKER_15]: You'll see anything that's owned by Sony.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and Spider-Man.
[SPEAKER_15]: Columbia Pictures, Action Flick.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, you're not going to be seeing dramas on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_15]: Exactly, you wouldn't see foreign films.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're not going to see that stuff on a PSP.
[SPEAKER_18]: With a new format, it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_18]: DVD has taken over the market.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's been the first thing since VHS to do so.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's always been a superior format to VHS out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Beta.
[SPEAKER_18]: Beta, Laserdisc.
[SPEAKER_18]: All sorts of stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: None of it could ever take over the market.
[SPEAKER_13]: The only thing I could see that possibly happened with this is the price point is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is $19.99 retail for these, which is kind of like that sweet number for movies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: You could see a new release movie coming out, UMD or whatever, at the same time.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's just really, honestly, the format, unless, and this is a big if, unless, like, the new PS3 is going to play UMD and DVD or something like that, you know, I don't really see any people buying stuff just to take it with them on the road.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, do you really need to watch, you know, Spider-Man 2 that much?
[SPEAKER_13]: And the difference, you know, a lot of times people, you know, have DVD players in cars, and I can see this is why they're trying to market this.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's because each individual kid has their own screen or there's a central screen there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kids are going to try to share a portable game system to watch a movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, it's just that Sony develops technology.
[SPEAKER_18]: And they feel compelled to use this technology somehow.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like Minidisc.
[SPEAKER_18]: How many years has Sony spent trying to pimp Minidisc?
[SPEAKER_18]: They're still trying to pimp that shit.
[SPEAKER_18]: 700 years.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, they're still trying to push minidisc as a viable format, and minidisc will never be a viable format.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, it has its uses, sure.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a neat little machine.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, if the PSP took minidiscs, that would rock.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it's not happening.
[SPEAKER_17]: That would have been a smart idea.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because the discs are the same size, am I not correct?
[SPEAKER_18]: Except for the UMD is rounded.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_18]: So...
[SPEAKER_18]: But yeah, it's like, if your PSP could play minidisc audio, that would be sick.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, it's the same thing with the UMD movie format.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like, Sony developed the technology, and they're a publicly traded company, so it took them, you know, a gajillion years, and stockholders are going like, what the crap are you going to do with this UMD?
[SPEAKER_18]: And Sony was like, we're going to make a portable game system out of it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now they're like, we can play movies with it too.
[SPEAKER_18]: So they feel compelled to use it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's good.
[SPEAKER_18]: It'd be nice that it takes off, and I think that it's cool to have a handheld that's going to play discs.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this proprietary new format will never, ever, ever be able to be pirated to a PC to be played on an emulator, or pirated over the internet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because it's proprietary, and they just can't read them.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know that in like 20 minutes they're going to be on Licksang.
[SPEAKER_18]: Licksang's going to be like, you can only buy these for purposeful backing up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Very legal.
[SPEAKER_18]: Don't pirate.
[SPEAKER_18]: You'll get a suit.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we'll see how the format does when the launch of the PSP is coming up very soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you remember the launch date?
[SPEAKER_18]: March 24th.
[SPEAKER_15]: March 24th.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you live in the Sacramento area.
[SPEAKER_18]: GameStop, Marconi and Fulton, come reserve yours now.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you don't, when you come in to buy one, and I don't have any because I won't, I'm going to laugh my ass off.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will not be getting a PSP on lunch today.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll have our, you can check it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, that sounds good.
[SPEAKER_18]: I traded in a DS.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, see, I love my DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: We had two.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still have my DS.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, that's good.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's our DS now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It lives in my laptop now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, well I guess it's my PSP.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: God told.
[SPEAKER_18]: Jamie just popped me the bird.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you believe that that kind of behavior would be going on here?
[SPEAKER_18]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, if you think about what it means in slang terms, you know, hey, hot.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's get to the Orange Lounge Radio cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_15]: Three songs doing battle with each other and you get to pick the winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on chat to participate.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is just a fun little thing we do for you guys to have an input and a say in what goes in Orange Lounge Radio Live's 24 hour a day, 7 day a week, Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_15]: You get one song to put in there.
[SPEAKER_15]: So...
[SPEAKER_15]: Here are your three choices for tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: The way this works, we play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: The one that gets the most votes from you guys in the chatroom goes into rotation all week long.
[SPEAKER_15]: You only get to hear a clip of the song that won last week.
[SPEAKER_15]: And speaking of last week, we actually had a song win for the third time, which means if it wins tonight, it is retired forever.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it will become only the third song...
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge History
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm on a stakeout I'm on a stakeout
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: The feeling is elating, biding my time Yeah, I know that you'll soon be mine Soon to mine Can't let you see me Can't let you see me Can't let you see me
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, that was last week's winner for the third time in a row, Freeze Pop with Stakeout.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's get into some new songs that are going to challenge that tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we're going to start it off with Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_13]: Girls.
[SPEAKER_13]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I picked... No, I did not pick girls.
[SPEAKER_13]: That joke is old and done with.
[SPEAKER_13]: I meant...
[SPEAKER_13]: I missed my opportunity for that joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't worry, I'll come back.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so I picked a different song.
[SPEAKER_13]: I picked another, a different drum label artist.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this group is called the Dignity of Labor.
[SPEAKER_13]: And their song, actually the one only song I see that this artist has done, at least it's on a different drum.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's called XRV, the Never Rock A Mix.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's, I don't know what the hell an XRV is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't listen to the lyrics of the song, but it sounds cool, so this is the song for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, from a different drum.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Dignity of Labor, XRV, The Never Rockin' Me.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I even edited it down for you guys, because, you know, it was a club-type song, you know, so I edited the end down, so don't listen to all that, you know, drum track and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it's still a good six minutes long.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like five and a half.
[SPEAKER_15]: My thing says six and a half.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not six and a half.
[SPEAKER_15]: It should not be.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hold on a second here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you probably copied it earlier.
[SPEAKER_13]: Does that say edit on it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, that's because you didn't copy the right one.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was prepared.
[SPEAKER_13]: You just tried to screw me over.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had it all ready to go for you, and I took all the extra time to edit it down for you, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is the thanks I get.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, the 6.5 version would have been the one with the outro on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I got rid of that, so you don't have to listen to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So now we have the one that's good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dignity of Labor, XRV.
[SPEAKER_15]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: YXR, VVVVV
There is a fallacy
All I generate, there is no form I cannot penetrate.
If only you could see the pain I feel in you.
A mirror to your soul is free, without a trace of vanity.
I'll share with you the mastery.
Reveal your agony with exalting you.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that was song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Dignity of Labor with XRV, the Neveraka mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Was that A-OK or was it A-S-S?
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: There wasn't enough variation in it to really make it... It was very generic sounding, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: It gets so sick.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was better than Freeze Pop, I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Better than Freeze Pop, that's all you need to know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, is that all you have to say about it anymore?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's better than Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything is better than Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Give it a score.
[SPEAKER_13]: It gets a better than Freeze Pop score.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan, your opinion on the song, and then you give it something on a scale of 1 to 10.
[SPEAKER_20]: That song was eternal.
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't think it would ever end.
[SPEAKER_20]: That being said, it didn't suck.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was just really long.
[SPEAKER_20]: Talk a little bit about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I disagree with Loki, Freeze Pop is better than that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not that that song was bad, it was just very, very, very long and very, very, very dry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, I think I could cut about a minute and a half out of that song and I'd really like it, but as far as the six and a half minute marathon mix, man, whatever, no.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I give it a six for the number of minutes it almost was.
[SPEAKER_20]: For dry, long songs, I realize it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, your turn, your pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: What did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, I know it's a remix of Bloodhound Gang.
[SPEAKER_15]: It sure is.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Bad Touch.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Bad Touch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, but it's by KMFDM.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I had forgotten that I had it and then I looked on a DVD and was like, oh, I have this, cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything else you want to say about it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bloodhound Gang, The Bad Touch, KMFDM mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well now, we call this the act of mating, but there are several other very important differences between human beings and animals that you should know about.
I want you smothered, want you covered, like my Waffle House Ash Browns, I'm a disc of the FedEx, never reaching a fix, just like a football stock You are a clown to make me rise an hour early, just like daylight's taking time You and me, baby, ain't nothing but mammals, so let's do it like they do on the Discovery Channel You and me, baby, ain't nothing but mammals, so let's do it like they do on the Discovery Channel
Lost Catacombs of Egypt, only God knows where we stuck it Hieroglyphics, let me be specific, I wanna be down in your southeast But I got this notion that the motion of your ocean
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing but mammals, so let's do it like they do on the Discovery Channel Do it again now You and me, baby, ain't nothing but mammals So let's do it like they do on the Discovery Channel Do it now You and me, baby, ain't nothing but mammals So let's do it like they do on the Discovery Channel Do it again now You and me, baby, ain't nothing but mammals So let's do it like they do on the Discovery Channel
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, that was Bloodhound Gang with Bad Touch, KMFDM Mix, song number 3 tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see what the folks in the studio thought of that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: I love that song, and I had, you know, set it aside, and then I found the mix, I was like, I love this mix!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a great mix of a great song, so it gets a 9.8 infinity.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's both of our own songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I get to vote for any damn song I want to as official goddess of this radio station.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, also you have to remember though, yeah, you got pwned again.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have to remember that we actually don't get to vote for the winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: We just get to give our big fat opinions.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like American Idol.
[SPEAKER_15]: Simon gets to give his opinion, but he doesn't get to pick the winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it's like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, your opinion.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gets a 10 because it's KMFDM.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fair.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's better than Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually like the original song quite a bit, but I'm sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really did not dig that remix at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wasn't feeling it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like the Eiffel 65 mix of that song a lot, but maybe because it's more Euro.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I wasn't into that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can only really give that a 6 as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan.
[SPEAKER_20]: That remix was the mad generic.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_20]: Words from the song.
[SPEAKER_18]: Words from the song.
[SPEAKER_18]: It gets like a four and a half.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's only because if I score it any lower, Jamie will throw heavier things at me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, well while Jamie... Oh, three and a half.
[SPEAKER_15]: While Jamie finds something heavy to throw at Dan, let's recap the three songs you can vote for tonight, starting with Freeze Pops, Stakeout.
[SPEAKER_06]: One and a half.
[SPEAKER_06]: Six point nine.
[SPEAKER_15]: Song number two, The Dignity of Labor with XRV.
[SPEAKER_15]: And song number three, The Bloodhound Gang with Bad Touch, the Apple 60, I'm sorry, Bad Touch.
[SPEAKER_11]: And no Euro crap on my song, thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry, wishful thinking there.
[SPEAKER_15]: The KMFDM Mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your votes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Boy, did I fuck that one up, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_18]: Now your words are a mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what's going on in the sim scene lately?
[SPEAKER_21]: Have we heard any more news about the election that was last year?
[SPEAKER_15]: What in the hell are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_13]: Just say no, because there's nothing going on in the sim scene!
[SPEAKER_13]: Nothing, zero, nada!
[SPEAKER_13]: There's more going on in my bathroom right now than there is in the goddamn sim scene.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zilch.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: To be honest, there's more sim files out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_13]: They still suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's more really crappy songs that people make that still really suck, and there's more Max remixes out there that still really suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: To be honest...
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Really, you know, get into another game, maybe, you know, discover girls, I don't know, just something else, but really, there's nothing going on at all in the sim scene, nothing nada, except for one little thing, and that's just that this is...
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, doing his part to promote the hobby.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is a DDRXXMix official website.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're doing version 2.0 right now, and they have this funny little thing on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just have to read it because it's just, you know, funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it is this little English thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It says, how we stand as dancer to dance.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I just thought that was funny, and that's all that I have to contribute as far as that.
[SPEAKER_15]: How can we stand as dancer to dance?
[SPEAKER_15]: DDRUK is gone.
[SPEAKER_13]: DDR Maniacs is never coming back as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's been gone for months, so really, does anyone miss it?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_13]: DDR UK, I'm sure they're going to come back someday, but it's going to be too late anyways.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just like the melting pot, remember that old-ass site that used to be around?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm afraid to say it, but yeah, there's nothing going on in the sim scene.
[SPEAKER_13]: The sim scene's dying.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's really, there's not much left.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played a cool thing that one of our listeners did.
[SPEAKER_15]: He did a Simphile to the Gem theme song by FreezePop, and it was pretty rad, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_15]: Check it out, guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is outrageous.
[SPEAKER_15]: Truly, truly, truly outrageous.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, the Misfits songs are better.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want, you know what I want?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, oh my god, sim people, oh my god, sim people, sim people Oh my god, oh my god, do this Get all of Jem's songs and make like an all Jem DDR mix And you can have some Misfits songs too because they were cool too But like, I want to make like this whole mix of DDR just out of songs that were featured in Jem Tell me that would not rock That would not rock You're a liar!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: They can open up DDRUK back up for this.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was just going to give you an example here of why there's nothing available right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I really got to find the song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I downloaded it earlier, and I know I'm probably not going to find it because there's just too much shit out there right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, this is a perfect example of why you do not need... I mean, just sim files nowadays, they're just really bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I cannot stress how bad they are, but I think I can come close with this song right here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, granted, it's not as colorful as Mac's vagina, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's...
[SPEAKER_13]: Pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this is a sim file.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can go out there and you can definitely thank Thunderbird, that's B-Y-R-D, 24 on BomaniStyle.com for this wonderful piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is six subs, seven grams of fat.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or seven subs of six grams of fat.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
Hey!
This is the week with you!
[SPEAKER_15]: You make this song stop and you make it stop now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ow, my eardrums.
[SPEAKER_15]: How do I unplug your computer?
[SPEAKER_06]: How do I do it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Please, turn it off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jesus, yes I can.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh dear God.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, that right there is why this stuff sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really, do we need this crap?
[SPEAKER_13]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is why the sim scene is dying.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's because of this crap.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I just made a last call for cage match votes, and it's been about 30 seconds, so I think that's enough time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you guys want to know who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do we ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is a very interesting situation.
[SPEAKER_15]: One vote yet again decides the cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it decides the cage match to be a tie once again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tie cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: Song number one tied tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dignity of Labor, XRV.
[SPEAKER_15]: And song number two tied tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_15]: And let's go to the rule book that shows that, oh yes, if in case of a tie, the host whose song did not get picked gets to break the tie.
[SPEAKER_15]: So Jamie, is she going to retire Freeze Pop or is she going to deny Freeze Pop that right and pick the other song?
[SPEAKER_15]: Freeze Pop's going down.
[SPEAKER_11]: On one hand, I could torture all of our listeners with more Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_11]: You did that last time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did that last time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loser!
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_15]: Loser!
[SPEAKER_15]: That's alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so new winner tonight, thanks to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie denies Freeze Pop the entrance to retire.
[SPEAKER_15]: XRV wins.
[SPEAKER_15]: But in reality, kids...
[SPEAKER_15]: If you don't agree with that, maybe you should have gotten your friend to vote.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because only one vote made the difference there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: So next week you all get Britney Spears remix, courtesy of me.
[SPEAKER_15]: So enjoy that next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to have an awesome cage match next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki's going to play that song we just heard.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, yes, we definitely need the FUs after that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're going to go to break, and then when we come back, the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_15]: So send us your FUs over private message, and we'll get to them.
[SPEAKER_15]: In this break, you get a potpourri.
[SPEAKER_15]: You get potpourri de mamani.
[SPEAKER_15]: Potpourri de mamani.
[SPEAKER_15]: Potpourri, rock.
[SPEAKER_15]: Potpourri.
[SPEAKER_15]: Starting it off with Setsugeka from TenStyle.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_15]: More Orange Launch Radio.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody, welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are going to get into the FUs of the week fairly shortly here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you guys for being loyal and sticking with us.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, I don't care this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only ones I saw, I saw Finding Neverland, which I really, really liked, but for some reason people wanted to stay far away from that movie, but it was really good, I guess because supposedly the guy was an accused child molester or something, but it was a good movie, whatever, let it just be a movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I saw Sideways, which was also funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_15]: And actually, I would say the best motion picture of the year would be Paris Hilton's sex tape, actually, would be the Oscar winner for this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if you saw it, but it was a fine performance by Miss Hilton.
[SPEAKER_06]: Negative.
[SPEAKER_15]: When she just stops in the middle of what she's doing to pick up that cell phone, I was moved.
[SPEAKER_18]: There was no dramatic focus.
[SPEAKER_13]: Personally, I thought that the art direction in Cameron Diaz, the bondage video that she did, was much better.
[SPEAKER_20]: Say what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, there's a Cameron Diaz bondage video.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's fucking hot!
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_18]: We have to use Jamie's computer to look up some porn.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now we know where that spyware is coming from.
[SPEAKER_15]: We did...
[SPEAKER_15]: We did watch, I don't know, like 10 minutes of the Oscars while it was sitting here on the TV, and we were waiting for the show to start, and Drew Barrymore came out, and what did Loki say something about, I saw a movie with her in it where she was naked and had blood on her boobs.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_15]: What was that you were talking about?
[SPEAKER_21]: She was in this really shitty horror movie, and I don't remember the name of it, but there was a shower scene where blood was coming out of the shower heads, and it was going over her breasts, so she was being...
[SPEAKER_13]: It was her, naked, with her boobies, and her boobies were being covered by fake blood.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the funny thing about Drew Barrymore was she was like 10 at the time.
[SPEAKER_18]: And she was already cracked out and had to take these really bad movies to keep her career alive.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's move on to the FUs of the week, shall we?
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, why is it we do these FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_20]: Because Danny hates humanity.
[SPEAKER_20]: That includes all of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, all of this is bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here is justice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here is punishment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here is... This is fucked up!
[SPEAKER_11]: They expect you to dust.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the two years of it we... worth of it that we stirred up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Five years.
[SPEAKER_11]: You didn't live in that damn apartment for five years.
[SPEAKER_12]: Four years.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lots of years.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up, my F.U.
[SPEAKER_11]: Big F.U.
[SPEAKER_11]: to my allergies.
[SPEAKER_11]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_11]: to stupid people who speed past me in the rain.
[SPEAKER_11]: to Dan for interrupting me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm surprised that actually you guys don't get an F.U.
[SPEAKER_18]: to Dan every week.
[SPEAKER_18]: In fact, I think that by now it should just be a feature.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, Jamie, F.U.
[SPEAKER_18]: to Dan, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Fucking duh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or I'll throw the ferret at you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Throw the ferret?
[SPEAKER_18]: Does that mean what I think it means?
[SPEAKER_18]: It doesn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: And F you to being sick for a week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ow, you bitch!
[SPEAKER_20]: I threw the ferret back.
[SPEAKER_11]: The voice thing landed on my collarbone.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to pain.
[SPEAKER_20]: Collarbone nothing.
[SPEAKER_20]: I hit her in the rack.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm a good throw.
[SPEAKER_11]: You hit me on my damn collarbone.
[SPEAKER_20]: Shut up, this is radio, they don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: You hit my laptop, you die.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aha, deflected.
[SPEAKER_11]: She wears such a bad aim.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, FUs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, FU to being distracted by the ferret being thrown by Dan.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to my laundry not being dry yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, uh,
[SPEAKER_11]: SU to Chipotle for having really good rice that I can't eat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: First off, fuck you the Oscars, because they still suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: Even if you do get Chris Rock to host it, that does not make them any better.
[SPEAKER_21]: They just still suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I feel sorry for Chris Rock for having to do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know he's hard up on money, and the need to take that job, but my god.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, what's going to be next?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dave Chappelle hosting the Oscars?
[SPEAKER_13]: That might get me to watch it, but I don't think it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, fuck you to my computer for, first off, you know, the power supply being all fucked up, and then I had to get a new one, and then the stupid little fan that was, you know, cooling my graphics, uh, proc card there, uh, well, it's too noisy, so I had to pull it out of there as well, and come to find out it wasn't doing shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, the...
[SPEAKER_13]: Fan was not even over the heat sink, so it was doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that kind of was lame.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then, um, fuck you to Final Fantasy because it's been all laggy and weird lately.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like you'd think that they hosted the servers in the United States or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because, I mean, they're really shitty.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then, uh, fuck you to Golf Land because, once again, you just do not maintain your stuff there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, my god.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't believe...
[SPEAKER_13]: You would think that they were Microsoft or something with all the shit that was broken there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just don't get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, um... Finally, um... Fuck these Macs because they suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm really getting sick of your bullshit, you little game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Link, come over here so I can kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: and F you to me sleeping 12 hours yesterday and 10 hours today.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a lot of sleep.
[SPEAKER_15]: And F you to some drama that was going on last week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, F you to big projects that fall in my lap at the last freaking minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate that stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate it!
[SPEAKER_15]: You guys have more advance notice of this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Quit giving it to me at the last minute and then making me, like, die.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hate you neither.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have not.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't say I have.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then F you to people bitching about the Oscars because, you know, I have to do this show.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't get to go to the big gay Oscar party and sit around and be catty and talk about how ugly everybody looks in their dress with people.
[SPEAKER_11]: The big gay party.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: If I wasn't doing this show, I would be at a big gay Oscar party right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know I would.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because the Oscars are the Super Bowls for gays.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is.
[SPEAKER_21]: If I wasn't doing this show, I'd be at an Oscar party too because we're having a free one at work and I get free booze and food.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the only reason I'd go though, is for the free booze and food.
[SPEAKER_21]: I wouldn't go because of the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'd just
[SPEAKER_21]: I do what I do for all of our company parties.
[SPEAKER_15]: I go get food, get full, and leave.
[SPEAKER_15]: And say, fuck them, I ain't waiting for the end of year party.
[SPEAKER_15]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_15]: Free food would have rocked.
[SPEAKER_15]: I could go for, like, some cocktail weenies right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't make the gay joke.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We did that for the Seinfeld last episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: We totally crushed the Seinfeld party.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ate their food and left.
[SPEAKER_15]: Were there cocktail weenies there?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they had cake.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cake is good.
[SPEAKER_15]: See, I could be eating Oscar cake right now, but I'm doing this show.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm spent.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, you have one you wanted to add, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to Squenix for pushing back the date for the Final Fantasy XI Atlas.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are they writing it themselves?
[SPEAKER_17]: I think you gotta blame Brady Games for that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Brady Games took it anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan, did you have any FUs of the week you wanted to give?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd like to level a giant FU at Ultracade who think that they're super clever trying to trademark the name MAME and the logo for MAME because he wants, you know, to have, I guess, a hold on the emulation market.
[SPEAKER_18]: The guy's name is David R. Foley and he's an asshole.
[SPEAKER_21]: And he'll never win because it's not his logo to begin with.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, it predates his company by like, what, five years?
[SPEAKER_21]: Ultracade, by the way, sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ultracade sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I bet you if you take apart an Ultracade and decompile his source code, I bet you that it's made anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: Faster.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ultracades need to burn in hell.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I was all down with Ultracade because I'm like, dude, that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was going to save that for, you know, our podcast, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, that's all good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, no biggie.
[SPEAKER_18]: Talk about it on the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Say fuck off to Ultracade.
[SPEAKER_18]: Y'all go to arcades.
[SPEAKER_18]: You go to arcades, kick the Ultracade when you walk by it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I did yesterday.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not just talking boot at once.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm talking kick the fucking hell out of it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll make that the first...
[SPEAKER_15]: Church of Orange Lounge Proclamation Kick the Ultracade Commandment 1 When thou see an Ultracade machine Or an Arcade Legends Thou will kick it with thy boot Several times Or boot it with your kick That is the first official proclamation of the Church of Orange Lounge I hope you're writing this down Ultracade Thou shalt boot There will be a quiz Yes there will Alright
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's move on to the chatroom FUs, unless you had anything else.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck all for me.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want chocolate.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been eating like so much ice cream today, it's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm rating Rob Scrooge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, let's go on to the next chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zaku, our old buddy Zaku, the metalhead, says FU to actor-director Clint Eastwood for denying veteran director Martin Scorsese his chance at an Oscar.
[SPEAKER_18]: If Martin Scorsese wasn't such a cocksucker, he'd win more awards.
[SPEAKER_15]: Clint Eastwood deserved it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't get in another argument with him, please.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you give the man a hug, please, Dan?
[SPEAKER_15]: Negative.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you try?
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you give the man a cyber hug?
[SPEAKER_18]: If he's a real metalhead, he's all greasy and nasty and doesn't want to be hugged.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about a handshake?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll give him a bong hit.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what were you going to add to that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Nothing?
[SPEAKER_20]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to my mouth being held tightly by a rubber band because of my braces and the pain it brings.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been there.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to having two unmerciful midterms this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: And F you to people that rag on Dillager Escape Plan's song in Guitadora V.
[SPEAKER_15]: Illusion says, F you to all the freeze pop haters.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's all about fancy ultra fresh.
[SPEAKER_15]: I read a review that said the CD sucked and it was better used as a frisbee.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then I scrolled up on the page and saw their glowing review of Yellow Card CD, Ocean Avenue.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then I said, oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have horrible taste in music.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, I'm rambling.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was one week from retirement.
[SPEAKER_15]: One week.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Suck it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Got told, bitches!
[SPEAKER_13]: If your song was good, it would have made it the four weeks, but it sucked!
[SPEAKER_15]: No, better yet, F you to the people that voted for the song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Illusion continues on saying, P.S.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to that awful Guitar Freaks drum mania song that you played earlier.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like my ears were on there, period.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, man.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: I take offense to this because...
[SPEAKER_11]: No man will ever, ever know what that's like.
[SPEAKER_11]: No one will ever know what the pain of PMS is.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why we have to share with our attitude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I think we do.
[SPEAKER_18]: You'd like to think that, wouldn't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, see, we have to suffer the physical pain, so we share the emotional pain with you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Come on, what's worse, physical or emotional pain?
[SPEAKER_18]: Life Long Torture.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll just get advice for your balls next time.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's Punishment From Above.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd like to level a fuck you to PMS.
[SPEAKER_18]: That goddamn excuse for women to be bitchy doesn't need to exist.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fucking deal with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's going to happen for the rest of your life.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it won't.
[SPEAKER_10]: When menopause hits, you get it every day for the rest of your life.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've still got like seven people to go through.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's when you get killed.
[SPEAKER_17]: I heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you ever see Logan's run?
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got a runner.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know that when they're pregnant, they're front heavy, so when you just put them next to a cliff or something, two birds with one stone, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, hey, look, what are you doing throwing the weasel at somebody, or the weasel?
[SPEAKER_18]: What are you doing throwing the ferret at somebody else?
[SPEAKER_18]: Slut.
[SPEAKER_10]: I used to throw it at Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, but we know Rob's not going to throw it at me.
[SPEAKER_15]: My cheeks hurt from laughing so hard, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lama Juice says, F you to Fred who works at Red Octane and I'm so damn glad his ass got fired.
[SPEAKER_15]: He lost a lot of people's orders making me wait another month for my Octane pad.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to school because apparently they had no problem sending them to GameStop, however.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're all at the GameStop on Marconi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Come and buy your damn dance pad.
[SPEAKER_18]: A big F you to the GameStop Distribution Center for sending me 14 red octane ignition pads.
[SPEAKER_15]: Llama Juice also says F you to school because I have to wake up early tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_15]: And F you to anyone whose name starts with a J, just because I can.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie has an issue with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who was that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Llama Juice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Llama Juice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, and F you to anyone who can't pronounce my name correctly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Leama Juice, WTF.
[SPEAKER_15]: Leama Juice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, if you name yourself after an animal, a butt ugly one at that, expect to have the name pronounced like damn animals is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ooh, Jamie's on the warpath now after the J comment.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkLionXVI says, F you to the gangster that hit my cousin in the head with a hammer four times.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Though my cousin's fine, he suffered a big lump and several stitches.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want those bastards responsible to be dead in front of me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_20]: Either that hammer was too small or that gangsta wasn't swinging very hard.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Somebody was just trying to imitate Donkey Kong where they had...
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkLionXVI says, F you to the right side of my body.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whenever I play 2DX and the note pattern dominates the right hand side, my right arm gets numb.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just hope it's not a stroke.
[SPEAKER_13]: I completely know what you mean, because you know, when I'm masturbating vigorously, you know, my rights, I get numbed too sometimes, so it's totally understandable.
[SPEAKER_18]: I knew as soon as somebody said stroke, there was going to be a joke.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Angel says, F you to me feeling like shit, Tearsniff.
[SPEAKER_15]: You'll notice she's not here tonight, that's because she is giving an F you because she feels like shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Flareone says, F you to Roanert Park, Scandia, for getting Madden Football as their token one new game every six months arcade game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, fuck them for hypnotizing me into losing my keys there last night.
[SPEAKER_15]: StepItOff, 1215, says, F you to all the good games coming out at the same time so I can't afford them.
[SPEAKER_15]: And F you to the people who don't show up for Outside the Box, but I appreciate what Sky did on Thursday because the chat was great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: DJ Ranma S says, F you to Million Dollar Baby, yo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Explain to me how the fuck does a movie that barely anyone heard of win?
[SPEAKER_15]: Someone pass me a 40.
[SPEAKER_15]: And lastly, SSJ100Matt,
[SPEAKER_15]: says F you the week to me, to Skype, for playing the tub girl theme.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, Christina Aguilera's dirty on Thursday's show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Long story.
[SPEAKER_15]: And also an F you to Scorsese being screwed over for the Best Director Oscar.
[SPEAKER_18]: He got screwed so he gets an F you?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: He doesn't get an F you for being a jerk.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know we're going to hear about this for months.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'll be on entertainment tonight, all night long.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_18]: Seriously, you'll go to a news site and it'll be like, Scorsese fucks for the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I heard today from my sister?
[SPEAKER_13]: She's telling me that there's a show that's called Celebrities Without Makeup.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's played after American Idol and it's just ugly ass celebrities.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was a big post It premiered on Thursday It was ugly.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Simpsons The Simpsons
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, American Idol is their top-rated program.
[SPEAKER_15]: You gotta give them that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, yeah, but come on, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's Fox's show?
[SPEAKER_18]: Like, what?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's on season, like, 3,406?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's been going a while.
[SPEAKER_18]: In the next episode, Homer becomes a psycho killer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fox didn't have Seinfeld.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was NBC.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's her name?
[SPEAKER_15]: Patsy is a lesbian on it now.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, Patty is a lesbian.
[SPEAKER_15]: Patty.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Patsy, Patty, same thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, it's like, who the hell didn't see that coming?
[SPEAKER_15]: So when did they get their AIDS character?
[SPEAKER_15]: Like Sesame Street.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_15]: That was Sesame Street, Africa that had the character because a lot of folks in that region where that Sesame Street was, it's a very real problem they have there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, what do you think got Mr. Hooper?
[SPEAKER_15]: All those, you know, monkey lovers out there.
[SPEAKER_19]: What is Grover anyway?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's adorable.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, he's not.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's a fucking, like... Near?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, because... He's an illegal immigrant is what he is.
[SPEAKER_13]: From where?
[SPEAKER_13]: They're all fucking hiding in the alleys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: They all live in Oscar's trash can.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know that market that's on the street?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a big front.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a big, you know, fucking heroin and all sorts of drugs.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I had an illegal immigrant living in my house, I'd be a grouch, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Snuffleupagus?
[SPEAKER_15]: Man, what a pot fiend.
[SPEAKER_19]: And what about Big Bert?
[SPEAKER_15]: Total queer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we already know about Bert and Ernie.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Bert is evil.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am so mad that the Bert is evil side is gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's gone?
[SPEAKER_11]: What happened to it?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's been gone for some time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think someone mirrored it, but the original site's gone.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did PBS slam the Iron Fist of Justice on their ass?
[SPEAKER_18]: It was only up for like 600 years, probably.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, but... Oh, how sad.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Children's Television Workshop got medieval on their ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: One more story for you guys, and then it's about time to start calling it a show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Red Octane, the group that creates the Ignition Pad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come to the GameStop Walmart.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got millions of them.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're going to be publishing video games for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: Interesting, because Red Octane, to this point, has always been like a distributor, a pad maker, and they've never really made games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not that kind of pad maker.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, they've never made games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure their games are just going to rock.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're going to be awesome, because they have so much experience in making games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh wait, no they don't!
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, they're not actually making the game, they're just going to distribute it.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're going to be publishing the software.
[SPEAKER_15]: The first title for the PlayStation 2 computer entertainment system will be announced in spring of 2005.
[SPEAKER_15]: Kai Huang, president of Red Octane, says, Launching into a new business segment with the publishing of video games is a natural evolution for us.
[SPEAKER_15]: We are committed to delivering the same high quality and fun found in our peripherals with the upcoming Red Octane software line.
[SPEAKER_18]: So everybody, buy Red Octane accessories now, because they're going out of business.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you know, you can look at this as a good thing or a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are there any, like, great dancing franchises or something that happen from over here?
[SPEAKER_13]: I smell something.
[SPEAKER_21]: I smell a distributor for In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was just about to say, wouldn't that be hilarious if the title they end up announcing is In the Groove?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, Bomani Scene would not shut up for months.
[SPEAKER_15]: They would not shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: You could shoot them in the face and they would not shut up about this.
[SPEAKER_15]: If that's what they end up publishing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Didn't someone just recently announce that they're doing a Pump It Up mix over here too?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who's doing that?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mastiff, who did...
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, Mastiff designed the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Designed?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think Anna Mero's going to put it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't... Ah, do we have it on the site?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anna Mero did pump it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Anna Mero did pump it up originally.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who would release it in the States?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, Mastiff's going to design it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mastiff did something else pretty cool recently, I think.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anna Mero.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought that would be a natural fit for a Red Octane distributor.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that would be good, because then Red Octane can make a whole new pump-it-up pad, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would certainly be interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: But unless they have something real popular, Home DDR still sells real well.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I don't know if anyone here really cares, but... Yeah, how does this... You actually work... Home DDR sells real well.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: You sell lots of copies.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why won't people buy fucking ignition pads?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, uh... But you sell the $20 pads, no problem.
[SPEAKER_18]: Home DDR... Oh, fucking tons of them.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because people come back three or four times, like, buy one good one.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_18]: Although no one buys MC Grooves.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it's like, they're going to release some sort of game, and it's just going to get smoked.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then Red Octane is going to go out of business.
[SPEAKER_18]: So get your ignition pads now.
[SPEAKER_18]: I won't have them forever.
[SPEAKER_18]: Someone's going to buy those pads, or I'm going to find someone to take them off my hands.
[SPEAKER_15]: If Red Octane was publishing in the groove...
[SPEAKER_15]: Doesn't Red Octane have, like, Konami's official blessing to be their pad distributor or something like that?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're not a licensed pad, but Konami has, I guess, what, didn't Jason Enos say that it's the best pad you can get?
[SPEAKER_15]: Pretty much, because Konami doesn't really do their own pads anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: They did them, like, once in a great-ass while.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've gone right up to Konami, and I've gone up to Namco when I go to trade shows, and I go to manager conferences, and I say, Hey!
[SPEAKER_18]: Why the hell can't we get more Konami brand dancepads?
[SPEAKER_18]: And they go, well, because Konami makes games.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're not a peripheral manufacturer.
[SPEAKER_18]: We make enough to promote the sales of the game.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then we let the third parties take over.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's talk to Konami style.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'm just saying, if it ends up being that it is in the groove, because, you know, it's just kind of the pieces of the puzzle fit together.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm, Red Octane announces they're going to publish a game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm, in the groove says they want to do a home version, but is looking for a publisher.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm, hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: If it all ends up adding together, it would be very interesting to see what that effect has on Red Octane's relationship with Konami.
[SPEAKER_18]: It won't matter.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because, again, Red Octane does not operate with the explicit...
[SPEAKER_18]: They don't license Konami.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's why the red octane pad doesn't look just like what you'd think a Konami pad would look like.
[SPEAKER_18]: It looks real similar.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it looks different.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a totally different sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just because Konami says, yeah, these pads don't suck, wouldn't it suck if the official Konami manufacturer was Mad Catz?
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be true.
[SPEAKER_18]: Konami's going to say, hey, look, you can get dance pads from any of these companies out there because it saves them having to make them.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it still lets their products sell.
[SPEAKER_18]: So they may as well say that somebody's the best, and apparently that was Red Octane.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, it'll just be interesting to see how things heat up when In The Groove does possibly find the publisher.
[SPEAKER_18]: Does In The Groove use a different pad layout?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's the same pad layout.
[SPEAKER_18]: Then why would it be?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it's competition for Konami.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not competition for Konami.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like if I went out and I made a flip cartoon and tried to put it up against, you know, the Incredibles.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd get crushed.
[SPEAKER_18]: Crushed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I mean, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, we got to wrap it up, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: We got to go around and get everybody's final thoughts because it's time to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_18]: Red Oxen Edition pads.
[SPEAKER_18]: GameStop on Marconi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Come and get them.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go outside.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except if it's GameStop.
[SPEAKER_21]: If it's GameStop, invite the red octane ignition pads.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because, you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: You need them.
[SPEAKER_15]: You need to buy them.
[SPEAKER_15]: Plus, they're comfy to sit on.
[SPEAKER_15]: My final thought is, um, I want a beer.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want a beer to not spill on my new ignition pad that I bought for the GameStop on Marconi.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need an ignition pad for my pain.
[SPEAKER_11]: From GameStop.
[SPEAKER_11]: On Marconi.
[SPEAKER_11]: On Marconi and Fulton.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: One word and one word only to wrap it all up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sum up tonight's show in one word.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know I gotta give it to Dan.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan?
[SPEAKER_15]: What is tonight's final word?
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I will offer everything Even if I'm crushed I won't show my tears to the snake
[SPEAKER_08]: Ame no naka ni futari Nurete hikaru kizu ato Atsu wa mienai demo futari Shinjite osorenai
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Nozomi, Snake Eater I am still in a dream Snake Eater
Shrek, what are you doing?
Shrek Shrek Shrek Shrek
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, what's going to happen now is that we're going to go back from our live broadcast to our basic show so we can do some work on our podcast, which you should be checking out.
[SPEAKER_15]: www.OrangeLaunchRadio.com Click on Orange Launch Radio to go.