[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of February 28th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming, and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello again everybody!
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to another edition of the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, our podcast where we get to talk to you about video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: And honestly, a few that do suck sometimes, they just slip in there by chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always, my lovely co-host, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Suck is relative.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I may think sucks, you may think not sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like freeze pops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XI because that's all I've been conscious for
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, you've been battling the sickness this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: The disease.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it kind of help you to just sit there and veg out to the roleplaying?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're like, slash, slash, cure, cure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or in your case, cure, cure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, in my case, it's been, the order is blind, poisoned, paralyzed.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got your system worked out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I have my system worked out, sadly.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're much farther in the game this time than you were the first time around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I hit level 10 on my sub job.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think is doing it for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the fact that you have more people to play with this time?
[SPEAKER_03]: The fact that I just have people to play with in general.
[SPEAKER_03]: I maybe played for three months and played with people all of twice.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_03]: And some Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for the heck of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Dan wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Loki, what have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I played, well, I started off the week trying to get some other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played a little bit of Final Fantasy featuring Charlie's Angels.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Final Fantasy X too.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that lost my interest really quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just too annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, the voice acting drove me away.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just...
[SPEAKER_05]: Scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't possibly go through that game anymore with Riku yelling some really weird shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So then I went and played a little bit of Derby Owner's Club and my horse, i.e.
[SPEAKER_05]: Children, is doing very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now explain, some folks out there may have never heard of Derby Owner's Club because this podcast goes to a slightly different audience.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is Derby Owner's Club all about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Derby Owner's Club is this game made by Sega.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's giant, it's huge, it's a good $100,000 cabinet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically what you do is you raise and race racing horses and it's pretty much got the whole jockey thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You train your horses and you...
[SPEAKER_05]: I should scan some of my cards for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: I only have four horses, because my...
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a horse named Brittany Spears somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: She might still be in my wallet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember Politary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I had a horse named Politary as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Magical Sound, who's retired.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Last Message, and Shiroi that's an all-white horse, which is like one of the rarest ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have Gangoro, who's a panda.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also had a horse named George Bush at one point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, so I could whip him.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other horse racing game I like was Daytona.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember Daytona and the horse code that they had?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the game that they used to have at the bowling alley here in town where you would ride the horse humping machine?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Furlong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Furlong!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, that game was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they still have that game, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't see it when I was there a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I know they had it at one time.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had it at Paradise Island.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Prop Cycle!
[SPEAKER_04]: Prop Cycle's cool, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to position myself next to the back of the bike and feel the breeze, especially after a game of DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I worked at a Namco arcade when Prop Cycle came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: My boss played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're early to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually do have Prop Cycle in the main cabinet, and sadly enough, something's lost in the transition.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is not the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: Prop Cycle's one of those games that cannot be emulated.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can hook up an exercise bike to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: God bless Dave and Busters.
[SPEAKER_04]: A place where you can drink and then play the games, even though the games are extremely overpriced, as are the drinks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Still fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing, though, in the defensive final furlong is that it's a really good ab workout.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got very tired playing that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you've been playing besides Derby Owner's Club and your horse, I Eat Children?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, what else have I been playing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, I haven't been playing anything other than that, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, we played a little bit of the guy game this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, damn you, I was going to bring that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me and Loki were playing the guy game this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll let you talk about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I will say is I played the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I'll finish.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was playing the game, and you know, some folks may be surprised by that statement because I know the rumors that are going around about me, and they're all true.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Playing those kinds of games are fun once in a while, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you get to see boobs, and that's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we were playing this game, and man, the girl that I decided to play as, she was so ugly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So ugly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I won.
[SPEAKER_04]: So my girl got to do a lap dance at the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: And everybody was like, God, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: As I put it earlier in the other show, she was a cross between, I would say, Tori Spelling and Bea Arthur.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was China.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of, except like, you know, blonde.
[SPEAKER_05]: She had the Tori Spelling horse face.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's this one thing, picture of her where she's wearing like an orange nightie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it looks like she just ate a baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because she spread it out, and it's sort of like the color, because it wasn't too crisp of color.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of matched her skin color, so it looked like she just blew up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I remember exclaiming, oh my god, she exploded, and Loki's girlfriend was just in stitches for like 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So was I. It was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds riotous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too bad there's not going to be a sequel because of that lawsuit and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sure there will be.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they got the lawsuit!
[SPEAKER_05]: They're still going to do it, I bet you, because they'll probably say, oh, well, you know, breach of contract.
[SPEAKER_05]: or whatever you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's got to be some sort of protection.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can't do breach of contract because any contract created with a minor is voidable.
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind of protection do companies have against people that are going to be lying to them?
[SPEAKER_03]: The contract is still voidable whether they know the age or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they are of the age of minority within their state, then there technically is no contract.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legally, there is not a contract.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they could probably still sue them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can't see there, but they can take a suit.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was the... There is a suit they could probably take against their parents for allowing the...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but couldn't they, like, you know, take losses or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Couldn't they blame the losses of this game because they had to pull it off the shelves on these parents?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Long story short, it's too hard to see the boobs in that game anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, you gotta cheat if you really want to see the boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not ever gonna see the boobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even realize it, though, when we played...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, yesterday, I thought there was like three different sets of pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I went and scrolled down, there was like a good seven or eight sets.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, holy crap!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, I have to go through all of this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was a lot of boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's change the topic to something else that is completely on another topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Completely from boobs to the family-friendly Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we've kind of been speculating that Nintendo's going to do this for quite some time, but they're actually going to do this new thing with the DS, and they're going to start testing this in Japan, where you can actually use these kiosks in selected stores around Japan, and you can download things to your DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, you know, duh, we kind of suspected something like this would happen for a while, it's just a, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: An obvious side effect of the technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is an awesome idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is the cool thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be able to download demos onto your DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you ever walked into like a GameStop and you've been wanting to play the demo that's there but some damn seven-year-old kid's been sitting on there for the past two hours while his mom's in Victoria's Secret or something and left her kid in GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you've been wanting to play the demo but the damn kid won't get off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well now you won't have to worry about that stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just download the DS demo right onto your DS and you could just walk out the store and play it in the food court.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as you don't turn your DS off, you can still have that demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: They actually sort of did that with the GBA, like in Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could play the game on your GBA, but if you turned it off, you lost it of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's probably where this idea started to stem from.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, unfortunately, you had to have the GameCube and the wire and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now that we got Bluetooth and wireless, hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that is also, from what I hear, that's what they're doing with the Nintendo Revolution system, the brand new console system that they're going to be unveiling, is the connectivity with that is going to be similar to what the Advance was with the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be shocked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be absolutely shocked if the Revolution did not have some type of Bluetooth...
[SPEAKER_04]: All their controllers are wireless.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all going to be wireless.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's not a bad idea either, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's time for that to happen too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we can lose the controllers right along with the remotes, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's time for that to start happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's also interesting is the game Jam with the Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's this game they have in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't have it here yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember if they have plans to bring this over here yet or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can actually download additional music for this game via the kiosks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it saves to your DS somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I never knew the DS had a type of drive in it, but it must have some type of memory flash or something because...
[SPEAKER_04]: The information will actually save.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess if you think about it, Loki, aren't the games just on flashcards anyway?
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe when you're downloading the information, it's going right onto the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea how that works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enlighten me, TechMassa.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm being distracted by Tekken 5 here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're going to turn that off.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then I suppose we will get into Tekken 5 news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about Tekken 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tekken 5 is out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really just kind of came out in the middle of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I remember mentioning it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It came out Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: But really, it was like, dang, all of a sudden Tekken 5's out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's the crazy thing about Tekken 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got Tekken 1, 2, and 3 all in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, and, and, and Starblade.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was Tekken, the first Tekken or Tekken 2 had like a Galaga Yeah For the loading game That's right This one has freaking Starblade as the loading game Talk about a step up there That's pretty cool Ridge Racer had Galaga Huh But a lot of the Namco games had loading games
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, have you gotten a chance to play much Tekken 5 at all yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: I unwrapped it before we walked out of the door, literally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you haven't really had a chance to, but you played the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I played it in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only arcades in my hometown are Namco arcades, unless you count Ground Zero, and that's just privately owned.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the first thing I did was make a beeline to Tekken 5, because Tekken 5 had just recently come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: in California, but it had been out at all the Namco arcades ages ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: So no one was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got to play it as much as I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so I'm looking forward to playing this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give you a full review on Tekken 5 as soon as I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki and I will both.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will duel to the death on Tekken 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: I suck at Tekken, so that'll be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I get to own you both.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not that great at Tekken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie will kick both our asses, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Huarong because he has this really cheap move I always do with him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is he in Tekken 5?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he better be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm saved.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, my man Gene is in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can tell I'm such a Tekken 5 noob and I have not touched the arcade version yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, seriously, every time I want to go play in the arcade, huge line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have my card.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been able to use it since I came back in the States.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of doesn't seem like there was much time between the arcade release and the home release, but I guess what you're saying about the Namco... I remember the little movie at E3, and then, bam, arcade, whoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bam, arcade, and then, bam, home version.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, yeesh.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go ahead and move on to one other quick story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting announcement.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've had something Nintendo and something Sony with Tekken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now let's get to something Xbox, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hironobu Sakaguchi has joined up with Microsoft to develop role playing game video games exclusively for the upcoming next gen Xbox system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is this such a big deal?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you didn't recognize the name, Sakaguchi is the creator of the Final Fantasy franchise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to see them expand on games like Fable.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox needs some
[SPEAKER_04]: like different variety kinds of games I think I think Fable was a good place for the Xbox to go despite how you might feel about that game it was kind of like what is the Xbox really freaking lacking oh a good RPG well finally you get Fable way later so I think this is a good direction for Microsoft to be looking into so just my thought I don't know any other thoughts from you guys
[SPEAKER_04]: I could definitely hopefully they're gonna be making some good games maybe an online game I would hope for an online game I don't know about MMO because I'm kind of headed up to here with MMOs but I don't know I guess that's where the money's at right I'll wait and see wait and see all right now of course we here at Orange Lounge Radio we're not just here to fill you in on all the video game news that doesn't suck but we're here to better your lives as well
[SPEAKER_04]: What better way to do that than allow Jamie to give you her advice column.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, DarkSakura, turn that anger that you usually have on our three-hour program at OrangeLaunchRadio.com and turn it into a little bit of love for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to you people, I give you good advice and you never follow it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did someone fail a lie detector test last week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a bunch of liars listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and his name is Mr. Jackson.
[SPEAKER_03]: Today's advice is how to get to the surface if your scuba tank runs out of air.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, signal to your fellow divers that you are having a problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Point to your tank or regulator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's just common sense, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I need to hear the other steps.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number two,
[SPEAKER_03]: If someone comes to your aid, share his or her regulator passing it back and forth while swimming slowly to the surface.
3.
[SPEAKER_03]: If no one can help you, keep your regulator in your mouth as air may expand in the tank as you ascend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look straight up so that your airway is as straight as possible.
4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Swim to the surface at a moderate rate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exhale continuously as you swim up, but do not exhaust all of your air in the first few seconds of your ascent.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you do not exhale continuously, you risk an aneurysm.
[SPEAKER_03]: And another bit of the thing to add to that, just don't go scuba diving.
[SPEAKER_03]: If people were meant to swim that deep, they'd have gills, like in Waterworld.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or if you go scuba diving, go down like maybe 20 feet at the most.
[SPEAKER_03]: Use a snorkel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you actually see the Waterworld movie?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know they had gills.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kevin Costner, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I just made a comment about not wanting to talk about MMOs, but I had to mention this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anarchy Online players will soon be seeing advertisements on billboards that are stationed in central regions of the game's landscape.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're teaming up with New York City-based Massive, the folks that create Anarchy Online, and they are going to be putting ads inside the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about ads in MMOs?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hear, though, the game's gonna go free, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, now, that would make sense, why there's ads in it, I suppose, but seriously, after the news that we got about the Slash Pizza in EverQuest 2 last week with the Pizza Hut, I mean, this is a totally obvious... To be honest, I mean, in a game like that, I don't really, I haven't ever played Anarchy Online, but if it's on billboards or something, I really don't see that deterring away from the game really that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: If it were in Final Fantasy XI, though, that would totally detract.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that would make more sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait for the day when I go into one of my Burning Circle Notorious Monster Battles and it's like, Pepsi presents the Burning Circle Battle!
[SPEAKER_04]: Britney Spears coming out singing a song, and then you get to attack the monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who is Britney Spears, actually?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can understand something like that, say, in Matrix Online, where you're going to have billboards and ads.
[SPEAKER_03]: In that type of environment, something like that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would actually be
[SPEAKER_05]: PowerAid, just like in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would actually be a good way to get a little bit of extra money in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't see it in Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: To be honest, if they're going to put ads in a game and then they're going to say, I don't know, make it free or reduce the fees it's going to cost every month, of course you're going to get people that are going to be like, fuck that, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, as long as I don't...
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as it's not pop-ups, because I fucking hate pop-ups.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's going to deter from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all about gameplay and these things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, you're going to get people not going to shell out the 20 bucks or whatever it is a month to play these things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Anarchy Online seems like, to me, it's a pretty dynamic game as it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty futuristic and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I guess it could fit.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, and a few billboards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, whether it be some generic thing that doesn't exist or an actual product, who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it doesn't detract from the game that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even if they have like, you know, what is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like maybe even vending machines or something that we're like strewn about, you know, or other crap, you know, product placement and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about like in Duke Nukem 3D where I could blow those vending machines up?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like this ad!
[SPEAKER_05]: We shall see how far they take this idea, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything they can advertise on, they'll do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still waiting for my slash pizza and slash porn, but, you know, no luck yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be releasing a whole lot of titles in May, including Pokemon Emerald and Fire Emblem, the Sacred Stones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also coming out in May, Donkey Konga 2 and Geist.
[SPEAKER_04]: And any of those games going to be on the DS?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, they are all being released for the... Not Pokemon... I'm sorry, Pokemon Emerald and Fire Emblem, of course, are Game Boy Advance titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Donkey Konga 2 and Geist, GameCube titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shocking, no DS titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, only one in February.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gee, I don't think the PSP is going to blow them out of the water when it fucking gets released.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mean the Great Game Shooter?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the Great Game Shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemon Emerald, of course, being the next saga in the... It's another Pokemon game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else do I need to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's another freaking Pokemon game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I remember another console system a while back that actually had pretty good graphics but no games for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if anyone remembers the Atari Lynx.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, we've got a Lynx.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a bunch of games for it, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because you own it doesn't mean it was successful.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Lynx was awesome, and it had that great commercial where the kids snuck out of class to sit in the bathroom to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Lynx had Tempest 2000, which was rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: My point being, though, is that if they... Oh, no, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting the Lynx... No, I'm getting the Lynx mixed up with the Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's... See, that's how much I played these systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: If I had a ruler and was a nun, you'd be in trouble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: The point being is the fact that they have the lack of games is going to kill that system, sadly enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really need to get on the ball here with getting even third-party... But it can play the Advance games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need the Pac-Man Marvel Advance game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Game Boy Advance can play the Game Boy games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need Marble Madness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn straight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Crystal Castles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Using the stylus as a trackball.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be a good idea for Atari or somebody to put out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smart people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fire Emblem, of course, is the long-running strategy RPG series, and it'll have new characters, yada yada.
[SPEAKER_04]: Donkey Konga's the game with the bongos, you know, music game, lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Geist.
[SPEAKER_04]: You will be in the role of a ghost who possesses people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fire Emblem Wind
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Little piece of news here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Fable soundtrack is coming out, or it just came out recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it has the Fable theme, which was created by Danny Elfman.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, you know, oingo boingo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's being released by Something Else, S-U-M, Something Else Studios.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it has a lot of the score as well by Russell Shaw, which kind of makes me think...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why the hell don't more video games get soundtrack releases?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do in Japan, just about every game that comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, sure, in Japan, but I'm talking about America, so I don't have to pay... It's happening more often.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for games like Fable, what about games like DDR getting full soundtracks?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they have the VRairs, I guess, but there's other games with great soundtracks as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Katamari Damacy, hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that had great music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the domestic soundtrack release?
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, I know that...
[SPEAKER_03]: of course the soundtrack will probably cost as much as the game but hey well there are games that did come out that they put soundtracks out for like I have to think about it actually it's sad you know what they could do well for all of the
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what they could do, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't they just release Katamari Damacy Special Edition, including the soundtrack and a poster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sell it for $30.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You made your money and you sold the game again.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could do it in Korea and include an umbrella.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: People out there are buying Special Editions.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a brand new thing now that they're doing with all these games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tekken 5 Special Edition, $100.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want your soundtrack, put it in the Special Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to wrap it up for tonight's podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys very much for downloading us and staying loyal to our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, any parting words for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Al.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Altercade trying to copyright MAME is bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do not play Altercade and fight this to the death.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not only is it bad, but it's stupid, and they have no legal grounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so bad, it should have its own word.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like bad wrong, or badong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, that's a Kung Pao reference there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my final thought, I guess, would be, thou shalt kick an Ultracade machine when you see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great one, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Orange Lounge Radio To-Go Edition is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.