[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of February 7th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello again, everybody, and welcome back to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks a bunch for subscribing.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me, as always, awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Save it for the three-hour show.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Tecmo Bowl and High Impact for SNES Ice Hockey and Blades of Steel
[SPEAKER_02]: because it's pretty it's pretty watching tv it's pretty i don't know i just i feel like a lot of it i think we've talked about this on the three-hour show before but to play a sports game i feel like i should be outside actually playing the sport that's just me though i like sports entertainment games like raw and smackdown yeah because that's stuff i would create a wrestler because i'm a big macho man loki your thoughts on sports games
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't play sports games unless you consider, you know, BMX XXX a sports game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just don't do it for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like watching sports normally and I don't like playing sports games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just dislike sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you guys want to talk about sports games, there's some other podcasts out there where they do talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that there's anything wrong with that, just, you know, not our cup of tea.
[SPEAKER_02]: We want to talk about other types of video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: For instance, the games we've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jimmy, what kind of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We broke it back down.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played some Papa 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you've had quite a Bomani-filled week, a music gaming week, haven't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a couple days.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time I go home, Dan's either playing...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, he's now playing Snake Eater.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought he beat Metal Gear Solid 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: He didn't bother.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he's playing that now, but I've been coming home to him playing Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been so cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at least it's both Konami games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you go from US Konami to Japanese Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I was playing Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so weird to hear you talk about playing Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was me and Loki's thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't play it that much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like an hour a day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: After school.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how it starts.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me too!
[SPEAKER_03]: I go to school and the gym and I work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I work and I drink.
[SPEAKER_03]: You exercise your liquor.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I work out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I pick up that heavy bottle of liquor and I pick it up and bring it towards my mouth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little flick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who am I trying to kid?
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than Final Fantasy, not really much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some Flash games last night that were weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I can't remember the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just, like, they had one, it was Drunken Walk, where you had to, like, make sure your character's balanced, otherwise he falls over and passes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was another one that was called Wheel, and it was, like, it was some weird Flash games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of really interesting stuff out there that people make, and
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Angel, who's a common guest we have on the Sunday show, she's heard me constantly bitching about no good games out on DS right now, so she decided to bring over Mr. Driller on the DS so I could check it out, because she's like, hey, there's this new game, and I played it a little bit before, maybe for like five minutes, but I didn't really get to play it a little more in depth until earlier, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the same Mr. Driller game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's really not a whole lot that the DS adds to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, oh, it's another freaking Mr. Driller game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Mr. Driller is kind of one of those games where I really want to get good at it because I like puzzle games a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of my favorite games are puzzle games like Tetris, Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo, and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to be good at Mr. Driller, but
[SPEAKER_02]: The strategy isn't clicking for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I can't figure out how to get good at that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just, I keep hammering.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to drill down as fast as possible because I think that's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's, you have to think about where the bricks are going to fall and my brain isn't developed yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's too tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, Mr. Driller DS, it's just freaking Mr. Driller.
[SPEAKER_02]: D.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: PiktoChat
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember which game it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a game coming out where while you're playing the game I think it's even like a puzzle game or something like that where you're playing the game and there will be a little icon or whatever that will come up if someone's within distance of you that's in PictoChat and you can quit out your game to go to PictoChat or invite them into a multiplayer game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was kind of neat and I wish that they would add that to future games because
[SPEAKER_02]: or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they need.
[SPEAKER_02]: I absolutely agree the DS needed something like this from the start and a lot of Xbox Live games when Xbox Live was first out didn't have this either and they really needed it because
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I want to know if certain people around are playing the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's in PictoChat?
[SPEAKER_02]: What room?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, when they first advertised the DS, do you remember that movie they were showing at E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: And they showed like the kid was reading a book upstairs and the mom was sending a message on PictoChat saying like, come down and eat dinner?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how would the kid ever know that?
[SPEAKER_02]: If your DS is off, you're not in PictoChat.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing doesn't beep to let you know somebody's trying to send you a PictoChat message or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the system...
[SPEAKER_02]: now granted when you see things at E3 it's stuff that's in development so you know maybe that thing hadn't been finalized or whatever but at least it needs something where I think you were saying this to me earlier at least it could show you like who around you if people are playing DS's around you like when you if you look at the webcam for one of our Sunday night shows here we do on Orange Sounds Radio there's usually five people here in studio all playing DS's there should be a way to see what game each person around you is playing honestly DS needs something like that so
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: 250 or as they would have you want to know 249 of course that doesn't figure in the tax so you really are going to be paying 250 plus for this and it's going to come with a 32 megabyte memory stick including there will be 24 games that are confirmed for the launch which is probably more games than the DS has out now so that's one thing the PSP is going to have going out the gate so if I were Nintendo I'd be a little worried right now but
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP has a firm date set.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There may be another, I think, or what was this deal here?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, okay, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also in the pack, headphones with a remote control, battery pack, AC adapter, case, cleaning cloth, game demo, so you're not getting any
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: As if you didn't know in the movie on DVD already.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, talk about a horde movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you can get Spider-Man 2 in the checkout lane at the grocery store.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how, like, everywhere this movie is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, it's a huge movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a very audience-friendly movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people like the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: But damn, talk about oversaturation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that's, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't make me that excited to be one of the first million people who's like, Ooh, I can have Spider-Man 2 again in my pocket to watch again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just wondering if they fixed the amazing game launcher function.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mention this one more time for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game launcher function where if you twist it, your game shoots out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can hold up a bank with the game launcher, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, one of the things that I have to laugh about this is the memory stick thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: With that, I'm sure people are going to have Linux on this in no time.
[SPEAKER_02]: People will install Linux in a shoebox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything with a monitor, they will try to install Linux on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't we talk about this last week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember which show it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked about Linux being installed on the iPod, and I'm just like,
[SPEAKER_02]: They will install Linux on anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will install Linux on an iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're working on Linux on the DS right now, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they have Linux on Commodore 64?
[SPEAKER_02]: That rocks.
[SPEAKER_02]: That so rocks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: quick gaming note, I want to get to DarkSakura's advice column for the week, I want to give a quick gaming note, this is a series I played for a little bit, I didn't finish this game though, but it was a good game, it kind of felt like watching a movie sometimes though, I didn't have a lot of control over the game, Xenosaga, it's getting a sequel, it came out a while ago, it came out, it felt like it came out quite a while ago, it's just now getting a sequel, February 15th,
[SPEAKER_02]: Very soon, Xenosaga Part 2, developed by Monolith Soft, same studio that did Episode 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Xenosaga 2 will have more than 100 skills for characters, including Last Revenge, Overload, Double Power.
[SPEAKER_02]: New to the battle system are Double Attacks, and that will be like a team-up mode, where you do a team-up and you do one big assault.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Xenosaga 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever play the Xenosaga games at all, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't just really get into the series?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you were the one that... That was... One of my old buddies made me play it, actually play it, but I thought you were the one that first told me about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was Miklatov, who was into Xenogears.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't remember, however, the hint to the existence of Xenogears in Final Fantasy VII, when Cloud's in the hospital.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's mumbling incoherently.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he says, Zenogias.
[SPEAKER_03]: Z-E-N-O dot dot dot.
[SPEAKER_03]: G-I-A-S.
[SPEAKER_02]: All sorts of little inside jokes in those Squeenix games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: We here at Orange House Radio, not only do we want to make your lives... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only do we want to talk about what's going on in the video game world, but we want to make your lives better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Therefore, the usually angsty DarkSakura...
[SPEAKER_02]: has her little advice column for you guys and we call it DarkSakura's Advice Column.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, what did you bring for us this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Today's bit of advice is how to win a bar fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most state laws stipulate that you may use sufficient force to stop an attack, but you may not deliver any sort of punitive retribution to your attacker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remembering this may save you a costly trip to the court.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, in English, you can stop someone from attacking you, but you can't punch them back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's the fun in that bar fight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, this is just how to win.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about breaking a bottle on their head?
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that count?
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's enough to stop them from hitting you again, sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, here's four easy steps to win a bar fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, attack the most sensitive areas of your opponent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eyes, groin, knee, and throat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stay close.
[SPEAKER_03]: If your opponent is large, he will need room to hit you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two, attack repeatedly and be efficient.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make fast, repeated blows to any or all sensitive areas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a nice, clean, efficient bar fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: That means kicking the balls repeatedly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number three, if necessary, use a weapon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Choices include telephones, pens, bottles, books, beer mugs, coffee cups, and keys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Four, protect yourself from additional attackers by fighting with your back too, but not up against a corner or a wall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also have a little bit more to add to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a move that they taught us in my karate class.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you happen to be picked up and have the ever-loving chick squeezed out of you, all you have to do is get your hands free and hit them on the side of the head with your palms.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would demonstrate, but our listeners will not see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like how when you do something stupid, your mom smacks you upside the head and goes, What were you thinking?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, it's more of like with both hands at once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Both hands on the side, because it will disorient them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, maybe not, but it doesn't stop it from happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess what game's coming next?
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, you knew this was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Variety is reporting that Microsoft has quietly put the finishing touches on a million dollar deal with the guy that wrote the movie 28 Days Later to adapt Halo, the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, first of all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I like 28 Days Later.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a good movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a good zombie movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weird ending, but you know, it was a good movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: We better not see what the Master Chief looks like.
[SPEAKER_02]: 28 Days Later, a good zombie movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Evil Dead, a good zombie movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: 28 Days Later, what the hell was that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was more like what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, you know, we want to kind of do a Dawn of the Dead, but
[SPEAKER_02]: not quite Dawn of the Dead let's make them run because that's a little different you know they don't normally run and then um we'll just go ahead and um I don't know make a really shitty ending here's the weird thing about Halo is that in many aspects it already is a movie so I don't kind of understand the but of course a lot of the Resident Evil games had a very movie feel to them and they made a game they made a movie out of that anyway but I mean yeah they made they made two movies out of Resident Evil but
[SPEAKER_02]: The only movie that should ever be made, and I'm sure Jamie's going to agree with me on this, is Red vs. Blue the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we need Red vs. Blue the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the only way that this movie will be any good, because Red vs. Blue, they could honestly put that on TV, and that would be entertaining.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say Castlevania the movie, which we've been bitching about for years, and no, Van Helsing was not Castlevania the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It needs to be like Dracula X version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's good because at least then it will stay Halo
[SPEAKER_02]: and not like Hollywood Halo well it's easy not to fuck up their movie don't get it to that one guy that made those three movies I mean he's the one that's crapping out these really shitty scripts actually I believe Resident Evil and Mortal Kombat were done by one guy and then Alone in the Dark and House of the Dead were done by another guy House of the Dead and Alone in the Dark guy that's the guy that should not touch any scripts for anything ever never ever ever touch anything okay
[SPEAKER_02]: It scares me enough that the guy that directed Catwoman is going to be doing Akira.
[SPEAKER_02]: That scares the shit out of me.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he will be doing the live action Akira.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, so look forward to that piece of shit coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somewhere inside, I am crying.
[SPEAKER_03]: And watch him fully base it off of the anime, which would absolutely suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need to base it off of the manga for it to be any good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did you hear that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I realize you kind of work in the industry a little bit, so you pick up on things like that, but where did you hear something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on Ain't It Cool News like a while ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have, um, because they had a whole big thing about it and how they're like, oh god, why?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, but, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get me wrong, I love Ain'tItCoolNews.com, but I hope that's another one of their fake-ass rumors.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were some other ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was, um, oh god, I want to say...
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: James Cameron's going to be picking up Battle Angel, which is going to be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: James Cameron doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can see that being pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then, of course, you have the live-action Aeon Flux movie coming out, which should be pretty good, I imagine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have issues with Charlize Theron, though, but I'll save that for another show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of movies, now let's go the other way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about movies going into games.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a big story this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA is developing a game based on an old movie, The Godfather.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're doing a Godfather game, and this made news this week because I believe Marlon Brando was quoted in an interview a long time ago, or somehow an article came up about him this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he wasn't quoted, but somebody had said about him that he initially refused
[SPEAKER_02]: The part he played in the movie The Godfather, you know, you can't refuse that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He refused that because he felt that the movie glorified the Mafia.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it turns out he actually has loaned his voice talents to this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he's dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did it before he died.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game's been in production for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Marlon Brando actually loaned his voice to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what is this game going to be doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Glorifying the Mafia, you betcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hear that he's going to be releasing a new album with Tupac coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Elvis.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Elvis, yeah, because they make new music even after they're dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, you were saying?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Robert Duvall and James Caan will also be loading their voices to this, so that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And EA is going to have a big gala premiere of The Godfather February 10th.
[SPEAKER_02]: and guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be first shown to the public in the New York City neighborhood of Little Italy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that cute?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more news story for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm excited about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really am.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saved the best for last.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom is going to be doing a couple new compilations.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know how they did the Mega Man Anniversary Collection last year, which was such a good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it was such a good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was very pleased with that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play the Mega Man compilation at all?
[SPEAKER_03]: I did, but the timing was way off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play it on GameCube or PS2?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that we had Dan try it out on PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because on the NES, he can do Quickman's level without using the time stopper.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he couldn't do it on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he came home and did it again on the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but Mega Man, they're also going to be doing a Mega Man X collection, because the Mega Man Anniversary Collection did so well, they're going to do a compilation of all the Mega Man X games.
[SPEAKER_02]: This really shouldn't be a surprise to anyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this is kind of a foregone conclusion, but that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually released this little trailer that just, they haven't said exactly what games are going to be in it, but they did catch one unlockable that's going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mega Man Battle and Chase will be an unlockable that's in the Mega Man X collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty obscure, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I mean, if you think about it, the two arcade games that they put in the Mega Man collection to begin with were also pretty obscure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's Mega Man Soccer?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want that in a collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what they need?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is fucking Mega Man Legends 3, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I love those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even a Mega Man Legends Online would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that could totally, you know, become an RPG, even though it's like all weird and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom, by the way, is also going to be developing a Capcom Classics Collection, and it's going to be basically this compilation of classic games from Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: They haven't said what games are going to be in it, but they're hinting that it will include old school favorites, such as those that have been seen in the Capcom's Generations compilations that were released in Japan for the Saturn and PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have one of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the Makai Mura set, which is...
[SPEAKER_02]: ghouls and ghosts, ghosts and goblins see now I think those are the kinds of things and might I say Capcom pretty pretty pretty please I have a couple requests Bionic Commando, Strider Magic Sword Strider and Quiz and Dragons how cool would that be okay I'm kidding on the last one
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I want them to do, though, an arcade compl... The thing about Strider is that they released it as part of the Strider 2 set.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is funny, because they even made the changes... Because we have the Japanese version and the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: version, because my fiancé is a big Strider fiend.
[SPEAKER_03]: For any of our listeners who ever frequented any of the Strider sites, he actually had Neo Strider's Strider Zone back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is one of the first ones out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the first one where he's swinging, he sort of goes, ha, ha, ha, ha, the whole time.
[SPEAKER_03]: He doesn't do that in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: one, and they fully did the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: when they brought that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we need Captain Commando.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need Captain Commando.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we need the D&D games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I want Super Slam Masters again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Slam Masters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Captain Commando did come out on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was three-player.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember that coming out on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: It did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I have high hopes for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope it's as good as those Midway collections.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, those are some of the best collections I've played.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hope it's not like the Nintendo collections where they put 20... I'm sorry, they put one game, released it for 20 bucks on a Game Boy Advance cart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially when it's games that were unlockable in other games, i.e.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, a couple of them were cool, like Zelda was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, $20 for Donkey Kong?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not the way to do these compilations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Midway knows how to do the compilations.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope Capcom takes the page out of their book.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could just play Animal Crossing and get all those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Crossing is like a $240 value.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one way to think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's going to do it for this podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, any parting words for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: Parting words?
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well then I guess I will be apathetic too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for subscribing to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next week guys.