[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of February 14th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming, and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody once again, and thank you for subscribing to our podcast and downloading yet another episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we are, the week of Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you all are having a lovely Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm single as hell, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura is actually out tonight because she's spending the holiday with her fiancé.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we have some guests filling in tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi DDR Angel, welcome to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I put a PC, a Micro ITX PC, which is a form factor.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 15 centimeters by 15 centimeters is the size of the motherboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's inside of an Xbox that's painted orange.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hence the orange box.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if Bill Gates finds out about this, do you think you're going to be in any trouble?
[SPEAKER_03]: The only trouble I'd be in is because I have a pirated version of Windows in it, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that and the movies that might be on the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not RIA or MPA friendly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do know anyone can download this podcast, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll put Linux on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't make me put Linux on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn it, I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Free BSD all the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how's the monitor work?
[SPEAKER_04]: You took like a little PS1 monitor that, you know, they don't really sell so many of those anymore because they don't sell the PS1 so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you actually took one of those little portable 5-inch monitors.
[SPEAKER_04]: How the hell are you able to see anything on this thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very carefully enlarged all the fonts on it to very large.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, I also have, thank God for Windows and having that, you know, feature the magnifier for those people that can't see shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You load that up there and anything that you, you know, move over with your mouse, it will enlarge in this little window for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I've used that a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to be honest, actually you can see quite a bit on that monitor because it's such a high resolution monitor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Small text is the only problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: I notice it's very crisp, so if you do plan to use it for movies or games or something, it's going to be very crisp.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of hard to see, but interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I thought we'd go around, and before we get into this week's gaming news, since we do have some guests on the panel tonight, I thought we could talk about what kind of games you've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of stuff have you been into?
[SPEAKER_04]: Angel?
[SPEAKER_01]: The MXO beta test, which was...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those not in the know, in the acronym know, that was Matrix Online, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Matrix Online.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever, I'll give it another week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think it's... I noticed that people are selling... Because you had to have a code to get into the Matrix Online beta test, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed people are selling those codes on eBay.
[SPEAKER_04]: My first question is, A, is that legal?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: But B, is it worth it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can get it at five bucks for fries.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, at fries.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to fries and get it for five bucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I...
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're doing like a pre-order then, and then you get to play the game on beta test as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Loki, you've been playing this too, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm only level two.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I played it maybe about an hour, an hour at the most on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little difficult to get into it because it's just like they kind of,
[SPEAKER_03]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, what else have you been playing this week, Angel?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I watched someone play World of Warcraft, so I'm kind of getting a... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I kind of want it, but I kind of don't because I don't want to be whooping on Final Fantasy XI too much because I do like that one a lot more.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_04]: As much as I love Final Fantasy XI, everybody is raving about World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the time I saw it, I was kind of like... Because I watched somebody play it too, and I was kind of like, eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I kind of feel like I owe it to myself now with everybody just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what you like.
[SPEAKER_01]: With our copy of World of Warcraft, we actually got a 10-day trial thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You could actually give the code to somebody else and try it for 10 days.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's open to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can do it, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you do end up doing it, I want your 10-day card that you get because I want to check it out a little more in depth.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, you mean if I buy my own copy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've also been playing a lot of there this week now for those that don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like TSO but better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa, you're playing the acronyms game again.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sims Online.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's chat about TSO and MXO on OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: See?
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Acronym game.
[SPEAKER_01]: For those that want more information on their Open Up Your Internet Explorer I mean Explorer
[SPEAKER_04]: or Firefox if you're smarter.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, you can't because it's picky about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It won't let you do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't want to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like an XML thing or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, yeah, so just go to there.com and find out for yourself if you really like it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's kind of like The Sims Online but without all the prostitution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's so fun in that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, that's the only reason why I play The Sims Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I heard The Sims Online turned into.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like Vegas, and I don't know if this is true, but I was reading articles on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sims Online turned into this big gambling, crack-dealing site.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just know that The Sims Online was not quite as popular as I think they'd hoped it would be, considering the popularity of The Sims.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also got to see Minish Cap this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, speaking of The Sims, I want to get this out real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sims celebrated its fifth anniversary this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And get this, The Sims has shipped, since its release, 52 million units and been translated into 17 different languages.
[SPEAKER_04]: The series of games has been a top seller for four of the past five years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, yay for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first time I played The Sims, I had to kill people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about the rest of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know this is true with you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you did your review of The Sims 2, you were like, how many interesting ways could I kill people in this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, and I have to really go back to that and find some more ways to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because my elaborate death house didn't turn out as fun as I thought it would be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ended up with piles of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, people just didn't want to die that quickly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I was putting in the cheat codes where you can move any object around.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was picking up people that were walking by the house and throwing them up into a room that was enclosed.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't like that too much and they were panicking.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was trying my best to catch a guy on fire but that really didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember how you put the giant diving board on the roof and you were going to wait for somebody to dive and then you were going to take away the pool while they were in the midair.
[SPEAKER_04]: But nobody would ever jump off the board because they were all so sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: They also didn't want to jump to their death.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that would be, you know, a way to do it, but no one wanted to commit suicide.
[SPEAKER_03]: They really need to, like, release a patch where, you know, it's less, you know, friendly, you know, just kind of let people die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, I have the nude patch, so people will be walking around naked all the time, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Sims Morbid Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you've been playing, Angel?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, not that I can think of at the moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bud, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maps.google.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, that is a very cool site.
[SPEAKER_04]: I checked this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it's fun to just play with those Atlas programs and like, oh, here's my house and here's, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, what they don't have, which I think is really cool, and I think MapQuest has this, but it has like the satellite view version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or does Google have that now?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have something similar.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was actually an article on Hackaday.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a website that had both
[SPEAKER_03]: Google's map feature and this other map feature where you can actually plug in I don't know, it was like coordinates actually and you can view the Google map and then also the actual satellite picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the London one, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, he's going to look that one up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you've been playing with that though?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet again, another Linux.
[SPEAKER_03]: They stuck Linux in a Billy Bass.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is a Billy Bass?
[SPEAKER_02]: The singing fish.
[SPEAKER_03]: The singing fish things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why, people, why?
[SPEAKER_04]: A follow-up to last week when we were talking about they won't install Linux in anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go, they've installed Linux in a Billy Bass.
[SPEAKER_02]: My pants are still Linux-free.
[SPEAKER_04]: For now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else you've been playing with other than the maps game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing the real world game of employment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't had time to play a damn game this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well you're a lot of fun to have on this show then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even make it to Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched my Mac sleep all week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played Halo in a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, what I've been playing this week, I've been playing... I actually decided... Well, I played Mr. Driller a little more, because Angel let me borrow Mr. Driller, and I actually... Remember how last week I said I needed to get good at the game and figure out the strategies?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'm getting okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm finally learning how to get some of those tricky air capsules without having to dig straight down all the time, and I'm getting the concept.
[SPEAKER_04]: All it took was a little time, and I figured it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also...
[SPEAKER_04]: I decided to go a little retro this week because you might remember that DarkSakura, she brought with her to the three hour show last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: She brought Dracula X, but the Japanese version on the Turbo Duo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we were watching little clips from that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I remember somebody said that there was a Super Nintendo version of that game that came out and I played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's awful compared to the one that she brought last week on the TurboDuo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is just dreadful and I remember I had played that game a long time ago when it first came out and I was like, what happened to the Castlevania games?
[SPEAKER_04]: They used to be so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I decided instead to go back and play Super Castlevania 4 because that game is awesome and it's a great Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I was feeling a little retro this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had a common angel?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to say, I didn't even know you had a Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, he did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_04]: on my PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what kind of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Matrix Online and Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't even gotten back to Grand Theft Auto San Andreas yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really need to go back to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: No other game I'm going to be playing soon, which comes out tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, WarioWare Touched.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be the next game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very excited about WarioWare Touched, and I think it's great that they're releasing it on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that are downloading the podcast throughout the week, he's talking about Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, does it ship?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is one thing that always confuses the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it shipping tomorrow, or is it shelving tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know that they have a ship day, and then usually the shelf date is one or two days afterwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it shipping or shelving tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have only been going by IGN's site, which has the release date for tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, whatever that means.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably the ship, so I'm not going to go to the store until Tuesday, but I'm very excited nonetheless to be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll bring you a full review of that next week, because you know we're all going to be playing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You like the WarioWare games too, right Angel?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_01]: There might be a GameStop trip in the near future.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it supposed to have multiplayer in this one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they took some of the good ideas from the GameCube one, because the GameCube WarioWare was like, eh, you know, because it was basically the same darn game, but it had such a cool, like, multiplayer edition.
[SPEAKER_01]: But multiplayer is so much fun!
[SPEAKER_04]: It is so much fun!
[SPEAKER_04]: Only one player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_04]: Classic Nintendo, they'll do the multiplayer in the next release, and it'll be the same damn game, but multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well, gotta love them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's talk about some news this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll actually start it off with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have quite a little bit of Nintendo news to talk about right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: EBGames.com is listing a Metroid pinball game for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, they're listing it on their game as tentative December 5th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo of America will not comment on this, but if you think about it, in the game, in Metroid the game...
[SPEAKER_04]: Samus does condense into the little ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of the first things she gets, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: This would be kind of a fit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why did that suddenly bring me back to, like, Sonic Spinball?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the first thing I thought of, too, was Sonic Spinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it had, like, that same look in the sewer stage in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic Spinball and Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess the Pokemon pinball games do pretty well, so why not, since we haven't had a new Pokemon game in a while, why not go into another series?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario had a pinball game as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Mario had a pinball game not too long ago on the Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why with the pinball games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it would work, though, with the two shoulder buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The screen's tall.
[SPEAKER_03]: yeah I don't know I could see it as more as like a little mini game that they might include with like you know the Metroid Prime Hunters or something like that interesting to see coming out soon or actually I should say just was released not too long ago Judge Dread Dread vs. Death why are they releasing Judge Dread games honestly I am the law couldn't tell you that one um
[SPEAKER_04]: Also in the news about Nintendo, this story is coming out of the Japanese Trademark and Patent Office, or at least that's the place that inspired this story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo has registered a couple trademarks recently, one of them being the Nintendo V-Pocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you don't know what that means, but it also has a little logo that goes with it, and the rumor is saying that maybe it's some type of DS adapter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Could it be that rumored MPEG-4 and MP3 adapter?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is the adapter.
[SPEAKER_03]: V Pocket.
[SPEAKER_03]: Video Pocket.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't take a genius to figure this one out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because everyone loves and is eating up portable video.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now that the PSP is going to have the UMD format, of course they're going to need to come up with their own format for, you know, to be used with the DS or to be used with, you know, the GBA.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, of course, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we'll see if you're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of the games coming out for PSP, or I should say the movies, there's actually going to be some movies released on UMD format on April 19th here in America, and we're going to have films XXX, XXX, whatever you want to call it, you know that Vin Diesel movie, Hellboy, Resident Evil Apocalypse, and Once Upon a Time in Mexico.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be released on that UMD format specifically for your PSP so you can watch movies on the go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sound interesting to anybody?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this something you'd be interested in?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting in perspective of me, because I work at a video distribution company, so it's yet another format that won't take off, just like the DVHS.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, nice try.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see how long it goes, but I don't think people are going to be buying other copies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what's going to happen is they're going to find a way to just put this on a flash card for, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: It won't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aren't the USPSPs coming with Spider-Man 2 and UMD?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is one of the stories we talked about last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you buy one of the first million units, you're going to get a copy of Spider-Man 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as I mentioned last week, who doesn't own that movie already anyway?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, anybody that had a remote interest in that movie probably has it already.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just my thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: But another interesting thing about this format that I think is interesting is that
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really see this catching on too much because I think there's a very limited genre as to what can be released on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see them releasing Academy Award winning foreign films on UMD format.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be mostly these bang bang shoot-em-up films.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I believe they also opened the format.
[SPEAKER_02]: The hardware to create the format is not readily available, and therefore it's probably not going to fly that well.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be like Minidisc, it's going to be an underground thing where there's going to be some people that have it, and a lot of people that don't even know what the fuck it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and it seems to me that if you want to watch movies on the go, they already have portable DVD players.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't have a proprietary format.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many formats do you want to buy your movies in?
[SPEAKER_04]: DHS, DVD Here's where I think Nintendo actually might be more successful in this This is the interesting part, if they do decide to release their thing Because if you look at the Game Boy Advance movies that they have out right now Like the Spongebob and the Strawberry Shortcake and all that stuff they have out The reason why these are easy for kids is because they're great for car rides You give the kid the little game and they can sit and watch it
[SPEAKER_04]: while they're on the road and on the road a long drive to somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can't imagine giving a kid a PSP and having them watch Hellboy in the backseat of the car, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Nintendo and their bit of a family-friendly, quote-unquote, edge, although they took a lot of crap for that back in the day, I think that's going to help them out in this market.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's just my personal thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless the PSP decides to get competitive and release some of their own kid-friendly stuff, because I think that's really where this stuff is handy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what do I know?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just waiting and waiting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: The PSP has got the memory stick port on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they're going to release something that's going to plug into that damn thing that you're just going to be able to put some other format of movie on a flash card in that damn thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see people going out and buying all these UMD format movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why bother?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why even, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't even rent them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe portable, but... No, I mean, to be honest, if you've got your PSP, okay, and this is just my thought, if you've got your PSP and you're on a car ride, you're playing fucking games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not even watching movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why you bought PSPs, to play the portable games, not to watch the movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is portable PlayStation, not portable DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is a trusted name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to another.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I wanted to say real quick, though, there is another Nintendo trademark that got filed.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's PCGP.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the way the logo looks is every letter is in a circle.
[SPEAKER_04]: No idea what that could be about, but the speculation is perhaps the P is like Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe it's a new peripheral for some type of Pokemon game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: PCGP sounds like some new drug I don't know, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: PC adapter to play?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, if I was going to guess I would say maybe I'm probably going to be way off on this PC gaming portal in other words it's something for the DS if you have a wifi adapter or bluetooth or whatever to be playing over the internet with someone else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or to download more content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That guess is very cool, but I think you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it just seems a little early for that, but that's a very cool guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's a guess, but they will be announcing something of that sort at E3, so whether this be what it is, that will eventually happen, so that's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other quick story.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we don't talk about the N-Gage too much on here, and there's a reason for that, but I thought it would be interesting to mention that the X-Men Legends game, it's done pretty well on the consoles, actually, and it's not a bad game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of reminded me of Diablo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like Diablo X-Men was kind of what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's going to be coming to the N-Gage, which... The N-Gage seems very limited to me, and I just don't know how they're going to pull it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever, it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they might as well put it on the Game Boy Color, but what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think my cell phone, which is actually very similar to the N-Gage, is more useful than a freaking N-Gage because I don't have to taco-talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the one cool thing about it, it will feature a wireless multiplayer mode, and that was one cool thing about X-Men Legends, that it had a multiplayer mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, you had to play for a little bit before you could get multiplayer with it, but it does have multiplayer mode, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know none of us in here own an N-Gage, but hypothetically, if you did, would there be an interest in this?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have to really question why I owned an N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd have to find the other three people in the country that bought the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, really, I had to laugh every time I walked by the N-Gage booth at E3 and all the people trying to get you to go in.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my favorite part because they were like, come on, check it out!
[SPEAKER_03]: And I go play, I'm like, this is crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, one more quick story and then we're going to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought this was interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually read this story.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a link that was on Slashdot earlier this week, specifically their games portion, games.slashdot.org, which is a very cool site.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out if you haven't already.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're a nerd, chances are you're already very familiar with Slashdot, but maybe you're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had a link to this article that talked about
[SPEAKER_04]: How important are review scores in game buying, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I thought I'd kind of pose that same question to us here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: How much do you pay attention to the reviews that a game gets?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever been influenced to buy a game based on the reviews?
[SPEAKER_04]: And if not that, what does influence you to buy games, out of curiosity?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll start with Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really go by the numbers or whatever, but I'll listen to what they have to say about the game and consider those factors, you know, since they've played the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But a lot of times it really... That would be a review.
[SPEAKER_03]: No shit, Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about like, I'm not going to say, okay, if he gives it a 10, I'm not going to go out and buy it just because he gives it a 10.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to look at the reasons why he's giving it a 10.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good test so I can save my $5 and not rent the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really, most of the time when it comes down to reviews, I don't really listen to reviews.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more buzz that I've heard about the game beforehand.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much what Loki said is what I do, except for the fact that I'll go to a friend's house or something that already bought it right away and I'll try it there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty much a visual review, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I'm trying to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you review by watching somebody else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or trying it myself afterwards and whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Usually, probably about 95% of the time, I will end up getting the game that I try because it's just crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I Ask My Friends
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I feel very similar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buzz does a lot more for me than an actual review.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, I have bought games based on reviews, but not necessarily because it got a glowing review.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because everybody likes different types of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: For instance, we don't talk a whole lot about sports-based games, although it's a huge market for gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: or FPS.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe one of those games comes out and it gets a great score.
[SPEAKER_04]: And perhaps it's a good game, but it's not really just the kind of game I want to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time, maybe a game comes out and it gets a pretty low score.
[SPEAKER_04]: Case in point, DDR Ultramix 2 got a low score from one of those magazines out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I say, yeah, Katamari even got some low scores out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very few, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a pretty critically appreciated game.
[SPEAKER_04]: but it's still you know I know I love that series of games so I'm going to pick it up anyway but sometimes there has been a game based on the review like maybe they have one on one of the TV networks they're reviewing a game and then I look at the game in motion I go oh that looks like kind of a cool game I want to pick that up like you remember Under the Skin we saw that on a review show I don't even think they gave it a good review but we were just like cool you can be an alien and like you know fuck with people so it looked like a cool game I played it all of one time
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, if you guys have comments or feedback for our show, we always do appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Email address is togo at orangeloungeradio.com T-O-G-O at orangeloungeradio.com We've got to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're running kind of long tonight, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're almost at a half hour of a show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty long for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm going to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much for being here tonight, DDR Angel, and filling in.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final thought?
[SPEAKER_01]: More Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bugged, thank you very much for filling in and being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your final thought?
[SPEAKER_02]: Demobass
[SPEAKER_04]: and my final parting words is thank you very much for tuning in as always and I'll hope to see you guys again next time on our Orange Lounge Radio podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one, everybody.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Orange Lounge Radio To-Go Edition is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next update.