[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of February 21st, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more time, thanks a bunch for tuning in to subscribing, downloading, whatever it did.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm feeling kind of crappy tonight
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into video game news that doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe it's some sucky news, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: What have you been into?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I should say, what have you been playing for the past two weeks?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing Spill the Seven Up on my arm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, what a fun game!
[SPEAKER_04]: Only $49.95 from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that the sequel to Cool Spot?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing Silent Hill 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to go clean my arm.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll come back to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: What have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing My Computer's Broken.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the power supply went out.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I know is the power supply was very fucking hot, and I shut off the computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I was running through town as my mule in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did your computer finally just decide to tell you, look buddy, you play too much of this damn game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think it's the power supply because it was really, really hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I was touching the case and the case was actually burning my fingers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's not usually a good sign if that's happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think the power supply is just shot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could be all the dust that was in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might have stopped the fan and then the power supply overheated and just died.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I got Binding Power Supply and that sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before that, I was playing Final Fantasy XI, a little bit of Matrix Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when I say a little bit of Matrix Online, I cannot stress how little I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played through the tutorial again and got bored with it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, what else did I do?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was playing this stupid game that was like it was another freeware game where you launch gnomes into the air and you like see how far you can get them to fly and I don't know that was amusing for about five minutes and then uh that's about all I've been playing I'm gonna actually start getting into some more console games this week since my computer's down so now heaven forbid yeah you might have to play some console games this week what are you gonna do
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm hopefully going to get my Grand Theft Auto San Andreas back because I want to play that, but if not, I guess, Shudder, I guess I could start and play through, maybe, with cheating, of course, because I can't play these games legitimately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy X2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ten.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was a big issue a while back on the three-hour program that we do over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually wrote Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wrote them an email and said, you need to tell us how this is pronounced.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it X2 or 10-2?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this is a huge argument between Jamie and our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it turns out Jamie was right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm always right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's 10-2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so silly, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, it makes sense at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you call this Final Fantasy X-I?
[SPEAKER_04]: and Super Punch-Out!! !
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on, Super Punch-Out!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Punch-Out!
[SPEAKER_04]: If I remember right, it kind of came out towards the end of the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of overlooked, it feels like.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was in the high day.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems like not a lot of people knew about Super Punch-Out!
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody knew Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot of people were in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it was just my neck of the woods.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gradius 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is like the only version I think that Dan and I could beat.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Super Nintendo one.
[SPEAKER_04]: What possessed you to get into Silent Hill 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: As opposed to four.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, the Xbox wasn't hooked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's as simple as that sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: As for games I've been playing this week, WarioWare Touched.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went out and got Tuesday the day it came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the WarioWare original on Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't such a fan of the one on Game Boy, or not Game Boy, GameCube, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem with it for me is it was just a rehashed version of the same thing I'd already played.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not that it was necessarily a bad game per se, because the multiplayer stuff was hilarious, but I just got really annoyed that I fell into that Nintendo trap of buying the same thing, just a little bit better, a little newer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it made me mad, and I only played it a couple times.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now, WarioWare Touched is out, and it's not a rehashed version.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got like 180 new games.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just so cool with the pen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little weird because they have microphone games mixed in now, and every microphone game is some type of blowing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like, draw, draw, draw, draw, draw, draw.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of WarioWare, but hey, if you like the original WarioWare, if you like Feel the Magic XXXY, very similar, you'll like WarioWare Touched.
[SPEAKER_03]: I recommend it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the parrot minigame is very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we couldn't get to work at first, but then we finally did, and that was the best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the unlocks are so weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the original WarioWare had some awesome unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it had Dr. Wario that you could get in it, and it had the little game you got with the little bird that would eat the things that fall down from the sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: WarioWare Touch doesn't have quite the same cool unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you can unlock a calculator.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can unlock a fortune teller.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can unlock a yo-yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the gelatin thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, one of the unlocks is a piece of jello.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the custard game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all you do is you poke it with your stylus and it goes boing, boing, boing when you poke it with the stylus.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's the kind of thing you come to expect from WarioWare, so it's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into some news that's going on this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie was mentioning about Xbox, so this is certainly important to announce.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check the date on the bottom of your Xbox to see when it was manufactured, because if it was pre-October 2003, specifically October 23rd, 2003, you're entitled to a power cord replacement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check out Xbox.com for the details.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently, the old power cord was causing some Xboxes to overheat and possibly catch fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Careful.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we checked the date on mine, and luckily it was in 2004.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm okay, which is good because I'm lazy, and I probably would have never filed a claim.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might need to replace you for the orange box because... Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You may be eligible for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox.com for more information.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since you guys love to talk about Final Fantasy XI, and hey, I do too, it's only natural that we mention this about Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XII Final Fantasy XII Final Fantasy XII Final Fantasy XII
[SPEAKER_02]: Squenix, Squenix
[SPEAKER_04]: This is an exciting story for those of you guys that are fans of Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're making an arcade version of Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get too excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only announced for Japanese arcades right now, but then again, F-Zero AX was only supposed to be in Japanese arcades at first, and it did end up coming to America, albeit very limited release because the machines were very expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Mario Kart is coming to Japanese arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the weird thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's using the Triforce system, which is Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_04]: Namco, and Sega now they haven't said anything about what Sega's involvement is with this game necessarily but Namco sure as heck is involved because Ms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pac-Man and Pac-Man and Blinky are all going to have their own karts so you can race Mario vs. Pac-Man and we were kind of talking about this earlier on the 3 hour show what if you could play as Sonic or some of the Sega characters I still hope that Sonic doesn't get a car
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Sonic would just run alongside him.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also need Mappy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mappy from Namco.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Knights needs to be in it, but Knights needs to fly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the dude from Katamari Damashii, the prince.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he needs to roll to Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know they're going to have all these inside jokes in the background and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, that's very exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to use the card system as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know the initial D and F-Zero AX had?
[SPEAKER_04]: The little magnetic card that you can use in the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to have that as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So very exciting news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep your fingers crossed that this stuff comes over to America because I bet it'll be a big hit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though, I don't know if it's just me, but arcades are just not as cool as they used to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bunch of ticket eaters now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to make another game like Starblade was with the giant rotating machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something else for me to... If I'm going to pay 75 cents or a dollar a game, I want the machine to move with me in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about just another Dragon's Lair?
[SPEAKER_04]: Those games are cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do need another game like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about an arcade version of Katamari Damacy with a trackball?
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: A giant trackball.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a game that's been out in arcades recently, and it's coming to the console very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tekken 5 is coming out February 25th.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the first game that's been released since, of course, Tekken 4 in the Tekken series.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was back in 2002, so this is the first one we've had in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to sell for $49.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, there's going to be a premium set that comes with a special controller designed specifically for Tekken 5 and a Tekken-themed 6-disc DVD case, $99.99 if you want that.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2, February 25th I know you were a big Tekken girl, DarkSakura I love Tekken Any thoughts on Tekken 5?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so happy, and then once the game comes out, I get the poster at Dan's GameStop You just want the free stuff Dude, it's coming with the first three Alright So how can you go wrong with that, having arcade-perfect versions at home?
[SPEAKER_02]: instead of having to use our the main cabinet.
[SPEAKER_04]: How does the Tekken 5 cards work?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this may sound like such a dumb question, but I never really got into the Tekken games, especially in the arcades, because the people in the arcades are scary good, and I cannot waste money playing them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They will school me 11 ways from Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can put it, you buy the card, and you choose a character, and you raise your character on that card.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually accessorize them, get them like hats and
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's Barbie Tekken.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you also save your improvements that you make with the character too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of improvements, Orange Lounge Radio To Go is here to better your life and what way to do it better than DarkSakura and her advice column.
[SPEAKER_04]: Her piece of advice for the week to help make your life a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Today's advice is how to fool a lie detector test, which everyone needs to know in case you're ever arrested.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number one, examiners will administer a pre-test before the actual polygraph to create a baseline of reactions.
[SPEAKER_02]: During the pretest, force yourself to breathe faster than normal and display confidence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never appear nervous or shy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, maintain eye contact with the examiner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not fidget.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not, however, sit completely still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Move something subtly but regularly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your toes, your fingers, hips, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number three, do not try to anticipate the questions you will be asked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think positive and relaxing thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the last one, number four, when answering questions,
[SPEAKER_02]: When answering control questions truthfully, bite your tongue slightly.
[SPEAKER_02]: This hopefully will give a false reading.
[SPEAKER_02]: Examiners may find it impossible to decipher your test because the readings are inconsistent, as in they show stress both when you're answering truthfully and when you could be lying.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit of trivia about the polygraph.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy who created the polygraph is also the creator of Wonder Woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: No way.
[SPEAKER_02]: And her golden lasso is a tribute to the lie detector.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You learn something new every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: This program being no exception.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was also into bondage and SNM.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for sharing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that explains a lot about Wonder Woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really, really does.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is interesting because apparently what's going on right now is there's a new bill going around the California legislation right now where they are trying to pass a new bill that will limit the sales of M-rated games to minors.
[SPEAKER_04]: In other words, it's going to make it illegal to sell M-rated games to minors.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you guys think about this?
[SPEAKER_03]: The games are intended for people over the age of 17 anyway, so I don't see why that's a problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this an excuse for lazy parenting though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: As I always say, parents need to do their job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't rely on the government to do your job for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm okay with this law and all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's such a bad thing, but I think...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of an excuse, in a way, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why aren't the parents being more involved?
[SPEAKER_04]: The parents should know what games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's giving the money to the kids?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if you're under 17, chances are you don't have a job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you do, maybe you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if that's the case, you're probably also old enough to know what games are good for you and what games aren't.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, my question is, if the parents are giving the kids the money, shouldn't the parents know where the money's going?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I'm okay with the bill.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have any feedback, you can email us togo at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything that has to do with what you hear on the Orange Lounge Radio to go edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, that's to go to go at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Think of Togo and Slana.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then think of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting announcements going on this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Midway sent out a press release that they are reviving the Gauntlet series.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be releasing a game called Gauntlet Seven Sorrows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Need game badly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blending an intuitive combat system, accessible role-playing game elements, and new junction skills, Seven Sorrows features the dynamic co-op it's known for, and for the first time ever,
[SPEAKER_04]: It is online, supporting up to four players.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seven Sorrows is the fusion of fantasy fighting action with a strategy of user-friendly RPG elements, providing gamers a deep, engaging gameplay experience, complete with solo play, co-op, and an online community.
[SPEAKER_04]: The new fighting system allows for easy pick-up and play, while simultaneously offering deeper choices for more advanced players.
[SPEAKER_04]: Additionally, online role-playing game and collection elements add significant replay value to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That all coming from their press release.
[SPEAKER_04]: remember don't shoot the food so basically this sounds like Gauntlet Legacy except you know now it's going to be online and I gotta admit I wasn't all into Gauntlet Legacy I mean it was it was okay it was kind of Diablo to me but the original was just so good and then this new one comes along and I don't know it just seems repetitive granted the old one wasn't
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, repetitive seemed to be okay back then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how to explain it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Gauntlet, the original, didn't feel quite as repetitive as Legacy did.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe it's just me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I didn't give the game a fair enough chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I tried to get into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We played it at home a bit on the N64.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't even into the old Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had it on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't even into the old Gauntlet at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked Gauntlet 2 on NES.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my favorite.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, any thoughts on Gauntlet?
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Gauntlet Legends because I was always Pojo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pojo all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was a giant chicken walking around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shooting fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was that like a code or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: I never knew about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there was a code.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could be Pojo the entire time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was... I think it was egg and then 911 was the password.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Midway Arcade Treasures 3
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they're going to do a 3, but I'm a little weirded out by 3 because this is the deal with 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only going to be, it's not going to be 20 games, it's only going to be 8 games because there's somewhat newer games in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's the other weird thing, they're all racing games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Badlands, Hydro Thunder, Offroad Thunder, Race Drivin', San Francisco Rush, San Francisco Rush 2049, Stun Runner, Super Offroad, and the bonus Trax Pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be best if it was multi-tap or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hydro Thunder was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Offroad Thunder was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game was pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And San Francisco Rush and Rush 2049, those are pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't say Arctic Thunder, did it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It did not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_04]: but it's all about Hydro Thunder because Dan and I on Dreamcast we played Hydro Thunder like crazy and I used to go play it at the arcade all the time now see that's the thing that weirds me out about this is that I'm cool with all these games they are great games but for me they're great games in the arcade there's so much of a difference between like actually sitting in the big Hydro Thunder cabinet and changing the gears and racing and that and having the force feedback and everything there's such a difference between that and the console experience to me it's just not the same I don't know is it just me
[SPEAKER_04]: it's a matter of opinion I guess, maybe
[SPEAKER_04]: This will certainly be worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoy Treasures 1 and 2 so much, but I think it's one of those things, to me, this strikes me as something that Midway is just trying to continue to cash in on this Treasure success, but they've released all their games now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully their port of San Francisco Rush will be better than the PlayStation or the Nintendo 64 versions of that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, these should be, hypothetically, arcade-perfect ports.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should be just arcade-emulated ports.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hypothetically.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well damn, I want to see my copy of Offroad Thunder then for MAME because I want to download that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on in video game news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought this was way, and I think this is a good one for us to close on tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: This story was just far too interesting and shocking.
[SPEAKER_04]: We did bring it up on the three hour show, but we gotta mention it here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're gonna be incorporating a new slash command into
[SPEAKER_04]: EverQuest 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the MMORPG EverQuest 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when I say slash command, I mean like, you know, sometimes you get hit slash attack to attack something, slash say or slash shout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now they're going to be putting in a new command called slash pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when you type slash pizza, it will bring up a Pizza Hut ordering window and you can order Pizza Hut express delivered to your door so you have another excuse to
[SPEAKER_04]: Never to get up from your chair except to go to the bathroom As if people playing EverQuest needed more excuses What slash commands are going to come next?
[SPEAKER_04]: Slash beer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Slash orgy Slash prostitute for blowjob?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, I understand why they're doing it Although it's got to be a little bit insulting in a way, too
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, you guys are too lazy to get up and use the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wouldn't want to take you away from your questing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're facilitating the addictions.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that Final Fantasy XI would ever get something like that one because they have the little disclaimer, you know, don't forget your real life.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I think, to be fair, I think EverQuest 2 does have some type of disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this could just as easily be built into any... I mean, it's just EverQuest kind of gets that bad rap to begin with.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is something that they could have honestly built into anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: EverCrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's EverCrack with pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could I get my pizza with crack on it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, any thoughts?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was this something you'd use, probably?
[SPEAKER_03]: Only because...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would not be using it, only because we don't have any locally.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they would be of no use to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, hypothetically, if there was a Pizza Hut a mile away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell yeah, I love Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't like online ordering, because honestly, I've worked at a pizza place.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know how dumb they are.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no way that they can do online ordering very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they've gotta mess that shit up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, and really, I mean, I have a portable phone right next to my computer, I just pick that sucker up and I can order a pizza while playing a game at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you can do it over the phone probably a lot quicker too, and it wouldn't interrupt your gameplay as would a, you know, giant window over your screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then they can repeat back your order to you to make sure they got it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, to be continued.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys think that this will be a trend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seeing these more commercial sell-out integrations into these games?
[SPEAKER_04]: As somebody joked during the three-hour show, it's just a matter of time before you can buy the pizza with gil, or gold, or whatever the in-game currency is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sure it's just a matter of time before we start seeing more of these types of commercial integrations into our favorite online RPGs, because we spend so much time in them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Addicts!
[SPEAKER_04]: And on that note, that's going to do it for tonight's podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks a bunch for tuning in and subscribing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great night, everybody, or day, or afternoon, or middle of the night, whenever you're listening to this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.