[SPEAKER_11]: I need you, I need you everyday I love you more and more without you I need you, I need you
[SPEAKER_11]: We are young, heartache to heartache.
[SPEAKER_11]: Love is a battlefield
[SPEAKER_01]: Toto, I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, for mommy talk and then some.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, mostly the and then some part of that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio is created by a bunch of potty-mouthed adults.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain sexual, perverted, and mildly retarded content.
[SPEAKER_19]: You probably shouldn't let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I will spank your child.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're not going to do your job, goddammit, I will.
12th
[SPEAKER_10]: Searching for a boy in high school is as useless as searching for meaning in a Pauly Shore movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I hope your babies look like monkeys.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've got a sniff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Skye.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I'm playing it for the bartender, so suffer.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hate you!
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, there we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are live and this is episode number... We are live and this is episode number 66 for October the 26th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned into the Bimani Scene's most underprepared radio station of all things Bimani.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: For you, my name is Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_03]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm is Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how much of a voice left there for.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will be speaking in spirit all evening.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you feeling this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Better than last week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: In that corner, say hello to our tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other special guest of my laundry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, we have something that is now even worse than Gator.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's something out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a software for your computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is worse than Gator.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is worse than Banzai Buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is worse than Gator with a Banzai Buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the worst spam software you could ever have on your computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we'll be talking about that later.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm very happy to be here with you today, DarkSakura
Thank you for watching!
Darlin', Darlin', you can see me here, right?
Darlin', Darlin', I'll forget about that day.
Darlin', Darlin', maybe you know how I feel.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't help falling in love with you Shall I say what they say?
[SPEAKER_11]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_17]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio Because real radio makes Captain Jack cry
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back, boys and girls, to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 66 in progress.
[SPEAKER_03]: Join in our chat room if you want, www.callybomani.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click on Orange Lounge and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a whole shitload of people there tonight just waiting to talk to you and tell you where our webcam's at if you want to stare at us, although Jamie never is on cam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, $2.99 a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: We might talk to you in other ways.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I charge for my PMs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's the only way you can vote in the cage match and also send your FUs of the week and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: So for those of you guys that listen to the show on a regular basis, I'm sure you've heard Loki in the past talk about his experiences when he goes to Raley's to get Chinese food.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the lady that works at the Raley's department that always says, Do you want a sample?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the sample lady at the Raley's.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I had the chance today, Loki and I...
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki and I went down to Walmart today to run some errands and do something else that we're going to talk about much later in the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We went to Walmart and then we went over to Rayleigh's to get some dinner because I was going to get some Chinese food.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki said, hey, this is the Rayleigh's where the sample lady works at.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was all excited because I didn't realize that we were going to the Rayleigh's where the sample lady works at because I always thought she worked at another one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rayleigh's, for those who don't know, because I forget, it's probably only in California.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a big grocery store chain.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Rayleigh's is a big grocery store.
[SPEAKER_03]: and this is the most fucked up Raley's I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: This Raley's here in Folsom where we live.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have the Rainbow Cafe.
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, when you walk right in the door, the Rainbow Cafe.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds like something that belongs in Lavender Heights in Midtown.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you have the Rainbow Cafe when you walk through the door and then right next to the Rainbow Cafe is the takeout place.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do they call it?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Hot Walk.
[SPEAKER_03]: A hot walk.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so Loki and I walk in and Loki's like, Oh my God, the sample lady's working today.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's her, that's her.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I got all excited because I saw the sample lady.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, since I saw the sample lady, there was nothing I wanted more than to hear her go, You want sample?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Loki gets up there and orders his food.
[SPEAKER_03]: And shockingly enough, she didn't say it.
[SPEAKER_03]: She didn't say it to him.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was starting to get all upset because I'm like, I can't be here and not hear the you want sample thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I went up there and I was like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, um, yeah, can I try a little bit of the garlic chicken?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and try an egg rind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you want sample?
[SPEAKER_03]: It didn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: She didn't say anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: She just kind of like gave it to me and then got my meal and we were gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there was this really stupid guy that was there too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um, you know, after I took my garlic chicken and I ate the little thing because they put it on a toothpick, they put a piece on toothpick so you need it.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, so was it good?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: People don't think that you're weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eat me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so I didn't get to hear the You Want Sample thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the lady who was checking us out, she looked like a brunette Donatella Versace, which kind of scared me a little bit, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my God, that woman is... Get out!
[SPEAKER_06]: That woman is hideous looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: She looks like Droopy.
[SPEAKER_16]: Welcome to Donatella Versace's Halloween party.
[SPEAKER_16]: I give you candy cigarettes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's some candy, here's some cigarettes.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I love when they impersonate Donatello Versace on Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so the lady who chipped us out looked like Donatello Versace.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there were these two kids that were like trying to play in one of those power wheelchairs.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how like if you're handicapped and you go to the grocery store, they give you like a complimentary wheelchair to sit in?
[SPEAKER_21]: What a complimentary wheelchair.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were these kids, and I swear to God, they were about ready to ram right into all the candy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm really upset because I didn't get to hear the you want sample thing, so I just have to rely on Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki is the only one that can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then he had to go, like, I'm trying to train her not to offer the samples, because she does it at the wrong times.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, you already get your food, you know, she's already given it to you, it's all ready to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I got sweet and sour pork, and then she'll, like, give me a sample of sweet and sour pork, like, gee, I didn't know what it tasted like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, that's so good, maybe I should get some.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait, I already did.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's like, she's so retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then this other, on Friday, they had a person that was even dumber than she was, this old guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was like, oh, you want food?
[SPEAKER_03]: You want Chinese?
[SPEAKER_03]: What kind of rice do you want?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like, so fucking annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're so slow.
[SPEAKER_03]: They like operate in another dimension.
[SPEAKER_07]: They operate in the fast path.
[SPEAKER_03]: Friggin' old.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Rob had to go and ask for a sample, and now she thinks it's okay to ask for samples.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then she went back to asking people for samples.
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You messed it all up for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God she recognized you when we walked in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We walked in, and she looked at you with that, hi, look on her face.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was kind of like, oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: She recognizes Loki as a frequent customer.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what was so weird is right before you went up there to get help...
[SPEAKER_03]: She started, like, staring off into space.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, she was staring at some person on the other end of the store.
[SPEAKER_03]: And mind you, there's a line of, like, five people there waiting at the counter.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's just like... She's looking at her ancestors.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's staring off into space.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, like, you know, she's seeing the ghost of Christmas past in front of her or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fucking crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So... But, you know, the woman's entertaining, so I'll continue to patronize that, Ray Lee.
[SPEAKER_03]: For nothing else than good stories to fill up time on Orange Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have plenty of things I could patronize.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, um... Completely different sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's start off the lovely show with How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_03]: Our favorite way of letting you know what's going on in our lives.
[SPEAKER_21]: It sounds like Jamie wants to start.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God, that gives me a headache.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, how was your past two weeks?
[SPEAKER_21]: You were out last week for sickness.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Thursday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, how long have you been sick now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like three weeks?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have SARS?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I was, I was starting to get sick around Wednesday-ish, and Thursday, um, Dan's like, hey, let's go out and have dinner and shit, and so I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, you had dinner and shit?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything makes you shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not soup.
[SPEAKER_07]: With my digestion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be like chunky, creamy cheese soup or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, could you repeat that revelation for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_03]: The beef soup makes your urine smell like beef.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fact.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like honey smacks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honey smacks makes your urine smell like honey smacks.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's quite fascinating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honeycomb, honeycomb, we want honeycomb.
[SPEAKER_03]: A honeycomb doesn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just honey smacks and beef soup.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's also like the blue Hawaiian punch makes you urine green.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, if you were to eat, like, beef soup with honey smacks on the side, would your, like, urine turn into this sudden, like, stink bomb?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you could just, like, you know, whip it out?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pow!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, what about my week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Freaking piss sniffers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's different for a woman because you sit when you pee so you don't really smell it because it's kind of contained in the potty, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: The smell is right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when you're a guy, you're whipping it out and you pee right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't help it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I seriously think that's why some guys sit when they pee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everyone here in the studio does have their pants on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what the hell they're talking about.
We can fix that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey now, what the hell is that big black scratch?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, Bradley sort of looks like he's not wearing pants in the webcam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your head's in the cam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_21]: You okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: You sure you want to talk about your week here?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want something to drink?
[SPEAKER_21]: You want some honey smacks?
[SPEAKER_21]: Ouch!
[SPEAKER_03]: I had beef soup, but now all I have is, like, chicken soup.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, fucking go in the bathroom and take a pee right now, because I'm sick of hearing about your urine, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have to pee, stop talking about it, just get in the bathroom and pee.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have so many Jamie quotes in, like, the past, like, two minutes right there to use in the next intro.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not to mention that the blue light turns your stool green also.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are in the perfect position for me to just knock you right out of your chair.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, that would be my chair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Knock you right out of Loki's chair.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you, I could throw the ferret at you, but that's too much effort.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_06]: I had two weeks, and I was sick the whole time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess as everyone can tell, I still have this nasty cough.
[SPEAKER_06]: And last week, when I called in, as you can probably vouch for this, I sounded really shitty, and I was getting dizzy in my chair, and I ran fever all weekend, I ran fever at work, but it's nothing that's like super contagious, it's a sinus infection.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I didn't know that time I thought that I had like leukemia and emphysema at the same time.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Dan thought I had emphysema, that was funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Who was mistaking emphysema for bronchitis?
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't emphysema something smokers get?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you quit quite some years ago, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Five and a half years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so that's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, so all the snot in my nose that's been consistently draining since I had this infection start has been going right into my lungs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I've been, of course, coughing it all back up
[SPEAKER_06]: I sound like I'm going to die every moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I got over all the nasty, you know, fevery, shakes, all those symptoms, but I cough myself into headaches now, which sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a headache right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it got bad enough that Tuesday when I was doing laundry, I stopped breathing for like a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to go lay down.
[SPEAKER_06]: I took like three puffs off my Ibuterol, laid down,
[SPEAKER_06]: It felt better finishing my laundry, but I called the doctor the next day.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they gave me more asthma medicine that night.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they said, I get a call the next day that says, either come into the doctor or if we can't schedule you, go to the emergency room.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was like, okay, oh shit, that's like pretty, pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I went to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Turns out I had sinus infection, drainage.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then they prescribed me more drugs.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now I'm on an antibiotic and I'm on Robitussin with codeine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Robitussin.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I swear at night that, okay, you know me and my insane tolerance for alcohol.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coding will just totally screw my head up.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I take it before bed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm really groggy when I wake up in the morning and dizzy and all kinds of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm on all kinds of drugs now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on top of that, my voice sounds really crappy at work in a call center.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I'm hoping that I get over this crap before I go to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, to, that's next Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be on a plane next Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, so that's also why I sound really crappy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm about to, you know, spew up one of my lungs on your carpet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can put it on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, feel better soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that kind of sucks that you have to go back to work tomorrow and talk, but on the bright side, maybe, you know, it'll build something up, the talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how that works.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have no idea how gross it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can kind of imagine, because I know that, you know, as somebody in my position, I have to talk a lot of times all day long, too, when I'm teaching.
[SPEAKER_03]: I talk loud, too, because I'm teaching.
[SPEAKER_03]: And usually, if I go for a while, like if we're in between classes and I'm not talking a lot loud, and it takes me a little while those first couple days when I get back into class, where I have to kind of build up my voice again, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about actually coughing up everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really gross.
[SPEAKER_03]: Luckily, I haven't had to go through being sick and trying to do all that yet, but who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk to Bradley.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bradley, how was your day and how was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think I'm sitting on the cord.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, we'll give you a little more room there.
[SPEAKER_03]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tear each cord.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's as long as you're going to get to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I have the long one.
[SPEAKER_22]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now it's all untangled.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, this week not too much happened.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sat around most of the day doing not much.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, actually I shipped out like 20 or so packages to various places in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: and six other countries.
[SPEAKER_22]: On Tuesday, I finally went by Fireside Lanes, which is like a mile from where I live, so I went and checked out their DDR Extreme, and it's in pretty good shape, so I played two games then, and then went back on Thursday and played six.
[SPEAKER_22]: And now my foot hurts from all that stomping.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_22]: and yesterday I fixed up my 2DX controller a bit so I can actually play some 2DX for the first time at home for the first time in like two months.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I haven't played 2DX at home in a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really hoping that, well, I mean maybe we'll talk about it later, but I'm just hoping that there is in fact a new consumer style coming out and yes, I know they got all the signatures and da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll address it later.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just really hope it happens and they don't try to dick us somehow.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It better not suck, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Considering we've had to wait like a year and a half at least, if not two years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not have to wait two years for this new 2DX, basically, from the time we got the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it sucks, Konami can, like, just go to hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It better be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It better have like 300 songs on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, man.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then... Let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_22]: If anything happened... Uh...
[SPEAKER_22]: Not really much else happened.
[SPEAKER_22]: Played more 2DX today and passed a few new things.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was like played a few courses and passed a few new ones.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's about everything that happened this week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, on to someone else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, didn't do anything today except for work on my cabinet a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's coming along quite well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm on my last sheet of stuff to cut out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the only thing that's holding me back is the damn battery power in the jigsaw.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, otherwise I would have been done today.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, once it's all cut out, which will be this week, I will start putting it together.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then comes the wonderful job of finding out where we're going to put it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Earlier this week... I said we just get rid of the couch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, what I was thinking is that we move that small chair somewhere, put the couch against the window, put the cabinet where her chair is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, obviously, the...
[SPEAKER_03]: You okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously the camera would be on top of the cabinet sitting somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, I don't know, figure out where to put the other chairs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe burn that or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, figure it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, uh, then today, before the show, as you might have seen on the webcam if you're watching, I was calibrating the TV to look nicer, which I don't really notice anything, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I noticed that the chat room's more readable than usual, except when people use colors.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so we were watching that and said, do not go beyond your abilities or something and showed someone like trying to pry off something on a circuit board and getting electrocuted and then the house started getting electrocuted and then it burst into flames.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was great because the house caught on fire and we had laughed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, um... What else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, not much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ordered the rest of my parts for my cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ordered my buttons for popping music, so those are coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Along with my bezel for the monitor.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, a little black thing that goes around it so it doesn't look like a TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks more like an actual monitor.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, um... Yeah, it should be coming together pretty fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: So... That's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and saw Scary Movie 3 this weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard it shattered like a gazillion records.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just, you know, like you hear the names like Airplane and Naked Gun, and your expectations are high on what the movie's supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was really funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like the first movie that I've seen in a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually made me laugh out loud in the movie theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, a lot of the jokes were ruined from the previews.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, that's why I didn't want to watch those clips, because I knew it would ruin the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, no, no, not those.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about like the previews.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like one of the funniest ones, like the Michael Jackson thing, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing else to say about your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: My week and my day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a pretty boring week, nothing too exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I've kind of gotten sick of going to Golf Land to play F-Zero and all that, because, I don't know, F-Zero, now that I've unlocked pretty much everything, it's kind of like lost its flair a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's still a fun game, and it's way better than Initial D, but I'm just kind of bored with it now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus, what's weird about Golf Land, the local arcade that a lot of us play at, is that they now have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Two Initial D machines for a total of four cars to play Initial D with.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and then DDR Extreme's still cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still trying to AAA stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I got anything new this week, but, you know, I'm working on my heavy AAAs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Getting a lot of single-digit grades, but no heavy AAAs, but I'm working there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: For some reason, I want my PA to get better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that I'm ever going to be that great, but, you know, I can try.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: And then pretty much I've been working on my game of Final Fantasy X. I won't spoil where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_03]: I won't give a spoiler.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll just say I'm at Mount... What the hell is it called?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mount Gagazil, I think it's called.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where I'm at right now, so for those of you who play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think by my estimations I'm probably about a halfway, somewhere between halfway and two-thirds through it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, still got a ways to go, and I'm trying to burn through it before Final Fantasy XI comes out on Wednesday, except I don't see that really happening, because I've got Vanilla Sky tomorrow night, and then Final Fantasy XI comes out Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the interesting thing is, I work a short week next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm only working Monday and Tuesday, because I have three days off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm supposed to go to Hollywood for Halloween, but I foresee that the trip might be canceled.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to find out for sure tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, if the trip ends up getting canceled...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I've kind of been staying away from information on the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've looked at the benchmark.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've looked at the demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I watched Brad Lanky's style.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you listen to Vanilla Sky, he's on there a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was a beta tester for Final Fantasy XI, so I saw it a little bit over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But other than that, I've really been kind of just keeping it a surprise what all is going to wait for me in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't read up on the classes or anything, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is, is that come Wednesday, I want to make sure I get the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I want to be one of the first people with the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I want to make sure the name I want doesn't fucking get taken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I hate that shit when people steal my name.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's my name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back off!
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a radio show and you don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Therefore, I'm entitled to the name.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of just anticipating my vacation next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: And then not a whole lot too exciting this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been to play 2DX in like six weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been to Scandia in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just Golfland and playing stuff here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Playing Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki bought the new Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll talk more about that tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm an else guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I think we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when we come back, we'll talk about some more news and some things going on in the Milani world.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think maybe we'll do the news story next.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a news story that aired locally here in Sacramento, California, where we all live.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's comedy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you guys definitely want to stay tuned and listen for this because we're going to play it for you guys and make fun of it because that's what we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back after a set of some five-key Beatmania songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: This should be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will be right back.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm out to play, gonna have me some fun In a world that is totally mine
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_00]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 66.
[SPEAKER_03]: UPN United Paramount Network
[SPEAKER_03]: United Postal Board United Crappy Television Network United Wrestling Network That's the only thing they're famous for I like Smackdown That's the only show they've got, basically That and Enterprise And Black Television And yes, the leader in Black Television So anyway, UPN did this story about
[SPEAKER_03]: Dance Dance Revolution and this aired on our local affiliate Channel 31 here in Sacramento and we wanted to play the story for you so you can see what the real people out there have to say about DDR so we're going to fire up the clip here and we will be of course stopping it and interjecting our own snide comments occasionally so here we go we're just waiting for it to load are you going to put it on TV so Jamie can see too?
[SPEAKER_03]: you don't think it will work over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, you're going to have to come here if you want to see it, otherwise you have to just listen.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you think of video games, what comes to mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: The joystick, the chair, the set of steady eyes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not very loud.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you turn it up?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the home version on PlayStation right now of DDR, which we talked about at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because gone are the days of Pac-Man fever, the Donkey Kong craze.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is an interactive video that swept the nation.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's definitely not for couch potatoes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And GES's Tara Moriarty is shaking her groove saying it's John's Incredible Pizza in Stockton.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're playing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like two split screens.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've got...
[SPEAKER_03]: They basically have Konomics playing in the background on a widescreen TV in the studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then they got some dumb bitch on the spot in, what was it, John's Famous Pizza?
[SPEAKER_03]: John's Incredible Pizza, which is pretty much like Chuck E. Cheese.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got tons of rides and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They actually have carnival rides in there, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're playing DDR Max 2 with all the employees who aren't working.
[SPEAKER_04]: Justin Timberlake They're having a dance-off There's two employees on the machine playing something on basic He's been doing the machine
[SPEAKER_04]: and you're really good.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pause it, pause it, pause it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a conceited little bastard.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I hear you're good at DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yes, I am actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I would have loved to have been there to kick his ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody else I know, they're not talking to the person on the machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're talking to some guy off the machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to see him play at the end of the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: But everybody else I know that plays DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody that's good in tournaments and stuff like that, it's like this thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And don't get me wrong, this thing bugs me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, you ask somebody if they're good at DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could be talking to somebody who comes in like top three in tournaments and they'll go, yeah, I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I play it sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's like sometimes DDR community is just like over-humblefied.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: If somebody asks me how good I am at DDR, I'm going to say, well, let me just put it this way, I kind of used to play it a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's more my response.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just say, I haven't played for a few years.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've practiced a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you have to hit play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I have to hit play.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so, who does this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, old people, young people?
[SPEAKER_20]: Everybody now and then.
[SPEAKER_20]: They come, they try, and they really have fun on this game.
[SPEAKER_20]: Even if they're not good, they can really dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the key?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I think it's really difficult.
[SPEAKER_20]: Actually, the key is to listen to the beat and just watch the arrows go from bottom to top and hit the corresponding step.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, and so what are these two doing right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing like the light version.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do heavy, moderate, or light.
[SPEAKER_20]: There's three difficulty settings.
[SPEAKER_20]: There's light, standard, and heavy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're going to cut over to Lloyd and Beth so we can see how they are stacking up against this competition here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take a look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you guys ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, Tara, we're picking our song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, okay, so they're having this dance-off, quote-unquote, between the people playing in the arcade and then the two hosts in the studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how the fuck that works, but they're having a dance-off, which means we're going to make asses of ourselves all at the same time on this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: He looks completely unenthusiastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, these people have no, they don't need to be touching this software at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this is why old people, I'm sure these guys aren't touching the software, that's what interns are for.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I used to be an intern at a television station, trust me, that's what the interns are there for.
[SPEAKER_03]: These guys don't have to know shit about the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, let's watch and laugh at them as they make an ass of themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: And in response, yeah, they were playing the whistle song at the beginning.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not going to pick the maniac level.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basic.
[SPEAKER_01]: Use your arms with me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on, you're a big boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just bounce.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, ready?
[SPEAKER_01]: Left.
[SPEAKER_01]: The guy is not even looking at the screen and they're playing dive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pause it, pause it.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_03]: Turned around and bitch-slapped her and said, Stop it!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm making a big ass out of myself on television as it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: And... Move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll give you the link to the video at the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and look, they failed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pause.
[SPEAKER_03]: It took them a whopping 15 seconds to fail dive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoever decided to pick a four-foot song for these two incompetent hosts to play on the start, that was a bad mistake.
[SPEAKER_06]: That intern is so fired.
[SPEAKER_03]: That intern is so genius.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, I fucking hate those bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: They make me do all their fucking workflow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll make them look like fools on TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now the male host is so shocked that he failed, he has Sylvester Stallone face.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's got like, oh, Adrian, I fucked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meanwhile, the employees are still going at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meanwhile, the employees are still going at it on the whistle song and not working.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now the female host is asserting her authority and just yanking the other two employees off the machine and letting the third employee, who happens to be a DDR maniac here, put in his coin.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then you get to pick your own song.
[SPEAKER_20]: Pick your own song, pick your own difficulty level.
[SPEAKER_20]: Look, words in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_20]: This game will give you the seizure.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Max 2, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have about 20 seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's going to do the heaviest difficulty possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this guy, I mean, this is like a workout.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you don't want to go to aerobic class or... So you go straight for Healing Vision Angelic Mix, because he's going to show how big his dick is right here on TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll just fade out here, Beth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just catch this guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he also picked the song where the woman's gonna have to stretch for like 20 seconds to fill this blank spot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so fucking amazed.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can see my reflection.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pause it!
[SPEAKER_01]: God, she did not go dance, dance, dance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, she just said dance, dance, dance, revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like either she read the teleprompter wrong or something happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're playing dance, dance, dance, revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: The sequel to dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, revolution, revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let the bitch finish.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox is going to come out with a version that's DDR Ultra Mix, and the one we have in our studio is thanks to Jim and Suzanne Eckes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just cuts off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Notice I say nothing about Konomics in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They say nothing about, oh, Max 2 is out now and you can buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is further proof that Microsoft is trying to buy out the world with this stupid Xbox thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's another place, and we'll talk about this later in the show, where they have a huge advertisement for DDR on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: They say nothing about, oh, Max 2, available now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all about, no, the Xbox version's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: When she said right at the beginning of the thing that she said for PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: But she was playing Kanonix.
[SPEAKER_03]: She wasn't even playing what's available right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And thanks to these two people who are probably interns or something that brought it in, I would have been like, oh, fuck this Yoshi bitch, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to fucking do doubles and kick his ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be like, oh, man, that makes me so wet and hot because he's so sexy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's better than that Asian man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, man, I want a piece of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then it would have all been like, oh my god, he is so cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we need to write them and say, hi, we host a radio station about the money and we think you're stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love, Orange Elves Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will write that letter if you want me to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will write that letter telling them, you know, that their article was... They should interview us.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think we need to waste our time with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be honest with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just, you know, let it be whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got bigger fish to fry than trying to get our faces on UPN Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to watch that story and laugh at it yourself, the link is www.upn31.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Telemore's Lounge Radio sent you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The link there, by the way, is on the bottom right of the page.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says, Beth and Lloyd cut a rug in a video game dance-off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who fucking says cut a rug anymore?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just ate Taco Bell and I've got to cut a rug right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello and welcome to the fifth piece.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh man, I gotta cut a rug.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, that's cut the cheese.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whenever I hear cut a rug, it makes me think of farting, or queefing, probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta vibrate the rug a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cutting a rug, isn't that like what porn stars do?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, they get prepared for their videos, you know, they cut their rug and make sure the carpet's all trimmed.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's called shaving their private area.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, cutting a rug doesn't make me think of dancing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, dancing and cutting a rug are, like, completely different.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, to cut a rug you have to be bent over and, like, actually, you know, cutting the rug with, like, a knife or something, whereas, you know, dancing you're gyrating about to music, so I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stupid hippies.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we're going to take a break, and when we come back, we're going to talk a little bit about an interesting... We'll come back and take scissors to your carpet here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and we're going to cut the rug here in the studio when we get back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when we're done cutting the rug, we'll get into the Orange Lounge Cage Match, so make sure you're in the chat room so you can vote in tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're going to talk about a really interesting location, probably, dare I say it, the most interesting place I've ever seen a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't think I've seen a unique...
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll talk about that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_03]: This break, I think we're going to do some DDR Euro stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's do some music from... Let's just have some Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: You want Eurobeat?
[SPEAKER_03]: You want Parapara music?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go for some Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we'll do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll do God.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are going to hate us for this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but no stylist is going to piss his pants.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be short and painless, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we'll be back after some quick block of music from Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Launch Radio.
Parapara.
Thank you for watching!
Don't wait for me
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge Radio Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and I believe we've been doing this show, what, 66 weeks now?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that is probably only the second time I can ever remember us doing a para-para music break.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't help it when Eurobeat was on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I found myself starting to do part of that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was my first para-para.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those songs, by the way, for you guys tuning in that maybe don't know much about the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boom Boom Fire was the first one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was probably, I think for most of us, the first para we learned.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Abra, Abra, Cadabra
[SPEAKER_03]: Parapara songs are really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like some of the better ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there needs to be more of them in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like if 2DX just needs more songs, just take some from Parapara.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of my early six stars was a Parapara song.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my first seven star was a Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I believe it was... My first two sevens.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_06]: My second three... Out of the first three that I passed, the second and third ones were Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: My first one was Please Don't Go.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'll vouch for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've been in the car with me with my Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a very safe, over-safe driver, and when I put that CD in, I go like 90 miles an hour.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember who I was with.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Ryan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody said that I get all cool when I drive with Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, what do you mean by cool?
[SPEAKER_06]: He was like, aggressive.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think happened with Parapara?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to kind of ask this question to anybody who wants to answer it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened with Parapara?
[SPEAKER_03]: It came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was the coolest fucking thing on the block.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody wanted to go to Milpitas Golf Line to play Parapara because it was like, oh, it's like DDR, but it's your hands, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: This all fucking sounds the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was done with Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think it was about the time it was released for the home version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I taught myself, like, four Paraparas so I could, like, go to the arcade and blend in with a cool crowd.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I just didn't give a shit anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I didn't really care about anything, Parapara.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember when RPGL got the Patapata machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there were people who were staring at that scratch in their butts going, Ugh, what do we do?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then...
[SPEAKER_06]: We got up there and Rick ate the paper that says do not shadow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, it was great because at Sunnyvale Golf Land, their machine used to have a big sign on it saying do not shadow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because if you've been to Sunnyvale Golf Land, you can't fucking walk down the aisle if there's anybody standing in it, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: So you don't want to have people standing there shadowing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was like this big thing too because Sunnyvale Golf Land is kind of where the backlash sort of began, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of those people who think they're cooler than everybody else kind of started that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then...
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the big sign on there that said, Don't Shadow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what ended up happening, that machine got moved from Sunnyvale to Roseville, Goughland.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first day it came in, one of our regulars over there took the paper off the machine and ate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we have a picture of it hanging out of his mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of a symbolic thing, like, kind of, screw you, we're going to do what we want.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I remember, it would usually be, I'd play, you'd shadow, and someone else would shadow, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the person would shadow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who else was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it Anita?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this was when we first knew Anita.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there was a couple people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just the parents were funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'd be like, uh, we're stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whatcha do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Some different theories from the chat room as to what happened to Parapara and why it's not cool anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: SnubDisanoid says, I think people saw themselves playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it ended.
[SPEAKER_03]: When somebody just saw themselves playing and went, God, I look like an ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: StablerX says, looks just like another passing Japanese trend.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think for me is I stopped going to RVGL.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a big part of it too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played when we go to Miggle.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: People look stupid when they play DDR too.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know if people seeing themselves playing is necessarily a turn off because you look just as stupid playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in fact, like Dance Maniacs, that's the worst.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I love Dance Maniacs, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm fucking building a Dance Maniacs machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, my machine covers everything, but Dance Maniacs is part of it, so there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Dance Maniacs too, but you look like a total boob playing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: You said boob.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did say boob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: SCDriftKing says, my DWI is equal to forearm exercise.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't want to know what my forearm exercise is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I want to address DDRcolic's idea about what happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: She says, I think what happened is all the haters started being haters and ruined it for everyone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what I say, if haters are bothering you, you need to fight hate with hate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't stand for that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Outnumber them and make fun of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is how you're going to stop the haters.
[SPEAKER_03]: You fight hate with hate.
[SPEAKER_06]: We used to fight them with making fun of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it worked.
[SPEAKER_03]: The people that make fun of DDR, we would totally, we would just like, we'd gang up on them, like some kind of geek gang.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd like all surround, remember the guy that made fun of me one night playing DDR, and then like ten of us, we all just kind of like jumped him, like sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were like, hey, you want to get up there and fight him, you know, play against him?
[SPEAKER_03]: And he cried.
[SPEAKER_03]: He ran to the bathroom and cried.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you offered to pay for his game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there's all those other people who I would just have thrown out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Haha, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're going to make fun of us, then you don't get to play anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was because, you know, submitting, you know, kind of playing para para is kind of like almost just like converting over to being metrosexual.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, that's why people weren't playing it because they're like, you know, afraid of the bright, shiny side, if you would like to call it that.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think would happen if you were to show that to the folks from Queer Eye for the Straight Guy?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never watched that show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crab people!
[SPEAKER_03]: I think even the Queer Eye for the Straight Guy people would go, okay, that is too gay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get that out of your house.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's too gay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Too gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you want to know what, though, before... It's going to be in this house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before there was a pata pata.
[SPEAKER_06]: Though, I don't know if you remember, but there's videos that I found way back when.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, the par videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the ones where they were demoing the game in Japan with the little girls with their flowery shirts doing the pata pata on the machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because the little Japanese girls are fucking hot and they're like, I'll do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then also, you know, the guy, get that guy Bucky to fucking come over here and just like beat ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if he was like the main like star of the game, people would be just falling over that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jumping backwards a little bit, about three people in the chat room because of the buffer are asking, what is metrosexual?
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently you haven't watched South Park, but anyways, metrosexual is where you act gay, but you're not gay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like being high in fashion stuff and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Metrosexual is being gay to get chicks.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the thing where five years ago, make fun of gays, can them, all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trust me, I was afraid to come out for a long time because I didn't want to face this backlash.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, five years later, if you're gay, you're cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, you know, being metrosexual is being one of those guys that's kind of up there going, you know, on a date with some woman at a candlelight dinner, you know, yeah, you know, I blew a guy once, you know, just experimenting type thing, and that's supposed to, like, make him more attractive.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know... I don't think it's that at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's better to be that than manual sexual.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just what that means.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, anyways, it's like, you know, I think it's just like, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, define it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Manual has to do with using your hands.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, anyways, um, it's like, it's like, you know how smoking was cool back in the 90s and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like being gay is cool now in like the year 2000 and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, next year it'll be like bestiality or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, it's fads.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey kids, be cool, fuck a sheep.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're at sexual.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, um.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, and now I'm being corrected on this too.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's metrosexual or metarosexual, it's either or.
[SPEAKER_03]: They mean the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: People say it either way because metro, hetero, get it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Metro is like city.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, right.
[SPEAKER_03]: A metro is kind of what it's supposed to be, but people say metro.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of formed into that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying in the chat room Ben Affleck is a perfect definition of a metrosexual.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say more like Justin Timberlake is a perfect example of someone who's metrosexual.
[SPEAKER_03]: He does all these really fucking gay things like being an NSYNC, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was so good she could never have another man after me.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why she's gone lesbian, and that's even harder.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so the moral of the story is, leave being gay to the gay people.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, be accepting, but be straight, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, going back to my live journal post about National Whatever Days, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: They need to have National Blowjob Day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do have all these like sex appreciation day, masturbation day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they have a blowjob day somewhere on the calendar, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just don't have it penciled in.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because they're gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will look it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki is going to look up National Blowjob Day for you all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's shift gears a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to ask a question to the chat room, going back to something actually Bomani related.
[SPEAKER_03]: Send this to me over private message, by the way, because I'll read these later.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to hear from people who aren't in Sacramento, first off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys for listening, our local friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I want to hear from people outside of Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to hear the strangest place you've ever seen a Bomani machine, whether it be DDR or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to hear the strangest place you've ever seen a DDR or some kind of a Monty machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because what we found out this week, let's rewind to Monday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monday, Vanilla Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: After Vanilla Sky was over, LankyStyle, RicePrincess, and I, we all went to Walmart to do some shopping, or at least I was shopping.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to go buy Cheesy Poofs, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was going to Walmart to buy some Cheesy Poofs, and hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki says National Blowjob Day is October 3rd.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also National Go Commando Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: So National Blowjob Day is October 3rd.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you missed National Blowjob Day, I want you to celebrate tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: So here's your chance to make up for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy belated blowjob day.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't have anyone to participate with you, then get some flexibility.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now can I get back on the topic of strange blowing machines?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so send me a private message.
[SPEAKER_03]: Strangest place you've ever seen a Bomani machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm Sky in the chat room over at www.callybomani.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click on orange lines and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vanilla Sky, went to get Cheesy Poofs, and usually, whenever I go to Walmart, I can't help but go into the electronics department, because they have cheap electronics.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cheap mouses, cheap CDs, cheap games, cheap everything, because Walmart is the land of everything cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mouses.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for whatever reason, on this Monday, we went to toys and games, we went to stuffed animals and things like that, we did not go into the electronics department.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come to find out Tuesday morning, this comes up on the boards at sacromoney.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey guys, did you hear...
[SPEAKER_03]: Walmart got a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm thinking to myself, no they didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just there at the Walmart in Folsom on Monday and there was no DDR machine to be found.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, turns out, this DDR machine is smack in the middle of the electronics department at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, most Walmarts I think are all laid out the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those listening internationally, Walmart is this huge chain of stores in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big, big, big store that sells everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most Walmarts, I think, are laid out the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, when you walk in the electronics department, you have your CDs off to one side, and then off to the other side, in this Walmart, giant DDR solo machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just standing right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fully operational, takes 50 cents to play three songs, or get three coins, or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, now, I've heard of a Walmart having a DDR machine out in the front arcade, or an arcade on the side, but I have never heard of a machine anywhere in the middle of a fucking store.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, of course, couldn't resist, had to go play it today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Had to go rent some errands anyway at Walmart, so I went to go play the Solo 2000 machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: And again, I want to state, this isn't like the Walmart in Lodi or other places that had it in the front or in a separate arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: This Solo 2000 machine is right smack in the middle of the electronics department, so as everybody's walking by, people can look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The machine is not for sale.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not trying to sell it.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, they even have a sign on the Solo 2000 machine that says, hey, the Xbox music game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They changed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess they updated it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But last week it said, hey, the Xbox music generator is coming out on such and such day.
[SPEAKER_03]: It had nothing to do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: They changed it today.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says Xbox DDR coming out November 18th, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, says nothing about the PlayStation Max 2, says nothing about the already available DDRs out there on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all about promoting the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's almost like Microsoft bought them that machine and put it in the store.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But now we have this DDR solo machine in the middle of Walmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: It won't be there for long because the parents will see the needles and the barely dressed nurse.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Walmart, king of censors.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the one reason I won't really buy CDs at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll look and see what's new, but I won't buy because I fucking hate that Walmart censors the albums.
[SPEAKER_03]: You go to buy an album at Walmart and you will buy the desensitized version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at the fine print, look at the label, and you will see that the CD you're buying at Walmart is the edited version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meaning they've taken out all the fucks and shits and cop killer statements, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Even a CD like Madonna's American Life that just came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Walmart version in track one, the first song, they took fuck it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, oh heaven forbid, we're going to hurt our children.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is so...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's another case of companies taking responsibility for other people's children
[SPEAKER_03]: Why should Walmart do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: They shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't they just not sell the CD that says caution?
[SPEAKER_03]: The CD has the word fuck in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the parents don't want the children to listen to something with, you know, bad language in it, they need to freaking police what their children are doing themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Walmart should not have to institute these kind of policies, but they do because they're run by the religious right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a whole other story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I prefer calling them the religious wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, that's a discussion for a whole other show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excellent point by Leadfoot in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet they sell rated M games in the gaming section.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll sell rated M games, but heaven forbid they sell a CD with the word fuck on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the video came wrong, how bad could it be?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you hear about these parents that are suing the makers of Grand Theft Auto because some people got shot or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not the parents.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the relatives of the victims who got shot because some kids went out and imitated Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sue the kids' parents for being idiots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not the game's fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the damned impressionable people.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, they're the social sheep of the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, back to DDR before we got off on a little bit of a tangent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to DDR in the middle of Walmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's quiet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't really hear it unless you're on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The pad is so close to the machine that literally I'm six foot two.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the first time I've ever played DDR where I have to look down to see the machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to look down to see the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I played it like three times this week, all on different occasions.
[SPEAKER_03]: One was getting a pro-action replay so I could cheat in F-Zero GX, and the one that was getting Castlevania, then today was just going there for the hell of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And all times I played on there, and they'll actually pay me to play because I'm good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm like, you know, whatever that guy's name... Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am like Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_03]: How does that work where they were paying you to play?
[SPEAKER_03]: What did they do?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll give you 50 cents.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're supposed to give you 50 cents so you can play this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just because of people that aren't paying attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's one nice guy that's been there the last few times.
[SPEAKER_03]: He offered to pay for my games and he did for like one of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, no, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got the other ones, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like, I don't want them to just...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's kind of cool what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like, for some reason, Ultramix is getting a lot of press, it seems like, for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I mean, look, you have the news story, you've got, like, machines in stores.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, that's all you're hearing around this goddamn Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's like they're really pushing this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Walmartrion is located in Folsom, California on Riley Street, I think it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where you will find a DDR solid machine in the electronics department.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other words, way out in the middle of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to hear if any other Walmarts are doing this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So check your local Walmart and let us know if your Walmart's done this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they moved that one on Lodi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I want to get back to the question I posed earlier to the chat room and read their responses here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's hear about some strange places.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zodiac Knight says the strangest place he ever saw a DDR machine was at a Tri-County flea market.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Machine and the Flea Market.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Tri-County Flea Market.
[SPEAKER_03]: Baka says, strangest place you ever saw a DDR machine was in a pizza parlor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's kind of a weird site at first.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, it's kind of common where we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bumlover says, I saw a DDR machine in my butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, that's so mature.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for sharing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nostylan says, Walmart once had a Beatmania 5 key before DDR became popular.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: SnubDisfinoid says, pump it up in the middle of an airport in Brazil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Listen, like right in the middle of the fucking terminal.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pump it up machine right in the middle of the Brazil airport.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jazz kind of cites a pizza parlor as well and the Beatmania and Walmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: John Fields says, a pizza hut.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you like cheese on your pads, he says.
[SPEAKER_03]: So a lot of pizza parlors kind of being a strange place for DJ Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the reason why the pizza parlor thinks... I know one, a McDonald's.
I've heard of one being in a McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Say that in a...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also, I was told this, there was a Beatmania 6 mix, I think, in the middle of the mall outside the arcade in Mobile, which I'm going to actually go see if that machine is there or not when I'm there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, okay, I'm not even going to read that one because that doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said strange place to see a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, seeing a DDR extreme machine in the Metreon, says StaplerX.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a strange sign.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a strange sign because they held out for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then says a DDR machine in a bowling alley by my college.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's in great shape because no one ever plays it except the occasional drunken bowler.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's colleges.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I'm seeing a DDR machine outside of the CBS studios in New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: John Fields wants to remind us of that when the CBS Today show or whatever the hell it's called did their little thing on location.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that thing was really stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was really stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tapioca Express having a DDR machine, that was always kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one that's nearly dead now.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: The...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dance Fever Dance Fever
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to bring back StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait, I remember one that they had that was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a machine at the arcade in the Winchester Mystery House.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was short-lived, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it scaring off all the ghosts?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: The fact that they have an arcade at the Winchester Mystery House is strange enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then, oh, a DDR Solo machine in the middle of the baseball field, Raley's Field here in Sacramento, has a Solo 2000 machine just right there out on the, what do they call that, the course, the, what the hell do they call that, where the, concourse, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Conquers
[SPEAKER_03]: The way the cage match works, just a reminder, we're going to play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: You vote for your favorite.
[SPEAKER_03]: The winning song goes into rotation on Orange Lounge Radio all week long.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the only way you can participate is to be in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: www.calibermonte.com Click on Orange Lounge and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, here's the first song you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you only hear a clip of it because it won last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here's a long clip of Above and Beyond with the song Far From In Love, tonight's first pick for the Orange Launch Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can see behind your eyes that you're afraid of who you are Only silence now between us, I'm amazed we've come this far Far from in love
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, that was song number one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Last week's winner, Above and Beyond with Far From In Love.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, second song in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get to hear the whole thing, and it's kind of a long one, but it's Loki's pick, and he has picked for you... It's a remix, it's a white label remix of Broken Wings by Mr. Mister, and I guess this one's also by Emotion.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a group, and it's remixed by a group on the internet, well, it's a group of DJs, all women, called the Diva DJs, and it's pretty sweet, so I just found this today because I was looking for white label remixes, because I've got some really cool ones, and I don't know, just listen to it, it's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explain real fast what a white label mix is, for those who may not know.
[SPEAKER_03]: A white label mix is a non-official remix of a song.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not authorized by the actual artist.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more of kind of a thing that you'd find in a club.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone adds a little spice to their set by actually doing a live remix of something or making their own remix and then playing it on their set.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's where it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, here's song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Emotion featuring Mr. Mister with a song called Broken Wings.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that was song number two tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Emotion featuring Mr. Mister with Broken Wings.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go around and see what everybody thought of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll start off with our guest, Bradley, tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't really get into it very much.
[SPEAKER_22]: I give it a seven.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the 80s, so it gets a ten.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one of my favorite 80s songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I love the 80s, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, the original put me to sleep instead of that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it gets a seven.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't a bad mix, but it was pretty damn repetitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't find my inhaler!
[SPEAKER_03]: At three minutes in length, that song would have gotten a ten, but at seven minutes in length, it gets a seven.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't find my inhaler.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's move on to the last song in tonight's cage match, which would be Jamie's pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I noticed that Jamie is trying this artist again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie's picking an artist she picked last week, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: CyberX is cool, and this one's better.
[SPEAKER_03]: It features somebody else this time anyway, so it would be a different vocalist.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know which one I picked, but I like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, I'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's CyberX featuring Rupina this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where the hell is my inhaler?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else you want to say about CyberX featuring Rupina?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, yeah, this song is cool and I had it on repeat ten times today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, here's song number three tonight you can vote for.
[SPEAKER_03]: CyberX featuring Rupina with Like a Flower.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy!
[SPEAKER_03]: Like a Flower
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to make my dream come true, it's right here.
[SPEAKER_11]: No matter what the future holds, I will never give up.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will live in the present.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that was song number three for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was CyberX featuring Rapina with Little Flower.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go around and see what folks thought of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bradley, you're going to need to grab this mic unless you get up and grab Jamie's.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you think, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_22]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Her voice sort of got it to me a little bit.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't really like her voice all that much.
[SPEAKER_22]: I give it a six.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I give it a six.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that way better than the song you picked last week, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds very IU Trance to me, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: I seriously thought I was listening to IU Trance for a minute there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I seriously would give that a 10, except I think it needs to be a little tighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same problem I had with the last song.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could stand listening to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I like best that it kept changing throughout the whole song, all the background did.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I give it a nine and a half.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been listening to it all day, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a trance version of the chicken dance.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I have one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually, yeah, haven't you been threatening to put that in for a while now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so let's review the three songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob...
[SPEAKER_06]: You have it, don't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I gave it to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's do it for the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we'll play it in the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's review the three songs you can vote for tonight, shall we?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's start off with song number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's last week's winner and the song is called, it's Above and Beyond with a song called Far From In Love.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like that clip.
[SPEAKER_03]: Song number two you can vote for tonight is Emotion featuring Mr. Mister with Broken Wings.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here's a clip of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here's song number three you can vote for tonight which is Cyber X featuring Rapina with a song called Little Flower.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoops, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: My mouse is being over-sensitive today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's your three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we'll tally up those votes and let you know in a little while who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't that sound exciting?
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to do something else soon, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: What are we best known for, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranting?
[SPEAKER_03]: The FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll do those in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll do those next break or something.
[SPEAKER_21]: What is Loki whispering to me here?
[SPEAKER_03]: He's whispering something to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: The FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm on top of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to be prompted.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not need to be prompted.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Loki ran off to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to have him do a sim update, but I guess that's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Jamie, what's going to happen when you... You're going to be gone next week, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, not next week, but you're going to be here for next week's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: And after that, you're gone for a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're not going to be back until episode number 70.
[SPEAKER_06]: I may, I don't know that I'll be able to play the show, but I may have some degree of internet access.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: So at least be in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have pre-shows done.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have my cage match picks in case, you know, the winner don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'll be there in spirit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll eat some beef and pee so you can smell my beefy pee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those that were listening in the first hour of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said I don't eat beef.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll eat some asparagus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has really stinky peas.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll work.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, going off, let's plug the spin-off shows, what's going on on the spin-off shows, because I want to know what's going to happen to Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monday night's on the station, Vanilla Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomorrow night we're going to be talking about some big news in the Final Fantasy world that came up this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll talk about that and Castlevania, full review and breakdown on our thoughts on the new Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_03]: and other stuff that we usually talk about on Vanilla Sky, just randomness.
[SPEAKER_03]: As I kind of compare it, it's sort of the Oprah show on Oxygen, the one that's like after the real Oprah show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not watch Oxygen, I've just heard about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell us what's on Tuesday nights, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pump up the volume, starting at 7 o'clock with the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what time my show starts.
[SPEAKER_06]: 7 o'clock with the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_06]: 7.30 starts the show show.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you are in the chat room, you can request shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll play it, because I'm nice like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I may be doing requests, I may have to be a little bit more judicious, because I'm going to be recording this one, because it's going to repeat while I'm in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_06]: The week after, though, I'm doing the show on Monday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I will be on an airplane on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, our show is Swip Swap next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're going to swap next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But...
[SPEAKER_06]: I've pre-recorded last week's show, and I'm going to record this week's show again.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you'll get to hear them if you miss them, which you have no excuse to have missed them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kick you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's over at 10.30, and you have to be in the chat room, or else you miss the full experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, just like with this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else to plug with Hub of the Volume?
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me drugs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wednesday nights coming back the week after next, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_03]: You going to be ready for it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: The week after next?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Week after next comes what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be as ready as I normally am.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving to Wednesdays is... I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Live wire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lesbian hookers in outer space, Loki presents.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll change it to bondage lesbian hookers from outer space.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what happens on bondage lesbian hookers from outer space?
[SPEAKER_03]: I play music while bondage lesbian hookers from outer space entertain me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: November is going to be a big month for the station.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God we will have a new website done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have so many ideas for the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want it to be so comprehensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just fucking suck at designing websites.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need pictures first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get the pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bust the pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a website.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: Website.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll take pictures right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: None of me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to make some for you on Patreon.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can just, like, do a picture of, like, some character from, you know, 2DX or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Celica, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't I just give you all the pictures I made of DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_03]: Nah, I like my idea better.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not letting me off that easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, you're going to be the Junior Senior Robot now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I swear to God we'll have a new website this month at some point because I'm sick of the old ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to be the Junior Senior Robot.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a new location for the site that we're going to unveil too and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we have some new specials we're planning for November.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to be doing some new specials.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just got an idea for one today that's going to take a lot of work, but it's going to be really fucking cool if I can pull it off.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to work on that for November.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also in November, the whole way you hear Orange Lounge Radio will probably be changing.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to sound even better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though you're still on a modem line, if you have an MP3 codec, we're going to sound even better.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming in November.
[SPEAKER_03]: and of course you can't forget episode 69 episode 69 and unfortunately Jamie won't be here for episode 69 but she will be here for episode 70 which I think is what I said would be the season 4 premiere but I'm not sure I'm not sure yet so lots of stuff coming to Orange Lounge Radio in November which makes sense because it's November sweeps alright we're going to take a break and I'm going to tally up the votes to the cage match last call for votes on the Orange Lounge cage match by the way while we take this break
[SPEAKER_03]: The chat room is asking, since we're kind of doing these themed breaks tonight of a certain Bomani game, the chat room is begging, please can we do an Oha break?
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm saying sure, let's do an Oha break tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to hear the Oha Ska, and we'll hear Why, the Zona song, and we'll hear Candy.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Music, Music, Music
Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we care what people think of us?
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_11]: Do we want people to kiss our ass?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_18]: Extreme Bomani Radio, that's us, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, also coming in November, new promos!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Good God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tourney Mix 4th Plus has gone on DDREI.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: So go there if you really give a shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've lost all hope in Tourney Mixes anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really just don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't plan on entering them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just... I haven't played Set Mania in months.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm waiting until my cabinet's done, then I'll play on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to be honest, the Japanese people make better sim files than you fucking Americans and Europeans will ever make So shut up
[SPEAKER_03]: There's only a few of you that are any good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: And you people know who you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, the hell with all of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everyone else.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's only like, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Three people I... Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got that Matt guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got, um, Utterdude.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got, um, the people at DWI Insanity.
[SPEAKER_03]: They make really awesome sim files.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, Healing Vision is part of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are the only people that make any good sim files!
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tourney Mix has turned into the new Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: When it was first out, everybody thought it was cool, and now it's cool to make fun of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because they keep adding more and more rules to it, and it's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is, also, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's another group that was pretty good, too, in making sim files.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember who they are.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like the DWI New World Order or some crap like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the Japanese people make awesome sim files, better than you'll ever make, and they've been doing it for years.
[SPEAKER_03]: So just give up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just stop, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know... Do people still make stuff for BM98?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, oh man, the stuff for BM98 is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love BM98.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I'm sorry, but it takes a lot more talent to create something, a BMS file, for, you know, BM98 than it will for Step Mania or DWI.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we're talking like key sounds, they arrange it, they make their own, you know, song.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember playing BM98 before I'd even seen DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is just so much fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, I am so sick of hearing about Bomani Ruler because the guy supposedly quit making DWIs many years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many years ago did he say, I'm tired of people bitching about myself being too hard, so I stopped.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yet he keeps making them.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to quit, you quit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't keep coming back and then quitting again.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one cares.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're like fucking Michael Jordan, and he sucks now.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's the Hulk Hogan of the Bimani world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just stop making sim files.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, the few people out there that make actual good sim files, you know, I'm willing to try a few new people out, but a lot of times they just suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you get one sim file that's a 12-foot rating and it's just shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just delete the rest and, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: Play the few that are good.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are no longer after creating the largest step file collection on the internet, correct?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just I don't really care anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I download one of everything I don't have, but I'm not actively pursuing to have a huge collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not trying to have the largest step file penis on the internet, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just want to have the best looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't really care anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mine just looks nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: My penis is quite nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: But my Simfon collection, I don't really care because I don't play it anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not until my cabinet is done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once that's done, I'll play it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't need to sort through like 6,000 songs to find something I want to play because that just takes too long.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, to hell with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and there's some pretty cool skins out there you might want to check out for Stepmania Trans Machina, which is a good one I mentioned back a while ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might want to go check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe it's in the Stepmania thread or skinning.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can find it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm sure there's been some Stepmania updates because DWI Denver updates, so screw that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you go to...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's DDRAmerica.com or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that BitTorrent site I mentioned a few weeks back.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have the full set of, what was it, the full set of the Max 2 USA stuff already done, which I already downloaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I could have done it a long time ago, but I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all that I care about.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about, since it kind of relates to Step Files, let's talk about this whole Into the Groove thing that's coming out here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you bring that up for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to talk about Into the Groove tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the Madonna song, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'll take an excuse to play Madonna.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: A few things that are good about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, you've got Kiel making some of the music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, what the hell is Into the Groove?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, Into the Groove... Don't tell me what's in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell me what the hell is it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Into the Groove is gonna be a new arcade software very similar to the DDR that's supposed to be hitting arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's Linux-based, which... Whoop-a-dee-doo.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, it's Linux-based, which means geeks made it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big fucking geeks made it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it's, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: is created by the same, it's created by Christian Ferd, he's working on it, and he's the guy behind Stepmania, so there's a lot of similarities to Stepmania on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty much a lawsuit waiting to happen, but they quote that it's, you know, it's very different from DDR, but looking at the screen, I have to differ, it doesn't look like it's very different at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it looks kind of craptastic but anyways they've got some nifty stuff on there like they've got a mode where you can play where there's four arrows just like DDR but they're on the four sides of the screen and so the arrows are coming out of the center towards the outside which is kind of cool now it's a little different
[SPEAKER_03]: Dizzy, Sudden, Expand, Stetmania
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that's going to happen, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's interesting, because I see on this sample screenshot they've got Atom Bomb by Fluke, which is like that generic trance song that's on every compilation CD ever, but it's a cool song, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe got Atom Bomb.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then what, Romeo and Juliet?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never heard of a lot of these other songs, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you know these?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you said now, this is what's interesting, is that people in the DDR world are getting into this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You said that Kiel is possibly having licensed songs on this?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, he does.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's like, um, where'd he go?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember where I read this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says about Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know where to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's on the staff, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's on the staff, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's doing music on it, and Chris Danford...
[SPEAKER_03]: is doing some other stuff on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we play a Kiel original song on his tape.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've actually been playing it for the past two years.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's time for us to change it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm just saying, he's kind of been known in the Bomani scene a little while for making some good originals that would be good for DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's just kind of ironic that this is now going to end up in a DDR-style game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's not too surprising because he has some of the songs, I believe, that are on...
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say they're on that Flash game, that Flash DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my gods, maybe they're licensed Neo Max.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh god, I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those of you that keep telling me that Neo Max is going to be in a DDR mix, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nobody cares.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is like the most overrated thing ever, ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more overrated than... I don't know, but just shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually think I may prefer Neomax to Max, period.
[SPEAKER_03]: But fucking, who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: Neomax will never be on a DDR-type machine because they only put good files in DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, once again, this goes back to what I was saying before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why the fuck won't people let me put in a StepMania-based PC in a DDR machine and we'll just do it that way?
[SPEAKER_03]: Since most of the DDR machines are violating copyright laws anyways because they have licensed music that's out of this country that don't share the licensing in the U.S., basically, you know, it's like an import CD or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: The only people that would bitch about it, ironically, are the people that love DDR, which they're shooting themselves in the foot, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't understand why they just don't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I'm trying to push that on our local arcade here, but no one seems to be biting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think Konami is going to sue the pants off these people if this game ends up in an arcade?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think Konami is going to sue the pants off them?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't you think that's a little odd?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will they?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the rumor is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, rumor was a while back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if this was true or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm saying it's a rumor.
[SPEAKER_03]: But rumor was one of the reasons that Konami Arcade Mixes, you stopped seeing them, is because they ran into trouble with the folks that made Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some kind of like thing where Pump It Up got the copyright to make dancing machines in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and Amiro, the folks that made Pump It Up, had the copyrights on U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though they haven't done shit with it either.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but Pump It Up, it's just not as exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what Pump It Up is doing wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't put my finger on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just isn't as good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sorry if you're a fan of Pump It Up, but there's just something about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not the same as DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's not the fact that it's 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just the interface, the giant screen, the songs are subpar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what it is, but Pump It Up is not the same as DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so I think it was something like DDR sued Pump It Up overseas, and so Pump It Up got the rights in America and then sued DDR here or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the way the rumor went.
[SPEAKER_03]: So would Konami really have a right to step in and sue?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whether you did the Step Mania machine in some arcade or... Look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami hasn't sued Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I were Konami, if I had written DDR, I would have sued the pants off of Step Mania years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just going to say, as far as that lawsuit was concerned, it was basically, I think it was overruled.
[SPEAKER_06]: That they were considered different, therefore, I'll find the stuff on it, but I believe that nothing came of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, basically another frivolous lawsuit that resulted in nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray for the judicial system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is just people responding to Konami's, um, of America's unwillingness to make a new arcade DDR release.
[SPEAKER_03]: People want fucking a new DDR mix, and I'm just so pissed off with the fact it would be so easy to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so fucking easy to do, and we can actually license the music because there's a loophole because it sort of would fall under the category of a, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: AVM, what was it, sort of fall under the jukebox licensing rights.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's kind of classified as a jukebox.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a very gray area, but you could license it for a flat fee of like $364 a month, or not a month, a year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's change.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's like a buck a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: A buck a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't tell me that no one plays that machine not once a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hardware would be only a one-time buy of like a PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we wouldn't even really need to do shit to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And upgrades would be free.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's money in the bank right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're not jumping on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead, they're buying $1,500 bootlegs of really shitty, like, hacked DDR shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not even that good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just all flawed like hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand why people aren't jumping on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can work...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna, like I said, I'm gonna, my proposal, I'm gonna do the Golf Land, I'm gonna try, like, show the Keith and stuff, I'm gonna, like, redesign, you know, Step Mania's thing to be just like DDR, have, like, skins and everything to make it the most convincing, um, arcade port, cause it's not like some sort of hacked shit where it's gonna look like crap, all of, you know, really nice steps for songs, full sets of steps, not this, like, one difficulty shit, you know, full sets of steps,
[SPEAKER_03]: and all that stuff with no full unlocks and it's got you know you can hook it up so it runs off of credits like from coin slot it's it could work but you know people will be just like no because it's not official Konami but people are going to sadly buy this piece of shit machine and
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to see these in arcades now.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to be honest, I don't understand why... Well, now give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: You haven't seen this machine yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: But still, I don't understand why people aren't jumping the chance to do something like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I know Keith, if he was still at Scandia, would have jumped on this a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: He would have totally gone with the step mania idea for the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: He would have done it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because he wanted to do... If I could find a way to hack the actual disk, he wanted me to go ahead and do that and...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, make a mix that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if people can get away with making these shitty bootlegs that really look like bootlegs, why not try to make a convincing hacked version of DDR?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, what do you think, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you play this new mix?
[SPEAKER_03]: This into the groove thing that's kind of like DDR but not really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought from the first moment I saw it that it looked really stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if it's actually released, yeah, and it's there, yeah, I might give it a try.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it just looked really, really uninteresting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it didn't even look visually appealing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my advice.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to do this and you're going to put your balls on the line or whatever and you're going to maybe get threatened by Konami, here is what I've been saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami should be doing for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bring this up every episode for like the past year.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what I've said.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is how you can avoid the lawsuit and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make DDR competitive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make DDR a competitive game, and now it's a completely different kind of game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Steal the dance magic mode idea, but make it your own.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you're doing dance magic without necessarily doing dance magic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't fuck it up like that one Dreamcast game.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell was that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: The one, the, uh, the shareware Dreamcast game that we reviewed on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dita Fury!
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't fucking count.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take Dance Magic, make it cool, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what Konami of America should have done, or Konami of Japan, anybody should have done six months ago after Extreme was done and they were done with DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami of America should have put out, I don't know what the hell is stopping them, they should have put out a new American release by now and this is what's going to happen now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they're going to go to court and sue these other people and if these other people play their cards right, it's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami of America is done in the arcades with DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: At the same time, into the groove, it's probably going to suffer from the same thing that Pump It Up does.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be the same, but there's going to be something about it that you're just going to go, it's not DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: So don't try to be DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be something different.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I'm saying go and be more like a competitive game or come up with something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think of something we haven't thought of.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think if you put me in charge, if it was legit, if I could get the go-ahead to do something like this, I could make it...
[SPEAKER_03]: Mix of DDR, that would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would just, the machine would just keep going.
[SPEAKER_03]: People would keep playing this damn thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just because people get bored with the same songs and stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're bored with like, I mean, look at DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been out for like, boy, like a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Almost a year.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and people are bored with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's just like... Because DDR Extreme was nothing exciting to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Half of it, half of the excitement factor was old songs coming back.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other half of it was a bunch of Konami songs that have been beaten to death in the ground already through other games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only a couple of the Transplant songs, I can think of maybe a couple off the top of my head...
[SPEAKER_03]: Gummel and a couple and just these things that were like, you know, kind of they were lost in other Bomani games that became more popular again with DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: But shit like V and A, they were cool like at first, but now those songs are done because we wore them out with 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Dance Mania licenses were weak.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're the weakest they've ever been in a DDR game, ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: The US licenses in DDR were better than anything they licensed in Xtreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm saying right now that pretty much the last thing I heard about DDR was an interview with Naoki that they did for this last DDR Extreme live party thing that they're reporting on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my, I saw they had a little thing there on there showing the song list where they're talking about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it sounds like that Naoki is going to be working now on Beatmania stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Strictly, because DDR is either done completely as far as arcade and maybe possibly home versions in the Japanese home versions.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's either done completely or they're putting it on hiatus for a few years.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're going to come out with something new.
[SPEAKER_03]: People want more of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're getting new fans to it and they're going to the arcade and playing it and they're like, okay, I'm bored now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's just different to us here.
[SPEAKER_03]: But don't tell me DDR is dying in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we read it here on Monday on Vanilla Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: We read it.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Extreme, one of the top ten selling games in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Japan, a highly competitive market for video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Extreme still lands in the top ten.
[SPEAKER_03]: The home version, where DDR fucking sucks the place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't tell me DDR is dying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, oh, well, we need a petition before we release another home game.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Unheard of here.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they tried something like that here, I mean, granted, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: isn't Japan, but if they tried something like that here, they'd get laughed out of the country.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: The only trouble you're going to run into if you run a machine like this is you're going to get the RAA, you know, well these songs aren't licensed or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only trouble you're going to run into.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami's not going to even give a shit about the fact that your machine is a bootleg or something like that because your machine isn't supposed to be over here in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you're promoting awareness for the DDR home versions, which is the only thing Konami of America gives a shit about right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Extreme or whatever, those aren't supposed to be over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those aren't licensed for U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is the hilarious thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody made a damn good point, and of all places, DDR Freak this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was reading it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And somebody said, in the instruction manual to Max 2 USA, it says, go play DDR in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says, for the full experience of DDR, go play it in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck are you going to find in the arcades?
[SPEAKER_03]: You are not going to find DDR USA anywhere in the arcades anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell me, somebody tell me in Nortel, where there is more Bomani machines than anywhere else in the nation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make it California, period.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can anybody name me three places that have a DDR USA machine?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can anybody name me three places with a DDR USA machine?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't even think of one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Metreon, one.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you're telling people to go out and play DDR in the arcades, you're telling them go and play the machine that says don't play it because it's illegal outside of Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just, it doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're preaching two different things.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, yeah, this isn't supposed to be over here, but it's over here, so, you know, whatever, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that there's much that they can do as far as, like, complaining that there's licensing or whatever, like, as far as music goes, because the machines aren't supposed to be over here in the first place, music isn't licensed, so you would run into that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's, this is my whole thing, is why DDR USA, they're turning their back on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're, you know, saying...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just saying, oh, they're pretending they don't notice that DDR Extreme exists because they're not having to pay for the licensing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hey, all these great songs, we're not having to pay for, and they promote our home releases.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if we try to do this, the RIAA sucks so fucking much that they'd be taking all our money to do these licenses.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have Japan license the songs for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll bet you anything that is the true reason why Konami of America...
[SPEAKER_03]: They pretend that the importing doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because then that way they don't have to worry about licensing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all on Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then if an artist or a record label comes back and says, I'm seeing these things all over America.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's out of our control.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Japanese movement, that's out of our control.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can't stop them from importing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to be honest, I think you would get in real trouble if you started selling.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say I made a new mix, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a new mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have already a logo done for mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called DDR EX2, Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, say I made this and I went and sold it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where you get into trouble because you're fucking selling a bootleg hacked piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, if you're going to run it in one arcade on one machine and there's only one place in the world that you can play this thing, I don't see what the problem is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see where they're losing any money, because we know we have the latest version there, and they're buying all the official ones that come out, but they're not releasing it anymore, so it's just useless software.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like saying I take an arcade cabinet that has like an old version of Street Fighter in there, and I put another game in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't see what the problem is.
[SPEAKER_03]: John Fields is giving me a suggestion here about going to DDR Freak and looking at the California page and finding just how many USA machines are in California.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so 437 places to play DDR in California per DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see how many of those have a USA machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and I just hit cancel.
[SPEAKER_03]: So out of 437 places to play DDR...
[SPEAKER_03]: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
[SPEAKER_03]: And most of them are boomers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most of them are all boomers.
[SPEAKER_03]: So 20 locations out of 437.
[SPEAKER_03]: 5%.
[SPEAKER_03]: 5% of all places that have DDR, it's a USA machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you tell somebody to go out and play DDR, 95% chance some newbie is not going to be playing a USA machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to be playing a USA-made machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody's arguing how many I counted.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the places had two USA machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only counted it once.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't count if they have two USA machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, really, if you look at it, most places have multiple machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Extreme and Max 2, and forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just, let's leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just, I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be really easy just, you know, to do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, as long as people didn't make a big deal about it, I don't see what the problem is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, no, I don't see anyone at Konami going, oh my god, there's a bootleg DDR Megamix.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they're selling that shit, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're selling a bootleg and no one's coming down on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't think... That Megamix we talked about last week with the solid green boxes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, DDR Megamix, it looks like a piece of fucking shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are buying it for our $1,500.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as I'm aware, it doesn't have any new songs other than Extreme, what Extreme had, even though it said it had all the fourth mix and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you're buying a hacked piece of shit and selling on the internet, on eBay where everyone can see it,
[SPEAKER_03]: and Konami's not coming down on them for this shit because they don't care because it's not a threat so if I make one machine in California one machine in the fucking world I don't think it's going to be a threat so they're not going to come down on me
[SPEAKER_03]: Bradley, I've been so rude, I haven't let you comment on this yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there anything you want to say about the DDR bootleg machine, all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: If I can untangle the cord from this fucking chair that likes to eat the cords?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, who's back there folding laundry, anything else you want to say on the bootleg machines?
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't have much of a comment on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just think that, you know, if you look at, and this is honest, this is me, if I see a bootleg version on one side and I see an official DDR on the other, I am probably 90% of the time going to play the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care if it's, you know, upgraded extreme or an extreme, I'm probably going to go play the extreme machine, and that's me.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, I usually prefer to give my support to Konami instead of, even if it's Konami in Japan, instead of somebody's pocket.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they're not making Apothena, that's still another thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still will play the original over a homemade version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, break time.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we come back, we're going to do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So send those in over private message to Sky in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: This break, the theme is going to be DDR Euromix songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: The old school Euromix.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will be back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: There's nothing more than this Tell me one thing more than this
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 66 in progress.
[SPEAKER_03]: After a little bit of a heated discussion about the bootleg machines versus the normal machines and da-da-da-da-da, I want to respond to a comment that came into the chat room while we were on break there.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of our new listeners, hello, Wampa164, had kind of a statement.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I like this, how you said that to the people, designing the DDR clone running on Linux, we're huge fucking nerds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet you're running a radio show that talks about DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, it's a joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we're just, it's a joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: We make the joke, ha ha, Linux is a nerdy thing because most, you know, Joe Schmoes run Windows 95 and all that stuff and easy run stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, if it's programmed in Linux, it must be a nerdy thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: We realize we're big geeks and dorks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I take great pride in being a dork.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nothing wrong with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's nothing wrong with coding stuff in Linux either.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, please, don't take it too seriously, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, I'm making a fucking arcade cabinet for the house.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, how much more nerdy can you get?
[SPEAKER_03]: Look how much money this game has taken from us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look how much weight I've lost playing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But look, I would not be living in this apartment with Loki if it were not for DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would not have Jamius, one of my best friends, if it were not for DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would never have gotten Bradley to ever say a word, nor met him, if it had not been for DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I met Bradley at AX playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Expo 2000, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, he was that quiet guy standing there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meanwhile, I'm over there in my Joe costume singing Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, basically the point I want to make.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR is obviously, if we've gone to the extent to make a show near and dear to our hearts, so we put a lot of fucking effort into it, despite what you may think, because our website's out of date and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We put a lot of fucking effort into this station that nobody listens to.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we do it anyway because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we have all these, so obviously we have some very strong opinions about DDR, and when DDR starts to go in a direction that we don't like, we knock it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like when Star Wars fans call Lucas an asshole because he does something they don't like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, when all is said and done, we fucking love Konami.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me, there's a difference between Konami doing something we don't like and what Lucas did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm just trying to make a broad comparison.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, we fucking love Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it were not for Konami, we wouldn't have DDR, we wouldn't have all this great music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami Originals is some of the best music in DDR, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: When they make bad decisions, we're going to call them on it because they're affecting a game that means a lot to us.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of the purpose behind this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We slam DDR a lot on this show, but when all is said and done, we're only pointing out the flaws we see because the game means so much to us in the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, what was the other comment?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to be fair and kind of give the whole comments here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people commented that Konami doesn't care, but Monty went to pretty good lengths to listen to what the Konami community wanted with the public beta test and the poll they made to see that people wanted back, which might be primarily responsible for seeing Rhythm and Police again on a mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, if you listened to the show a couple weeks ago...
[SPEAKER_03]: I said, Max 2 has the best licenses.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did listen to what the people want.
[SPEAKER_03]: People said, We Want Heaven by DJ Yano.
[SPEAKER_03]: They put it on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pretty sweet song.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, Konami of America doesn't completely fuck up one after another time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just kind of like what's frustrating sometimes is that Konami, when they do things, they do it so well, why won't they keep doing it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why won't they make new mixes?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, what were you saying?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think I said?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here's what I don't understand, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole thing with DDR3, my mom was like, yes, they're going in the right direction, you know, they're getting input from the fans, no... Come in!
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, anyways, so they're getting input from the fans and everything, and they're like, oh yeah, we're starting over, we're doing this, and they're like, ha, no we're not, it's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Giving the players blue balls.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty much what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like you're getting them all psyched up for this new thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just going to keep going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then they're like, you know, we changed their minds.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't really want to do that anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just really annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: They frustrate the players.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, bottom line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at us.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're dorks.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we have a radio station dedicated to DDR, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We like it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because DDR has affected our lives so much, we feel the need to talk about it three hours a week, in some cases more, with our spinoff shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when DDR does something we don't like, we're going to point it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're going to give our kind suggestions in a comical way because this is radio and we want you people to have something to listen to.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we were just sitting here, well, I see that we're going to have the new Max 2 out in a couple months.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, it would be boring.
[SPEAKER_03]: So obviously we've got to say things that are going to piss people off because that's what radio is all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be like watching Masterpiece Theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we're done.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: We got so much on another tangent here that we didn't even announce the winner of the Orange Lounge Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is, tonight's winner of the Orange Lounge Cage Match, by quite a large margin I must say, is coming from a person who I don't think has won the Cage Match in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, your song won tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cyber X with Little Flower.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You love me.
[SPEAKER_06]: You all really love me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like going ferret squee.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good song.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad it won.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's your winner for tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry I didn't announce it earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got kind of sidetracked.
[SPEAKER_03]: That means I don't have to pick a song next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get into the FUs of the week, so we'll stop saying FU to Bomani and we'll say FU to some other stuff real fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Jamie, why don't you explain the FUs of the week for those people who haven't listened before?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is where we get really pissed off and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, first FU goes to my cough that will never go away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like I've been cursed.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, fuck my lungs and my nose for being drippy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, although I really do like codeine a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, another FU goes to, uh, being sick at work.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then...
[SPEAKER_06]: Another FU goes toward the attitude of some of my coworkers that I'm contagious, which is absolute bullshit because it's just a sinus infection, which is bacteria.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're going to get a sinus infection, you're going to get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another one goes toward not having any PTO left over after my trip from Alabama because I had to use half of it to go to what would have been my remainder going to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another one goes toward my car, still not being done yet, although they're making progress on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The biggest one right now goes to this headache that just won't go away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that was pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because I'm in pain.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm eating spaghetti.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dry spaghetti.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, um, F you to stupid drivers, because, um, you go too damn slow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially when I have to yell at you, and you don't hear me.
[SPEAKER_03]: That pisses me off too.
[SPEAKER_03]: So of course I should guess that you wouldn't hear me since my windows are down.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you should.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should see me angry and move out of my way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, F you to, uh,
[SPEAKER_03]: Walmart for having a Solo 2000, because Solo sucks, so, you suck, and F you to the DVD video that I had for calibrating my TV, it's very boring, so, yeah, that sucks, I expect it to be exciting, exciting, okay, with
[SPEAKER_06]: In defense of that video, it did have the electrocution and the fire and the alarm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to Rob for encouraging the old Chinese lady for giving people out samples.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had her trained really well.
[SPEAKER_03]: She wasn't going to give me a sample.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you had to fucking go and ask for a sample.
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What sample?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn it, F you the fact that we have to do these on Sunday because I'm more violent on Mondays when I'm pissed off at things, but now, like, I calm down by the weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not fair.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have much more to complain about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, oh yeah, F you to stupid high school whores because, um, you suck and we know that you're gonna get knocked up and pregnant and have some STD and then, like, collect welfare, so you suck in advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: and a continuing FU to Comcast, the worst cable company on the face of the earth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they're fucking over a bunch of my friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been reading a live journal this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Comcast has been taking people offline and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And worse yet, it's spreading.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's worse than Gator.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's spreading like a disease.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and that reminds me.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to lop.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll let Loki give the rest of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lop.com took over this guy's computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God, don't go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't want this thing on your computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's worse than Gator.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like SARS for your computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to Lop.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's not even Lop.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's some sort of spyware program that got on my computer from visiting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know what.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just somehow got on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was a bitch to get rid of because you remove it with all the adware programs out there and it will not remove it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only way you can get rid of LOP is to go to their website, find the hidden link on there, and then download their uninstalled program and run it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also avoid the program No Adware.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like called No Adware or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is adware itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Irony.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still vouch for the Seek and Destroy program.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been using Attaware.
[SPEAKER_03]: Attaware works well, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Attaware, and I have to use Attaware and then this one program called... Oh, I forget what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Seek and Destroy one finds programs that Attaware doesn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I stick with... I have about three different pop-up programs running at the same time to avoid any pop-ups and get some still sneak through, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you what, it's all about Mozilla.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it weren't slow as shit, Mozilla would be the best, because you can block the pop-up blocking is smarter than anything I've ever used.
[SPEAKER_03]: LOP will get in the Mozilla.
[SPEAKER_03]: LOP affects Mozilla, Linux, and Microsoft Internet Explorer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have found, though, that I haven't had...
[SPEAKER_06]: Nearly as much crap get on my computer since I've been using the Google Companion on Internet Explorer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has the search engine, the pop-up blocker, and an individual word search by every title that you put in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a very, very intelligent little companion, and it effectively blocks just by the pop-up that'll come through in anything it tries to install on your computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very effective, so I recommend it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can get it right on Google.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, Bradley, you have any FUs you want to give him tonight?
[SPEAKER_22]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you to not having money, because that's why Calum P.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: had to take my stuff away.
[SPEAKER_22]: He actually had options for paying like 90 bucks or something, but I had like two payments on Monday that I just barely can cover.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had to let him take it away, and it'll take me like two months to get it back if I can ever get to that.
[SPEAKER_22]: and fuck you to not having money because there's Papa John's Pizza ad right in front of me and it makes me hungry for it, but I can't really afford it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can turn it over if it helps.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you going to buy Bradley Pizza?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll buy Bradley Pizza one day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw, that's very nice.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you, thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, uh...
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, fuck you to the time difference between this coast and the other coast, because I fucked it up when I was emailing a person I was supposed to do a phone interview with, and then she fucked it up too, so we're supposed to have like... And then Daylight Savings fucks it all up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, that doesn't really matter too much, but... No, I'm not strong-sided, you dip.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not sad.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't... I'm hardly ever proud about anything.
[SPEAKER_22]: I try to, I try to, I make it up sometimes, but I don't, I don't tell people about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just, he's trying to be funny and he's not, just ignore it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, well, he's trying to be funny.
[SPEAKER_22]: He'll be fine if he does it in Portuguese.
[SPEAKER_22]: Miserably, miserably, miserably horrible.
[SPEAKER_22]: And, okay, thank you to that.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then she said, oh, so I messed it up, so I'll have like 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_22]: on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_22]: And so then, I think she called me at 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_22]: her time, because of my run running at that time, but I couldn't get to it.
[SPEAKER_22]: and then now fuck you to Mailsweeper because her company uses that and it started thinking my emails were spam so I tried like four or five different times to get through and it kept from blocking them so I still need to call her to make sure that my last message got through which didn't seem to be blocked and hopefully it'll actually work out and actually talk to the person and then they can reject me for not being full of the customer service skills that they probably want
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you to chairs that make too much noise.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because these hydraulic chairs, they're quiet at first, and then they start making noise on me for some reason.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'll wrap it up so people can get to the chatroom and finish it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it then?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on to the chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fucking A, there's a lot of them tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: NoStylen says, My FU of the week is those people that think they're cars.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, those people that ride the scooters and the motor ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: They get in front of you thinking they belong there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I go, um, get out of my way, you're not a bike, so go on the sidewalk.
[SPEAKER_03]: My next FU of the week is for my car not being fixed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, my next FU of the week is spending over $100 for art supplies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, FU for running out of ideas.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need more ideas.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: It got cut off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: EvilNaoki2DX says, My only FU this week is homework.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hi, Ne-chan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ne-chan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I'm a honky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jazz says, I don't have an FU because I'm a happy little ho.
[SPEAKER_03]: My FU is that I don't have an FU because I'm a happy little ho.
[SPEAKER_03]: John Fields says, FU to humanity in general.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, humans suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Without humanity, you wouldn't exist.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd be in a world of nothingness.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd be a robot.
[SPEAKER_03]: 23rd Magus says, F you to people who think they know what's in my head and then proceed to put words in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to Solo2000, you suck, you don't deserve to exist, you are inferior, good day, sir.
[SPEAKER_03]: I disagree, six panel owns you, but whatever, you're entitled to your opinion, even if you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: 23rd Magus continues to say, fuck not getting a call back from either Radio Shack or Papa Murphy's.
[SPEAKER_03]: How hard is it to email me or leave a fucking message?
[SPEAKER_03]: Die, K, thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: When they don't call you, you call them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my advice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wampa164 says, F you to teenage kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can't drive, but think they have and deserve more rights and have no respect for their elders anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, fuck it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kids today.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Alcoholic says, as usual, I don't have any real FUs, so I won't bother with digging down deep to find one.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, I do have to say, I miss my honey bunches of old Dark Child, who's away in Arizona because he's... Oh, well, this is serious reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here I am making fun of her, and it's a pretty serious reason why he's in Arizona.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just make fun of the cute stuff, but Dark Child's away in Arizona because his grandma passed away.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's been gone for two weeks, so I miss him, boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_03]: He comes back Thursday, though, so yeah...
[SPEAKER_03]: We're sorry to hear about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm only teasing you because I make fun of happy things in the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mintz says, FU to my college, I'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's too much stuff to go into specifics.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to anyone going to my college who is an IT major.
[SPEAKER_03]: Y'all dumb fucks that deserve the piss-poor future you're gonna get.
[SPEAKER_03]: LankyStyle says, F you to people who use the word asshat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The word is lame and annoying in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh shit, I just said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, you're an asshat.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, stop being such an asshat.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are wearing your ass as a hat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop being an asshat.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to the person who suggested switching Vanilla Sky with Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm not coming in on Sunday evenings.
[SPEAKER_03]: You switch them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Monday and Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody else is saying that, remember how Loki said that he should do Mondays, or Loki said that he'd be better at the FUs if they were on Mondays?
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be really inconvenient.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Mondays, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mondays are my night.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't have them.
[SPEAKER_06]: This song is really inconvenient, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: LankyStyle also says, oh, and in tradition, FU to this segment because I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Irene has an FU for playing a stupid barber because she hates it, but she's weird like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, cry me a river.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snub Dysphonoid says, Fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not reading that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, that's across the line a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to the stupid high school whores that kept screaming about how good I was at DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for announcing it to the fucking world.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other folks don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why the fuck do you have to scream about how I got four grades on 1998 extra stage?
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't appreciate it and I hope you get pregnant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then that means there'll be more of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fat old fuck you goes to the nasty smelling shit logs to take my turn on initial D. Hey, how about I take a fucking broken bottle to your head, then we'll see how badly you want my turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: You suck shit anyway, and you don't deserve life to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, there's a lot of anger in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's initial D, why are you getting concerned anyway?
[SPEAKER_06]: After his, I have another one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're almost done.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting the last, the straggling FUs now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that means I'm turning the music off because these are stragglers.
[SPEAKER_03]: EvilNaoki2DX has one last FU to his USB wireless adapter for blue screening my system.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Wampa would also like to say F you to MTV for being a piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't even play music but brainwash our youth and corrupt them to shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Similarly, F you to the same teenage kids that can't drive but instead ride their shitty racer scooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lastly, F you to midterms from Stapler X. That's it, last one, no more.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just wanted to add that I just forgot what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Way to go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, I remember what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: This stupid bitch on the Ragnarok Online community on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Her account got banned.
[SPEAKER_06]: And her husband's account got banned.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the thing is they don't know and Gravity's not replying back.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is, though, I understand that I would be upset if my account were banned.
[SPEAKER_06]: But apparently she did not check the ban list to see if it was a temporary ban or a permanent ban.
[SPEAKER_06]: She did not stop to think that because they've recently been hacked...
[SPEAKER_06]: This could be a maintenance issue and that their accounts will be reinstated once they've completed whatever it is that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Instead, she's acting rude to everybody on the list and acting like this is her life.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a stupid game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you think we're assholes when it comes to DDR, go look at this community.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know, I would be upset, like I said, I'd be upset if I was unjustly banned, if I didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: But she was just being really rude and nasty to people with no reason to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: When they were offering legitimate suggestions, things that she can do, the different solutions to her problem, but all that she wanted to do was bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: about the service, and she didn't even take any of the proper steps to be sure that it was indeed, you know, a true banning.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, it didn't have to do with the maintenance or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: This person was so stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just go to LiveJournal.com, users slash Wagner Rock online, and it's probably one of the older ones now, but she's a really stupid bitch and needs to be slapped upside her head.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just for being stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: She doesn't deserve her Ragnarok online anyway if she's that addicted to it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you going to slap her with your dick?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have one.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you had your hypothetical dick.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would slap her with... Your internet penis.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would slap her with the Red Bull cock.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Speaking of LiveJournal, Orange Lounge has a LiveJournal community that is posted in once in a great while.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, actually, we've got quite a few people watching it.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's some news and some questions that get asked on there.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's username OrangeLounge, all one word.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and there is a DDR one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually the LiveJournal community, Bimani.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there's also a DDR one, but it's kind of... No one updates it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just look for the Bimani one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on Dead Journal, there's DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: While we're winding down the show here, we're getting into the home stretch.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, is there anything we missed?
[SPEAKER_21]: You and I had tons of topics we wanted to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is there any last-minute things we forgot to talk about?
[SPEAKER_21]: We did the UPN story.
[SPEAKER_21]: We did the ranting about the bootleg machines and the new games and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's thinking.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's off in La La Land.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alter Mix goes gold.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought that was kind of old news.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alter Mix comes out on the 18th of November.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's going to be when I'm in... No, I think I'll be... Aren't you coming back right about then?
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to look at a calendar.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's about the time I'm going to be back.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, oh, oh, I have happy news.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God, that hurt.
[SPEAKER_06]: For old school gamers... Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is... For anyone who remembers on the Sega Saturn, the Sega Ages collection...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, in the U.S., they released multiple games on one disc, but in Japan, each game was released individually, like Space Harrier, you know, all those.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they're doing Sega Ages 2500, which basically, for the PS2, it's remakes of old Sega games that were supposed to sell for 2,500 yen, about 23-something.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they've released Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_06]: which I ordered, Fantasy Zone which is my second favorite game ever and so I ordered that too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fantasy Star was a really nice remake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are the three that I ordered.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then the other two that are out right now is Monaco GP and Golden Axe.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the best prices I've seen for our most reliable site is toysnjoys.com, T-O-Y-S-N-J-O-Y-S.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're located in Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have really fast shipping.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're selling it for $25.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I just had to make the mention for all the old school people because it's really neat that they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joy of Joys
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a song that's in DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a new mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but is that some fanboy's wet dream, or is that something that's actually been documented somewhere?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's documented.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, was that announced somewhere?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR UK is all over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I believe anything they say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're pretty on top of it for Euromix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: For most DDR news sites, they're pretty respectable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, they've got the UK end covered.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if that's all the news you got, I guess we can go ahead and wrap up the show here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's all the news I can think of.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go around and see what everybody's... Oh, and Jamie would like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're selling second mix machines on eBay right now, a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't like $4,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was some insane amount you could get an extreme machine for.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is that Dan and I have sat down and talked about what made it official.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're buying our house in the spring.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, next spring we're buying our house.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will have a house and we will have a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the thing is, we're probably going to have an extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not a second mix?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you can't grade a second mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get bootleg third.
[SPEAKER_03]: Korean, third Korean.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I do not want the third.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I get a third mix, it's going to be a third plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now the show's wrapping up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bradley, we'll start with Bradley, our guest for this evening.
[SPEAKER_03]: He hasn't said much, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what he's known for.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Be active, not passive.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let my performance today be an example of what not to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be done with my cabinet this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't you say that last week?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, really this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear I'm going to be done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, with part of it at least.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be done with the major cutting of the cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will we actually have a wooden, empty cabinet at the end of this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking...
[SPEAKER_03]: The battery power is the only thing stopping me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have, like, all the sheets I have.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can't take the power!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, all the sheets I have left to cut are just rectangular.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, it's not anything complex or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it's just putting it together.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's not much left.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we'll have a cabinet by the end of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be waiting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is I'm so happy I only have to work two days next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: That makes me giddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you don't have to work a full week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't exactly call what I do work, but sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get two weeks off in a row, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Blimey.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final word of the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nellie, you want to take a stab at one word, Nellie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you say one word?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just one?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: We expect you a nice play again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for listening and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio, The Afterbirth, the part after the credits have faded out.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit of WTF to tonight's fortune cookie, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explain yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going through my waves and I could not decide on one, so I picked the Sailor Stars transformation from the last season of Sailor Moon, in Japanese, of course, which I actually thought was a pretty good series because they killed Chibiusa.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except they bought in Chibi Chibi.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she needed to die too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I was a Sailor Moon fan once.
[SPEAKER_06]: When it was like new.
[SPEAKER_03]: I watched a couple episodes of it once.
[SPEAKER_06]: You watched the crap version.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have like, I can show you some quality Sailor Moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quality Sailor Moon, isn't that a bit of a, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Tuxedo Mask.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tuxedo Common But the guy they have playing him in the live action series is ugly!
[SPEAKER_03]: He's ugly!
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care what everybody else is going to say, he's ugly!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anything else you guys want to say in this little portion after the credits have faded here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ow, my head hurts I smell like sawdust At least you don't have pee beef
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you everybody for listening to and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really great.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, you know, if enough people select us as their favorite station, we get money.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we get reported on by the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we can be on UPN 31, too, because we'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance, dance, dance revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight's post show, you guys, this is an album I think some of you guys have been wanting to hear.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a brand new Dance Mania album that just hit the shelves a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we got a copy of it here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much, Tiger, for passing this along.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Dance Mania Trance Z is tonight's post show, so enjoy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And thanks for supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody needs a little time away I've heard it say From each other Even lovers need a holiday Far away from each other
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: I just want you to stay
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I could stay awake just to hear you breathing Watch you smile while you are sleeping While you're far away dreaming I could spend my life in this sweet surrender
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I just wanna be with you, right here with you, just like this I just wanna hold you close, feel your heart get close to mine And just stay here in this moment for all the rest of time Yeah
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Samba!
[SPEAKER_11]: Santa Maria
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: You can't touch this Break it down!