Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Toto, I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, where Monty talks and then some.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, mostly the and then some part of that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio is created by a bunch of potty-mouthed adults.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain sexual, perverted, and mildly retarded content.
[SPEAKER_17]: You probably shouldn't let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I will spank your child.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're not going to do your job, goddammit, I will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's to my big opening.
[SPEAKER_06]: A sphincter says what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm super, thanks for asking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you little bitch troll from hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: What am I doing here?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dodge this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is a tasty burger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, you stupid bastard, you've got no arms left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, just a flesh wound.
[SPEAKER_05]: Searching for a boy in high school is as useless as searching for meaning in a Pauly Shore movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I hope your babies look like monkeys.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had a Smith.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm playing it for the bartender, so suffer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio Arts.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_08]: This is episode number 64 for October the 12th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're tuned in to the Beemani-themed, most cream-filled station of all things Beemani.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's full of suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Skye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm is Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_21]: Never eat reduced-fat oatmeal cream cookies, because they suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get into that in a little while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also with us tonight, say hello to our tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Also with us tonight, we have some guests.
[SPEAKER_08]: Starting off with... Surprise me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have faced the evil reduced fat cookie of death and I have survived.
[SPEAKER_08]: And all I got was this crappy t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, let's say hello to 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really need to stop listening to Travis, because every time I see you, you're always like, I'm gay!
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, remind me to save that sound clip for the next intro, whenever we introduce Andrew.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be talking to everybody more a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a lot of news to talk about.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Extreme, where Matt's arcade cabinet stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio goes to the movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: And plenty more.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually went to the movies, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: When we come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I went to the movies, too, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you see the same movie we all saw?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, then you get to talk with us.
[SPEAKER_21]: That movie owns my soul.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't spoil it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And part of my intestines.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_08]: First, we're going to play a song from the new V-Rare album.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a long version of Drop Ta-Bomb.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll hear Un De Trois from Max Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Watch your mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: I called it Max Extreme.
[SPEAKER_08]: From DDR Extreme Consumer.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like 1, 2, 3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, like 1, 2, 3 in French.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to join in our fun, www.callybomondi.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Click on Orange Lounge and click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: and our chat room will say hello and give you our webcam link.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back.
Yeah, drop the bomb.
Drop the bomb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you can try to find the right system, now or never, it's a time trip It's easy to blast them all away, put a trigger for someone to say adios to today Don't get me wrong, I'm a pacifist, the mind can't do more than spit Explosives are not what it takes, you know the terrorists always make these mistakes What we gotta do is go momentum, if you need the right tools, invent them Ride the waves, time, count through the rhythm, the march of teachers, we gotta get with them The brain is degenerate, almighty, if I read it through, it's how your master's man goes sour Yes, I'm ready to take that fall, it's up to you to make that call to drop the ball Yeah, drop the ball
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see that ball Let me see that ball
[SPEAKER_04]: What we gotta do is build momentum, if you need the right tools, invent them Ride the waves, time to come to the rhythm, the march of the future's begun, get with it The rain is staring all mighty far, we need to do it now, your master plan goes sour Yeah, if you're ready to take that fall, then it's up to you to make that call And if you don't work, make the real thing, wipe it out So drop the fall Yeah, drop the fall So drop the fall So drop the fall Yeah, drop the fall
Just drop the bomb Loki drop that bomb
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft meets Ecstasy
Mr. Random Person on the street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think of the Orange Lounge being on a music and more show?
The music?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's unearthly.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's like being at a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hope you enjoyed that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And drop the bomb, the long mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: from the V-Rare album, the brand new one that just came out with DDR Extreme in Japan.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think you broke the camera with that cookie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're wondering what happened to the Orange Lounge Radio DDR Extreme premiere show, well, I ordered my copy of Extreme a little later than some of you, and therefore we won't be getting it until Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_21]: I forgot to order mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we won't be doing the show until Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oops, because I'm going to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, when do you leave for Alabama?
[SPEAKER_21]: Next month.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next month.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're still a little ways away.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I had to buy my ticket.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just did the math, though, and you're going to be missing episode 69, which makes me cry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Unless you put us on hiatus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Put the show on hiatus, never.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, we want to go to Golfland on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, let's just pre-record the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, we don't want the show on hiatus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember those days.
[SPEAKER_21]: I will pick my replacement.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you're going to handpick a replacement?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just be gentle while you're picking.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll break out the asbestos gloves.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I originally had told our chat room earlier in the week, for those of you guys that lurk in our chat room 24-7, get a life.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did say originally Monday because I thought that's what day I was going to get it, but I actually checked the UPS thing and it's not going to get here until Tuesday because UPS is slower than I remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it takes two days to get here, not one.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we are actually going to be getting it on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: But because of Jamie's show, we're not going to play it until Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's when the DDR Extreme premiere show will be.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will be Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much of a premiere, I know, because many of you have already played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I know a lot of you guys don't have access to Japanese PlayStation 2s.
[SPEAKER_08]: And maybe you're a little curious about the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because details have been a little... Details about the new DDR Extreme... You know, all the stuff we really want to know about has come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are the hidden songs?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do they sound like?
[SPEAKER_08]: What are the non-stop versions?
[SPEAKER_08]: All little things haven't really been talked about, so we'll be doing that on our webcam as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have the TV hooked up to the webcam.
[SPEAKER_08]: The little things, the cool things, the information mode things that we can't read, but will be funny anyway, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're supposed to promote the program.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm ordering my next week, because I have to buy a ticket to see Alan Jackson.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why are you buying a ticket willingly to go to a country concert?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because my mom wants to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's her birthday.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like when I was going to buy my mom a ticket to see Celine Dion in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then I realized I don't want to contribute to that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Your mom likes Celine Dion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, my mom loves Celine Dion.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know who else my mom likes a lot?
[SPEAKER_08]: Barbara Streisand.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry, but is she tone deaf?
[SPEAKER_08]: My mom also bought the Rosie O'Donnell Christmas album.
[SPEAKER_21]: But Celine Dion can't sing for shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: The only good song she did was like by Meatloaf.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Meatloaf's cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, he was Eddie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see Maren is in our chat room and she's going to Alabama with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she says, I don't have to go to Alan Jackson.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll make you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll buy your damn ticket.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just watch.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're coming to see Alan Jackson and Biloxi with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm probably going to leave her over at Mama Sun Ha ha, you opened your mouth Anyway I love that smiley Usually at the top of the show we talk about how was your day, how was your week But today I wanted to be a little different Let's talk about Orange Lounge Radio Goes to the Movies
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_21]: is different blood effects of various types, whether it be CG or liquid.
[SPEAKER_21]: Blood in various colors.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, no CG.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, there's still various different types of blood effects, like everything from the squirt to the splatter to the animated to the blood.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, it was blood.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lots, lots, lots, lots of it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Most of the movie was in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_21]: And there were puns in the movie, and if you don't really understand Japanese, then you won't get them.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I was there laughing in the theater, and people were giving me weird looks.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then, like, the people in the theater were funny, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, I'm not going to say what the scene was, but there was this one particular really awesome scene, and it gets really quiet, and this guy's back's like, whoa, and everybody busts it up.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the whole movie was just fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: On a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_21]: 5,000 million.
[SPEAKER_21]: Which is just one point short of Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what did you think of Kill Bill, Volume 1?
[SPEAKER_08]: I already knew it was going to be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I already read the script beforehand.
[SPEAKER_08]: You little pirate.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't pirate the script.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was online.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: How can I be a pirate if it was readily available online?
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it readily available from Miramax?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did Miramax distribute the script, or did some little kid find it and put it out for everybody to download?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because it's on the internet doesn't mean it's legal.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was at Moviesource.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, anyways, it was pretty, it was good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was everything I thought it was going to be, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: On a scale of one to ten?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ten.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's 10.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Oscar material.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see that ever happening.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pulp Fiction.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: See?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a little different than Pulp Fiction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pulp Fiction was different.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it doesn't matter because you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Pulp Fiction had way more dialogue than this movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not distributing screens for the small titles, so they're not going to win.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, ha, it's going to win.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pulp Fiction had way more dialogue than this movie did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pulp Fiction used the F word about... I counted one time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Pulp Fiction has the F word in it 256 times.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this movie had it maybe... 40?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because there's that... But there was blood.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I know there was blood.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine each blood spurt as another fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was a pair of the suckiest throws ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way... You throw like a girl.
[SPEAKER_21]: There...
[SPEAKER_21]: There are two tie-ins, by the way, to Battle Royale, not just one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Other than, what was her name, Kuriyama Chiaki?
[SPEAKER_08]: The chick who plays Chinguisa.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're saying Lingui-sa, which is Italian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chinguisa.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it, sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, that's her, but there's another one.
[SPEAKER_21]: In the animated sequence, the girl's voice actor is Maeda Ai, who played the girl at the very beginning of Battle Royale with the blood all over her face.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: And who is in Battle Royale, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_21]: And for other anime fans, Midori Kawa's in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can tell him by his nasally-ass voice.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there is an anime sequence.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably about ten minutes long.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was done by... It was done by the folks at Ghost in the Shell, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was done by... What studio was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Studio Gonzo.
[SPEAKER_07]: That studio did that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, my review of Kill Bill was, it was, okay, this is, this is the interesting thing because every geek I know just totally fucking loved this movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I've been reading LiveJournal over the weekend and stuff and all my geek friends who saw it was like, this is the coolest movie ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's an homage, it's a, it pays homage to everything geek.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is just like a tribute to everything geek.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it is, and, and this is the thing is that Tarantino is a fan of like everything that we talk about on this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, when I was watching the movie, I knew Jamie was just going to be wet watching this movie because I could see all these influences from, like, all of her favorite things that she never shuts up about, like Battle Royale and the anime and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was just like, oh, Jamie's going to be loving this when she sees it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I really loved it, too, because I like all that stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the blood was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um... What?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: And the spanking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I was just thinking that, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was one of the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to spoil it, but that was the best thing in the whole movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the pussy wagon.
[SPEAKER_15]: The pussy wagon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I won't say anything else.
[SPEAKER_08]: On a scale of 1 to 10, what?
[SPEAKER_08]: On a scale of 1 to 10, I give it a 10.1.
[SPEAKER_21]: I win.
[SPEAKER_21]: 50 million.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does Bradley have anything you want to say about Kill Bill?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I can't really add anything because people say it the most.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was kind of sitting there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I give it a 10 because it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can give it a 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd have to see it again sometime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Andrew, I know you haven't seen it, but what would you give it on a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_12]: Based on what Jamie goes, 25 million.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if everyone in this room gives me a dollar, I can go see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about no?
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll give you those sucky cookies to sell on eBay.
[SPEAKER_21]: God damn, am I the only person who knows how to throw a microphone?
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, were you guys going to go see it again tonight after the show?
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd be down.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dork boy has a way home.
[SPEAKER_21]: But we'll go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll go.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Call your dad and tell him you're staying out late tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to see Kill Bill again.
[SPEAKER_08]: After the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll go catch a 10 o'clock showing in Fulton or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you want to go after the show?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have to see it three more times.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we'll go see it.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, I only saw Freddy vs. Jason twice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_21]: So I definitely have to see Kill Bill four times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Explain Jamie's rating system by how many times she watches a movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: If I really like a movie, then, see, four is my favorite number.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is where my small bit of obsessive compulsive disorder sneaks in.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I'm thinking?
[SPEAKER_08]: The most number of times, not counting Rocky Horror Picture Show, that's an exception obviously, but not counting Rocky Horror Picture Show, the most number of times I've seen a movie in the theater is three.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I saw Titanic three times in the theater.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just don't ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got dragged by different people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I saw Shakespeare in Love three times in the theater.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think I need to see Kill Bill four times.
[SPEAKER_21]: This started back with the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: Which I've seen in the theater four times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you see Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2, The Secret of the Ooze, four times?
[SPEAKER_21]: I saw it twice.
[SPEAKER_21]: I saw the third one twice as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: The third one was cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: The third one was just neat.
[SPEAKER_21]: The third one was cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've seen Bill and Ted's Bogus Journey four times in the theater.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've seen Harry Potter and Chamber of Secrets four times in the theater because I didn't actually see I wasn't into Harry Potter when the first movie came out I've seen Freddy vs. Jason twice I've seen now there was one movie I saw six times in the theater and I forgot what it was just because I kept having to go with people and I didn't like the movie but that doesn't fall into my rating system Titanic I've seen The Matrix twice in the theater
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anyway, I thought we could all give our little review on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Andrew, just go with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll cover you somehow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll help you.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll take pity on your poor, pathetic soul.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we'll take pity on you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you're going to be offering it up to Tarantino anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get into an R-rated movie all by yourself now, huh?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: How does it feel to be a big boy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we, can you, wait, Andrew, will you stand up and pose on our webcam real fast?
[SPEAKER_08]: Will you stand in front of the cam?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I want to read your shirts.
[SPEAKER_08]: because your shirt, I swear it's like reading a novel right here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Stan, you don't read many books, do you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to read this for you guys who can't see it on the cam because it's kind of blurry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, Mom, Dad, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you told me not to have anybody in the house while you were away, but when my friends stopped by, I had to let them in.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't planned or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: I certainly wouldn't call it a party.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, I have no idea how the band got here or why the police were called.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm really, really sorry about the house, but that's why we have insurance, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: How many times do you get stopped so people can read that shirt?
[SPEAKER_12]: More times than people stop to talk to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that your way of getting attention?
[SPEAKER_21]: We need to get him the shirt that you got me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate my life.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hate my life.
[SPEAKER_21]: Every day I polish my revolver and I shoot my head like a rock star.
[SPEAKER_21]: This 80 year old lady stopped me in the grocery store to read my shirt and said it was the funniest thing she's ever seen in her life.
[SPEAKER_21]: and then while the rest of us are at Scandia lamenting it evil place why should we go to ARC for DDR?
[SPEAKER_08]: you're like one of the only people that sticks up for this little community college with a DDR machine and I have no interest in going to college to play DDR but I'm curious to hear why you love it so much
[SPEAKER_12]: It's cheap, it's loud, they've got all the unlocks, it's in perfect condition.
[SPEAKER_12]: They keep it in perfect condition.
[SPEAKER_12]: If it isn't in perfect condition, I damn well beat their asses for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, okay, somebody fix the pad, now.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what they need to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: They need to put DDR machines next to military drafting boards.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be the ultimate military idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Get stupid, nerdy people in there, trick them into going there, and then they're in the military.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to basic trick maniac them into the military.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was really dumb.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just brought this show to a screeching halt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I'm sure you would probably say that you pulled a magus, but I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would sound better in Portuguese.
[SPEAKER_21]: Especially since someone took your joke book so that they could wipe their ass.
[SPEAKER_21]: If anyone's been keeping up with my board, hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you like to give your board a plug?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: It needs to be plugged into the wall.
[SPEAKER_21]: It has some life in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I posted on your board this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and the puzzle pirate said that nobody reads.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I read it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's roleplay.darksakura.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: There is no www in front of it, so don't be stupid and put it in front of there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just roleplay.darksakura.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's that easy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sign up for it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Become one with the nerdiness.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's move into how was your week, how was your day, because I want to hear how your guys' week and your day was.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Jamie, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_21]: Week sucked.
[SPEAKER_21]: I had like a really bad night within the week, which was alleviated by some strategically IM'd cat pictures.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I was just really kind of crappy all week.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I had a really good day Friday.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then I was really disappointed because Dan was like, I don't want to go to the movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I was like, well, fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, um, basically what happened Friday is, okay, last week was customer service week all week, which was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, you know, Thursday was what is your favorite decade day, so I dressed all 80s, it was great.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, uh, played, you know, Duran Duran in my cubicle all day.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then, uh, Thursday, not Thursday, but Friday, I, uh,
[SPEAKER_21]: They fed us spaghetti.
[SPEAKER_21]: My supervisor cooked it, and she makes really good spaghetti.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then I get home, and I'm like, Okay, Dan, we're going to go see Kill Bill, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: And he's like, Uh, I cooked you dinner.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, how nice.
[SPEAKER_21]: He cooked spaghetti.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's had spaghetti twice.
And so I went to the...
[SPEAKER_21]: I went to the store and bought some garlic bread and some real parmesan cheese.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't like the powder parmesan cheese?
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to have the actual cheese?
[SPEAKER_21]: Since I've had real parmesan cheese, I have to have real parmesan cheese every time.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm such a snob when it comes to what I put on my food.
[SPEAKER_21]: You cheese elitist.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't bite my ass.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll show you cheese.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would not have eaten that cookie if I had known what it was to begin with.
[SPEAKER_21]: That cookie deceived me.
[SPEAKER_21]: That cookie is fucking evil.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you provide our listeners with a little bit of backstory on the cookies that suck?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I love oat milk cream cookies.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very, very, very much.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I usually go to the dollar store and buy the generic ones that have real cream in them, not this marshmallow crap.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I hate marshmallows
[SPEAKER_21]: So much.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because the texture just sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: The only way I will eat a marshmallow is if it's on fire.
[SPEAKER_21]: Flames on the side of my face.
[SPEAKER_21]: Heaving.
[SPEAKER_21]: Breath heaving.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't tease me.
[SPEAKER_21]: By the way, you're turning purple.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't see.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're getting retarded.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You love me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you said purple, not retarded.
Um.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing to throw.
[SPEAKER_08]: Finish your story.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, do not throw the cookie you suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that hit my tummy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, where's the ferrets?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: I do not know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway... Anyway, um... We get to the checkout counter at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_21]: You totally missed.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_21]: We got to the checkout counter at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I am delighted and thrilled to see oatmeal cream cookies on the Little Debbie snack bar.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I... What is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a baked potato.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Bake-O-Bits.
[SPEAKER_21]: Smells like artificial pork.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: I grab the box and I hug the box as excited as I am.
[SPEAKER_21]: and I freaking... She did, I was there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I fucked... I fucked... You fucked the box.
[SPEAKER_21]: I fucked the box.
[SPEAKER_21]: I forked over the money for this... You're eating bacon bits out of the box?
[SPEAKER_21]: My God.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tell your story.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, I forked over the money to get this thing of oatmeal cream pie things.
[SPEAKER_21]: Get in the car.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm halfway through the cookie, mind you.
[SPEAKER_21]: These things are too chewy.
[SPEAKER_21]: These things suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't taste the cream.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my God, it's marshmallow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then we look at the box and it reduces fat and I'm like, oh well shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, I gave one to, I had Rob eat one.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Rob agrees with me that they're the worst cookies ever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we decided that we were going to come back and make everybody else eat them.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we've been successful so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: This reminds me, there's one part in Kill Bill where there's a cereal box called Kaboom.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remembered it from when I was like five to ten years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hated that cereal.
[SPEAKER_06]: We grabbed it one day and it was the worst cereal that I ever had tasted.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we took one bite and we basically threw out the box.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the throwback moment from that.
[SPEAKER_21]: They need to make shirts.
[SPEAKER_21]: with old cereal boxes on them, like Mr. T Cereal?
[SPEAKER_21]: I want a shirt with Mr. T Cereal on the front.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or the Nintendo Breakfast System.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, it's for breakfast now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why is it... I feel really old.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, you were still... It was earlier than that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, nobody can hear what you're saying anyway, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, you know what, I've noticed that so many things from when I was younger are making a big comeback now.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, like, you know, they're doing all the re-releases of Transformers.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have my Season 3 box set now, and it's only the first half of it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I watched the worst episode of Transformers in history next to Carnage in C minor or major, whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the Starscream's Ghost episode for season three and it's the worst episode ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: You said everything from your youth is making a comeback, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's because they say like things cycle in 20 year cycles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like in the 80s, 60s things were popular again.
[SPEAKER_08]: And here we are in the year 2000s and the 80s stuff is making a comeback because it's 20 years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: So like all the stuff from our childhood is making a comeback.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just think, in 20 years, DDR is going to make a comeback.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember that retro geeky dancing game we all used to play?
[SPEAKER_21]: Technically, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_21]: Dance Aerobics!
[SPEAKER_08]: Man, that Dance Aerobics game was the shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, now we're getting what, um, Aerobics Revolution?
[SPEAKER_21]: Is that in Japan now?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have spirits.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it got quiet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, are you done with your story?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was telling a story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got sidetracked, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: That happens all the time.
[SPEAKER_21]: So whose turn is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, Loki's.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here you go, Bacon Breath.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_09]: Almost Bacon Breath.
Bacon Breath.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Bacon Breath.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, my week was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I finished both DDR pads.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're done, thank God.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so glad to be done with those.
[SPEAKER_09]: and so I finished those.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to kind of actually, they were finished last night, very late.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to do a really ghetto job on one of the panels because I lost one of the corner pieces somehow and so there's a nice little square metal piece holding one of the panels and I see it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a square mending bracket.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyways, I started this morning or afternoon, I started my cabinet so...
[SPEAKER_07]: by estimates it shouldn't take too long to do, probably about a week or two and it'll be done because I'm already, you know, almost finished drawing up the first, um, the first, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, um, yeah, I'm almost done drawing up the first, um, whole sheet of, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, don't be knocking it, you know you'll enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fucking being able to break out the old school games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, then yesterday we went down to Golf Land and played a bunch of F-Zero because there's no one playing it and there was a bunch of other people playing DDR and some retard unplugged the machine while we were trying to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuckers.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, not too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear Drum Mania is broken again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was in police call attendant mode, so as soon as Keith gets back there on Monday, I'll be fine again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then what else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, during the week sucked and didn't do a whole lot other than see Kill Bill.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, let's talk to, um, let's talk to Andrew.
[SPEAKER_08]: Andrew, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_12]: Week, exhausting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Day, to suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_12]: Just day after day after day of college, which is absolutely tiring.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we'll get to that a little bit in the FUs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Today I just sat around, played Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually leveled a couple of times, which is getting harder and harder, but figured it all balances out.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least got bored and decided to come here.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I've actually considered getting back into Ragnarok lately, but I decided to start Final Fantasy X again.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not until I finish Final Fantasy X. I'll tank your Acolyte.
[SPEAKER_12]: Play Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, are you on Loki server?
[SPEAKER_12]: I play on all three servers.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have to play on Chaos so I can take you out with my assassin and gain you like, what, 20 levels in an hour?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not until I finish Final Fantasy X. Because I started Final Fantasy X some time ago, like about a year and a half.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it was about a year ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it was when I was with my ex.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a year ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I started it and I never finished it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I only got about ten hours into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so last week after the show, I picked it up again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I said, I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need something to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm like, okay, I'm going to play Final Fantasy X. I'm going to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to beat it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I need to restart the international one.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in this one week, I'm already past where I was last time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just got past that point today.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to know what's going to be scary?
[SPEAKER_21]: The international version is easier.
[SPEAKER_21]: So if I get started playing, I'll catch up to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I know Final Fantasy X is so 2002.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a late bloomer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob's retro.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm retro.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: With Final Fantasy X-2 coming out pretty soon, you know, it means the story will be fresh in my mind.
[SPEAKER_21]: If anyone has ever been to the GameStop in Arden Fair Mall, that was my DVD in the machine there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember that crappy DVD that I picked up last time you were here, when Maren was here?
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the DVD that's been selling all the pre-orders at Arden Fair Mall.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever works.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, so my DVD, my piece of shit DVD went to a good use.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hear from Bradley.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, most of my week was spent looking for jobs type things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like working on my cover letter and trying a few things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Waiting for the... What was the...
[SPEAKER_06]: What the final word on that job I interviewed last week for and finally they got back to me and said I didn't get it on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, on that same day I got a one day job for Friday where I just went in and on Friday I went up and typed in a bunch of names and addresses and phone and fax numbers for a mailing list type thing for a sort of testing software, basically like
[SPEAKER_06]: One of those Excel access, all those type testing programs.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could have been their list.
[SPEAKER_06]: They might have just told me wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I listened to a woman in there talking about the Governator over and over again to various people on the phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hear grumbling in the background.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's over.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's not talk about it anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: This isn't even real Bako's.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they're Fakos.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're bacon-flavored chips brand bacon things with no MSG.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might have commented on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's my job to make the random side comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spent time putting stuff on eBay because I need to get money fast before I run out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: On Saturday, I got invited out to go see Kill Bill via...
[SPEAKER_06]: One person people know, Neil.
[SPEAKER_06]: He invited me out and said that he'd pay for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then I drove all the way out to Fairfield so that cost about the same amount as a ticket.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I actually had gas.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't have the kind of money to actually pay for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was in my wallet at the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we sold that and ate at the only Chick-fil-A in Northern California.
[SPEAKER_21]: Chick-fil-A is awesome.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they're closed on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I haven't eaten there for like a year and a half.
[SPEAKER_21]: Chick-fil-A is the best chicken fast food chain ever.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can only get Chick-fil-A, no, I take that back, because there's a Chick-fil-A restaurant in Mobile, but usually the only places I've ever seen them are in malls.
[SPEAKER_21]: And apparently the owner of the company is, you know, super Christian, and they're always closed on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_21]: But they have the best chicken.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, their chicken is very good.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Polynesian sauce.
[SPEAKER_21]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_21]: No one can hear what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Continue, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, and today, just put more stuff up on eBay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't need to figure out any other plan of action for looking for jobs really fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Food, food, food, food, food, food, food, food.
[SPEAKER_06]: basically, that's all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now everyone's asleep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wake up, wake up!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'll take over then because I haven't talked about my week and my day and I know everybody wants to hear about my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually did pay some money this week on Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had some tokens left so I went by Roseville Golf Land and played two games of two games of Tar Freaks and one game of DDR but then I failed on
[SPEAKER_06]: Twilight Zone, because I forgot to turn off the shuffle.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just failed right at the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, now you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_08]: For my week, I didn't do a whole lot of exciting stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played a lot of Final Fantasy X, and I did a lot of napping.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Vanilla Sky on Monday was great, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: And let's see...
[SPEAKER_08]: I went out to Golfland on Thursday and I played some DDR and some S0 and I also did last night, Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't really like going to Golfland on the weekends because I run into too many people that are in line and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that I... I mean, I like seeing some of the people in the DDR community that I don't get to see very often.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that was cool because I saw one guy I don't get to see very often.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to tell it during the FUs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then...
[SPEAKER_08]: I see some good faces and that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then there's just a lot of those people to get in the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't like that on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: And all the guy and their girlfriend that are trying to play DDR for the first time because it's cute and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I guess I should stop being so elitist because that's how we all get into DDR at one point.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just don't like waiting is what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get out of my way, I want to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's why Thursdays are always better for DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Friday night was supposed to be this great night where we were going to go see the movie and we were going to go out dancing and we were going to get our slut on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just went to the movie and then went to eat and then we went home.
[SPEAKER_08]: We ended up going out because we were all lazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my friend at work is going to kill me because we were supposed to meet her out Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Billy was supposed to come back last night.
[SPEAKER_08]: My sister Billy was supposed to be here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, my sister, Billy, was supposed to be here yesterday, but he didn't come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think a sheep ate him, because he lives in Chico, and all they have up there is sheep.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that was pretty much my day of my week, because I did napping, Final Fantasy X, some DDR, some F-Zero, and Kill Bill.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Jamie's destroying the kitchen, so I think now's a good time for us to take a break.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to take a break, and we're going to come back, and I don't know, what do you guys want to do when we come back?
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to do a cage match, FU's of the week, you want to talk about more stuff?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do the FU's of the week when we come back, so if you want to send your FU's of the week to me, Sky, in the chat room, and to get into our chat room, go to www.callyvamani.com, click on Orange Lounge, and click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, we're going to play in this break, I think we're going to do something a little bit longer in this break.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's longer and harder.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we're going to do the 80s Do It Right, the electro-extended mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do the long version of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's about five minutes long, but it's a good break song.
[SPEAKER_08]: So after this, we'll be back with the FUs of the Week.
Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura
What you wanna do?
Get into the groove
Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we care what people think of us?
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we want people to kiss our ass?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_18]: Extreme Bobani Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's us, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, we're back.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm eating, sorry, and I'm drinking shitty beer that Jamie's making me drink because she's a bad after-school special bully.
See?
[SPEAKER_08]: See?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Triscuits Reduce Fat and Wheat Thins Reduce Fat, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's those goddamn cookies where they like just totally don't even taste right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like eating reduced fat ice cream.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's ice, you know, ice cream's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're going to eat ice cream, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: The only beer that Orange Lounge Radio endorses would be Guinness, by the way, if you're curious.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say the only beer that we endorse is Guinness.
[SPEAKER_08]: And why do we like Guinness so much, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you ready to do the F.E.s of the week, Jamie?
This is fucked up!
[SPEAKER_23]: This is fucked up!
[SPEAKER_16]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everyone just missed everything I said, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_21]: I was just going to say... I can start all over!
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you want me to start the music over?
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: I said fucking people at Walmart for not taking responsibility for your cart, when you pull out your cart, you need to put it back up.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's really inconsiderate to leave it in people's way.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, and then I said about parents, fuck all of them, well, most of them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Especially if you decide that, you know, oh, I want to have a kid, and then you don't put any thought into the responsibilities involved with, you know, having the kid.
[SPEAKER_21]: You need to take responsibility for yourself.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then, oh my god, the people who blame everybody else for problems that they cause.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, you need to, people need to learn how to take responsibility for themselves, for their own actions.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, you can't believe everything that you see on TV.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can't believe everything that you read.
[SPEAKER_21]: You need to learn how to think for yourself.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so, fuck everybody.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I'm really tired of people.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not everybody.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everybody in this room is in the cool book, except Andrew.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're in the lukewarm book.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck Corona, because it sucks, but it's not as bad as that pale ale that I'm making Rob drink.
[SPEAKER_21]: And...
[SPEAKER_21]: Really, I can't think of anything else.
[SPEAKER_21]: What else was I going off about today, Rob?
[SPEAKER_21]: When I was going off in the parking lot at Walmart?
[SPEAKER_21]: I swear my best step is when I'm not on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck mages in Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm a mage.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fight me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_21]: For kill stealing.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then fuck glass time.
[SPEAKER_21]: For not bringing me the things to kill fast enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: So that I can level faster because I have an archer and I can snipe off the wall.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then... Fuck me for buying stupid things that nobody wants to buy because I was up to 800,000 zeny.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then I bought a bunch of stuff and then no one's buying it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I made poison belts.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm selling them for four times what they're worth.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we're gonna go to Loki, who has to explain his new music.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's in theme with the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It goes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have some choking here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, first FU of the week is gonna go to, um, Stupid Drivers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, more particularly, um, old people.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't like you and you drive too slow.
[SPEAKER_08]: And cutting in front of me and then driving slow really pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you're lucky that, um, I don't have a gun because I would probably do a drive-by as I'm passing you.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, um, since I don't, I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: All I can do is just get angry and give you glaring looks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, um, also, FU2, or, um, fucking neighbors, okay, can't park their truck worth of shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, yesterday...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yesterday, I tried to pull out of our space, and the guys over the line, like, I practically had, like, to squeeze through to get in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, they're getting high out in front of their house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, lucky as stupid people at Golfland, there's some kids that, like,
[SPEAKER_07]: went and jumped up on the pad and started tapping dumb buttons really hard while I was selecting a song and then left.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I didn't even give a shit at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just didn't even look at him, didn't even get angry, pretended it never happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: That pissed him off and that was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, um, fuck you too, uh... Oh shit, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, the fact that I don't have any food in the fridge because I ate it all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, I don't want the cracker.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm eating, uh, potatoes that are kind of going bad, if potatoes can go bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, uh, and then, um, let's see what else.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I don't know, I don't really have too much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you, those stupid DDR pads over at the, uh, theater because they were slippery as hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: I nearly killed myself on those just plain normal songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not anything hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I played anything hard, probably blood all over the pads, which would have been sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: and then finally, um, just, uh, FU Yahoo News because you report on this really dumbest shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, also an FU to British scientists because, um, don't you have anything better to do than to, uh, test to see if a cookie crumbles and shit like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid Brits.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're so dumb.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, it's all about budgeting.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, they start running out of money for funding, so they have to do stupid experiments so that they can keep their budget.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, actually, finally, fuck you to the RIAA.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, more, not really the RIAA, but mainly, um, well, anyways, let me, uh, just give a backstory to this.
[SPEAKER_08]: About a week or two ago, there was, um, an announcement of this new copy protection for this CD, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some loser band put out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably country.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, and, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it got put out, and then people found out they can get past the copy protection by holding down the shift key.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that was pretty dumb of them, now wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, so, you know, a few weeks later, this kid, um, in college, writes on his webpage, basically a kind of like a little, uh, essay or, you know, term paper type thing about, you know, copy protection, and he mentioned on that how you can bypass that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the company didn't like that, that they posted that on his site, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: They're suing him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, Yahoo reports this, reports a story saying directly in that article that this CD can be bypassed by holding shift.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, they're suing him for his term paper that got viewed by a couple hundred people, maybe, whereas Yahoo News gets viewed by millions and millions and millions of people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that a bit ironic?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was at Golfland yesterday, and there was this really cool girl there, and I have no idea who she is, but she wore a shirt that said this shirt was tested on animals.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought she was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's really good at DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, she passed Dropout, which, you know, that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, she was playing, and these asshole drunk people got up next to her and started playing, like, you know, without putting the money in.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were dancing on the pad, like, mocking her and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I fucking hate those people.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, F you to those people.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was really great because... You didn't have them burn out?
[SPEAKER_08]: I couldn't find them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was in the middle of my game, and by the time I was done, they were kind of... Well, this is what happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: is that they got up, as soon as I got off Extreme, they went up on Extreme to start playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she finished her game right as they put the money in the machine, so she kind of watched them for a minute, and then as soon as they went to select a song, the drunk guy was like, and he's trying to pick a song, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: And she just walked up, hit the down arrow several times, and then walked out the door.
[SPEAKER_08]: It decreased the difficulty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, they failed, by the way, if you're listening.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just would have had them done out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, I, Keith wasn't there, and I don't like any of the other employees, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know any of them.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what, I wonder if my trackers would be perfect to go with that single time.
[SPEAKER_08]: What, getting people thrown out?
[SPEAKER_21]: I get someone thrown out every time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not if you go Tuesday or Thursday, there's probably ever people there on Tuesday or Thursday, but, like, Saturday, yeah, you could.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could have gotten those people thrown out.
[SPEAKER_21]: That used to be my hobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, that's pretty much it, I don't really have, uh, F you'd anything else.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to the fact that they decided to split Kill Bill into two parts because I'm impatient and I want to see both parts on Friday.
[SPEAKER_08]: You suck, Miramax.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's hear from the others assembled here in the room.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll start with Andrew.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not chubbed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just do your F yous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, F you to my Linux teacher deciding to take a sick day two days before the final.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's our study day, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why you gotta take a sick day?
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody fisk him.
[SPEAKER_12]: Make him all better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh... F you to... F you to talking about all this, you know, talking about something and just not being able to get your point across.
[SPEAKER_12]: I find it happens to me way too often.
[SPEAKER_12]: Especially when I'm on the show, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not too angsty today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then let's hear from Bradley.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, uh, fuck you to not finding work so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't work hard on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least I had that job, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for that, at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: So fuck you to me for doing it too fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I got it done in like 5.5 hours, and they probably would have paid me for the whole day if I had slowed down a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Took a while to pass this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Being a lazy ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too good at excelling, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like thinking of other ways that I could have done it faster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, fuck you too...
[SPEAKER_06]: My falling credit rating, because I know it's doing that as we speak.
[SPEAKER_06]: And bad things are coming on the horizon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't move really, really fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm getting stuff started paying off.
[SPEAKER_06]: And finding a job, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm talking to the Bank of America, because they changed their credit card billing system.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it takes a day to pay instead of the same day.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it fucked me up last month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, I was lucky for taking so- the guy taking so long to finally tell me that I didn't get the job.
[SPEAKER_06]: Made me wait so long to wait for the inevitable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a huge general situation.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I must persevere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I think that's about everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, then let's hear from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our chatroom's not very angsty tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've only got like three FUs so far.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they just have been having a good week, so go figure.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll start with Baka.
[SPEAKER_08]: Says, my FU of the week is to school.
[SPEAKER_08]: Says, tomorrow is Columbus Day and we don't have it off from school.
[SPEAKER_08]: Says,
[SPEAKER_08]: Since I guess, finally, that our school has decided to be politically correct.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since Columbus never was the first person to discover America, but it was the indigenous Native American peoples.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn school, we should still have a day off.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to be a national holiday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fucking bastard holes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Numbnuts, I have to work tomorrow, so you can damn well go to school.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You should have to go to school during summer too, because I don't get summer off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zodiac Knight says, my fuck you of the week goes to BestBuy.com for fucking up my order, postponing my shipment of Max 2 US for another week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sue.
Sue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mintz would like to say a preemptive F.U.
[SPEAKER_08]: to the week coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be hell for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_08]: to the Bursar's, I hope I said that right, the Bursar's office at my college.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're charging late fees to me for a balance I paid off three weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sue them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Jamie, would you like to repeat that advice?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care if he's in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_08]: The show must go on, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Step Mania 3.9 Alpha 7 or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's out now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't even keep track because the name's getting too long.
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, um, some improvements have been made there, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, uh, I know that they brought back Easy to Dancer support, which, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, um, what else?
[SPEAKER_07]: People are ripping stuff for, um, Max 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, god damn it, if I did it, I would have been dumb by now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, they're still doing it, and Lawrence from DDRUK is kind of heading up the project.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of cool, because he does a really good job on him.
[SPEAKER_08]: What project?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is it a project?
[SPEAKER_08]: If one guy can do it in an hour, what is needing to be a project of it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they're retarded!
[SPEAKER_08]: These people are retarded!
[SPEAKER_08]: They can't fucking just do it, very simple, because it always has to be complicated.
[SPEAKER_07]: They always have to, like, get six people to do it or ten people to do it, and no one knows what they're doing, so that's why it's complicated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just wondering.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why has it always got to be so complicated?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um... Why you gotta go make things so complicated?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, other than that, there's going to be also, obviously, now do your extreme stuff to rip, so... And then, uh...
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, you don't have to pee too much if they're typing on a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_21]: Pardon me for interrupting your thing, but if you have to pee, just pee.
[SPEAKER_21]: We don't care.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pee on the floor.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, also, another thing I found in my little travels on the boards there, they have someone made a...
[SPEAKER_07]: As you know, Stepmania has an unlock system, just in case if you were to ever want to do unlocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they actually made an editor so you can do unlocks with an editor, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else?
[SPEAKER_08]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unlocks are stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're releasing songs for Stepmania, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't do unlocks.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kiss my ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm doing Unlocked for this goddamn hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you're gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, see?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that's RodSteel0014.
[SPEAKER_08]: You only live until you die.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the title.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a porno.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you see that Brad and Irene loaned us the Whore of the Rings 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't gotten to watch it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's who it was, Brad and Irene.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just thinking, Matt doesn't have porno like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tall Matt for those listening.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ice Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, there's really not much going on in the sim world.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been going on like four months now since I played Step Mania, yet for some reason I still download songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course I have it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bandwith Horror.
[SPEAKER_07]: You say that now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would have been a good parody of James Bond if they had just removed a lot of the porn stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it was funny on its own.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then they have people having sex for no reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it just detracts from it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also got six copies of Suicide Circle this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing much going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well, I think we'll take another break then.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, we could talk about the actual news going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll talk about it when we come back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we're going to play, in this break, we're going to play some more stuff from the V-Rare CD.
[SPEAKER_08]: No Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the CD, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to play Freedom by B4U.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we're going to play the original mix of Think You Better D. And then we'll play So In Love Train.
[SPEAKER_08]: So In Love Train.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the soul train.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so we will... The soul in love train.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back after this break and we're going to talk about more news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stick with us here on Orange Lounge Radio.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm waking night and I start reaching for you every single time I wish you'd live a little closer There's nothing else can make me feel the way you do And the phone calls don't provide the warmth it needs in the night that's over Music
Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_08]: Testing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Testing 1-2.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Does this thing work?
[SPEAKER_21]: This thing reads like stereo instructions.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is this on?
[SPEAKER_21]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Broke down ghetto Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: What the f***?
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe it
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a comment from the chatroom during the break that we're not our usual chirpy selves or perky selves tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're kind of in a meh sort of mood.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't feel perky.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we just all need to get laid.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I did.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean... Hi, welcome back.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's such things as doors that need to be shut.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, okay, so if you got laid, Jamie, what's your excuse?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm all tired out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you're spent.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see how it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, me.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're all just spent then.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we're all in a weird mood.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's just the weather or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm plenty happy and perky.
[SPEAKER_08]: The rest of you are being... Are you saying we're bringing this show down?
[SPEAKER_21]: You're bringing me down, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to kiss my ass, woman.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not my job.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's nobody's job.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll get you a puppy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want... Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're disgusting, Andrew.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad nobody can hear that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you wanted to talk about some actual news going on right now?
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish sometimes we were a TV show so you could have seen that throw.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I know what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Kitty Joe says, you guys are cranky.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that makes me think, yeah, I think we're just all on our collective period.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're all on like the same cycle.
[SPEAKER_08]: So right now, never mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last time I checked, Kitty Joe wasn't a psychiatrist.
[SPEAKER_09]: So shut the hell up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, actual news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, first thing would be DDR Extreme, you know, coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, we forgot about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That, you know, that we've been playing the V-Rare songs from and the Consumer Track songs from all night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, we were kind enough to steal them from Bomani Style because we haven't gotten ours yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have PMS.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do that all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, news.
[SPEAKER_09]: It came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't a surprise because we knew it was going to come out for a while now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what's funny about this is that yesterday, the 11th of October, was actually National Coming Out Day.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's kind of funny to keep hearing you say, we knew it was going to come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to come out for a while now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just laughing because I'm thinking of National Coming Out Day and DDR Extreme and how DDR is really gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, but anyways, yeah, there's some songs on there, um, most notably the, um, songs that we knew were there, and people weren't, you know, saying, no, you're wrong, like Max, period, everyone's like saying, no, that's a dumb name for a song, how could that be coming out, meh, well, guess what, it was in there, and so, hi, laugh at you, and then, um, what else, oh, there was, um, a new, um,
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, obviously we found out that the song that everyone liked that we thought was called Overloaded was actually A Stupid Barber, which is a stupid name.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a very stupid name for that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then also, obviously, Undo 12 was in there, which is another one that was rumored to be in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Scorched Moon, which I'm sure we'll hear later, was another one that was in there, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: And see, now, what was interesting about the whole DDR Extreme thing was
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, you had a new remix by 2MB, which was Max Period.
[SPEAKER_09]: And second... And second of all, Max Period... Max Period, which was... Don't interrupt, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, also, you have Max Period, which is, you know, people are kind of hearing that song going, okay, well, is this the end of DDR?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, is this like...
[SPEAKER_09]: What's this mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because obviously when we play it later on, and for those that have already heard it, it's got the part, thank you for playing, and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a really weird song.
[SPEAKER_09]: It kind of gives you the impression that it's over and done with.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing more other than this compilation crap that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, another thing also, which is interesting, kind of unrelated to the whole thing, is that I was looking...
[SPEAKER_09]: I was looking actually in the Max 2 disc, and you know how you can pull up, because every single remix, or every single game that comes out has a full list of all the songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty much a master list of all the songs that are actually going to be in the consumer mixes and arcade mixes and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you'll have this giant master list.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Max 2 USA, it's
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty much a compilation up to DDR Extreme and also with, I believe, the Ultramix, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: But one of the things that I found in there, which was quite interesting, was there's yet another Max remix that's going to be coming out pretty soon, which I have to find my list.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's one of the songs that was in there that was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Maximimizer, which is kind of a weird name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maximimizer, I guess?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maximimizer.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I guess maybe that might be the new Max for Ultramix, maybe?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I don't think that anyone in their right mind would actually name a song Maximimizer other than Kusami.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, that's pretty much all the news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you want to read these songs that you have on your list there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll read them.
[SPEAKER_09]: These are songs that are going to be coming out or were going to come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, for instance, there's some of them that I recognize.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of them, Stronger, by Britney Spears.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was rumored to be in... Euromix 2, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it was in Euromix 2, but it might have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Things That You Do, Hula Radio Mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that was also in Euromix 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tammo was in Euromix 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Funk Boogie, I have no idea what that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Addicted to the Bass, I believe, was Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Disco 2000, I have no idea which one that would be.
[SPEAKER_09]: It Takes More, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I Would Die For You, and For You being number four in U. I don't know what that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I keep thinking of the Garbage song, but that's number one crush.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shake Your Body, which I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't recognize any of these songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: One Step Closer is going to be in the new Dancing Stage Fever, I know that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Freak Like Me might also be in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: When You Look At Me is the Christina Milan song from... It's a song that we have in rotation on the station, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I recognize the song.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's from Euromix, too, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then there's Virtuality, which is another one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell me it's in DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's in DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dizzy, which I don't know what that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Darn, from back here it looked like dirty and I got excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: 2020 Vision, which is, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maximizer, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Saturday Night Live, or Saturday Night Love, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: And those are the new songs to expect to see on some... Clarification, what was the Funk B one?
[SPEAKER_09]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Funk Boogie.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no idea what those are, but I guess they're going to be coming out later on in some release to look for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'd be interesting to look at the DDR Extreme list because you're going to have even more of an update list on that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't wait to hack that disc.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes I can.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to have to wait until Tuesday at least.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's hoping UPS doesn't say, you know, screw you guys and decide to wait until Wednesday or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they deliver the Rockland.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's close.
[SPEAKER_08]: UPS is, you know, fuck me over before.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, yeah, that's all that's new.
[SPEAKER_08]: That and Party Collection coming out, but we already know about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Party Collection coming out at the end of the year, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I want to fork out the money for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to have to have the Butterfly video, I figure, in order for me to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll get it, because that's December, so that's a ways away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: The next one we're going to be waiting for, though, other than Ultra Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, I can't wait for DDR Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is anybody in our little circle going to be getting it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, you're going to have to cash it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll probably have an Xbox by then, because obviously we know that they're probably going to drop the price.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because as you guys know, GameCube dropped to $99.
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation 2 is rumored to be having meetings talking about doing the same thing by next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And supposedly they sent promotional material to Target already that says, $99, PlayStation 2 is
[SPEAKER_08]: So if that happens, Xbox is going to have to.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not going to have a choice.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to have to drop the 99 as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then also those N-Gages, they suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was so excited when Dan got me Puyo Puyo for our N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: And this is me saying that Puyo Puyo sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're sitting here with our, at least we didn't pay for our N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard nothing but awful things about the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, poor Nelly just got beat with a mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say... Hey, that's a good quote right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio, when you taste the suck, you won't feel the pain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to put a link in there for everyone to see.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is me making fake ads.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll do one for Orange Lounge and a bottle of Corona.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, the next one I think we have to really wait for is pretty much Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: Karaoke Revolution is going to be a big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Ultramix is going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: The interesting thing about Ultramix is because of these song packs, we'll be talking about Ultramix three months from now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, they released another song pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually kind of looking, you know, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually really want an Xbox all of a sudden because I want Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want a hacked Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox Live is the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want a hacked Xbox so I can download games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I hate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is like me admitting I like Apolitary Song and admitting I like Bag on the Air.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need a hacked Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know what the difference is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was just going to go to GameStop and get a refurbished one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the difference of it, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: We take an Xbox, we have someone hack it for us, you put in a 120 gig hard drive in there, and then you download games for free, baby.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the worst Austin Powers impression I've ever seen in my life.
[SPEAKER_08]: That wasn't a pressure.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you went like, yeah, baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had to see it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm throwing this mic around badly.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, the thing that's going to be real interesting about DDRXbox is the sucky pads.
[SPEAKER_12]: Since we can't plug in, like, ignition, I don't think they make a PlayStation do Xbox converters.
[SPEAKER_11]: They do?
[SPEAKER_11]: Good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I might get an Xbox for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then again, I haven't gotten...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm scared to play Xbox Live with DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can tell you right now my name will not be Sky on there because I don't want you people finding me and seeing how bad I really do suck at DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to have some other name on DDR Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll use a disguised voice whenever I talk on the headset.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be like, I'll use my British accent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm going to play DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a jolly good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crikey.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll be me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um, yeah, I don't want to like the Xbox, but I'm going to have to.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I really want to play PSO on the Xbox, because somebody left their GameCube PSO for their Xbox PSO.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's because we already had the Xbox Live account.
[SPEAKER_21]: For some reason, they closed my GameCube account, so I just decided that I would play on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maren says she's going to be, if you see a Sky OLR on DDRXbox, that's Maren.
[SPEAKER_08]: The DDRXbox screens look very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually kind of, I'm excited about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're arrows.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have a picture for it, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's in the GameStop promo books.
[SPEAKER_21]: and it's got like all sorts of characters on there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll bring it next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, the cover of DDR Ultramix is like a big DDR character orgy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's arrows and music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let it stick to arrows and music.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty arrows and pretty music.
All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we'll take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then when we come back, we'll do the cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because our chat room is demanding a cage match, so we will have to give it to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this break, I think we will finally play the max period.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you guys have been dying to hear it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll hear that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to hear a stupid barber.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we'll play Think You Better D, the original mix, because I fucked up last time and I actually played I Need You instead.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to actually hear the original mix of Think You Better D this break.
[SPEAKER_08]: So when we come back, we'll do the cage match and talk about more stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: More news, more fun, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
DarkSakura
Thank you for watching!
Outro Music
[SPEAKER_16]: Come on baby, won't you be my girl?
[SPEAKER_16]: Come on girl, let me rock your world Come on baby, won't you be my girl?
Come on girl, let me rock your world Look around, look around, look around now The most important thing
[SPEAKER_22]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_22]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_22]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, Max Resurrection and Neomax suck, and they will never be in DDR, and so stop asking, stop wanting, get over it.
[SPEAKER_08]: When real music gets made, it will be put in the DDR, not this crappy fan-made shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, no one could hear that, you're not mic'd.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said I laughed out so you could hear me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So a little bit of the discussion from commercial break carrying over to the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: You do that again, I'm going to shove that ferret so far up your ass that you'll be pooping ferret noises.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's so easy and never fails to be entertaining.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, won't Max Resurrection and Neo Max be in your sim on your big arcade machine?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll purposely be leaving them out?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have like 27 max remixes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really don't need them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna eliminate it down to like three or four.
[SPEAKER_08]: But will the Legend of Trance be in there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty long, so of course it's gonna be in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's mine!
[SPEAKER_08]: Mine was better anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I do think Legend of Trance was better than the other songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neomax is okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like they sat there all cool because they're doing like piano noises.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just sounds like MIDI.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like StarMine, you know, when that was made, that was actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, if you get like Onokin, man, to do a remix of like Max 300 or something, or even The Legend of Max, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, I mean, obviously, what we're going to see here in the cage match, Onokin did my pick for the cage match last week, and he made Paranoia pretty kick-ass, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd like to see him take on Mac, so, well, try that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, during the commercial break, in the chat room I was talking about, I was poking fun at one of our people in the chat room who's having some trouble typing tonight because they're missing some keys, and I was suggesting some Mavis Beacon, and I was just thinking about, like, how hot Mavis Beacon is, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's rawr.
[SPEAKER_08]: Has anyone ever seen Mavis?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many versions of Mavis Beacon teaches typing have we had?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're on like version 15 I think I saw.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: I never ever took any typing classes ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me neither.
[SPEAKER_08]: I learned how to type on my Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_21]: I learned how to type out of the sense of competition with my roommate.
[SPEAKER_21]: My roommate at the time was a secretary and she could type really fast.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, out of a whole sense of competition and wanting to keep up with people in chat rooms, I can now type at my best at 90 words a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what Iguana Girl and I used to do when we worked together.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'd have little competitions, just friendly banter to see who could do more issues in an hour type thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were the two best workers in that whole fucking building.
[SPEAKER_21]: Even when I'm under stress, I can still type at 70 to 80.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I type with perfect grammar.
[SPEAKER_08]: I suggest if you want to learn how to type, you buy yourself a Commodore 64, because those computers are the shit, and they have the computer inside the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_08]: How cool is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can play Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, shall we get into tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_20]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last week, in the Orange Lounge Radio cage match,
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki's pick won, and he picked a remix of Paranoia called P8107 by, who is it again?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ono Ken, and that was the winner.
[SPEAKER_08]: It won in a pretty overwhelming response by the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: The chatroom really, really liked it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So will they like it two weeks in a row?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're only going to play a clip for you guys because it won last week, but nevertheless, you can vote for it tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's song number one, the winner from last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is P8107.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember to vote for the winner in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: You must be in our chatroom, www.calibermani.com, C-A-L-I-B-E-M-A-N-I.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Click on Orange Lounge and click on Chats.
[SPEAKER_08]: While you're there, visit the Naoki Boards of Randomness, because our forums are there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: A clip of last week's winner, P8107.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, hope you enjoyed that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was P8107, a little clip of last week's winner, song number one you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, what is your pick for tonight?
[SPEAKER_21]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_21]: What did I pick?
[SPEAKER_08]: Your song is a group called Turbo Black Cat.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's one I got from Justin.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a remix of Black Cat by Turbo.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's in Korean.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Song number two tonight you can vote for.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Jamie's pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you get to hear the whole thing because it's a new pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Black Cat, the history remix by a group called Turbo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy.
It's a dream.
Thanks for watching!
You're cute, my black cat, your red ribbon looks great on you
DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, song number two, Turbo with Black Cat, the History Remix.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm being told that was the pick in Tourney Mix 4, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, I don't know, because I don't keep up with Tourney Mix, and I don't play Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, who cares?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's about the song, not about the step file.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Jamie, would you care to rank your own pick?
[SPEAKER_21]: Eh, I'd give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, it actually wasn't my first pick.
[SPEAKER_21]: When I went to go check how long it was, it was 12 minutes, and I can't edit it down that small, so this was my next pick, and it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_21]: And one of these days, though, I am going to bring him to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: My thoughts are that's the gayest Pump It Up song ever, and it gets a 6.9.
[SPEAKER_09]: I never did like Black Cat.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was good up to when The Sims kicked in, then it just started reminding me of, like, We Like to Party by the Venga Boys.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the Venga Boys are, like, so 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, uh, I give it a... I give it an 8, because it was alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was catchy, but I ignored most of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Bradley, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: You killed my butt.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give it an eight.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, an eight from Bradley.
[SPEAKER_08]: Andrew.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've heard better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe a six.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honesty, best policy, put the ferret down.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So a six from 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, the ferret.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Our opinions don't mean shit because it's your votes that ultimately decide it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, it's like American Idol like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here's my pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is an artist I actually put in the cage match like four weeks ago, I think.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can't pick an... Oh, artist.
[SPEAKER_08]: An artist that I put in the cage match like four weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I like this song like three times more than the song that I put in originally.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it's
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an old favorite family of mine to be put in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Danny Minow tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the song is All I Want to Do.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's not the Sheryl Crow song.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's even better.
[SPEAKER_08]: So enjoy this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is song number three.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my God, I saw a Danny Minow video at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_21]: She's such a slut.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I love her.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Danny Minow with All I Want to Do, my pick for tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy.
I wanna do, I wanna do without you I wanna do, I wanna do
Thanks for watching!
Take a look inside my heart Tell me what you think you see I may not be the innocent girl that you wanted me to
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that was song number three, Danny Minow with All I Wanna Do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_21]: Seven.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's too repetitive.
[SPEAKER_21]: And she's a slut.
[SPEAKER_08]: I give it a ten.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the best song ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: I give it a seven because I've heard that song way too many times because you play it all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bradley?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give it a six point five.
[SPEAKER_12]: After hearing Angel play it on her radio show all the time, it still doesn't get old.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's still pretty damn good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, remember, our votes don't mean shit, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's your votes that count, so place vote now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm sorry, we actually have to recap before we place vote now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Song number one you can vote for tonight, last week's winner, P8107.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, song number two you can vote for, Turbo with Black Cat, the History remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and song number three you can vote for tonight is Danny Minow with All I Wanna Do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Place votes now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send those votes to private message to Sky in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so we'll tally those votes in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, more witty banter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought I'd read this story for you guys and get your thought on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a story coming from BoycottRIAA.com.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, that page.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of our favorite websites.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the headline.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kazaa plans to end free music.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was sent by one of our chatroom loyalists.
[SPEAKER_08]: Charmin Networks, like toilet paper.
[SPEAKER_08]: Charmin Networks appears to have finally crossed the line with a bid to get into bed with the big five record labels in the RIAA.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kazaa backs plans that could spell an end to the days of free music is the headline in the October 10th edition of Australia's The Age.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Australia is, you'll recall, the place Kazaa calls home.
[SPEAKER_08]: The world's most popular song swapping network, Kazaa, has thrown its weight behind a plan to start billing song swappers for their music downloads, says the article.
[SPEAKER_08]: The proposal, which could finally end the days of the free lunch for millions of music fans, has been put to big U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: record labels at the same time as the new legitimate version of the former file swapping giant Napster is launched in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: The idea is to phase in a billing mechanism for peer-to-peer networks, such as Kazaa and Morpheus, that allow users to copy music directly from each other's hard drives, she states.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_21]: First of all, they have no real way to track something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: First of all, this is pretty much just like Napster was, where they're focusing just on Napster or just on Kazaa.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't they realize that people have already left the BitTorrent or WinMX or something like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're just going to drop ship on one and go to another sharing service like WinMX or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Trust me, for everyone that comes up or converts over to pay-only, you're going to have five more free ones pop up in its place.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing they can do to stop it.
[SPEAKER_09]: This isn't even a victory on their part.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is just another company...
[SPEAKER_09]: that they're going to try to create that's going to go under super fast, just like Napster did.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, alright, keep trying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what do you think, 23rd Magus?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, uh, sure, sure, let Kazaa go to pay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm still going to use Kazaa Light, still going to go on the same network, still going to get the same shit for free, they can't track me, more power to them, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_12]: and the crowd goes silent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_21]: First of all, I don't use WinMX because it's shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it actually has... I've known people, though, who through WinMX have had credit cards stolen off of their computer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, so don't use WinMX.
[SPEAKER_21]: I deleted that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I use WinMX.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, yeah, but a friend of mine who is very secure with the systems... It's not the only person who this has happened to.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, if you have PayPal...
[SPEAKER_21]: It broke into a PayPal account that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I don't have PayPal save my credit card information.
[SPEAKER_21]: But even so, get that crap off your computer.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not good for it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I have a feeling that's how I lost my last hard drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not really using it anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I only use it occasionally.
[SPEAKER_08]: BitTorrent is really my main thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm still backing Kazaa+++.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bank has auto protection against all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because it doesn't log IPs.
[SPEAKER_21]: It doesn't log your username.
[SPEAKER_21]: It completely changed mine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it blocks port 80.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, it keeps you protected.
[SPEAKER_21]: It keeps you anonymous.
[SPEAKER_21]: And there can be multiple anonymous at Kazaa.whatever users logged in.
[SPEAKER_21]: It does not keep a track of it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And on top of that, if you actually have it do not link to your files, nobody else can download from you.
[SPEAKER_21]: so they have no way of tracking, no way of knowing what's there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I always thought Kazaa was stupid anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've never used it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate Kazaa.
[SPEAKER_21]: The new Kazaa is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_21]: The Kazaa Plus, it's so, it's absolutely easy.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I downloaded, and on top of that they've even tweaked the program now.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have had 17 downloads going at one time on Kazaa Plus Plus Plus.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_21]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still a big BitTorrent fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's the way.
[SPEAKER_21]: I use BitTorrent for my anime.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what kind of
[SPEAKER_08]: And actually, it doesn't even have to be webpages, because you can distribute torrents amongst...
[SPEAKER_09]: IRC Chatrooms.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing they're going to be able to do with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're fucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not going to be able to do anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: They better be back in iTunes, and they better do it fast, because that's the only... All I've got to say is, all they're doing is they're just fucking stirring up the hornet's nest.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're making things worse.
[SPEAKER_08]: People are getting pissed, and they're just going to say, fuck you, instead of downloading the one song I want, now I'm going to download the whole goddamn CD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kitty...
[SPEAKER_12]: Caza Light does not have spyware in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: The original Caza used to.
[SPEAKER_12]: They claim now that it never did.
[SPEAKER_12]: It did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it is bullshit.
[SPEAKER_08]: It did.
[SPEAKER_12]: It had massive spyware.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the other thing that I attribute to the loss of my last hard drive over, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Adware is our friend.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, there's a better program than that.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's called Adware Search and Destroy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, it hunts down any, not just that, but like basic installers, like for Bonzi Buddy or whatever, and gets them off of your computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fucking Gator.
[SPEAKER_21]: I, uh, with the, I had, actually, um, also WinMX does install spyware on your computer, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because after, after I was using WinMX, I went and checked, and I had tons of spyware on my computer just from that program.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, I actually checked about two months after using Kazaa++ and ran the spyware check and there was nothing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Other than what would have, you know, come through like a webpage.
[SPEAKER_21]: But really, it's nothing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hardly anything.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like maybe 10 files as opposed to the 200 and something before with the old Kazaa.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll tell you one reason I actually really like WinMxo is that it's the song sharing program of choice in Asia.
[SPEAKER_08]: So a lot of good Asian, Korean, Japanese, Chinese stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just... Kazaa, I hate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate Kazaa.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that's just me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Want to hear tonight's cage match winner?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a squeaker tonight, boys and girls, by one stinking vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tonight's winner of the cage match by one stinking vote was the one, the only...
[SPEAKER_08]: P8107 That was a close one tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Votes were pretty much spread all out tonight, which usually doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well, Jamie and I will try again next week to dethrone P8101, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: P8696969 Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have to think three weeks in advance for...
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, you're going to... Because I'm actually going to be gone the Sunday beforehand.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to have your work cut out for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because of family deals.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie's going to be gone for three weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are we going to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to pre-tape pump up the volume though, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I might record Tuesday's show and then repeat it while I'm out of town.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, the third...
[SPEAKER_21]: on November 3rd.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm actually taking Monday so I can do my show before I go to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we'll do a show swap.
[SPEAKER_21]: So there's only going to be two weeks where it'll be old material.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm also going to be doing a special thing that I'm doing as a favor.
[SPEAKER_21]: More on that later.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it'll be replayed while I'm out of town.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's really about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of our spinoff shows, Monday nights on Orange Launch Radio is Vanilla Sky where we talk about
[SPEAKER_08]: I have an idea for Loki What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: You should do one with the Sierra games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember the old Sierra RPGs?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those were the shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so there.
[SPEAKER_08]: King's Quest, Police Quest, Leisure Suit Larry, Space Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else was I thinking?
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming November again, LiveWire on Wednesdays.
[SPEAKER_09]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_08]: One Saturday a month coming in 2004.
[SPEAKER_08]: With prizes.
[SPEAKER_08]: With actual prizes.
[SPEAKER_08]: For our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, for chatroom and in-studio players.
[SPEAKER_08]: One winner each, so it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be so exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So pretty much imagine Starcade with all the video game playing, with a ton of trivia thrown in, that's what you got.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a very complex show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to do a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen the rules for this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's insane.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I win.
[SPEAKER_08]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, would you like to plug what's on Tuesday nights on this station?
[SPEAKER_08]: A cookie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Cookies of doom-doom.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's my show.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a Triska eating show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Go ahead, Bob, say something and I'll let you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Tuesday nights on Orange Lounge Radio at 7 o'clock is the Pump Up the Volume pre-show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then at 7.30 is... It's Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_21]: Which is where nobody requests anything because you're all... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nobody ever requests anything on my show, so I'm like, okay, why am I doing this?
[SPEAKER_21]: So...
[SPEAKER_21]: It's basically where you sit for three hours and listen to whatever I feel like playing for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you were in our chat room and requesting songs and I would play them, hello.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's over at 10.30.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's, yeah, it's some of the volume.
[SPEAKER_21]: My fun little show.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think what we're going to do, we're going to take a quick break and then we're going to come back and...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, we're going to fill 45 minutes somehow with something we'll think is something creative during this break.
[SPEAKER_08]: List list or match game?
[SPEAKER_08]: List list or match game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't done a list list in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to do a list list?
[SPEAKER_08]: What subject do we want to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know we never did do the top ten names for Comcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I bet for the top three cars you'll never see an initial D game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't like cars.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't like initial D.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, we'll think of something.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you guys want to suggest a listless topic, we'll be listening for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this break, we're going to hear Sean the Horny Master with Scorching Moon.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's another Dance Revolution EX consumer track.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we're going to hear a trance remix of music.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know where this came from.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you know where this came from?
[SPEAKER_08]: The trance remix of music on your computer?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it came from...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a transversion of music, it's the Madonna song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Play a... I think it's a Night In Motion remix one in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that next?
Here, I'll pick something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beatmania does Outphase, Sink Into Trance remix.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's break away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that any good?
[SPEAKER_08]: How about... We could play something from the Nightstyle soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll play your song from last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: What song was that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, the Boom Boom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell us about this mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a remix of Enigma because their newest album sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll be back after this little break.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do Sean the Horny Master and Boom Boom.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we decided to say screw listless, and we're going to do the match game instead.
[SPEAKER_08]: So in order to do match game, I need some contestants.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here's tonight's qualifying question.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first two people in our chat room to send me a private message with the answer to this question will be playing in tonight's Orange Launch Radio match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to ask you a question from Monday's episode of Vanilla Sky, Video Game Trivia to Bad Music.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the question.
[SPEAKER_08]: First two people to send me the correct answer will play match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was the name of the game put out by Universal, which was similar to Dig Dug, but the object was to collect cherries or kill all the monsters, including ones marked E, X, T, R, and A with your Powerball?
[SPEAKER_08]: The category, just to help you out for last week's Vanilla Sky video game trivia on Bad Music, was 80s video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more time.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was the name of the game put out by Universal, which was similar to Dig Dug,
[SPEAKER_08]: But the object was to collect cherries or kill all the monsters, including ones marked EXTRNA with your Powerball.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, while we get some answers for that, we're going to play another Loki remix here because they're cool and people like them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to hear the Big Thunder Mountain mix of Stoic again, so we're going to play that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll be back while we get our qualifying contestants for match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Coming back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, hello, we're back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio here.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's time, ladies and gentlemen, to play the Bomani Match Game.
[SPEAKER_08]: How exciting is that, everybody?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to explain the rules because we have some new contestants tonight who we haven't had play before.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bet you want to know who those contestants are, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell us, Rob, tell us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, in tonight's Bomani Match Game, we have Zodiac Knight is contestant number one.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a buddy of mine from LiveJournal, so I'm excited to see that he got the correct answer, which was Mr. Do.
[SPEAKER_08]: We all knew that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last week, I tell ya, I don't think any of them got it right.
[SPEAKER_08]: None of the people here got it right that Mr. Do was a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that was the game with the cherries and the EXTRA monsters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Contestant number two tonight is AZN Buddy Paul.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_08]: He got Mr. Dew, and he was second.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just in case, we have a standby as well, if one of them should drop.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: The way the Monty Match Game works is that I'm going to ask a question, and somewhere in that question is a blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: For instance, the question could be, Arcadian42 went to the store and decided to buy some blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: So all of our celebrities here in the room will write down what they think should be in the blank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Propel!
[SPEAKER_08]: So Propel would be the answer that Jamie went right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your job is to send me the answer of a private message that you think is going to match with the most celebrities.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm supposed to kick nose styling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why would I kick nose styling, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Change your name!
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so I hope the contestants have an understanding of the rules, yes?
[SPEAKER_08]: You just send in what you think we're going to say for the blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then for every match, you get a point.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for every non-match, you get ridiculed horrendously by all of us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Introducing tonight's celebrities.
[SPEAKER_08]: Celebrity number one is DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: And her latest movie out in theaters now is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck You, Bitch, Die.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Celebrity number two tonight is Bradley, Arcadian42, and he is here tonight to promote?
[SPEAKER_08]: My world tour event of sitting in front of people and doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Celebrity number three tonight is the one and only Loki, and he's here tonight to promote hatred.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you here to promote tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hatred.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Contestant.
[SPEAKER_08]: Iraqi suicide, baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just a hint, contestants, the more you listen to this show and the more inside jokes you know, the more points you will get.
[SPEAKER_08]: Celebrity number four tonight is 23rd Magus, who's here tonight to promote my ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please leave.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: And celebrity number five tonight is the biggest celebrity of them all, it's me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm here to promote... Your big ego.
[SPEAKER_08]: My big ego.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm here tonight to promote safe sex for all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, yes, AZM Buddy Paul sends to me over five months and says, so it's just like the TV show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's just like the TV show, except we don't want to get sued, so it has a different name.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's four questions tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to write five, but I got lazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here's question number one tonight, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky, oh, that's me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky was sad to watch $80 go bye-bye for DDR Extreme to be sent to his house.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn!
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky exclaimed.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's $80 I could have spent on blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go ahead and send me your answers over private message, contestants.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was sad to watch $80 go by.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you're in the chat room, help our contestants.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give some answers that Zodiac Knight and ASEAN buddy Paul can use.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just say them out loud in the chat room and maybe they'll take your hint.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky was sad to watch $80 go bye-bye for DDR Extreme to be sent to his house.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn, Rob exclaimed, that's $80 I could have spent on blank.
[SPEAKER_21]: By the way, someone is spelled with an O and an E. It's S-O-M-E-O-N-E.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Socks is spelled S-U-C-K-S.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie Summers teaches typing, version 2, now available in stores.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, it's called teaches how to spell.
[SPEAKER_21]: Use the spell checker if you don't know how.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have one contestant... I am the Grammar Avenger!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm waiting on one other one.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the celebrities ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are all ready?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I'm just waiting on one contestant.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just waiting on one contestant here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, suck someone.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm interacting with the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got both answers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, you guys ready?
[SPEAKER_21]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ding dong, man.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ding dong.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hear what Zodiac Knight had to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was sad to watch $80 go bye-bye for DDR Extreme to be sent to his house.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn, Rob exclaimed.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's $80 I could have spent on, Zodiac Knight says, male prostitutes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Male Prostitutes AZM Buddy Paul says, Damn, that's $80 Skye could have spent on food Are you saying I'm fat?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we have male prostitutes and we have food We'll start with Andrew, what's your answer?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's $80 he could have spent on?
[SPEAKER_08]: Chocolate martinis and F-Zero Chocolate martinis and F-Zero Good answer, good answer, but not a match
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, that's $80 he could have spent on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Manhorse.
[SPEAKER_08]: Manhorse, that's a match with Zodiac Knight.
[SPEAKER_08]: One point for Zodiac Knight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the score is now one to nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bradley, you've used it for 320 quarters to gamble with.
[SPEAKER_08]: 320 quarters to gamble with.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very good answer, but unfortunately not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: My answer, and this would be the correct answer, by the way,
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn, that's $80 I could have spent on booze.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, close to a match with food, I don't think the judges rule that a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Propel.
[SPEAKER_08]: $80 I could have spent on Propel?
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, does that count as food?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't think it does either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because you drink it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: The score is now 1-0.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zodiac Knight has one point, and AZM Buddy Paul has no points.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's okay, because here's his chance to catch up.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: Question number two.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie left to go to Alabama for three weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: While she was gone, her evil little friends at Orange Lounge Radio decided to leave her a surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: When Jamie got home, she exclaimed as she walked through the door...
[SPEAKER_08]: God damn it, who covered my house in blank?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie left to go to Alabama for three weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: While she was gone, her evil little friends at Orange Lounge Radio decided to leave her a surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: When Jamie got home, she exclaimed as she walked through the door, God damn it, who covered my house in blank?
Alright, just waiting on one contestant here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie left to go to Alabama for three weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: When she was gone, her evil little friends at Orange Lounge Radio decided to leave her a surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: When Jamie got home, she exclaimed as she walked through the door, God damn it, who covered my house in blank?
[SPEAKER_08]: All the celebrities ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll start with AZM Buddy Paul, who's behind right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie left to go to Alabama three weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: When she was gone, her friends at Orange Lounge Radio decided to leave her a surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: When she got home, she exclaimed as she walked through the door, God damn it, who covered my house in... AZM Buddy Paul says, Eurobeat posters!
[SPEAKER_08]: That is evil.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zodiac Knight says, God damn it, who covered my house in toilet paper?
[SPEAKER_08]: Traditional.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unimaginative, but traditional.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hear what the celebrities thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Andrew, God damn it, who covered my house in... Engage swag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Engage swag.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki...
[SPEAKER_08]: Goddammit, who covered my house in Cookies of the Suck Cookies of the Suck Wow, that would be horrible That would be a horrible, horrible fate indeed Bradley says, goddammit, who covered my house in Dead, stinking, fetid, rotted RVGL children Ewww, that's almost as bad as mine Eww, gross Alright My answer was, goddammit, who covered my house in Politary Albums
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, not a match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Mine was human kidneys brought on the New Orleans Blight Market Internet website to remind me of home.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, I remember my urban legends.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, very close, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ready for question number three?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki...
[SPEAKER_08]: did not take a woodshop safety class before starting work on his Bomani cabinet.
[SPEAKER_08]: The cast of Orange Lounge Radio was shocked and awed when they heard a loud drilling sound and then Matt exclaimed from the work area, Sweet Jesus, I just cut off my blank!
[SPEAKER_08]: Matt did not take a woodshop safety class before starting work on his Bomani cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: If none of them get it, then they have to be released.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, sweet Jesus, I just cut off my blank.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're waiting on our contestants.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, I'm waiting on one more contestant here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are all the celebrities ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: Almost, just about.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to drink some more of this crappy beer right here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mmm, gross.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, are all the celebrities ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have both contestants.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Zodiac Knights Ahead won nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And his answer is, to this question...
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki did not take a woodshop safety class before starting work on his Bomani cabinet.
[SPEAKER_08]: The cast of Orange Lounge Radio was shocked and awed when they heard a loud drilling sound and then Matt exclaimed from the work area, Sweet Jesus, I just cut off my... Zodiac Knight says, Penis!
[SPEAKER_08]: I just cut off my penis.
[SPEAKER_08]: AZM Buddy Paul says, Sweet Jesus, I just cut off my feet.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Feet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's hear what the celebrities have to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have penis, and we have feet.
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus, sweet Jesus, I just cut off my... Gonads.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gonads!
[SPEAKER_08]: Point.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gonads and stripes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I... Gonads would be your balls, not your penis.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's in the area, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Judges say overruled, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's ahead anyway, he doesn't need the pity point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, sweet Jesus, you just cut off your...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is like four or five inside jokes back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big black cock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that would be a match with penis.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: So Zodiac Knight now has... I thought it was big black after you cut it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zodiac Knight now has two points.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: On to Bradley.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sweet Jesus, I just cut off my... Newly soldered wires.
There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: A nice G-rated answer from Bradley.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Newly soldered wires.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: A nice clean answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: My answer is Sweet Jesus.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just cut off my nipple just like in Ichi the Killer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sweet Jesus, Loki just cut off his foot.
[SPEAKER_21]: I drilled myself in the foot.
[SPEAKER_21]: How did I do that?
[SPEAKER_21]: I need that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent answer and a match for AZM Buddy Paul.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think close enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: So AZM Buddy Paul on the board with a point.
[SPEAKER_21]: Play clip now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play clip now?
[SPEAKER_08]: If I can find the clip, I'd be glad to play it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Play clip for the obvious.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm very surprised that I was the only one that went for the obvious one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that was excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: You did an excellent job, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: For those that missed it, you guys, by the way, here you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: God damn!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ow, my foot!
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did I shoot myself in my foot?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it hurts so bad!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, my foot!
[SPEAKER_03]: I need that for walking!
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the score is now two points for Zodiac Knight and one point for AZM Buddy Paul.
[SPEAKER_21]: I finished the shitty Corona, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the last question, and it's AZM Buddy Paul's last chance to catch up, or Zodiac Knight's big chance to make this lead even bigger, to cement the win.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I may have done this question before.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll have to stop me if I have.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 23rd Magus was going to show off his new leet freestyle at the next NorCal tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said, hey guys, I have this leet new move called the blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus was going to show off his new leet freestyle at the next NorCal DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said, hey guys, I have this new leet move called the blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: As our celebrities furiously write down their answers as well as the contestants.
Alright, I'm just waiting on our contestants to send the answers and I think the celebrities are still thinking some of them.
Yes?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, are celebrities all done with their answers?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'm just waiting on the contestants here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'm just waiting on one more contestant here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's hear.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hear AZM Buddy Paul first, since he's the one that's got to catch up.
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus is going to show off his new leet freestyle at the next NorCal DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said, hey guys, I have this leet new move I call the, AZM Buddy Paul says, blow!
[SPEAKER_03]: Blow me!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Marin's answer in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: She says, the Portuguese joke book.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zodiac Knight says, hey guys, I have this leet new move I call the boo boo kitty fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hear from the 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus, you have this leet new move and what do you call it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the
[SPEAKER_12]: My new move is the met yourself on the bar, curl into a field position, twitch twice, and die.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hear from Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus has this leet new freestyle called the Dirty Sanchez.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bradley...
[SPEAKER_06]: 23rd Magus has this new move and it's called the... Run out the door and spare the people watching move.
[SPEAKER_06]: Run out the door and spare the people watching move.
[SPEAKER_21]: I instantly guarantee him a win.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Close.
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus has a new move and I said it's called the white guy being poked with a cattle prod.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought that's how he danced anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Jamie, 23 Magus has a brand new elite freestyle move, and it's called the... The seppuku.
[SPEAKER_21]: He joined the suicide circle just to make it work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good answer, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, our final score is... Drumroll, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zodiac Knight, with two points, wins!
[SPEAKER_21]: That's like the most points anyone's ever scored.
[SPEAKER_08]: Asian Buddy Paul with one point, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think two points is like the record.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_08]: What'd you get?
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you got two?
[SPEAKER_08]: So now you tied with 23rd Magus, who played a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what does Zodiac Knight get for winning?
[SPEAKER_20]: Nothing!
[SPEAKER_20]: Absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: We get to insult you as the winner.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could have done better than two points.
[SPEAKER_08]: You stink.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're horrible at the money match game.
[SPEAKER_21]: You win ferret sex.
[SPEAKER_06]: We give you our everlasting scorn and disdain.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's what you win.
[SPEAKER_21]: I burped.
[SPEAKER_08]: You win one free coupon, good for going out and getting a life.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can get him some Suck cookies.
[SPEAKER_21]: You win the cookies of Suck, except Andrew ate them all.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what does AZM Buddy Paul win if they run her up?
[SPEAKER_21]: Air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, you win the air around you to breathe and enjoy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Jamie won't come take it away from you, because you know that if you were somebody else, she would run in the room and go, just to take away your air.
[SPEAKER_08]: So enjoy as the runner-up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Zodiac Knight is very happy because he loves ferret sex, and he's very happy he won it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, thank you guys for playing in tonight's Bomani match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was fun!
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to do that again sometime.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's another bit we can drive into the ground.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or we'll take a slow break, I don't know what we're going to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: But when we come back, we're going to be on our way to wrapping up the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we'll do some quick Ask Orange Lounge, if there's anything you guys want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we'll be talking about some good movies we like or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: After this, I'm going to play... I'm going to play... I'm going to play Max 300.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why, but I feel... Actually, I'm going to play...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm going to play Max 300.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you want to hear?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that from?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have the original soundtrack on my computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Twinby?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do Twinby.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can play something else from Guitar Freeze for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll be back after Twin... If I can even find Twinby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll be back after some music.
Thanks for watching!
One, two, three, four!
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_08]: What will we learn this week on Ask Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's the whitest in the room?
[SPEAKER_08]: I bet you wanted to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me tell you, it's Andrew and Baia, long shot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our first question for Ask Orange Lounge comes from AZN Buddy Paul, who wants to know, who would Matt do...
[SPEAKER_08]: If he did lose his big black cock, I'm sorry, what would Matt, not who would, what would Matt do if he lost his big black cock?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, can I answer?
[SPEAKER_08]: What would you do if you lost your big black cock?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I guess I'd just have to use my reserve big white cock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, excellent, excellent question.
[SPEAKER_08]: AsianBuddyPaul would also like to know, would any of the Orange Lounge Radio staff enter Iron Chef?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd be first in line.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be fucking great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Today's secret ingredient is microwave!
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it tastes really good if you add a nice butter to it, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, I would, yeah, I'd enter.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd be Iron Chef's superfood, so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, the thing is, though, is that I could probably enter Iron Chef and fake my way through it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just because I used to watch all these cooking shows with my grandmother, like the Galloping Gourmet.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, I can cook really good, I just don't... I'm not saying that I'm as good as those guys, but I'd enter that Iron Chef, just to be funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: What would be the secret ingredient you'd secretly wish for?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, instant rice.
[SPEAKER_21]: My secret ingredient would be chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maren says propel.
[SPEAKER_21]: Propel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cooking with propel.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, I bet that berry-flavored papel steamed rice would be good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or lemon-flavored.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next question we have is from, I hope I pronounced this right.
[SPEAKER_08]: My apologies if I didn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okyun, O-K-Y-U-N, Okyun, Okyun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okyun would like to know, how are you?
[SPEAKER_21]: How and you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm super, thanks for asking.
[SPEAKER_21]: How am I what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just how are you, that's the question.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, how are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anybody else care to tell how you are?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, how are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never really tried eating myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I'd be a little bit chewy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bit chewy, kind of gristle, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you marinated me just right, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd be damn good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Teriyaki me would be good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I, I, it was, it was Okion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okion.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how I'm supposed to pronounce it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever happened to the fava beans and the nice Chianti?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_21]: God damn, no movie references.
[SPEAKER_08]: I, I got the reference.
[SPEAKER_21]: It puts the lotion on its skin.
[SPEAKER_21]: My God.
[SPEAKER_21]: You picked that up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can't have been much effort.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have something you want to say, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't want to say anything.
[SPEAKER_21]: Go to the next question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pip would like to know, wasn't Pip the kid on South Park that was a porn kid?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, I'm Pip.
[SPEAKER_21]: When do I get to helmet?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do American PS2s not play Japanese DDR games?
[SPEAKER_21]: What kind of a dumb question is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to mod my PS2, even if it means I would get the better DDR mixes.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's country lockout.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's just country lockout.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they do it for the market.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe the question is deeper than it sounds.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why does Sony feel the need to lock out the PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_21]: The same way they do for all games and have since the beginning of video game history.
[SPEAKER_02]: But why should they have to do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why lock us out of the Japanese game?
[SPEAKER_21]: Market share.
[SPEAKER_21]: Domestic versus foreign markets.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's assy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's assy and I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And copyrights.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know...
[SPEAKER_21]: True that with the Nintendo all it was was finding an old copy of Garamite and, you know, putting it on your Game Genie.
[SPEAKER_21]: But still, you know, they've had lockouts since the, I think the Master System had lockouts because of the PIN cards.
[SPEAKER_21]: The PC Engine, you can't even find a good converter to play Japanese Hu cards on a TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, however, the games did not have country lockout.
[SPEAKER_21]: The CDs did not, but it was new technology.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it doesn't really matter anymore anyway, because we do have all these fancy ways of getting around the country lockout.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know how I got around it?
[SPEAKER_08]: How?
[SPEAKER_21]: I bought a JPS2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I held the shift key while putting in the disc.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now they have this thing, I think they sell it on NCSX, where you pull the lid, it's like a new case that you put on your PS2, and you can lift the lid off, and you have a card that will stop the game from spinning, and you change out the disc.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's really stupid.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like the old... Remember on the old PlayStation, the multi-swap?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've seen someone do the seven-point swap.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: That's why we had... We bought the last DualShock system that still had the I.O.
[SPEAKER_21]: port so we could use our GameShark.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we still had the old 101 series, where you know what it took to play import games with that?
[SPEAKER_21]: A paperclip.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on to the next question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joe Mama would like to know... Dude, there's a name I haven't heard in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, we haven't heard that from that guy in a while, but Joe Mama would like to know... Can I have a dollar?
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: All your dollars are belong to us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Bradley would like to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can have a dollar if you give me two dollars first.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go, I like that answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can have a dollar when you give me five.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, Zodiac Knight would like to know...
[SPEAKER_08]: In your opinions, at what point, what number mix, would it be a good time to stop the DDR series?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Infinity is not an answer.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was with Max, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you think DDR was pretty much dead at 6?
[SPEAKER_21]: I keep playing it, why not?
[SPEAKER_21]: But, you know, it's just the same old thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's not really much innovative that they can do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anybody else care to answer?
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, I still think the second mix was the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have an answer, but I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Magus?
[SPEAKER_12]: Take it to 9th, make a final, be done with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Make it like Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just take it to 9th, make a final.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, care to comment?
[SPEAKER_07]: They'll just keep making more.
[SPEAKER_07]: And be glad it's still around, because then they're not going to make stupid rip-offs like Brittany's Dance Beat the Arcade game or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ugh...
[SPEAKER_08]: Barney's Dance Magic.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_22]: You love me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a drunk inside a suit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's my thought on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR should stop at 8th Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: Extreme should be the last one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember how the little thing said... It doesn't make any sense though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's so cryptic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope, this is my thing though.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR as we know it should be done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want DDR DX now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want DDR 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want DDR something new.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR, as we know it, is done.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, forget it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think dancing games by Konami are not done yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think we'll see something new, and it's going to be something competitive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I always say this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I say this at least every month on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: The next DDR should be something competitive.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR has always been a very cooperative game, with some competitive modes, but they haven't been very... Eh, there hasn't been much to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Second Mixed Step Battle was maybe the most competitive thing DDR ever had.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then he had unison mode and then battle mode was like nothing that was just another way of doing versus mode but having like a dance magic competitive mode or something more competitive I think is where DDR should go next but who knows what Konami has an idea of maybe they'll surprise me but please god please no sequels to Dance Dance Dance thank you Justin B would like to know will you play my crappy remix so that people can laugh at it he has a new remix he wants us to play
[SPEAKER_08]: We're running out of time on the show, but we'll do it in the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll all laugh at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_08]: AZM Buddy Paul, and this is the last question of the night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you all for participating in Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: AZM Buddy Paul would like to know, what do you think about Skye starring in Kill Bill Vol.
2?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think that he would probably be the first one killed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey, hey, hey, I don't like that attitude.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kill Bill Vol.
[SPEAKER_08]: 2 is already done and shot, so I can't really be in it, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I would love to be just some guy that has a cameo that decides to purchase the pussy wagon when all is said and done.
[SPEAKER_08]: The new owner of the pussy wagon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Loki, you want to answer the question?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would have just shot her dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: She has a sword.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you're going to go ninjutsu on me, huh?
Pfft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Indiana Jones all over again, bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to spoil anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I could say something, but I don't want to spoil anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: I already know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, thank you very much for asking Orange Lounge tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We hope you all learn something, as we do every week on Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't feel like singing.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so, well, kids, it's about time for us to wrap up this train wreck of show that we call Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll start with Bradley.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope I make it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I certainly hope I do.
We hope you make it, too.
23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boobies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boobies is your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's so mature.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're such a teenage boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are such a teenage boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Toga.
[SPEAKER_08]: Toga.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is bingo!
[SPEAKER_21]: Did I take your word out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you have another final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we'll get to the word in a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get to the word in a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just wanted to thank everybody for listening to and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Without you, we're nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: We suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're scum.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we're still great either way.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, we do thank you for your support.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thanks for tuning in as you do every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_08]: And take care of yourself and each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tonight's final word goes to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lakata.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: We expect you a nice play again.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: As your leader, I encourage you from time to time, and always in a respectful manner, to question my logic.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're unconvinced a particular plan of action I've decided is the right one, tell me so.
[SPEAKER_05]: But allow me to convince you, and I promise you right here and now,
[SPEAKER_01]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_05]: The price you pay for bringing up either my Chinese or American heritage as a negative is, I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, if any of you sons of bitches
[SPEAKER_05]: Got anything else to say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back, boys and girls, to Orange Lounge Radio, to Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_08]: So as promised, this week we covered an Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: Can I collect your fucking head?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you may not collect my fucking head.
[SPEAKER_08]: We kind of have to make this a quick afterbirth because we're running to the movie theater to go see Kill Bill for the second time.
[SPEAKER_08]: For Magus' case, the first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a Kill Bill virgin.
[SPEAKER_08]: I encourage you, by the way, to see Kill Bill as many times as you can at the theater.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this should be the new cult movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: This should be like the Rocky Horror Picture Show Part 2 or something.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wouldn't this be fun to shadow cast?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd so be like a member of the 88 Gang.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would, of course, have to take Go-Go's character.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is from our very own Justin B. We play things that our chat room builds because we support our chat room just like they support us.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Speedy Mix by Justin B
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S S S S S S S S S
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we need to laugh at it now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha ha remix, ha ha ha speedy mix, ha ha.
[SPEAKER_21]: And if Foss hasn't seen Kill Bill by the time we go to Alabama, I'll pay to for her to see it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, I can just upload it to her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now we don't endorse piracy here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We endorse it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, I don't really have anything interesting to say in the afterbirth tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I have a headache.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we're just all in a mad kind of mood.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're all in a pissy mood, remember?
[SPEAKER_08]: What I feel Orange Lounge vocal edit, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, was that the one where I was going, I feel, or who was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually that's my thing, but yeah, Loki does it sometimes too.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is Loki going to do an Orange Lounge Christmas album?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's beginning to look like Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody in our chat room, I think it was Project DDR USA 2, I think, was making the Strong Bad skin for Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: That should be a riot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, was it BRP Ohio?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my bad.
You're a beast!
[SPEAKER_08]: Eurobeat?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I have any Eurobeat albums, really.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't you have my CD with the 614 megabytes of Eurobeat?
[SPEAKER_21]: Ooh, I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, I'll find it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to fill time while I find it, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because, you know, I was supposed to do a Eurobeat marathon, and I didn't.
[SPEAKER_21]: Damn, I feel so bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody alert Nostalin.
[SPEAKER_21]: I played Happy Hardcore instead.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it was, like, Volume 7 of Happy to be Hardcore.
[SPEAKER_21]: I need to, like, go back and get the others.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think you'll get that CD when you're done with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody alert Nostylan that we're going to do a Eurobeat marathon.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, make sure that he's got a change of underwear handy or something.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because he's probably going to go through about five of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: The room's already excited about this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: So hopefully the CD's not scratched too bad and it'll play all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll see what happens here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I think we're set here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just going to cue up all the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you once again, boys and girls, for your loving and caring support of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this Eurobeat's for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll go pa-da-pa-da our way to the movie theater.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we're going to pa-da-pa-da our ass off at the movie theater.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um, is it going?
[SPEAKER_08]: If it skips, I apologize in advance.
[SPEAKER_08]: The CD might be a little skipped, but we're going to do our best.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good night, everybody.
And I give to you my love
I wanna be your angel, baby
Thank you for watching!
We play together till the morning, I don't stand a chance
DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching!
Baby, let me take control Yes, I do, yes, I do, you are my target No one ever made me cry What to do, what to do, and it's so bad You're like a cruelty bite, your blood is cold like ice Fighting for my pain, I'm breaking my chain One look and you can kill my pain I'll be your thrill, your love is for me I said, try me, take a chance on emotion But now it never comes
Thanks for watching!
Don't stand so Don't stand so
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: 4, 3, 2, 1 No one sleeps in Tokyo All night with the light No one with the radio Tokyo is on fire
All right, in the fight, I'm okay, come on!
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: 1, 2, 3, 4 All night, cross the night Dark, your heat's on fire Dark, your heat's on fire
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
No one quits the radio Tokyo is on fire No one quits the radio
Lonely Love
Thank you for watching!
All the life, only you can take my side The affection, all my dreams, the passion of my love Breaking all my heart, follow me tonight You can hear the music, the light of the night Lonely love, I love my life Cause all of destiny, hold on my soul for you Lonely love, music of my life Like a fly in the sky, in the deep of the night Just one lonely love, made in a
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
No matter where we go
Thanks for watching!
I don't know what I'm doing
You got me out of bed