[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, June 3rd, 2007, rumors surface about Mario Kart Wii, Blizzard strikes against Gold Farmer's WoW, and a famous 80's movie is about to be made into a PC game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should know by now that we're that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gamer culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be here with you for the next few hours in two parts of a show to talk about the latest and what's going on in the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello also to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beer!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's what's tasty.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my weekend was beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I don't really care for much beer except for Guinness, which isn't a beer, it's a stout.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, you need to have Newcastle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've had Newcastle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Newcastle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Newcastle is permissible.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually got my husband to like a beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: He likes Killian's Red.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, if I'm going to drink, I'm going to drink something that's actually going to get me drunk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Therefore, beer doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Depends on what you drink.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shimei Shimei Shimei Shimei
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Boobies!
[SPEAKER_03]: Boobies!
[SPEAKER_06]: Video games are really expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't talk about that enough on this show, but they are freaking expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I have my Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been going to the gym.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm back to going to the gym now that my doctor's giving me the okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I get on the recumbent bike and play with my Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's a recumbent bike?
[SPEAKER_03]: The recumbent bike is where you sit down like you're in a chair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds dirty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know a standard stationary bike has you upright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Recumbent means leaning back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I go on the recumbent bike.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like one of those boats that you pedal by.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or those lame-ass bikes that you see people pedaling.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're sitting back, and it looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, on the streets and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually works out your legs, though, a different way.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not always much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I have to work back into my whole routine, I'm doing the recumbent bike so I can sit down and play with my Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you cannot play Pokemans on the elliptical.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that would be kind of tough.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't even freaking read on the elliptical.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, I've got to move my arms, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have I pinged out of chat?
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat room hasn't moved for me in a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's concerning.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll check on that while Loki talks about his gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, did it involve going to the gym?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember if I did go to the gym this week or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I did one day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: One day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like to, so I don't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, this week I played a lot of weird stuff, other than the usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played more Super Paper Mario, and to be honest, it's getting very repetitive towards the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Almost like they've ran out of ideas what to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, well, let's just throw a hundred of these towards you, and how about let's make you replay levels again, and oh, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'll be very glad to see this game over, and I'll be very glad to return it for some store credit.
[SPEAKER_07]: because it's not worth playing again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even with all the side crap, not worth it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then I played my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, dusted that thing off, and then did a nice old firmware update, and then created myself a Japanese account to download Folklore.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I played it, and it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although, since it's in Japanese, I have no idea what the storyline is.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is this game all about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I know nothing about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, um, I'm not really sure, like I said, because it's all in Japanese, but, um, there's two different characters you get to play as.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played through as the guy in the game, and you actually, what you're doing is kind of stealing the souls of these, like, critters that you kill, like, different, uh, enemies, almost like in Final Fantasy, and you gain abilities that they have, and you use those as your attacks throughout the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, once you've gotten some abilities and stuff, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure there's something that I'm just not getting in the translation of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of all this shaking and body parts and stuff, what do you know about the Mortal Kombat Armageddon on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'm really tempted to get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks awesome, and apparently it's pretty easy to play because of the controls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm tempted to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Plus it has motor combat, and you can use, you know, your... That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your... I guess it's supposed to be sort of controlled almost like... Not necessarily... I guess like Excite Trek a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played the one on PlayStation 2, and it was decent.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there was a lot of stuff they crammed into one, you know, considering it was on the, I guess you should say, current-gen consoles or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: They really crammed a lot into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, I'm interested in checking out the one on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear it's pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, just from some of the descriptions, and they had, like, a little gameplay video there, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Showing, you know, how you would play the game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looked very simple.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, even I would be able to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was looking at that list of fatalities that went out to the internet this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for some reason, we get Midway press releases all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is pretty much the same things you end up seeing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because game blogs just copy-paste what they're sending out in the press release, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So we get those same things, but we never get free games for Midway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, lucky you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_07]: I got, let's see what, Spy Hunter?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rampage?
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did get free games from Midway once, because there was this very sweet gal that worked there that I met at some trade show, and she hooked me up with the Classic Game Archives, which I really like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Midway put out some of my favorite stuff in the 80s, so the only thing that I complain about, about those Classic compilations, is that I have yet to see Journey the Arcade Game show up in one of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though it ran on the same hardware as Timber and all that other stuff, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you've got the licensing rights and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they can get Tron on Xbox Live, I can get Journey on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't stop believing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will hold on to that feeling.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do that, sir.
[SPEAKER_07]: So then I also played, well, I've downloaded a bunch of Japanese demos.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've downloaded the Hot Shots Golf 5 demo, so I haven't played that, or I guess Mineno Golf 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I also downloaded some weird, I don't even know what the fuck it is, it's like their mascot in Japan, like some cat thing that you have, you basically raise it and it reads you Japanese news or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that the cat, the white cat with the big face?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what you're talking about, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only problem is, in order to play that game, I had to download some update or something, and it took like an hour to download, so I got very bored with that real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: That cat was actually based off of old text emoticons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: B-Boy Breakdancing
[SPEAKER_07]: Not exactly like Bust a Move or anything like that, but it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It takes a lot to get used to the game, though, because there's a lot of transitioning and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of rhythm stuff in there as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I've got that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then what else have I been trying to play?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have the full version of LocoRoco.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't touched that yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then also Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got that on...
[SPEAKER_07]: The PSP, and then I got Nelly, the DS one, so she's been playing that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: But she doesn't really get the game, but she's been playing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been trying to finish that game up.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're almost done.
[SPEAKER_07]: We almost got all the weapons on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just trying to finish some of these harder levels.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, I think I haven't really been playing too much else on...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: or videos, I believe.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you have to put the file in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I didn't know that, and so I've been kind of banging my head against the wall trying to figure out how to get this thing to work, because I'm like, well, I converted it, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is it not fucking seeing it?
[SPEAKER_07]: So finally, I figured out that's what I need to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Works like a charm now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So lots of hacking and stuff in your wake, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is only going to be a gateway to putting porn on the PS3 now, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, I'm glad you... At least you have a goal in mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's good to have goals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta have goals.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looking at the chat room for some feedback here, SSJ100Matt says, That's not a surprise, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the same with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: But see, that's the thing with the PSP is I put it in the video folder for the PSP because the PSP is even worse than the PS3 as far as how strict, you know, the...
[SPEAKER_07]: What folders and the file names and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I thought, okay, well I'll just throw it in there and see if that works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope, that didn't work either.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I actually had to use, it was funny, my camcorder that I have because the batteries don't work in it anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I just plugged that in and now it's a 20 gig jump drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Rob D in chat says the PS3 is a gateway for porn.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by the way, the PS3 is fucking easy to download demos to the Japanese accounts.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so easy to create one.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no restrictions whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can download all your games just like the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything you download on Japanese accounts is playable on all accounts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, good tip.
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week was pretty short.
[SPEAKER_06]: There wasn't a lot to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been playing a lot more World of Warcraft I hit level 55 I've been grinding a lot this week trying to get to Outlands I want to get to 58 very bad because a lot of the guild which by the way our guild like blew up in the past couple weeks we have tons more people on the guild now I played I know I saw you on the other night yeah I forgot to say that I played yeah for like half a second though because then Shane kicked me off my computer because he wanted to get on and kick people out of the guild or whatever his because Shane is actually the guild leader so he I didn't get kicked tyrant and he booted like three people one night but as a joke I mean it was it was funny yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: So I've been working on that because a lot of the guild is in Shane and some of them are in Outlands now and they won't shut up about how awesome the Outlands are and how they're never going back to the old world.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm working on it, trying to get there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You went to Outworld?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that Mortal Kombat or Outlands?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I got my Mortal Kombat mixed up with my... No, you said Outlands.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did I?
[SPEAKER_06]: I said Outworlds.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wouldn't surprise me if I screwed something up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I usually do.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then besides World of Warcraft, I've been spending a whole lot of gaming time
[SPEAKER_06]: Actraiser
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Check the forums for more details or the live journal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry to the live listeners because I know the live listeners kind of got screwed last week because we did our thing live at Faname.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, we won't have a show next week, but we will be back on June 17th.
[SPEAKER_06]: That should be a fun show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then June 24th is the 5th anniversary show of Orange Lounge Radio, the official 5th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I should mention that the live station, which went up a little bit earlier than we actually did a live show, because remember, our station was up for a little while to promote that we were going to be doing a live show back in 2002.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our live station turned 5 years old this week on May 30th, so happy birthday to the live station.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll be officially celebrating on the 24th.
[SPEAKER_06]: How?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and, of course, everybody in chat's kind of crying.
[SPEAKER_06]: ChainsawJuggling says, boo.
[SPEAKER_06]: ShadowCharlie says, since I'm traveling also, I won't have to worry about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, guys, but surely you understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need vacations, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, why don't you start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and there's some interesting news, not surprising at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, according to the website, JudeFrance.com,
[SPEAKER_07]: They have run into a credible rumor, they say, that says that Nintendo is going to drop the bomb at EA, or not EA, E3, Mini E3, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: That they're going to be announcing a brand new Mario Kart game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on, it's only a matter of time before a Mario Kart game comes out for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully it's not a part of the arcade game, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other rumor is that there's going to be some new hardware news as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whether this be a revision to the current Wii hardware, something altogether new, or possibly, you know, I'm thinking maybe it's a DVD playback, something like that, but no idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, obviously there's going to be some announcements at E3, but Mario Kart, if that happens, I'm not too surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: Besides, this is why I buy every damn system that Nintendo puts out for Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it seems like a foregone conclusion to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, obviously this game is coming out on the Wii at some point, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like saying a Mario game is coming out on a Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that'd be, uh, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course there's a Mario game coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you guys heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a new Zelda game coming out on the Wii at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't know much more about it, but there will be another Zelda game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody beat us to that, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Goddammit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy XIV will be coming out to some console at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely definitive news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wouldn't it be funny if that was a PC game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Then that wouldn't be a console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop trying to screw our exclusive news, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of the... You know what's funny about... I was trying to figure out if that was the same site that a long time ago...
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like in 2005.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got an email from some French website about E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they actually didn't mean to send it to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: They meant to send it to some staffer that had a very similar name to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like it was a missent email to my Gmail box.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the weirdest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I ended up writing the guy back and he spoke English luckily.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I ended up giving this site pictures from E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if it was the same site.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it was like a French Nintendo only site.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they only used the pictures from the Nintendo booth that I took that year.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was so interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Also talking about Nintendo and Virtual Console, obviously I was very happy that ActRaiser was like the 99th Virtual Console title to be released, but that means that this Monday, the 100th Virtual Console title will be released, and they've already announced it's going to be Zelda II, The Adventure of Link.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that is coming out on, I believe, what, June 4th?
[SPEAKER_03]: Am I one of the only people that doesn't like that game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you're not, because I've been reading game blogs, and a lot of people have been kind of saying, like, oh, it's one of the weaker Zelda games in the franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that was a CDI.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just different.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you think about it, weren't all the sequels on Nintendo really different?
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: 2, very different from 1, yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: 2 was not Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, it was the whole... There was a Super Mario 2 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doki Doki Panic or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was just like the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't say all that international garbage.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the Zelda game was released in Japan as a Zelda sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, how about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Simon's Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Completely different from the first Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_06]: And completely better.
[SPEAKER_06]: True.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to agree with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was better than the first, you know, Demon Castle Dracula.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, whatever, Miss Prim and Proper.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Miss I-play-nothing-but-import-games-my-entire-life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not play nothing but import games.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Rob D says, Well, excuse me, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to make that a sound file.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to find that old clip from the old 80s Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just replace Princess with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or leave it at Princess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be appropriate.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pay me my respect.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo is putting out Zelda 2, The Adventure, Link, and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're bragging that the internet connection rate is 40%.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's more happy, though, for our friends in the UK.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the European Virtual Console, actually, I guess I should say Europe, but there are going to be some pretty fun stuff coming out over on the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get Streets of Rage 2, which I love the Streets of Rage games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're really fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And then coming from the TurboGrafx-16, it looks like there's World of Sports Competition, which is, well, shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you saying that just because it's a sports game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there's some pretty awesome old school sports games I'm waiting for.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not like World of Sports Competition.
[SPEAKER_03]: It ranked right there below Keith Courage.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, now that I have ActRacer, you know, and now what virtual console game will I complain about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, obviously there's The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember when Zelda 2 came out on the European Virtual Console in January?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they got it a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: So did Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've been having to wait this whole time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma says Zelda 2 was underrated and by far was one of the better titles.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was!
[SPEAKER_06]: It was not one of the better titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was okay, but it was like... I will say it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: His sword looked like a fucking dagger throughout the whole game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have found some fun hacks for that game, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the penis hack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember I got stuck on like the fifth part of the game where I couldn't figure out jumping down the, what was it, the chimney?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where you had to climb up on top of the house, but you had to get the double jump to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually ended up, I don't know how, but I skipped random levels on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll probably download it and he's
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I said penis, shut up!
[SPEAKER_07]: Preferably Super Mario RPG.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you never know if Squeenix put Actraiser on there finally.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's always a chance.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a chance.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about the regular Mario Kart, not Mario Kart 64?
[SPEAKER_07]: That needs to come on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if it's true there's a Mario Kart Wii in the future, I would think they would time that around the release of Mario Kart Wii, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I guess I gotta wait until August too for all the Metroid games.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68, by the way, stop doing the freaking color over your text.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you do make a good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did have the best ending thing when you died.
[SPEAKER_03]: Game over, return of Ganon.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you died, it would say, game over, return of Ganon.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's killed everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's murdered the children.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's raped the babies.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's all because of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And next time you do the colored text like that, I'm going to kick you.
[SPEAKER_06]: WonderDogHerald wants to know when the heck Zombie 8 My Neighbors is coming to the virtual concert.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, that was the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hostile1 wants RC Pro-Am.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good choice, but that's a rare game, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Fester's Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the most random title to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blaster Master.
[SPEAKER_06]: No it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need Blaster Master.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, fuck Blades of Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want Blaster Master.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Scratch my earlier comment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blades of Steel can fucking wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Blaster Master.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, and, and, and, and, and, and, and.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blaster Master has to have the grenade trick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the way you pause it and over and over on the big jellyfish guy and some of the other bosses.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it explodes him faster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, here's the thing, though, is that, like, every time the virtual console comes up, we keep bitching and whining about the games we want to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's move on, shall we?
[SPEAKER_07]: They also need to change the way I can find the games on the virtual console because this ghetto JavaScript shit is lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why'd you tell Firebomba to go to hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: I said Blade of Steel was better than Blaster Master.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to hell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, go to hell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to hell and burn there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And roast some marshmallows too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, ours has got to be one of the only video game podcasts out there that just totally tells their listeners to go to hell when we disagree with them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's because we're friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And everybody else is telling them to go to hell too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, mom mentality.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also need to get Yonoid because I was like... Oh, you know what else was cool?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uniracers!
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool spot.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll just get a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll just have one week where it's all like, you know, product placement.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we talk about new games, please?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, let's talk about Ubisoft because they like to port over crappy games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to hell!
[SPEAKER_07]: So Ubisoft admits that they were overporting some of their GameCube games to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or, you know, not necessarily GameCube games, but Xbox and you name it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, with such wonderful...
[SPEAKER_07]: games as Far Cry Vengeance, which, two-player multiplayer deathmatch, that's uber lame, okay, uber lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: Prince of Persia Rival Swords, which, you know, is just two thrones all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you were going to say Rival Schools, and I'm like, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then of course, they may apologize now, but Driver Parallel Lines is coming out later on in June, so they're still not done that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then of course there's also the Monster 4x4 World Circuit, which is a crappy Xbox game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then there was also that GT game, which was also a GameCube game that also sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just stop porting over crappy games, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make some new stuff, and make it better than Red Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, was anyone really surprised by this news that Ubisoft kind of admitted, yeah, we just ported over some of our old shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were in a hurry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dear Ubisoft, thank you for sucking.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, these games were bad for even GameCube games.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were crappy.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Wii Remote Control, Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked Far Cry, you know, on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Wii, it was a whole different game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just
[SPEAKER_06]: That's Gauss Panic.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but there's one, and then, like, it flips over to, like, the real demon face with, like, the blood pouring down his face.
[SPEAKER_06]: He goes, everybody, move your body.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's, like, this really horrible techno song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my favorite game on that MAME emulator ever because it's so random.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have all these pictures of boobies, MAME, M-A-M-E, whatever, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the E stands for emulator.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm being redundant.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like ordering a cheese quesadilla.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deal with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyway, but, oh, this is the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, please, if you have, ask your parents' permission, though, if you're under 18, because you do see titties in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or sneak.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I didn't say that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, yeah, the chat room's going to look for the link there, see?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura DarkSakura DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: How about my foot, you know, kicking you in the head?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully that gave Rob D something to work with.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can we do more stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we can.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll talk about, speaking of the Wii, because we're talking about the Wii, we'll talk about Mario Party 8.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has anyone played Mario Party 8 yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard mixed reviews on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard some people say it was good, and some people, like reviewers, saying it sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the real people I talked to said it was good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm not sure what to believe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played it yet, but there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Party 8 is out on the street.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the reason why we're bringing this up, that's not newsworthy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've already talked about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is newsworthy is that folks are trying to make backup copies, quote unquote, they're making backup copies of the game as they've made backup copies of other games, but their backup copies of Mario Party 8 aren't working.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not working with the modded Wii units.
[SPEAKER_06]: So has it been possible that
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo has come up with a workaround for this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or perhaps the Wii has realized that it's such a crappy game that it doesn't want to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, I've become smarter thanks to modding.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is this shit that you're trying to insert into me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Be gone!
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, JVmon says, I have it, Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gerardimo says, but really boring to play by yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, I mean, that's just Mario Party.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a party game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like, I don't know, Rayman's Raven Rabbids is kind of boring to play by yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fireboma says, because it's Mario Party, it's the same game being rehashed over three different platforms and only remotely changes when it moves to another system.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but the Wii, Wii Bo, Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: And BlackDevilerX asks, Sky, are you going to be Princess Peach?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell yeah, I always play Princess Peach in the games because Peach is the winner.
[SPEAKER_06]: She says so herself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then it must be true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, it must be true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about some other games that are going to be coming out soon, besides Mario Party 8, which is already out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about upcoming games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll start over in Europe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your mom, the game, is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Loki is coming out on PC on the 4th, which has already passed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, wait, that's tomorrow, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's already passed by the time you guys get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's also Nelly's birthday, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I was going to tell her happy birthday because my live journal told me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also coming out though on the 8th is Brothers in Arms DS, Forza Motorsport 2, Halo 2 Vista Edition for PC, of course, because Vista, you know, gives people headaches.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mercury Meltdown Revolution on Wii, Pac-Man Rally, Pangaea Golf with Style on Wii, Trion Cube, and Vortex Senko no Ronde.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is it coming out with the Japanese name in Europe?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's actually, that's, no, Sega Narande was the name that it was in Japan, but they added that Wartek to the front of it because that makes people want it more because it's got the word war in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, ooh, Wartek!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, in that case, it must be a war game or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess, you know, maybe it's just that people like,
[SPEAKER_03]: to have something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it beats their last.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forget what the name before it was because there was like Battlescape.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cinco Norondo was at one time a name possibility for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: How does it feel that you have a game named after you coming out?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen screenshots of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like fucking Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's
[SPEAKER_07]: It's definitely not about me because you wouldn't be able to contain such awesomeness in a game like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can understand MMO, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, SSJ100Matt says there is a code in the Loki game to unlock a Tingle costume.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, be on the lookout.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's reason enough to get it, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of these days, Loki, you watch.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to drug you and put you in the costume.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so this week we see the release in the United States for Tomb Raider Anniversary Edition on the PlayStation 2 and PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also on PC and coming to the 360, Call of Juarez, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: First person shooter western game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hospital Tycoon for the PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dragon Ball Z Haru Kanaru.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like a tongue twister right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Haru Kanaru, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Densetsu DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically just, you know, Dragon Ball Z RPG on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or is it a fighting game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, uh... Planet Puzzle League coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, another, uh... What was that one game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another rip-off of another puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Puzzlescape coming to PSP and then, of course, the Sims 2 H&M stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be funny if it was S&M stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: More Sims 2 stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: More?
[SPEAKER_06]: What is this, their 11th expansion?
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the H&M fashion stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, moving on to Japan and what's coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: On June 7th, Harvest Moon for the Wii comes out because, you know, you just can't have a Nintendo system without a Harvest Moon game on it, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pirates of the Caribbean at World's End, the Japanese version of that, coming out on June the 7th as well, also on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming out on the PlayStation 3, not much until the 14th, but that's when Ninja Gaiden Sigma comes out, so look for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out on the PlayStation 2, The Magician's Academy, also Wizardry X2.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wonder Price, I guess, is coming out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or maybe it's called Wonder Price because it's discounted.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would make a lot more sense, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out, because I first read it, I thought it said Wonder Prince, but I guess not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out on the Nintendo DS, you have Kabu Trader Shun is coming out from Capcom, Kazujin Taisen coming out from Nintendo, and also another version of Pirates of the Caribbean at World's End coming out on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Yoshi's Island pouches for your DS are coming out if you like Yoshi Island.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a game, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Take note, SNK!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so that's going to do it for release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's actually some really cool news for people who are fans of Second Life, is that this upcoming
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I think that it's already passed given the date of, yeah, it was on June 1st at 7pm, but BBC2 was broadcasting on Second Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were doing The Money Program, which is a business show that shows how big business affects everyday life.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently this looks like it might become a standard thing, I hope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did somebody throw cocks at them?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, for anyone in Second Life, the only place that you could go to watch it was the Red Run Red Cinema in Second Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally have never played Second Life.
[SPEAKER_06]: This stuff is all foreign to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried once and thought it was crap, so I stopped playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: All I ever can think about was Second Life with the flying penises.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw that one YouTube video.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have real life.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I have a first life.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be fun just to roam around Second Life and do stuff to annoy people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than the cool thing is that someone actually built the inside of the TARDIS and built Daleks and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nerds, all of you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would want to make a giant stick man that's like, you know, 500 stories tall that stomps around and smashes everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, can we have monsters in Second Life?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, can I make Godzilla?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, people made, you know, weapons of mass destruction and have blown stuff up, so... That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_07]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Giant Mario, have him get the star thing, turn into the pixelated Mario, Smash, Smash, Smash.
[SPEAKER_07]: People would find humor in that, I would think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw a really funny picture speaking of Mario Smash.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was someone's signature on our forums, on the DarkSakura forums, because that's where our World of Warcraft guild has their forums headquartered.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wellplay.DarkSakura.com There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And somebody made this little graphic or found it somewhere of, you see...
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3 Super Mario Bros. 3
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Check out the Fury Beta sign-up page at www.unleashthefury.com and slash beta.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can check out that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looks pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was some other game out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember the name of it, but it was a Korean MMO that's kind of like, they compared it to The Matrix.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of, you know, jumping on walls, or running on walls in gunfights and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love the title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wait, you saw the picture?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just watching it because Junami linked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I didn't even see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Junami beat me to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You bastard!
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meanwhile, I'm looking it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I got distracted by a post because somebody was spamming the forums again, advertising Viagra, and, you know, I was just really curious because... No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody reads those posts on any forum.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're just now seeing the Loki tingle graphic?
[SPEAKER_06]: One of our listeners did that, like, last week and put it on my All Games blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not good radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, and, uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: The sign-up started, it looks like, on May 31st, and I don't see a closed date.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, this is going to be an MMO from Perpetual Entertainment, and you get to be the son or a daughter of an Olympus god.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, uh, so you get to conquer enemies of Rome, you get to battle the iconic enemies such as the Cyclops, Minotaur, Hydra, so on, Medusa, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're into MMOs and you like Greek mythology, it'd be a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the, the
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Today's website of the week actually is brought to me by my amazing sauce, who is wonderful and full of internet nerdness and greatness.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's lolbots.com, and this basically takes Caturday and just macros every freaking nerdy thing ever in existence.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have you know that my wife looked at this and she didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: As did I. I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I lol'd a couple times.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do not have the geek vibe in you, obviously.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I understand why it's supposed to be funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like, it's old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, yeah, we get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's been games that have been translated, literally, you know, from their Japanese stuff, and it was funny because it was English.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, funny!
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, get over it!
[SPEAKER_07]: That was years ago!
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, literacy is not a jokey matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know where the hell we go after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Prozac.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should get some.
[SPEAKER_03]: Valium, maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: LOLbots.com Valium.com for Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you need to be reading some of those forum posts that advertise the, you know, antidepressants from the interwebs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, if you have trouble keeping it up, read the Viagra spam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well...
[SPEAKER_07]: Doing our weekly part in promoting GameTap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Swear to God we're not on their payroll, I swear.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we are.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're not getting paid.
[SPEAKER_07]: They fixed the glitch in accounting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_07]: On top of their normal subscription service, they're doing a free ad-supported service that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be rotating 30 games every so often.
[SPEAKER_07]: Starting off, you're going to get to play for free Panzer Dragoon, Metal Slug 2, Art of Fighting, The King of Fighters 95, and the upcoming Tomb Raider Legends.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I already bought that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's my money?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: All these games are old.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a lot of people probably already have them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I mean, it is the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are ways to getting stuff free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did GameTap open that up for those folks that are playing those?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can they still play them online?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they have access to the head-to-head service on there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think some of them will have online co-op.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe now I can play with some of the cheapskates and won't pay for GameTap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can play some games with them online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, I will pay so we can play real Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you could just come to my house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you could just wait until, I don't know, Metal Slug eventually comes to Xbox Live Arcade because, you know, SNK loves re-releasing that damn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Raven's Dolphin confirms it does have online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I wanted to mention briefly, I saw in some interview somewhere that GameTap is still being worked on for the Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it could be coming out very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if they had a date on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which makes Loki very happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, I'll make many Mac fans out there very happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that would be very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, why would it make me happy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't own a Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what we call in the industry, a joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: The first Sega games that I played, Rob, were on the ColecoVision.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the ColecoVision.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so sad that I sold my ColecoVision to get a Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have another one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had 70 games at one time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I used to go to flea markets and buy that shit for a buck each.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I can find my second one, would you like it?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because, yeah, that time is long past.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was thinking about hooking up the Atari 5200 the other day, just for kicks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, just for kicks, Gold Farmers like to annoy the shit out of me in World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, I know not all our listeners play World of Warcraft, but if you've been playing in the past month, huge problems with spammers on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gold Farmers just going crazy in the game, sending tells.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the cool thing is that with the latest patch, Blizzard really put the smack down on it, and what they did is that now you can just right-click on a name and report them for spam automatically, and
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: They went a step further and said this, Blizzard has filed a federal lawsuit against the operators of Peons for Hire, which is a popular gold-selling organization, which many of you have no doubt seen advertised, because they were the ones that were really spamming in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: As part of the lawsuit, the operators of Peons for Hire have been asked to immediately cease all in-game spamming efforts by all entities and websites under their control.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Blizzard's now putting the smackdown in court.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, it hasn't stopped, because now what they do, they'll send you party invites...
[SPEAKER_06]: and then send you the spam.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just automatically decline party invites I'm not expecting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do you think I don't party with anybody but who I know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's annoying because when you get a party invite, it goes, and the little thing pops up on the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, the TGFRCVHJI has invited you to a party, which is just some spammer who hit their keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just annoying because you're trying to kill somebody and then...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and Blizzard has partnered up with Capcom to get Phoenix Wright on the case.
[SPEAKER_07]: He'll get those spammers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_06]: He'll get them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Phoenix Wright 5 versus the gold spammers.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can see it now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if anybody is interested, because, you know, Activision is just, well, we hear things now and again.
[SPEAKER_03]: But according to their financial report, they're stating that Enemy Territory Quake Wars will be out by the end of summer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually was on paper to be due during the second quarter of the fiscal 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, all they're saying is that it's still just going to be done when it's done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me consult my magic eight ball here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Signs point to end of August.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what everybody else is saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, your magic 8-ball, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Invisible 8-ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: The 8-ball we don't speak about, ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially when Namco's in the room.
[SPEAKER_02]: La, la, la.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an 8-ball, not a Katamari.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell us some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, excuse me, DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, you didn't do it right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I don't want Rob to say anything else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob's not allowed to talk for the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you, Rob D., I heart you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob is not allowed to talk for the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you're taking over as our mediator here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lord help us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to throw something at... where's the ferret?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that a Kirby?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's a Jigglypuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see Jigglypuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll throw it at Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't reach Jigglypuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: The best part is, he sent me two.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, excuse me again, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hit Rob in the shoulder with a Jigglypuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the best fucking listeners of any radio program on anywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: So surprise!
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy XIII has hit its... Well, probably not the first, but one of the many delays.
[SPEAKER_07]: This being Final Fantasy XIII Versus has been put on hold.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to an interview with Dengeki PlayStation of Japan, Final Fantasy main man Tetsuya Nomura has revealed that he likes to only work on one project at a time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And obviously right now...
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy XIII Final Fantasy XIII
[SPEAKER_07]: Release only one Final Fantasy game at a time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't make 13-1, 13-2, 13-B, 13... I mean, it... You got a little happy with 7, because 7 was so popular, and it sold well, then you started doing this shit with 12.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fucking money-hungry bitches.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just make one game only.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then if people like the game, they'll say, hey, I want more!
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of saying, hey, we have 13 games coming out for Final Fantasy XIII, collect them all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gotta catch them all, Final Fantasy.
13.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fabulous, Kristen Novalis.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kristen Novalis.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what that sounds like?
[SPEAKER_07]: What was it, one of those Telemundo shows or whatever?
[SPEAKER_07]: Kristen Novalis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Telemundo, Telemundo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight on Sabado Gigante!
[SPEAKER_06]: Fabulous Christian Novella!
[SPEAKER_06]: Seems like none of this other news even matters anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Electronic Arts out of Canada recently lifted the embargo going on for the upcoming PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 racer Need for Speed Pro Street.
[SPEAKER_06]: Audi S4, Dodge Challenger from 71 Good times
[SPEAKER_06]: and of course some screenshots were released as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the new modes in the game, Tandem Drift, Drag, Grip, and Speed Challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out in fall of 2007.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can totally see in one of these screenshots here like a Drag Race kind of mode, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I really would love the CEA to make?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: A Cannonball Run game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've got the graphics, they've got the engine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get Burt Reynolds on this thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is an exciting... This makes for great radio, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: But this is the soundtrack I have to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dude, this is great.
I remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just looped that same thing over and over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I'm ready for the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura reads them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here she goes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dying a plague.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, excuse me!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, any...
[SPEAKER_03]: Turn off the damn music!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're trying to... You know, I was just over my PMS and you've made it worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: I single-handedly brought it back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, read an email.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got one from VoteForDan, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not voting for him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, DrBurst, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think WoW will come to the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did I answer this one already?
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't we do that one last week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I already answered this last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Download the old podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I will anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi everyone at OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to write a quick email to let you know that I listen to your podcasts every time a new one comes out and I have access to download it to my mp3 player.
[SPEAKER_03]: I listen to all your podcasts multiple times while I'm working.
[SPEAKER_03]: Each opinion from the OLR staff is extremely appreciated.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am a member on GameTrailers.com with the username NarutoCastle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be giving OLR a plug on my blog when I get a spare moment to write one on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll let you know when it's up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing Final Fantasy 3 and enjoying it a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cannot wait for Final Fantasy 4 and Final Fantasy 5 to come out on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thanks for reading my email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gregory in Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for the plug in your blog, because that's like word-of-mouth advertising, which is so essential for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, speaking of which, he also writes back and says, Hi guys, Greg here again, updating on my blog that lets GameTrailer members know about OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Feel free to take a look at the blog, go to GameTrailers.com and search for user NarutoCastle, and you'll see blogs, and most recent should be the OLR blog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Always doing my best to spread the word to as many people as I can, who either listen to podcasts or are into video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you so much for a great podcast, and keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, wasn't there a question there amongst all the lovey-dovey stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I thought there was a question at the beginning of his first email.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we have another one from Xenore, I guess how it's spelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: X-E-N-O-O-R-E.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey guys, love the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Been listening for a few episodes here and there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your group dynamic always brings smiles to my cheeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: It reminds me of my squad of geek gamers from times long past.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep up the awesome work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Recently during some banter amongst the group, you commented on the combat system of Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your discussion intrigued me enough to give the game a shot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope Squeenix sends you a big check for your promotion skills.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best luck to you guys in the future, Zenur.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't heard that expression before, bring a smile to my cheeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just hope you're not talking about your ass cheeks, because that's not a compliment.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't smile on your ass, damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Robway Gets 50 Points
[SPEAKER_06]: for Gryffindor.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What can we give the listeners to do cool stuff like this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mad props, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's not... I mean... A dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: The cars that people have been... That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, if you send us... Okay, here you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we will do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, if you will send us your PayPal, assuming... I don't know if it's your regular email, if you have a separate email.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will PayPal you $1 courtesy of Orange Launch Radio for your awesomeness for this car.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should frame it, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also coming from Rob's favorite person, Sakura Max.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: How old is he, 11?
12.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, big difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quick email to say happy birthday, Jamie Rules, Loki is cool, Sky sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had lots of dots after it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the Bimani music is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so sad because some 12-year-old on the internet hates me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boo-hoo, what am I going to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I asked for DarkSakuraHateMail, not SkyHateMail.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why aren't you people listening?
[SPEAKER_03]: Signed, SakuraMax, 12-year-old listener, one with the best email closings, wants a pet, grew, and loves Pokey.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you even read his emails?
[SPEAKER_06]: They bring nothing to the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just totally make an OLR car.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm supposed to get this game later this week, Forza 2, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no interest in Forza 2 whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't either, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, last email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft hooks me up sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, OLR crew, it's GS68.
[SPEAKER_03]: I enjoyed the OLR panel at Fanime, and I'm looking forward to seeing it again next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: How is Fanime anyhow?
[SPEAKER_03]: Any good stories to share?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was from GS68.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there was me deciding that my costume wasn't going to work and going in the dealer's room and dropping $120 to buy the stuff for my Iroka costume, and I ended up doing chick style.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I have a loan?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got yelled at by my husband.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Over breakfast.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bought a bit generation game called Colorist, and I have no idea how to play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got a porn star's autograph too, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I got a porn star's autograph for my wife, and she loved that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I also got two Harry Potter pictures for my wife.
[SPEAKER_07]: She liked that as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's one other thing I thought I got her as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought one shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the only thing I bought at all I found in May was a shirt.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got Dan the best thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I got him the Goomba that makes noise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that thing was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing you hit and it goes...
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you hit it one more time and it does the You're Dead music.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went back looking for the coin box and they didn't have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you keep hitting the coin box and every tenth one it gives you a one-up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this isn't intended as a plug, but you can order them from WYSIWYG.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's where I got my Goomba from.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also got a Totekeke.
[SPEAKER_07]: I also got a shirt that said Grand Theft Amish, Penn State Dutch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, from the same booth that he got that shirt, I got one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I actually posted a picture of the shirt in my All Games blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to see that, it's community.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: How the hell do you get there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Green Sky is my username on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just find me on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I posted a picture of the shirt I got.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says, This is Zelda!
[SPEAKER_06]: And it has basically, they took a picture of the guy from 300, they took a picture of his face and put the Zelda hat on him.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really funny if you see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen that one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't even see 300 and I get the joke, so I thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the shirt I got.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I didn't mention during my gaming week, though, since he asked about how was the rest of Fonamate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I got there right before our panel started, I didn't get to spend much time there, but I went to the game room afterwards.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went the day after.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I played some pop-up music on a Melo 2, and I got the high score on the machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot how to get high speed, and my dumbass picked the Galaxy Express 3.9 TV theme, which is fucking slow!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think you can put high speed on that one, at least I don't know how.
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't figure it out either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I...
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, dude, I can play poppin' music better than this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did, however, play like a crap ton of Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we had Parapara Shadowing going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, nerds.
[SPEAKER_03]: With people who could do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we'll be back if they'll have us.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the best part was hanging out with DJ Ranma S. The best part was the mini-disc player recorded the show this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_07]: The show didn't come out too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird shit, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably has something to do with the fact that the battery is slowly eating itself away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and the other great part, we found out that Loki's Mac Heckler lives in town, so we're going to have him on a future show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I found something cool, too, and I'm going to... Actually, next week's Side of the Week is probably going to be a plug for this guy's site.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hung out a lot in Artist Alley, because me being an artist and having a bunch of my friends in there, I had to go and hang out with the artsy-fartsy people.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it turned out that I got more photos taken of me wearing my Tron shirt with my Dolphy than in costume which was sort of sad but I also bought this great print of Iron Man for Sauce and this guy drew me Deadpool and he said that he'd do a full color print for me and he actually lives in the Sacramento area so I'm going to plug his site next week
[SPEAKER_07]: I know which guy you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: The guy that does all the comic stuff and he's at like every single anime convention.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think he's even at the Sacramento one sometime.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he was supposed to be here, yeah, but I'm going to give him a call about the commission for the picture because he did a really freaking good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a Sak anime convention coming up this weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't go because I'm in New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not this weekend, is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think it's coming up this next weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, next weekend, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'll go to the mall anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I think it's the one at the temple.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll talk about it offline.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, if you run an automate convention, you want us to come do a live panel, we're open to suggestions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, sweet, to the Rob D. We're kind of broke and can't travel too much, but we're certainly open to hearing suggestions, especially anything that goes on in Northern California or Southern California.
[SPEAKER_06]: Northern Nevada, someplace we can drive to.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, to the Rob D, they said that they did Anime Hell at ASEN, and I didn't know, but they put the full Sega Tatsunoshiro video in that, which is like, anyone who's a Sega fan has to have seen that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the epitome of the Sega Saturn advertising era.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to get back into some news, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enough talk about conventions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where shall we go for another story?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony releases its uncrackable firmware 3.5.
[SPEAKER_07]: It adds a bunch of new features including remote play so you have the ability to play anything that's on your PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, movies and whatnot over the internet on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, also it enhances some of the RSS feeds and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: One other feature that they forgot to mention, uh, it is actually very crackable and got cracked almost, uh, actually I think a day before it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that's possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, uh, yeah, so now they're working on a new custom firmware for, uh, 3.5, and it was kind of funny because they actually used the tools from 3.3 to crack it, and apparently it wasn't that hard, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Was that their unhackable firmware?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, their unhackable firmware.
[SPEAKER_07]: Each firmware is unhackable, you understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's impossible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, speaking of unhacking PSPs, it was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been taking apart PSPs to fix them.
[SPEAKER_07]: My friend's analog stick was broken and I actually took apart the entire analog stick.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: This was a very interesting statement made by Activision in a conference call they had with investors this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, keep in mind, Activision acquired the Guitar Hero franchise when they bought out Red Octane, essentially, or their acquisition of Red Octane, whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They got the Guitar Hero franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's interesting is they have now said about Rock Band, which is coming out, it wasn't surprising that Guitar Hero has attracted imitators.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so basically you're saying Rock Band is an imitation of Guitar Hero, except you may remember Harmonix originally made Guitar Hero for Red Octane before you bought it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that comment made no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when you consider Guitar Freaks came first anyway, by Konami, you all suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just make your games, make them good, and STFU?
[SPEAKER_07]: and technically they're all rip off of Amplitude anyways, Amplitude and Frequency.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the interface of Guitar Hero, that and Karaoke Revolution too a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, they really pay that guy the big bucks apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's real on top of everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you seen the gameplay footage of Guitar Hero 3 that's on the internet right now?
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks pretty sexy, but it doesn't look that different.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is the game that will finally jump the shark for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the series jumped the shark already for me with this 80s edition thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think Guitar Hero 3, people are finally going to go, okay, enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think that's good that Harmonix, instead of trying to do the same thing over again, is trying to... I give them a lot of credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're pretty...
[SPEAKER_06]: Badass company in many ways.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think the fact that they are trying to evolve with the marketplace, with this whole rock band thing, it's a huge risk.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, so is Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, but I think Activision is going to get left behind with the Guitar Hero franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be kind of like Guitar Freaks was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, look at Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_07]: How many versions of that game have come out and really they haven't innovated on each other?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yet for some reason they're still doing well in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of funky, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can either have one of two things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Either it's going to still do very well, or it's just going to tank.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think people are going to start figuring out, hey, maybe spending all this money on this guitar game each time around is not a good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like why DDR is starting to dip down a little bit in popularity, especially when it's coming out on all these new platforms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Buy all new hardware for this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, we haven't heard a lot about what's going on in the DDR world in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess maybe by the time E3 or whatever the hell it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly though, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, think of all the things that we probably would have expected with the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, really, the 360 version is just a prettied up version of the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the one for the Nintendo Wii when it comes out, it's pretty much just PlayStation 2 version of Supernova with Wiimote crap thrown on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very... I was going to say, I guess we have Wii DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very non-innovative.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, granted, yeah, great, you're doing stuff with the Wiimote, but you don't... I don't think you really need to do stuff with the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just like the iToy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the iToy support was there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not even remotely fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It made you look like a complete ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, anyway, sorry, we've...
[SPEAKER_06]: We've definitely beat this story into the ground, but just a dumb comment made by that guy at Activision.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a dumb comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: When have we heard much smart from that guy at Activision?
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear, doesn't he hang out with Kutaragi?
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't know, maybe they all have a secret bar they drink at all day.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mean crayon juice?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, something though that's pretty cool, well at least if you're into it, is that...
[SPEAKER_03]: S&K Playmore is to be releasing... A new game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing Fatal Fury Battle Archives Volume 1, which is Fatal Fury, Fatal Fury 2, Fatal Fury 3, and Fatal Fury Special.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, so close!
[SPEAKER_03]: But hey, we get old school, my booty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they going to be redoing any of the graphics whatsoever?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that'd be arcade quality.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, whoopee.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't those games come out 10 years ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, Fatal Fury Special, I think, came out in 95.
[SPEAKER_07]: To give them credit, their Art of Fighting collection was only $14.99 for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know the one thing that I liked about the Fatal Fury games that I thought was innovative was the, for old 2D fighters, was having the multi-plane.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you couldn't really tell which plane they were on, but you had the front and back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I love Fatal Fury, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was my favorite, like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Street Fighter and Mortal Kombat were kind of up on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, Street Fighter was up on a freaking pedestal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mortal Kombat was close behind.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then he had all these other knockoff fighting games below, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: In the 90s, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say Fatal Fury was my favorite of that bunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: More so than anything else SNK put out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fatal Fury paved the way for King of Fighters, and that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, here's what SNK needs to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, great, you're releasing games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just re-release, like, Neo Geo collections.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, have, you know, Magical Lord.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have, you know, the Fatal Fear games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, all this stuff together.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of just, here's two games that you bought before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's Metal Slug yet again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's, you know, this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then add some... Yeah, but who really bought that stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Those cartridges were like $500.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, though, they've re... You are a crazy bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're in your own category.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, though, they've re-released these games numerous times.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, a lot of them we got through trade.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only one that we paid over $300 for was King of Fighters 2000.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only?
[SPEAKER_06]: I see a $60 Xbox 360 game and I cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, but we have a lot more bills now, so we don't do that anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except I really want Samurai Shodown 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was the last Neo Geo game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will play it once.
[SPEAKER_03]: The fuck I will?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then put it in a glass case and say, I own it and you don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I...
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we rated M today?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rated M. Yeah, we're rated M. Yeah, ooh, watch out, that ESRB's on our ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're rated I for... Wait, we're not a game, dumbass!
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't play through us!
[SPEAKER_03]: We're rated I for immature.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks to Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something's telling me we need a little bit of a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: I think now's a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're gonna break you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Break you back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will break you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break and we'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this break.