[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're back here on Orange Lounge Radio with this, our episode number 234 for June the 3rd of 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be celebrating our 5th anniversary on June 24th of this year, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how we've hit so many episodes, if you wonder why 234 is a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, we're going to get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget Orange Lounge Radio is in two parts every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you missed some, be sure to go back wherever you got this episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably has part A linked as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be sure to grab that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_02]: Toshiba DVD Drives TSH-943
[SPEAKER_02]: That will allow you to play backup copies and legally purchased Xbox 360 titles, as well as it defeats all current and some future Xbox Live detection attempts.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, because of that, it's actually allowing people to be able to use Xbox Live without them knowing that you have a modded console.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, fight the fight, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Microsoft has always been, like, really good about fixing this kind of crap the second it comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I shouldn't say crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it actually is pretty smart.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, they put the banhammer on this stuff ASAP.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, how long is this going to last?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it depends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we'll see how effective this stuff is, but that's big business for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you look at Sony, they've tried and tried with the PSP, but there's no luck there.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I don't know how much of DVD firmware they can really detect.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not really a lot that they can do, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if they circumvent the few methods that they have of checking, they might be screwed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless they just do a whole hardware revision or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think the
[SPEAKER_04]: Hackers and Crackers will win in this war, or do you think Microsoft will be able to stay on top of them?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's one thing that always works in favor of anyone who decides to system hack, and that's called system becoming obsolete.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're not going to care if the next one's going to come out.
[SPEAKER_13]: They'll say, well, screw the old one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everyone's like, yay, we win, because we held out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's kind of like a, it's a waiting war, essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, I mean, if you look at the PlayStation 2, you know, they had, granted, you know, the methods of, you know, doing swap discs and stuff like that, and the DVD loader and stuff, and now, you know, you have the whole running off of hard drives and stuff, and it's just like, shit, I mean, you don't have to buy anything for the PlayStation 2 anymore, you can download everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: If people want it bad enough, they'll find a way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember the days of the seven swap tricks.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think that's fucked up to cheat in online games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think those types of people deserve to get banned.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's doing it for cheating in online games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's just not having to buy those $60 games is what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe imports.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imports might be nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't agree with region control.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand why they do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not trying to say it makes no sense because of licensing and all those other things for the music and what have you that they get in the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the end of the day...
[SPEAKER_04]: It sucks for the consumer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, something else that is confusing, nevertheless, for the consumers is that Destructoid ran this article earlier this week about the Xbox 360 and the fact that Metal Gear Solid 4 is confirmed for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the article was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: The guy who wrote it, Ron Workman, was actually on our year-end special
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm kind of wondering if we should call them up and try to figure out what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know if they'll talk because supposedly Konami sent out a cease and desist.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Destructo has always been a pretty respectable site in my mind, so I don't think they'd pull these stories out of their butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just kind of wondering, like it was very interesting to kind of watch that happen where they had to be very vague about it and then they have this cease and desist coming from Konami which seems to cement it if that is legit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know, could the whole thing be an elaborate prank?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: But Computer Game World seems to think so because they ran a counter story a little later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, that's Computer and Video Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, carried it to the wrong site.
[SPEAKER_04]: Computerandvideogames.com ran a counter point a little later on in the week saying Konami's confirmed nothing is essentially what it's saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: So saying that no, Metal Gear Solid 4 has not been confirmed for 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami's confirmed nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the weird thing about this report is that they're basing it on the fact that they've talked to Konami about
[SPEAKER_04]: and Konami refuses to comment on the rumors and that they've made no statement regarding the 360 version and in my mind I kind of go well that's what we all I mean of course Konami's not going to say anything about it if they send a cease and desist to one site it's because they're not ready to comment on this trust us we know this very well okay that so it kind of doesn't mean anything to me that doesn't discount the story at all so I don't know well speaking of the rumor mill
[SPEAKER_13]: and Konami, wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: There actually were rumors that popped up in this month's issue of EGM stating that Silent Hill 5 was going to be a release this year and handled by Konami USA instead of in Japan.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there was also an interview with the director, Tsubuyama Masashi, who, like I said, was the chief director on the project.
[SPEAKER_13]: and he stated that they don't have anything official.
[SPEAKER_13]: They actually were looking more next-gen console, multi-platform.
[SPEAKER_13]: He did say to keep our eyes on the upcoming press conference on July 11th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's during E3, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_04]: So they'll probably be revealing Silent Hill 5 at that time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Try to find my invite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as the series doesn't jump the shark, I'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think multi-platform is the way to go, though, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, Xbox 360 still hasn't really cracked the marketplace in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, obviously, I think most of us here would like to see it show up on 360, but over in Japan, you kind of have to put it on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wii is just probably not going to be able to handle what they're going to want to do graphically with the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should have Silent Hill where you play as, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill Babies coming to ABC Family Saturday mornings.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wonder Dog Harold says Pyramid Head Mysterious Dungeon would be a fun day.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: With cutesy little music and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super chibi Pyramid Head, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, he just beheaded the cat.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: and other interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming out of the Halo 3 beta, there's been people actually hacking the beta to reveal all sorts of fun stuff, including they have a brand new chopper that you can ride in the game, the sword, as well as radar jamming items, player-operated turrets added to the wraiths, actually playing with the wraith
[SPEAKER_02]: and different modifications including, you know, ground speed and gravity and all that sorts of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And pretty cool, I guess, that you can modify the beta to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't believe people have already cracked the game and it's already in beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, just imagine when the game actually comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not surprised they did this because people love their Halo almost a little too much, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also something to mention about Halo 3 is that GamePro is going to be running an article talking about that there are, you know, well actually I should say the article is going to be showing new vehicles, new maps, new weapons, and armor.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, because Halo 3 is going to have armor in it, new armor.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can create, or I shouldn't say create, but you can get armor for your characters, like new shoulder pads, new helmets, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I look at this one helmet on the particular scans from the site, it looks like an alien head or something on the helmet, so kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead Rising Dead Rising, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dead Rising has some new costumes and themes for Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_13]: But the costumes are a white suit, a striped outfit, and an accountant outfit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, because I really like to look like an accountant when I'm beating up the undead.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I put on my suit.
[SPEAKER_13]: You could.
[SPEAKER_13]: One beheading.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two beheadings.
[SPEAKER_13]: Doesn't that game keep a body cage anyway?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it does.
[SPEAKER_13]: So...
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess you can look the part when you're adding up the corpses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can also dress up like an accountant and slam a cash register into them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, keep the change!
[SPEAKER_13]: Office space the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they have a Naked Time costume in that game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, underoos or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have really tight shorts that you can wear, little kid shorts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a little scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can run around as hard gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beating up the zombies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hapitai
[SPEAKER_02]: including some bills being passed regarding the ESRB ratings and selling minors M-rated games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the law has passed and it's going to make a felony, a Class E felony at least, the least severe felony in the state, if you sell a M-rated game to a minor.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, better be careful before you sell those minors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mortal Kombat, Grand Theft Auto
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's bullshit!
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Grandstanding is what it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get into, and actually I'm looking at some comments in the chat room here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft says, Law sucks in general.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma says, Unless New York State does a lot of secret shopping and or undercover sting operations, which they won't, this law will not fucking stick at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Gerardimo says, Oh, I'm a New York minor.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I only have a Wii, so I'm going to have a hard time finding an M game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Scarface, Manhunt, Driver.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but don't buy Driver.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you want to laugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bad AI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, folks, it's about time that we play a little bit of our favorite game to play here on Orange Lounge Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's... The Match Game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ladies and gentlemen...
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to open up the phone lines right now to get a contestant.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have one contestant from the chat room, and we just need to get an opponent.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you'd like to give us a call, we'll take the first call on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can call us either way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And first off, we'll go around and introduce the special guest that will be playing tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, please help us introduce the guest tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, and guest number one, your name.
[SPEAKER_02]: And where have you come from?
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And guest number two, your name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I don't care where you came from.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, where did you come from, Miklatov?
[SPEAKER_09]: Galactica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, we got a contestant call here, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Wonder Dog Harold.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Wonder Dog Harold.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You win.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to play match game tonight, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Huzzah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hold on the line while we introduce the rest of the panelists tonight, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, tonight, speaking of panelists, tonight's edition of the match game here on Orange Launch Radio, we had to do it tonight, dedicated to Mr. Charles Nelson Riley, who was from the 70s edition of the match game, which, you know, obviously we are,
[SPEAKER_04]: We are blatantly ripping off the match game from the 70s.
[SPEAKER_04]: You see the reruns on Game Show Networks.
[SPEAKER_04]: He passed away this week and was one of the main reasons to watch that show.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was awesome, so we're dedicating this edition to him.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, so yes, Rice, Princess, and Megalotop are here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are sacrificing some of their precious time away from watching Battlestar Galactica episodes back to back to back to be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you guys have watched, like, what, like seven episodes so far this weekend?
[SPEAKER_04]: How many?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't want to take up too much of your precious time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So also joining us is Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: And DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_04]: And me, because I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so you have five folks tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And WonderDogHerald's on the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: You still there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's going to be playing against HitStun from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: HitStun from the chatroom won our drawing during the break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now, WonderDogHerald, do you know how the game works?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're going to, for those that don't, I'll just explain it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to be asking some questions, and we're going to put in the blanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's blanks at the end of them, and you are supposed to come up with what you believe belongs in the blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you match with anybody in the studio, then you get a point.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, we only have three questions tonight, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a short game tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you ready to play?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you ready to play, Wonder Dog Harold?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob just landed himself in big trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: When trying to purchase yet another virtual console game with his credit card, the card was declined.
[SPEAKER_04]: Upon calling the credit card company, they told him, Rob, we turned off your credit card because you've been buying too much blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: All our guests are thinking about their answers and writing them down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, we've turned off your credit card because you've been buying too much blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
Ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have some dings.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dingy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, we're done.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm waiting for the... Okay, there we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, you got an answer, Wonder Dog Herald?
[SPEAKER_04]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's still thinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, while you're thinking... Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll read the question one more time, then we're going to go to you for an answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob just landed himself in big trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: When trying to purchase yet another virtual console game with his credit card, the card was declined.
[SPEAKER_04]: Upon calling the credit card company, they told him, Rob, we turned off your credit card because you've been buying too much... What do you think, WonderDog?
[SPEAKER_04]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Porn, says WonderDog Harold.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too much porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hit stun...
[SPEAKER_04]: also said porn, so this isn't going to be a very exciting round because if anybody gets porn, they both get a point.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what our celebrity panel came up with.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll start with Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's been buying too much?
[SPEAKER_13]: Silent Occupied Caprica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too much Silent Occupied Caprica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that a match?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that would not be a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something from Battlestar Galactica, actually, and we are playing video game match game now.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Miklatov, he's been buying too much... Because porn is such a totally video game related thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's been buying too much Helo, which is like Halo, but Helo.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be porn for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another Battlestar Galactica reference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too much Helo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a match, though, even if that is the object of Shane's fantasies we don't need to hear about on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, he's been buying too much... Actraiser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actraiser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loved it so much he had to buy it five times over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, to put it in the top five.
[SPEAKER_04]: He bought it for all of his friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Filled up one whole page of Actraiser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I should do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, he's been buying too much.
[SPEAKER_12]: Propel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Propel.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't used it in ages.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, Propel.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually drank some Propel today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it good?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like fitness water.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, we turned off your credit card because you've been buying too much candy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Candy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: No matches for either contestant that round.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, WonderDogHerald.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was very emotive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ready to get some points on the second question?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I like, some excited contestants.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question number two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie is not typically the arts and crafts sort.
[SPEAKER_04]: Liar.
[SPEAKER_04]: But she's been very... It's a game, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play along.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie is not typically the arts and crafts sort, but she's been very impressed with all the video game arts and crafts she's seen on game blogs lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, they have the little coasters that have Zelda pictures and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just go to Kotaku or something, you'll see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should be very impressed with all the video game arts and crafts she's seen on game blogs lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: She joined a community college class on knitting, but got kicked out of the class when her first project she brought in was blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: She joined a community college class on knitting, but got kicked out of the class when for her first project she brought in blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, uh, Ding.
Ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just waiting for our chat room player.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hopefully our phone player has thought of an answer, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: The chat room is helping out.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, one of these answers is an incredibly poor taste.
[SPEAKER_04]: I usually are nobody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is everybody dinged?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie is not typically the arts and crafts sort, but she's been very impressed with all the video game arts and crafts she's seen on game blogs lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: She joined a community college class on knitting, but got kicked out of the class for when her first project she brought in... Wonder Dog Harold?
[SPEAKER_10]: A sweater with Clark Gay on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: A sweater with Hard Gay on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's been paying attention to the show because Jamie's been watching Hard Gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see if it matches.
[SPEAKER_04]: HitStun said a shotgun.
[SPEAKER_04]: She brought in a shotgun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which might be... Too soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_12]: She brought in... She brought in a Cylon Occupy Caprica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_04]: Cylon Occupied Caprica is not a match and is still a Battlestar Galactica reference Rice Princess, we are playing video game Candy is not video games either, so shut up Nintendo Cereal was candy There's a Battlestar game coming out, so take that Will it have Cylon Occupied Caprica in it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably Alright, here it is For her first project, she brought in Hilo Guys, you know what your next answers have to be, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: This, by the way, will be the last appearance of Rice Princess Miklatov on our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say goodbye, folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been a fun five years.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's been swell, but the swelling's gone down.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, she brought in... The corpse of Charles Nelson Reilly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too soon!
[SPEAKER_04]: In my refrigerator, hi!
[SPEAKER_02]: She brought in the corpse of Charles Nelson Reilly to her knitting class?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's horrible!
[SPEAKER_02]: She needed a reference, you know, a lifelike reference of knitting his corpse.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, she brought in... A Glock 37?
[SPEAKER_04]: A Glock 37?
[SPEAKER_04]: Too soon!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a gun!
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you watch the news?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are not supposed to make guns at college jokes, that's not cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you don't make fun of it, how will you ever recover?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, true.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, it's a half of a match, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is a Glock 37 a shotgun?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, but it's a firearm, so it gets to have a blink.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, porn and Hilo are not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Neither is shotgun and whatever Jamie said.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's a powerful gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: GS191 says, does this mean I can call Loki a nappy-headed hoe, then?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: He kind of is.
[SPEAKER_04]: My hair is not nappy.
[SPEAKER_13]: The chatroom calls for half a point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's nice for the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too bad it's not their game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said that she brought in, because it was a knitting class, she brought in a quilt with Pyramid Head raping a corpse.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know you don't make quilts in knitting class.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's why they kicked her out, stupid!
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, my other answer was going to be Bloody Steel Needles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Pyramid Head was raping Charles Nelson Reilly's corpse, so go figure.
[SPEAKER_12]: With a shotgun.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would not be attractive.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be attractive, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Wonder Dog Harold, I'm very sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You still have a zero.
Ow!
Shit!
That hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Dark Sakura just injured herself, so at least you get that.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I injured my laptop and indirectly injured myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wonder Dog Harold, are you going to get a point on this last one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki was very impressed with all the cosplay he saw at Fanime.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was shocked, though, at one thing that was missing.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said to himself, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year I'm coming dressed as blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was shocked, though, at one thing that was missing.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said to himself, that's it, next year I'm coming dressed as blank.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, ding!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, ding?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dingy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm waiting on the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sir Dingly Dang.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: No extrovert, you're too late, you can't play now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want a ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to do a bonus point.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't do a bonus point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Extrovert wants to be a bonus point.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think we got an answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the end of the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki was very impressed with all the cosplay he saw at Faname.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was shocked, though, at one thing that was missing.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said to himself, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year I'm coming dressed as Wonder Dog Harold.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hilo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hilo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Says... Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so I see the tactic you're taking here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, let's see if it's a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess.
Wait, I have the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's the other guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitsun, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitsun said, I'm coming dressed as Miss World 96 Nude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we have Hilo and Miss World 96 Nude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's start.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess was number one, though, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine, Miglatov, what was your answer?
[SPEAKER_04]: My answer?
[SPEAKER_09]: Cylon-occupied Caprica.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you doing this just to screw with our... No, we had already planned that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess, what did you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year I'm coming dressed as... Answer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Gaeta.
[SPEAKER_12]: Gaeta?
[SPEAKER_09]: He's in the CIC in Battlestar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lieutenant Gaeta You guys totally screwed Wonderdog Harold out of a point I had already planned mine Wonderdog Harold, would you care to yell at our celebrities?
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody could still say Hilo Alright, here we go That's true, somebody could still say Hilo Loki, he decided to come dressed as I was just going to say myself I don't cosplay, fuck this shit
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't cosplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, he's going to come dressed as?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hadoukei!
[SPEAKER_04]: Also not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I said, next year I'm coming dressed as?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, obvious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tingle!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, he's coming dressed as Tingle for finally the OLR fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could be happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Extover wants a bonus point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if there's a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could decide the game right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to come dressed as... I was going to say Hot Dog.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, from Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking hate this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, nobody won.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: HitStun got zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: That means we win.
[SPEAKER_04]: And WonderDogHerald, I'm sorry to say, you got zero as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you have to give us money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I say something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: My dog's been lost for two days and they found her.
[SPEAKER_03]: In one piece?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Woo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody be happy for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad the bitch is okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was really depressed for two days.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wonder Dog Harold, as a consolation prize, I'll let you plug any website or something you want to give a plug to here on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a man of many words, Wonderdog Harold.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for calling in and being a contestant tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to have you on the show more often.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wonderdog Harold said like ten words.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like when Miklatov guests on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says ten words the entire show.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need to be in studio.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we'll see if you speak more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so we had 0-0.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody is a loser.
[SPEAKER_04]: HitStun says, the chat failed me.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're fired.
[SPEAKER_04]: HitStun says, you know, I can challenge WonderDogHerald at Tetris DS or Mario Kart or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know the chat room was screaming tingle.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would have been a point.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's it for Match Game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And at this point, I will now kick out all of the guests because... It's hot in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously need to go watch Battlestar Galactica some more.
[SPEAKER_13]: Give us some ice cream, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you guys going to get ice cream?
[SPEAKER_13]: Get milkshakes.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys get ice cream.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can give me a milkshake.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or we can go get ice cream and not bring any back.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we'll let you guys take over the afterbirth while we go get ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to do that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Can we make our own cage match?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I put in an awesome song.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, think about it and give it back to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll just be a theme from Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can let me do it and it'll all be Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, tonight's match game was a colossal failure.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because Doctor Who is cooler than Battlestar Galactica!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a pretty good show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't egg them on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, seriously, don't encourage them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's talk about porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I get a yay for porn?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, this isn't real porn, but it's Leisure Suit Larry, which is kind of like, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: Leisure Suit Larry is coming to mobile platforms
[SPEAKER_04]: Larry fans worldwide have a strong allegiance to the classic Leisure Suit Larry adventure game format.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are delighted to be doing just that with the mobile version.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've kept the iconic Larry humor and attitude intact while adapting the graphics, language, and controls for a mass market global audience.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go, some pixelated JavaScript titty coming to a cell phone near you.
[SPEAKER_02]: and if you want your titties to be more realistic then Dead or Alive the movie is coming out June 15th and well it's going to be about as deep as Mortal Kombat the movie probably less deep but it will be coming out to theaters and there will be lots of chicks fighting and I know there's one scene with a chick fighting
[SPEAKER_04]: Topless, but of course, you know, this is... Is this because you've already watched the whole movie on Google Video when it was out a while ago?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I downloaded the PSP version of it off of Google Video.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, speaking of things that have no depth, SingStar 90s is... Oh my god, why are people still playing... You know what, the SingStar games don't look that bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I played it at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I had to do Motorhead.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm more excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heaven forbid I'm saying I'm excited about a PlayStation 3 game, but I think SingStar will be better on the PlayStation 3 we can download.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that way you don't have all these freaking CD expansion packs, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, thank you for reading my story for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't said anything about what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, what I was going to say is that there actually is some speculation that for the PS3 SingStar there would be some more data for download via the download service.
[SPEAKER_13]: But actually SingStar 90s actually was announced for New Zealand stores for August 3rd.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of songs are in this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there a song list?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a gallery.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, here's a song list.
[SPEAKER_13]: Never Ever, All Saints, Barbie Girl, Love Shack, One Week, Achy Breaky Heart with a big fat typo on the page.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game already fails.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unbelievable.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, that was a good song.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here Comes the Hot Stepper.
[SPEAKER_13]: It has Stay on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really?
[SPEAKER_13]: By Shakespeare's Sister?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, Lisa Loeb.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You Can't Touch This, Bitch, which I don't like that song at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Moving on up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Torn...
[SPEAKER_13]: Step by Step.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, New Kids on the Block is on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game might be interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, Where the Wild Roses Go.
[SPEAKER_13]: I fucking love that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that the Nick Cave song?
[SPEAKER_04]: And Kylie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: It has Poison on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wannabe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if that game will come out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, Radiohead.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got one of the Spice Girls.
[SPEAKER_13]: It has Savage Garden, Kiss from a Rose, Baby Got Back.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Zombies on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, he's got the cure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blackboy in our chatroom says, SingStar needs more Bjork.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_00]: See, I do a great impression, don't I?
[SPEAKER_12]: What was Margaret Cho's impersonation?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry that I tried to eat your head.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, there's this YouTube somewhere of, and I know we talked about it on the show before, but it's worth bringing up again.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where somebody took, because you know Bjork one time beat the crap out of some reporter in an airport in Thailand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, somebody put Street Fighter graphics and music over it, and it's really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on YouTube somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure one of the chatters will dig it up somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there it goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, something else you can find on the internet is a role in a movie!
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing!
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, but I don't know if you really want to be in this movie because it's an Uwe Boll movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, he's actually auctioning off a role on eBay for a role in Far Cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: The bidding started at 2,498 euros, which would translate to about $3,360 USD.
[SPEAKER_04]: The winner would get five days on the set of the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unfortunately, though, they would have to cover the flight and the hotel.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go figure that nobody bid on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I had the money, I'd do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you're like, hey, look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in that crappy movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then I could say, I was in the movie and it fucking sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: The official eBay page is all in German, so it's kind of hard for me to make out, but it didn't sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't look like it sold.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Tigerclaw, for finding the Bjork Street Fighter video.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, stories about Uebol make us very angry, so you know what that means, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time for the FU's of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, start us off.
[SPEAKER_13]: What makes me angry?
[SPEAKER_13]: What makes me angry is the check engine light coming on on my car.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because, well, we checked all the emissions, everything was clean, there was no problem with any of that, so I think it just needs new spark plugs.
[SPEAKER_13]: But other than that, it was just really aggravating.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, and one other thing, F you to office drama.
[SPEAKER_13]: And new leather smell on my massage table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, any FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, FU to the key flash component to VGA thing I've got because it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least it doesn't work like it should because, you know, my picture shouldn't be flashing on and off on the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: That probably would mean it's not working.
[SPEAKER_02]: So fuck them and fuck you for wasting $50 of my money.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to the fact that I'm flying out to the East Coast in 48 hours and I haven't done any packing yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So FU to myself for not packing yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe after tonight's show, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, back to rumors and speculation.
[SPEAKER_13]: There actually was a...
[SPEAKER_13]: A little bit from Famitsu announcing that several Metal Gear Solid 20th Anniversary titles were supposed to be out.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they've listed for the 26th of July Metal Gear Solid Collection for PlayStation, PS2, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also Metal Gear Solid 3 on PS2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Metal Gear 20th Anniversary Metal Gear Solid 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did I just say that?
[SPEAKER_13]: They listed it twice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: There also is Metal Gear Solid for PlayStation and Metal Gear 20th Anniversary Metal Gear Solid Portable Ops for PSP re-releases, I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, yay, you can just go to your used video game store and get them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they going to redo graphics or anything?
[SPEAKER_13]: It doesn't say anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's just basically repackaged, repriced.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whoopie!
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I wouldn't discount the fact that something else might come out with it to make it all kind of special, but it doesn't say anything yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I'm not going to put any stock until I get something official.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, something coming soon, or at least a rumor will be coming soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tony Erickson, of course, the rumor's been going around saying that there's going to be a PSP phone coming soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, apparently there's been a patent that's been spotted on the US Patent website, and there's some pretty hard evidence there showing kind of a prototype of something that looks like a very thick phone that's going to have a rotatable screen, almost looks like a PSP, just a little bit thicker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of the same stuff, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: This thing looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes me think of the great phone taco.
[SPEAKER_04]: The N-Gage?
[SPEAKER_13]: I had a phone taco.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: You had an N-Gage?
[SPEAKER_13]: I told you I had one.
[SPEAKER_13]: They gave us one for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loser.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was free and we gave it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheap loser.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so that's what it would be.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes more sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like what would happen is you'd actually have your directional button and stuff like you'd normally have on a phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, and then that whole screen would flip around and then you would have kind of like a PSP looking thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that would work very well.
[SPEAKER_13]: It looks unwieldy and kind of crappy like the Blackberries do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just, you know, PSPs aren't that expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just stick with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Turn the PSP into a phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about get a phone, get a PSP?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I would rather have a phone that I can do two things on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Number one, call people.
[SPEAKER_13]: Number two, text message.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's frickin' it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's why I paid 30 bucks for my phone.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I have a nice phone.
[SPEAKER_13]: But if I want to play a video game, then I'll just get something that's dedicated to video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can take pictures with my phone, which is fine because I have a camera and all, but sometimes you can take pictures with your camera phone when people don't know it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, that would be a number three.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be a number three.
[SPEAKER_13]: But seriously, this iPhone crap and this PSP phone crap, why don't you just...
[SPEAKER_13]: Get a PSP or get an iPod.
[SPEAKER_13]: How hard is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: PSPs are pretty large, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't really want to use it as a phone.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, if somebody gave me an iPhone, I wouldn't disagree.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or if I got a big fat discount on one, I wouldn't disagree.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it was not something that I think is worth $600 for, and neither would this PSP phone thing be.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a phone that works, and I have one PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: and I have a bunch of DS's so I can just play whatever you can probably buy a pretty nice phone for $600 I'd like to think my phone is pretty nice it was only $200 a year ago I could buy like a full GPS system with you know built in headphones to talk to anybody in the world for enough money but you know why would I want to do that I have my phone I think that all of this is ridiculous it's just because people are tech addicts and need to have something that does more than it needs to do
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, you know, on that PSP, you could play this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also being reported in Famitsu is that a new version of Ultimate Ghosts and Goblins is coming out for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out in Japan, and they're redoing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be kind of making the game a little closer to its arcade roots.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number of continues is going to be limited, and players will be forced to complete the game twice before seeing the ending.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it
[SPEAKER_04]: In other words, they've made this game even harder than it was before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was pretty hard before.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ghosts and Goblins, it better be hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: So August 2nd is the day the game is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: No import plans announced yet for the game to come out in North America, but we can all hold our breath.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe we'll get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm sure it'll be dumbed down and made easy, just like most of the games they bring over from Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe we'll die first.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more story, then we're going to get to our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or you can call us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is our username.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, two more stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is our username on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two more stories, my bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, at any rate, you remember the whole Second Life exploitation that was going on?
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't we cover that last week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it involve cock-throwing?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, at any rate, a Pennsylvania attorney is taking Linden Labs to court because she's saying that they illegally took away the items that were supposed to have been acquired during, let me see the quote, allegedly acquired using an exploit by an SL user.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was banned, lost everything, and the
[SPEAKER_13]: Court actually is denying the request to dismiss the case.
[SPEAKER_13]: They've denied it twice.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's actually a big quote on here that says, The case will still need to play out and only concerns the sum of $8,000.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, it appears that greater scrutiny and enforcement of commerce within Second Life and other virtual worlds is possible and may be necessary.
[SPEAKER_13]: The commerce, largely characterized by pyramid schemes, faulty valuations, and unreal exchange rates could be subject to real-world law.
[SPEAKER_13]: So,
[SPEAKER_02]: That's when you make third life.
[SPEAKER_02]: But second life is too real for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to third life.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if someone steals all my equipment in World of Warcraft, I can like sue them over it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be kind of cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm suing you for vandalizing my building by throwing cocks at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn you to hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: If someone threw cocks at me, I'd sue them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking I should sue these guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Codemasters.
[SPEAKER_02]: They never seem to fail me when it comes to thinking up video game ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're creating Dirty Dancing, the video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's right, Dirty Dancing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Such a wonderful game, and I don't know what the hell they could be doing with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat idea if they pull it off, but I really wish they'd put this baby in the corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: because it's kind of late.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to put her down.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently it says working alongside a team at Kellerman's Resort playthrough, a fantastic variety of fun mini-games, earned camp dollars to purchase Dirty Dancing memorabilia, cabin furnishings, and all-important dance lessons with Johnny and Penny.
[SPEAKER_02]: How will you fare in the end-of-the-season dance contest?
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't they already try bringing back the Dirty Dancing franchise with that Havana Nights movie or whatever it was that tanked?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it tanked, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree with WonderDogCarol.
[SPEAKER_04]: WonderDogCarol says, I want Mannequin the video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: With that one guy with the glasses?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell was his name?
[SPEAKER_04]: The really flamey guy in the movie that was like the assist... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know somebody's going to yell it in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mannequin the video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirty Dancing the Game, DarkSakura, Hollywood, BlackBoy
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get to the Skype line, shall we?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you'd like to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The phones are now open for business, so give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll just sit here and wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, great, we got some calls coming in already.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a little bit of a delay, so it takes a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you already know this Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Zaku, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about, now I know you're into cell phone games, what do you think about Legion Suit Larry on the mobile phones?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, I haven't seen it yet, but I would assume it has to be, you know, it has to be like text and graphics based, where you just have to like, you know, it's like basically text and images based.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically the whole... It's just the whole premise of cell phone games just to garner the casual gamer's attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, if it works out, that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe some pixelated boobies, who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, what did you call in about tonight, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, you know, just random stuff like the fact that, um... I forgot what I was going to say, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's like, I don't know, just getting, you know, about Tekken 6 and the fact that, you know, all the rumors about it going to 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, just in general of how the state of affairs is with, you know, with trying to make games.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're starting to lose exclusives because everything's going multi-platform.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask DarkSakura a little bit about this because you're right, we didn't talk about Tekken 6 tonight at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just kind of missed our show role.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: It'll look a little bit better, play a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that and Namco has just been all about Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then you also have Ace Combat 6, which is 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a time exclusive, which the PS3 version will come afterwards.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's kind of like the inverse.
[SPEAKER_02]: It probably also helps that the Tekken 6 arcade hardware is built off the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's probably pretty simple to port it over to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might take a little longer for Xbox 360, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, they're going to put it over on the 360 at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you looked at the recent Mini E3, you know, lineup list that they had, apparently, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like all I see is like very few exclusive, you know, PS3 games from other companies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, obviously, Sony's the only one making their own PS3 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, who knows, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony may have some surprises in store.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't really...
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, usually the announcements about what we're going to see at E3 is shit we already know about that was delayed from last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, a lot of it's going to be surprises, but I'm assuming if E3 operates any similar way this year that it did last year, which I'm assuming will be the same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chances are it's going to be much smaller, much more closed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, besides that, I mean, the way the news works, you know, I think that'll still kind of pretty much be the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: The big boys who get in will have to feed off of them eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: At some point, the rest of the internet will get fed up with it, but we'll just wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, anyway, Zaku, anything else on your mind before we take some other calls?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We New Yorkers have 2DX Happy Sky in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, where at?
[SPEAKER_07]: Same place where we find the only pop music machine in the city, Peter Pan Games in Queens.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might have to look that place up while I'm out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, later, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, 877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones and take another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Ranma, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: How'd you enjoy your trip out to California?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, it was fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we're having a hard time hearing you, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get a little closer to your microphone.
[SPEAKER_01]: I said I had fun and I enjoyed it very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like to somehow make my way out there for a weekend just to have fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're a fun bunch here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to call in and talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, one of the things everybody's been bitching on me about are pictures.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I'm posting a link in the chat room right now for the pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, do you have pictures of the panel and stuff?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a few pictures of the panel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's djranmas.mypockybox.com My Pocky Box?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, mypockybox.com
[SPEAKER_01]: forward slash gallery forward slash Fondame 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at some of the pictures right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got tons and tons of cosplayers.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was some of your favorite cosplay you saw?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I don't have to be biased, but I was really going for the Ranma 1.5 cosplays because there's been a while where not many people are cosplaying that series, but now lately, this is making one hell of a comeback.
[SPEAKER_04]: The series is kind of old, though, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but great series like that never go old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you know, one of the favorite pieces of cosplay I saw was actually Jonas, who's been on OLR before.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's been on this program before.
[SPEAKER_04]: He cosplayed as a Wii remote.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was him?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was him.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was actually going to come to the show tonight, but I don't think he got the address in time of where we're at now, because we've been in like four different studios.
[SPEAKER_04]: He hasn't been on the show in a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, that was one of my favorite pieces of cosplay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, there's the Dolphy pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's the OLR panel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we are.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Sky, who are you choking in this picture?
[SPEAKER_01]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me look.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number 124.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just posted it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who am I choking in this picture?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought Drew Nami was on the other side.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's Drew.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got a bunch of Orange Lounge Radio listeners there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of my friends, Ken, he took the picture for all of us.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't know you took a picture of my Dolphies on the table.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you asked me to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, the one in the hotel room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I thought you knew about that one.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a good picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anything else you want to share with us, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_01]: The last picture of you and William together in the chat room, the one that everybody loves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, is that in the gallery?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you putting personal pictures?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's my trip picture still.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see, because at the very end, oh, yeah, DarkSakura's pinball, all that stuff at her house, all the crazy pinball at her place.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's my friend John.
[SPEAKER_04]: How funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I decided next year, though, that I'm going to do Lolita Mario.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, the Gachamon cosplayers, that's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well Ranma, thanks so much for coming out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are a true fan, pretty hardcore, for coming out all the way to California to see the Orange Lounge panel and hang with us and go to Fatame and all that too, but you're just awesome, that's all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, plus it was my birthday the day before.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was a version of a giant birthday gift to myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drew, that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, happy late birthday a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll see you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be seeing you this weekend, the coming weekend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I will be posting a post in the forum so we can get things cracking for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, just make sure it happens Sunday afternoon because that's the time I got.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's go to some more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Raven Stolfen!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Raven Stolfen, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Match Game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, what about Match Game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know if you realize, but in GSM, when they used to do Match Game online, and I was really good at it, and I got on the board on TV that said your name on it, I was heavily addicted to that for a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't they still do that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but Comcast being dicks, they took off my...
[SPEAKER_10]: took off GSN entirely down here, and I'm pissed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't talk a whole lot about casual games on the show, certainly, but that's pretty cool that they have the, you know, you can play along with the game shows and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually never done that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love myself some game show networks, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but we cheated sometimes because some people watched it so many times they'd write down the answers and it was posted up in the chat room and we would get on the leaderboard every time.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else do you want to share with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: What else do I want to share with you tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to point that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no one more thing tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I updated my website.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to hear about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheap website plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make it quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Checkinggame.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I just remembered what I want to talk to you about.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hotel Dusk, Ring 215.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know much about, well, I mean, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know about the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played the game because it's just one of those games that is, you know, I can't play every game that comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about it, though?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not like Phoenix Wright, but I enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was very enjoyable.
[SPEAKER_10]: What makes it so enjoyable?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you play this guy called Kyle Hyde, and he goes to this place, and the room is magical.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this room grants wishes.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he goes in there, he doesn't know anything, and I'm not going to spoil anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he goes in there, and he's trying to find something out about his friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's very interesting how all this comes together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, I know Miklatov has the game, so I'll have to borrow it from him at some point and give a more fair review on the show later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's very enjoyable, I thought, but there's a lot of reading, so for you people that hate Super Paper Mario, you're probably going to hate this too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you hate Super Paper Mario because it's too much reading, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, anything else real quick, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, not Ranma, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at Ranma's pictures in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else, Raven's Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I just updated my website, and I just want people to know how it looks.
[SPEAKER_10]: TechieGames.com Alright, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, thank you so much for the phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, 877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, this is BlackDevilRx.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, BlackDevilerX, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, not much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, I'm trying to get a Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: San Francisco seems to be out of Wiis.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, so does Sacramento and a lot of areas seem to still be out of Wiis after all this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt, you can give us a distribution angle here, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell's going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still some coming in, it's just, it's slow.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still, everything's under, you know, allocations and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there a particular time that's best to check?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Sunday mornings seem to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of places are keeping them under wraps until Sundays when they put out their ads.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_02]: For a lot of retail chains.
[SPEAKER_06]: EB Games hasn't seen one for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you still do pre-orders with these guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do they not do that anymore?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of hesitate to do stuff online because I kind of had a real bad experience with it, but I suppose that's one thing I could do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: James Patrick in chat says, My Toys R Us got 200 of them on Memorial Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was there trying to get one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sold out in 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: My God.
[SPEAKER_04]: After all this time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that just goes to show, Wii's still a pretty darn successful system.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to get one for myself, like, kind of as a graduation present.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what have you been playing since you're Wii-less?
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I've been playing a lot of Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: In anticipation for the new one on the Wii someday?
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about all the stuff they've announced on the site recently, like the musicians and the power-ups and all that, and using the GameCube controller?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't actually checked out the site lately, but I've heard that Snake's going to be in there, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they have more of those single-player type modes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember how they had the old-school Mario level that you played Mario?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That stuff was so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they have more of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, BlackDevilerX, thank you so much for the call, and good luck on your hunt for a Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Try Sunday mornings.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the best advice we got.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, later, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you would like to give us a call, you can give us a call at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username is Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll take one more call here and then we're going to go ahead and call it a night on the Skype line and do some last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although it does seem to me it's been kind of a slow news week, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Compared to usual.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's because Memorial Day kind of got in the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of folks, video game employees want to go camping too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: No other calls coming in?
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw some others hitting on the line.
[SPEAKER_12]: God, my pinball room is hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's pictures of my garage with my amazing washing machine with my laundry in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's pictures of my huge ass on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, it looks horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: My ass doesn't look so bad in that picture.
[SPEAKER_13]: You see that Rocky and Bullinkle machine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an awesome machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Twilight Zone is mine, too, because the play board was made on my birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I wish they would have gotten a shot of the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Dark Knight, it's just a timing thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I saw that there were a bunch of people trying to get through, and then nobody for a minute and a half, and we're sitting here going...
[SPEAKER_04]: While you got through, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought I wanted to talk about something I posted on the website recently about a price cut of Lumenfall's next-gen system.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I would think that I knew it was coming, but this early was kind of a shocker.
[SPEAKER_11]: Being this early was kind of a big shocker to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, what about me again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you were breaking up a little.
[SPEAKER_04]: You say price cuts?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they said there might be a possible next-gen price cut.
[SPEAKER_04]: What makes this information more substantial?
[SPEAKER_04]: To be fair, it seems like every month we're getting some rumor of an upcoming price cut, and we have yet to really see a big one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, basically, the latest I got was that they said that Microsoft was going to go first at the end of the summer, and like a $50 drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would honestly think Microsoft's in a safe place right now until Sony drops their... Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Microsoft wants to try and get down there to compete with the Wii a little more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because honestly, if they dropped their core by $50, they'd be the same price as a Wii, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's what it was intended.
[SPEAKER_11]: They wanted it to be at least the same price as a Wii, the core.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see why not.
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems to make a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, I want your angle on this because you're kind of on the inside in this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't think that they have any firm plans on dropping any price, but obviously they're probably going to be ready to if other companies do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But some console makers are probably going to have to drop the price of their system.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, all these analysts just saying, oh, there's a price drop coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's a price drop coming eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're just trying to get out there and say, hey, see, we called it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're really good at analyzing stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say...
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we're analysts, too, of sorts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really, what do we do on this show for the past five years, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I would say if a price cut's coming, it's going to be just before the Christmas rush.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I would say, honestly, price cuts, I think end of summer's a good call.
[SPEAKER_04]: September.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say you're going to see some massive price cuts in September.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when I say, maybe like 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: 50 bucks on the 360 and the Wii, maybe, even.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially if it's... The source I got it from, they said Nintendo might not, would probably not think about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But maybe like just maybe the 360 and the PS3, possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if Nintendo announced this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we still know the Wii's are coming in different colors, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if they release the Wii's in different colors with no game included?
$199.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that would be good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I could do it right there or put in some other type of pack in like, I don't know, demos or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, just take Wii Sports out of the picture, charge $199 for the colored Wii's.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I could probably see that happening.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I knew it was coming, but I kind of figured maybe you might see it like maybe another year at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, by September, $50 price cuts on Wii and 360, $100 price cut on PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I was a Batman, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I say a $100 price cut on PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then again, they don't have to, actually, because what they could do is just, since they've already dropped their 60 gig or whatever, drop the 80 gig at the same price as their 60 and maybe do... Throw in a game or something to make it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, not necessarily throw it in a game, but do the 20 gig price for the 60 gig now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, then if they don't cut it by 100, they'll put something in there to sweeten the deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they'll drop it by 50, but put $50 worth of extra crap in it, like another game, the hard drive increase, like you're saying, something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I mean, worst case scenario is that if, like I said, PlayStation 3 does make that cut, you're probably going to see the PS2 hit the $99 mark.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I saw the thing, and I was like,
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't believe you told that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, thank you so much, Dark Knight, for your call, and we'll see what happens on the price cut front.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, take care, buddy.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going on to some... Lots and lots of comments from chat here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob D. says, I wouldn't be enjoying my 360 half as much if I wasn't a member of an online community.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wii doesn't really have much of anything going for it at the moment beyond the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: James Patrick says PlayStation 2 won't drop to $99 for a while Sony needs the profit from its current price let's see James Patrick says PlayStation 3 sales are in the gutter that needs to increase software wise I mean hardware is important too but software is what counts Blackboy says the 360 has been out considerably longer than the Wii but in terms of sales Wii is outselling 360 by crazy amounts
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting perspectives there in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackDevilerX says, We're using the Dreamcast as the minimum bar for sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, if you have more comments, you can always send us an email, mailbag at orangelondradio.com, and we'll read those emails next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, not next week, but in two weeks on the program, because a reminder, there will be no show next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and see if there's any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, I found something interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just some early pictures of the Guitar Hero 3 Les Paul controller.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pretty freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's so special about it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, they've done two other Gibson guitars.
[SPEAKER_13]: They did probably one of, in my opinion, one of their best.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, I'm going to link the article in the chat room so they can see the pictures.
[SPEAKER_13]: It actually looks really sweet, and the buttons on it...
[SPEAKER_13]: are black with the colored outlines.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's really a lot different than the other controllers have looked.
[SPEAKER_13]: More minimalist.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so I actually got quite a few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, some interesting stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, first off, there's supposed to be a rumor that the next issue of EGM is going to reveal a brand new Soul Calibur title.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Soul Calibur Legends, I'm guessing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, who knows, maybe they're doing that again.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could use the next gen Soul Calibur game, that'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, a new Soul Calibur game possibly being announced, so that'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another rumor that's going on, apparently a website, RPG Gamer, had an interview with NS America, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the questions was, or according to the Q&A, one of the answers to a question, is Disgaea coming into any other platforms?
[SPEAKER_02]: They mentioned the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you might get Disgaea on the DS soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, there's an interesting thing going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, certain...
[SPEAKER_02]: Lawyer type by the name of Jack was supposed to be... Voldemort?
[SPEAKER_04]: You mean Lord Voldemort?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Voldemort was apparently going to be debating or participating in a debate during PAX this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, this was supposed to be kept under wraps and no word if he's going to back out of that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had heard he already did because he put out some retort to... He thought it was...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: and VideoOut for playing on your television as well as SD card for game storage and etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, kind of nifty to see him actually making a console instead of modding them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking about homebrew stuff, there was a game I talked about on the show a while back called No Gravity.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like a Descent Free Space type game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I showed it to you, Rob, one time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The best fucking homebrew game ever on the PSP and they're actually going to have it finished in June.
[SPEAKER_02]: Full version will be coming out
[SPEAKER_02]: For free!
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's really sad because the game can, you know, wipe most of those other PSP games out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's developed independently and for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check out No Gravity later on this month.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: One other thing that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also a trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently Capcom made a trademark for Apollo Justice.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's two rumors regarding this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people think it's going to be a new rival schools game because apparently I guess the school is named Apollo or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's Justice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Justice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other theory is that it's a subtitle for the next Phoenix Wright game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could be either or, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: I want more rival schools, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a real quick last-minute story as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, Loki, you'll like this one, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1UP recently had an interview with the creator of the Mega Man franchise, and they were asking him about sequels and bringing Mega Man to the next-gen platforms.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he basically said, well, don't know if we would be able to recoup the cost of making a game on the next-gen platforms.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they said, come on, just imagine money wasn't an issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said this, quote,
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would probably be Mega Man Legends 3 and that's just not or that's not just me a lot of the original team members would also love to make a sequel they talk about it I talk about it sometimes I know they love that series and so do I if I were to say right now I have a tiny tiny tiny dream that I wish I could realize but I don't know if it's possible it would be to do a sequel in the Legends series hell yeah that's a series that they need to take it even further because these other series kind of suck that's a series they need to shoot in the head put it down like an old horse put her down
[SPEAKER_13]: Give me more Mega Man X, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the Legends series.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, I'm a 2D gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to see some type of next-gen Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's okay to do a 2D Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Continue Legends series on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's an original PlayStation game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can definitely push those kind of graphics on that system.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_13]: I do.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_13]: And for me, just to have it go 3D in the first place was like...
[SPEAKER_13]: Ripping out my heart and dancing the Lambada on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you like the Mega Man X series and the original Mega Man series.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a different series.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like the Marvel series now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the Marvel 2017 series and the Marvel Universe series and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just don't have to like this series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like this series, so they should make another one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I could say is, please, anything but those tactical games on the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: Amen, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we can all agree on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That series, put it to bed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Going on the same thing, though, that Loki's saying, that's actually based off of a completely different series.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Mega Man EXE is what those were.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, or the Battle Network, that's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it was Rockman EXE.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put it to bed.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was actually based off of an anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put a bullet in its head and be done.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not the same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is supposed to be Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is actually something 100% completely different, just borrowing the name.
[SPEAKER_13]: It makes sense why it's a different type of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: And James Patrick says in chat, Mega Man, Mega Man Legends, Mega Man X, Mega Man Zero, Mega Man Battle Network, Mega Man... Stop this!
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as they don't do a next-gen series that looks like the cover of Mega Man 2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: The US Capcom art in those days, I mean, did you see the cover for Bionic Commando?
[SPEAKER_04]: They were pretty awful.
[SPEAKER_13]: The only cool game that had any, you know, American redone art that was any good was like Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because the dude looked like, you know, hardcore awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, the truck has started to move.
[SPEAKER_13]: But at least in Bionic Commando you can kill Hitler.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and you know what, some of the,
[SPEAKER_04]: I always think of the box art even back from the Atari 2600 days where they had these elaborate artwork on the box, which of course the game looked nothing like because it was just a bunch of blocks on the screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Box art's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, why don't you start us off tonight, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I thought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is the screen for the Wii thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a portable screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still wouldn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until next time, thank you so much for tuning into and supporting independent podcasting and independent radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll see you in two weeks because there's no show next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you enjoy the show, please tell a friend or two and post a review of us on iTunes or whatever website you use to get our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We really appreciate the support.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two weeks!
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that from Total Recall?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!