[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, June 17th, 2007, Soul Calibur preps its fourth game for the PlayStation 3 and 360, Sony builds itself a blog, and has Project Hammer gotten some nails in its coffin?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's good to be back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were off last week and we missed you guys, but we're back this week to talk about the latest in video games, the gaming world, gaming culture, and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts and with me here, as always, right by my side, hanging on to my arm, clutching it, sucking the very life out of it, is Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ripping it off and beating you with it, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that like an attack you can do in Dead Rising, actually?
[SPEAKER_02]: It happened in Shaun of the Dead, except they ripped off his legs and then went after zombies with him.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the best scene in the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: OMG, spoilers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who hasn't seen Shaun of the Dead yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Go see Hot Fuzz, everybody, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here goes the chat room going, me, me, me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us, say hello to Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you seen Shaun of the Dead, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, twice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I have to admit, when DarkSakura, like, you know, because she does movie nights once in a while at her place, and I admit when she first, you know, was like, let's watch Shaun of the Dead, I was like, oh, God, all right, fine, we'll watch a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only two hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you were there a couple years ago, but we did Shaun of the Dead, and then we watched the new Dawn of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I think it was in the reverse.
[SPEAKER_03]: We watched the new Dawn of the Dead, and then Shaun of the Dead, and
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't there because I never saw the new Dawn of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the new Dawn of the Dead sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shaun of the Dead was awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Hot Fuzz is better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still haven't seen Hot Fuzz.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot Fuzz is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen it twice now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, give me one of yours.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to see it with Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: I seriously can't remember the last... That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we left, you guys went to the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I go see Transformers early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Before it comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you spend that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Through work and stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, through work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: A few days.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we a movie podcast?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, they're making a game based on it, and it's going to be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they should make a game out of Shaun of the Dead, shouldn't they?
[SPEAKER_04]: They should.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot Fuzz would be funny, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: A romantic comedy with zombies in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of these days, I seriously think the last movie I saw in the theater was Notes on a Scandal, which they should not make into a video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that would be a very interesting video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can control Judi Dench as she creates...
[SPEAKER_04]: Lesbian Scandal.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you take notes on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, I've been spending the whole week looking for my copy of Elite Beat Agents because Dan wants to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And playing some World of Warcraft, like hardly any, because I still want Burning Crusade so I can play a hot little elf.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You still haven't gotten Burning Crusade?
[SPEAKER_02]: What money do I have, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You certainly don't get paid for this, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't have much money, so no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless someone in the chatroom wants to buy it for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sell a pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're the spouse's.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to verify, because I haven't been reading up too much on Fable 2, you will still able to be a bisexual evil warlord, correct?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, yes, and you can get pregnant.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I'm a male, that might be difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that might be difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be a real fable right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There once was a pregnant man.
[SPEAKER_03]: They definitely do not, like,
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to be uber evil.
[SPEAKER_03]: so it's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other game I played was Monster Madness and now this game I was kind of looking forward to check out because it reminded me of Zombies Ate My Neighbors and who doesn't like Zombies Ate My Neighbors?
[SPEAKER_03]: This game is no Zombies Ate My Neighbors and it's awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: The controls in it, awful and it's way too damn hard so I don't recommend it at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other games I played, Mad Trax, I actually tried that out a little bit and that was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played through a few levels of that, although there really isn't too much to the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can probably beat it pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're kind of trying to sell those additional add-ons for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, not my thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't play Pac-Man Championship Edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: I looked at it, downloaded the demo, still haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm sorry, it's a sequel to Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have more to say on this, but I'll wait my turn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Dan downloaded that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, okay, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: He was like, I came home, all I was doing was freaking screaming at the ghosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't he do that all the time?
[SPEAKER_02]: He was really screaming at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was, like, calling them bastards.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, dude, you sound like me talking to my computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I downloaded the Project Sylphid demo today, but I forgot to play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I finished Super Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the end is, like, you saw it coming throughout the entire game, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like, once you finish it, you're rewarded with... Don't you fucking spoil it!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not going to spoil it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, once you finish the game, you're rewarded with, hey, you get to go back to this one level and fight 100 people, and they'll take another couple hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what the whole game is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's full of this, like, fight 100 people, do that for two hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, are you saying at the end of the game, you get told, we're sorry, Mario, but our princess is in another castle?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's more like...
[SPEAKER_03]: We're sorry, Mario, but your game sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more like, thank you for playing through the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: No replay value whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sell it back to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that's pretty much what I'm going to have to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did download Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why, but I've actually been playing this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can lend it to me before you sell it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can borrow my copy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not playing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you really want to play it, I'll loan you mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, you know, after you...
[SPEAKER_03]: Played through all of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just kind of... There's a bunch of side quests you can do that have no reward whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, Zelda 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I was talking about Super Mario.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Zelda 2 is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, Zelda 2 is fucking rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why people diss it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like one of the worst in the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go fucking play Wand of Gamelon if you want to see the worst ones in the series, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't feel like Zelda at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just very strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I remember playing through it and it being very hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: It still is kind of hard, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I can understand it more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did the name of everything really strange names is beyond me?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am Error.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went in and I'm like, oh, there's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that was actually supposed to have been something else, and it programmed in wrong, if I remember right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: With the translation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want that on a shirt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am Error.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's got to be a shirt somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can just have one made, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe his name is just Error.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to name my firstborn Error.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, fucking look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be a horrible thing for parents to do, to name their baby Error.
[SPEAKER_06]: With the middle name Oops.
[SPEAKER_03]: Error, Oops, Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, finally, the last game I've been playing, and this is weird because I've actually played this game more than I've played Guitar Hero, but it uses the Guitar Hero controller for the 360, and it's a game for the PC called Fret Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: The best way to describe it is it's like playing Loco Roco with a guitar, and it actually works pretty well.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they've got some really interesting level designs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only bad thing about it is it's only three levels long, but it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I recommend downloading that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I may post a link to it in my blog on all games so that you can actually find it because it's on some foreign website or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's cool and it's free, so I highly recommend doing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I don't play the
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Hero, it's weird we did this thing on Friday last week that it was basically this sales team building thing and we had to perform songs on stage and they have video of it but anyways they had like one person had the air guitar so I had to do the air guitar part of it because I didn't want to sing
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Hero Guitar Hero Guitar Hero Guitar Hero Guitar Hero Guitar Hero
[SPEAKER_03]: or because you were on the internet radio program about music video games therefore you can pass every catastrophic and DDR oh yeah back in the day maybe I could three quarters of those back in the day I wasn't so fat exactly because I played more DDR exactly then you get married and you don't have DDR time and it all goes downhill from there anything else about your gaming week you want to share um
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I played more Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got my last copy of Saints Row, and so we're going to be landing those five systems together very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just in time for the sequel, maybe?
[SPEAKER_03]: Saints Row 2, that's not coming out for a while, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: in New York City, and that was a great time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually went to Dave & Buster's in Times Square and just kind of messed around there for a little while and played this game called Jumpin' Jackpot, which is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have one of these at Roseville Golf Line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it's the virtual jump rope with the lights going around, and it plays this really super gay rave music while you're jumping.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's hard, and it's crack.
[SPEAKER_04]: You keep putting money in over and over.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we played some DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had, like, Superdome.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were playing a bunch of stuff, and it was a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you laughing at?
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave and Busters.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I have enough tickets to buy an Xbox 360 game, but I'm just not interested in anything that they have there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, so big thanks to all the listeners that showed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also went, Ranma took me to this video game shop, or I think he was the one that led the way, I mean all of us kind of went there, all of us that were still together at this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We went to this video game shop near Aster Place, where the big cube is, and they had like tons of stuff, like I sent you the picture of the Hello Kitty Dreamcast, and all these important stuff, but they were selling old school NES games, and my friend has an old school Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it in the box?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was just the card and the black sleeve.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I bought mine, I paid $10 and I got it in the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I got her an original cartridge of Guardian Legends, so that made me happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Completely unopened.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, my Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_02]: I opened it to play it, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, I got her a copy of Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should have just took it home with me, but I don't have an old school Nintendo here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm holding out hope they will put it on Virtual Console eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who do you know in this room who has five Nintendos?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to give me one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably, I could.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me talk to Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then maybe I'm going to send Amanda back to that store and get me more games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just buy a Generation Next.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, we'll talk about that later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's this other thing coming out I'll talk about later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, it's already out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, isn't it on the show roll?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, this is something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the thing we saw at E3 like a few years back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that thing!
[SPEAKER_04]: The $20 console thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: $60, yeah.
$60?
[SPEAKER_03]: $60 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they were only charging people $20 or was that just at the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was at the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should have bought it at the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, so yeah, obviously there was some 8-bit gaming goodness, Dave and Busters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I finally caved and I got a DS Lite, which by the way, I saw this story floating around blogs this week talking about how Nintendo World has these custom DS Lites that you can buy in all these different colors.
[SPEAKER_04]: They wanted $280 for those.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the picture that's floating around doesn't show you all the colors that they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they added some or what because I distinctly remember there was a green one because that's the one I wanted to get and you don't see that one in the pictures that made it around all the different game blogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check DJ Ranma's picture site which I'm sure he'll link in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's DJRanmaS.net and check out his New York City pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: He actually took a picture of the case with all the colors and some of the newer ones that were in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was between that and the fuchsia hot pink one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what the fucking website is but there is a website out there that you can buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: custom colored anything consoles $280 they wanted for that well you can buy it cheaper than that they sell iPods there they sell PSPs you know DS lights everything and you can get them in custom colors so I'm not sure about DS lights but I know they sold the original DS on this site but people just forget they can do that or just paint it I don't know take it apart and paint the damn thing
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, uh, well they also do engraving there, and I almost bought my new DS Lite at the Nintendo World Store to get it engraved, because they'll engrave your DS for only like 20 bucks, and there's all these patterns you can choose from, and I thought that was pretty awesome, but their engraving machine was broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I didn't get to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, sucks to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're engraving machines that I am error.
[SPEAKER_04]: But basically, when I got to Pennsylvania, I was like, well, sales tax is lower here than it is in California.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was so bored in Pennsylvania, I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: No offense to those of you folks that live in the Allentown area where I was at for a few days, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And you don't want your opponent, who's going to go after you, to be able to line up the skulls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because basically, to explain the game real fast, there's the story that all goes with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can cast spells, which are like special moves on the board, but to do that requires mana.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so the stones on the board are red, yellow, blue, and green.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you also have gold coins, purple experience stars, and skulls.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you line up the coins, you get gold.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you line up the experience stars, you get experience, so you can level up.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you line up the skulls, your opponent takes damage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest Puzzle League
[SPEAKER_04]: to really play, to give it a fair response.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know it's, I played it once, and I know it's very similar, of course, to Pokemon Puzzle League, but with some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You totally reminded me of the other game I was playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pokemans!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Pearl and Diamond?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or what do you have, Diamond?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Pearl?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm being not like everybody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have Pearl, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bah!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're being like me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bah!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm being different.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you having fun with your Pokemans?
[SPEAKER_02]: At the gym, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've learned the fine art of playing Pokemans on the elliptical.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX Live Arcades in an Arcade
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up with Namco and the rave-y soundtrack games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Namco made that Flaming Finger game at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made the Jumpin' Jackpot game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's rave whores that work.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all on Ecstasy over there or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pac-Man Championship Edition and also I played Prince of Persia Classic.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game looks beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the way they redid the graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the best...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Checking out the chat room, www.OrangeLaunchRadio.com Click on chat or you can go directly to chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com We tape live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackDevilerX agrees with Loki's I want to see Xbox Live Arcade in an arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should.
[SPEAKER_04]: TheRobD says, I hate Flaming Finger.
[SPEAKER_04]: And JVmon says, Flaming Finger told Sky to get his flame on.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the game said, when you start the game, have you played Flaming Finger at Dave & Buster's?
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched you play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and when you start it, you're playing footsie with my hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever you put your money in the game, whatever it says, get your flame on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm gay, and you know, they say flaming or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking at what else is going on in chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Gerardimo says, Pokemon Puzzle League sucked because it had no Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Making a reference to the old school Tetris Attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: GS68 points out there's a Ms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pac-Man machine at Miggle, Milpitas Golf Land, a very infamous arcade here in California.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blackboy says, I think I need the Fuchsia DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's almost a flaming DS Lite right there, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well that sounds like it's about it for our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's get into some housekeeping real, real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're going to get into tonight's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a whole lot of housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: A happy 100th episode to Bobby, because he had his 100th episode tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So congrats to Bobby Blackwolf, our friend over at AllGames.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of AllGames.com, you can always hear the rebroadcast of our program over there Monday nights at 5.30 Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: They replay our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's A and B back-to-back, so sometimes you have to wait for Part B on the podcast or audio blog feed for a little while.
[SPEAKER_04]: They replay it over there Monday nights and Tuesday mornings at 9 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We obviously missed a week last week, so Loki, tell us about what we missed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, some stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess the Halo 3 beta ended, so everybody's sad because they have to wait for the Halo 3 actual game to come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: They got a good turnout.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, Bungie was saying that they've clocked so many hours of Halo 3 that they could have
[SPEAKER_03]: If they were to create, I guess, one-on-one games using the same amount of time in that beta, they would have 700 years worth of gameplay, so... Go analysts!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, other rumors... I played it twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played it once.
[SPEAKER_03]: I beat you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Parappa 3, rumored to be coming to the PS3, and this, of course, is coming from EGM.
[SPEAKER_03]: No other information on that other than it's rumored.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's kind of saying, like, duh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Prince of Persia, the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming out July 10th, 2009.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody is excited because it's going to be very Pirates of the Caribbean-like.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hurrah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another updated or upgraded graphic version of Metal Gear Solid 4's Tokyo Game Show trailer has made it online with a little interesting...
[SPEAKER_03]: Bit that's missing towards the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people will notice that the PlayStation 3 logo is missing at the very end of the trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming to 360!
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear to God, this game's coming to 360!
[SPEAKER_06]: This game is coming to the 360!
[SPEAKER_06]: Why aren't you people listening to me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are going crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_04]: When they're ready to announce it on the 360, they will announce it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, they probably will, but keep your pants on in the meantime.
[SPEAKER_04]: God.
[SPEAKER_03]: And next being announced, coming to film, ultra-generic video game movie 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other words, City of Heroes is going to be adapted to film and TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I don't know, it's just a parody of all the other superhero things out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, generic superhero movie, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, Mrs. Coming to the DS, hurrah!
[SPEAKER_03]: Lego MMO coming in 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomb Raider Anniversary Edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, Tomb Raider is so fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woohoo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually coming to the 360, possibly as download content.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is coming from readings found on the ESRB's website.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people are thinking that's going to be download content, possibly for Tomb Raider Legends.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Pac-Man Championship Edition was released for the 360 and I guess it's the first actual sequel to Pac-Man, although I do remember there's like Pac-Man... Oh, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pac-Man, Junior Pac-Man... Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_02]: Pac-Man!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no!
[SPEAKER_03]: Those did not have different levels!
[SPEAKER_04]: Pac-Mania... No, no, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pac-Man Junior, though, was admittedly harder because it had the scrolling screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it just kind of sucked, generally.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Super Pac-Man, Super Pac-Man was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo, what the fuck about Super Pac-Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was completely different than Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, it's new, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is coming from the people that know Pac-Man, the people that made it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, this is the first Pac-Man with raving.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the first rave-alicious Pac-Man game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it's got.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You fucking bought Pac-Man again.
[SPEAKER_03]: You suck, you stupid bastard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo has another fucking Game Boy to throw at you, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dumbass fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so, yeah, it came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ten bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: You did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm taking my head in shame.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people on my friends list did, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people bought it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then when the next Namco fucking collection comes out, there'll be Pac-Man in that, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when the next console comes out, there'll be another Pac-Man game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because people buy Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're sighing, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are you sighing?
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you not play Pac-Man World?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it'd be like the Pac-Man family from the cartoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, and there was that side-scrolling Pac-Man game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember at Glass Gaming Expo, I bought that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You did?
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought it for the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_04]: You sucker!
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was the only copy that I have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well that makes it all... It's Pac-Land!
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Pac-Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember playing Pac-Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, oh, Pac-Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is going to be interesting because it's not Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Pac-Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, wow, this sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stupid MAME.
[SPEAKER_03]: Making me play crappy games because I don't know what they are.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you went back to Miss World 96 Nude.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: If ever you want the ultimate MAME experience, you just play Blazing Star.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to introduce our special guest tonight who came in a little bit late there while Loki was doing his story.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is your first time in the studio, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the last time I went here was in...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll be cosplaying.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sexy Nojuku Iruga.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know where people are going to know you from, Explicit, is your cosplay from Fanime this year, which is actually when I told you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the greatest ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because when I ran into you, I said, you need to come back on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell them what you cosplayed as.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: For those who did not go to FanimeCon, I was the one who dressed up as the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_02]: We saw you walking by when we were heading back to the hotel room.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're like, dude, is that a Wiimote?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think I said to somebody, I'm like, that's explicit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember him when he used to come on the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: We weren't there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was walking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was with somebody.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might have been Ranma or somebody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, that's explicit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, was it you, Matt?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, so now you're back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so we were able to exchange numbers and everything, get you back here on the program to give some more FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So feel free to chime in throughout the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of games have you been playing recently?
[SPEAKER_01]: Any Wii games?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, instead of a Wii, yep, WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was actually trying to get someone to play drunk WarioWare on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, there's an idea for the fifth anniversary.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: And let's, yeah, um, let's see, I've been playing Planet Puzzle League lately.
[SPEAKER_01]: Since I've been trying to get, trying to master all these puzzle games lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was actually pretty difficult just to master itself.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a lot easier, a lot harder than like Tetris or Luminous in which...
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought it, but I've only played it once.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but I've just seen that insane video that someone sent me a while ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was like 33x combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that on YouTube somewhere?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's on YouTube somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you played Puzzle Quest?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I was raving about that earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not played that yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like role-playing games, you like puzzle games, they made this game for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, they put a little bow on it and said, here, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: For DS, PSP, and supposedly Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember us doing a story that it's coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously, just get the DS or PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I have a friend that says the PSP version looks a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't seen it myself yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm content with the DS one.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pick your poison.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so Explicit, ladies and gentlemen, is here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So feel free to chime in whenever you like.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we need to get to this week's news.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Loki, if you wouldn't mind starting us off with a little piece of the news from this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, a piece of the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, you know, if you've been listening to all games, you've probably heard about it, but Sony has officially announced the agency for PC and the PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be a brand new spy-themed MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not exactly like Spy vs. Spy, but still pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, it's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: How do I know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the screenshots look cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you've got two people firing guns at a bunch of people with guns.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's all you need is guns and people firing guns.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he has a parachute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there fire, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's gunfire, muzzle flash.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That little spot on the ground looks like it might be fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's got fire, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just as long as it's not like, you know, she spies or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are so random.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, doesn't this like hook up with the PC?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it's like Shadowrun or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I thought I heard something about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets the hook up.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, seriously, can't you play, like, with the PC people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's an MMO, so I would imagine... Is it across the two platforms, or is it that they're just separate entities?
[SPEAKER_04]: I got the impression you could play across both platforms.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe it's cross-platform.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Shadowrun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it should.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the PS3's fucking supposedly powerful enough to run this shit, so, I mean, why couldn't they do cross-platform?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would think it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like live, you know, where it's their own self-contained network.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Sony, do whatever, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's something like, you know, here's something to wait for.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like Killzone 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, Killzone 2's coming next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, great, that's awesome that it's coming next year, but we're talking now.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just like saying, you know, back when the 360 launched, ooh, but the PlayStation 3's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, goody for them, but it's not out right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, it's just like, you know, I'm gonna, well, I'm gonna bring my friends, they're gonna beat you up, so, meh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the chat room and looking at the comments there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bandit says, I'd rather play a She-Ra video game other than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, I bet a She-Ra game would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, a She-Ra game would be pretty fucking badass.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like uber-barbarian chickly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hopefully the little wizard guy is hidden somewhere in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: GS68 says, PlayStation 3, gimmicks, gimmicks, gimmicks.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Madam Raz.
[SPEAKER_04]: And RawSteelUT follows that right up saying, Not as gimmicky as the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackDevilerX says, great, that'll give the PS3 another game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And RossDLUT is also rolling his eyes going, ew, cross-platform.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard the cross-platform so far, you know, with Shadowrun's kind of not working.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to give the definitive review on the game because I have not played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to attempt to review a game based on screenshots alone.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, word on the street around my blogs and things of that nature is that Shadowrun sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't know, I won't...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what do you expect when you turn a really awesome role-playing game into a fucking hate multiplayer-only games out there?
[SPEAKER_03]: That is retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to play multiplayer games all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes I'm in the mood for it, sometimes I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Saikun's Making Angry Face in chat says Shadowrun fucking rocks.
[SPEAKER_03]: It rocks, but it would have rocked even more as a fucking RPG, like it should be, because it's a RPG.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be, you know, a game that you can do, like, from FASA or something that would be good just multiplayer only would be MechWarrior or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Silent Hill 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have my attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Might have a U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: developer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it could happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could not happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, it could happen, but it could not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, rumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking hate stories like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No offense, Jamie, because I know you're just reading what is... I didn't pick it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you're just reading what... Someone picked this like they picked their nose.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you're just reading what all the video game blogs are reporting on this week, which is fine, but... This is not news!
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not news!
[SPEAKER_02]: La la la, I could hear once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we all know that Silent Hill 5 is coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: But to hear that it might have a developer that might be doing this with it, how is that news?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's even better is it may or may not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, thank you for covering all sides of possibilities right there, because there were only two.
[SPEAKER_03]: It may or may not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sorta does.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you can't have like... You can't have 50% on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're a US developer that's right on the border of Mexico or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're built on the border.
[SPEAKER_03]: So half of them are Mexican, half of them are in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's halfway true.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's being done by the Hawaiian division.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: They all got sent out to sea, didn't you hear?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no wonder why the game's not going to get finished.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, since Hawaii, some guy's like, what the fuck is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pyramid Headwind Snorkeling, you'll just have to deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Silent Hill, Extreme Beach Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if this is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, the nurses are pretty hot, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if this is what the news is going to be like this week, then seriously, Orange Lounge Radio has been preempted this week for the Dead or Alive movie discussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boobies, boobies, boobies, boobies, boobies.
[SPEAKER_03]: See?
[SPEAKER_03]: Street Fighter 2 movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: That movie was all about Kylie Minogue.
[SPEAKER_03]: That movie killed Raul Julia.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was his last movie, that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: It killed him.
[SPEAKER_02]: He could have had... Not even the life support suit could bring him back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plenty of more years left, and that movie's just like... He didn't even go... That's so rude!
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't even go Psycho Crusher once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't he have an HBO movie, actually?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, that didn't count.
[SPEAKER_04]: That he won awards for.
[SPEAKER_02]: That movie was Clint Eastwood, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just bought the Addams Family on DVD right before I left for New York.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Raul Julia at his finest.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how I prefer to remember him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Addams Family is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Addams Family values.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and then SSJ100 Matt comes up with the perfect witty retort that only our chat room can come up with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pyramid Head snorkels and gets taken out by a stingray barb.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just lovely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pyramid Head would probably just poke the thing with his big pointy head.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, I don't have to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go get some liquor, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: This might help me through tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't help me through tonight's show, Bob!
[SPEAKER_04]: You want some?
[SPEAKER_03]: You drove, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went to go get some root beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the nice root beer, and it fucking wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice root beer!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's diet shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diet is never nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, all they have is fucking vanilla cream.
[SPEAKER_03]: I fucking hate cream soda!
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate it!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hate it, hate it, hate it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Was there a video game show here once, or was it just me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Root Beer Tapper.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, it ties in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am not deviating from the show's plan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am talking about video games, or at least one step into video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm going to read this story so I can go get some booze.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, this is actually... This is real news, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony...
[SPEAKER_04]: finally got themselves an official blog.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's give Sony a round of applause.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations, Sony, you finally caught on and you got yourselves a blog.
[SPEAKER_04]: You finally figured out, hey, maybe that Major Nelson, he seems to stay in touch with the community pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox 360 seems to know what they're doing with the community.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo, they have Reggie, very likable, very personable guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ken Kutaragi, crayon eater.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what can we do?
[SPEAKER_04]: So they finally launched a blog.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can read it for yourself, blog.us.playstation.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: and, uh, at least this one's not faking the blee, you know, the be a, like an independent blog, like, was it that all I want for Christmas is a PSP shit?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this is actually fairly well done.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this is really what I think folks have been asking for.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some articles here, they're, they're pretty honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: This guy who is the US producer for Motorstorm is talking about the patch and how the 1.2 is going to have this time attack mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then talking about how there's a bug in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was another post that was talking about the PS3 firmware update 1.81.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they kind of have like a buffet of people, so to speak, writing for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's actually not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: So good job, Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a little late in getting here, but I guess it was worth waiting for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Better late than never.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, that's very true.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is probably no thanks to the fact that the PlayStation 3 software development kit got leaked a couple weeks ago out on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, that only helps things along.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they've started with actually allowing... Apparently, versions 1.1 and 1.11 of the PS3 firmwares can now access, I guess, burnt game ISOs where you can...
[SPEAKER_03]: But it won't play them yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess that's the first step in getting backwards compatibility with some burn games or possibly, I don't know, Piracy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of pirated games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Homebrew.
[SPEAKER_03]: But right now, nothing's coming of it, but they're working on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Sony has this to say about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't like the fact that people want to...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think anyone's going to try to run an old Sega CD game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then again, I have old Sega CD games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They claim that they're serious, which means that they're in serious trouble.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to be able to do crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the PS3 is so easy to crack this long, how many fucking updates have there been to the damn firmware?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's only a matter of time before they crack it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're not interested in going online and stuff, I would recommend keeping your firmware as low as possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're interested in that piracy stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as Homebrew, though, I mean, hello, you can install Linux on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you want to play old SNES games, you can fucking put it on Yellow Dog Linux.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I have better news than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is happy news, because I love the 80s.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero Encore has more tracks listed, which is like super happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have Hold On Loosely that was, well, all of these, but like one that I'm going to name was a cover.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the one that's not a cover is The Warrior by Scandal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the covers are Hold On Loosely from 38 Special, No One Like You by The Scorpions, Only a Lad, Oingo Boingo, it's a cool song, Radar Love by White Lion, Ballroom Blitz by Crocus, a great name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, Ballroom Blitz is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I like this song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just always laugh at the band's name.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I Like About You by The Romantics and Rough Child by Iron Maiden because Iron Maiden's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And others on the list, 18 and Life, Bathroom Wall, Lonely is the Night, Nothing But a Good Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, Poison, Play With Me, Shaken.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, I love Eddie, but it's like my favorite Eddie Money song ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Synchronicity 2, I Wanna Rock, I Ran, of course, The Black Seagulls.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the actual song too, so is the Twisted Sister one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Round and Round, I Want Candy, Metal Health, Holy Diver, and Heat of the Moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you excited about Guitar Heroes Rock Series?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: I love my 80s rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I went to go make some liquor, and I don't have a lot to pick from because I didn't stock up before tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mixed Malibu rum and root beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you think that's going to turn out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, I haven't tried it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to try it first?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be your sample.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, try that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't spill it on your laptop, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's some bizarre shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It tastes like Dr. Pepper, which is nasty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything tastes like Dr. Pepper when you mix it with alcohol.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me try this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of does taste like Dr. Pepper.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I hate Dr. Pepper, so I'm finishing off my root beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dr. Pepper is just a combination of everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to know what's still in my fridge, by the way, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: The bottle of pineapple Malibu from Fatime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Delicious.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackDevilerX wants to know, Sky, what kind of root beer?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Diet IBC.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so I mixed it with Malibu because that's all I had.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had that and citrus vodka, and I knew that would be really bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should mix the vodka and the Malibu.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drink that like a shot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I do a video game story, please?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Time Crisis 4 is coming out to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that you may have heard that somewhere before, or it was soon after Retracted, but we can officially...
[SPEAKER_04]: With permission, tell you now, that Time Crisis 4 is coming out to the PlayStation 3 with a GunCon controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, Famitsu, they were the first to break this news about Time Crisis 4 coming to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: You hadn't heard it anywhere before then.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 3 version will have an arcade mode, and it's just going to be just like the arcade game, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you like Time Crisis, you're going to be really excited about this game, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a GunCon controller that's coming out with this, which is kind of ugly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's orange and kind of looks like the Zapper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as ugly as the dude holding it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, that guy is fugly.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's cool, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was reading that they're going to have first-person shooter portions of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why the GunCon is so weird-looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: and apparently they're going to have it functions like the Wii you put these things on the left or right side of your TV kind of like how on the Wii you have the LED bar and then there's a camera inside the actual gun and that determines where the markers are at so that means that way you can use the gun con whether you have an LCD a plasma whatever it'll work on any type of TV which is good news what's kind of neat though and I mean
[SPEAKER_03]: GunCon games are out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, really not that many.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that this would be awesome for first-person shooters because you've got, basically, on the front grip of the gun, you have kind of the second half of a PlayStation controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got your own analog stick and two shoulder buttons, and then on the back of the gun, there's another analog stick right by the trigger.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, in a sense, this would be the perfect solution for, you know, gun games or first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess so, sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, you got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Upgraded Duck Hunt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Duck Hunt 2, coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Funny story, I heard that, I'm not sure about Duck Hunt, but I heard that some old NES Zapper games, you could actually get perfect scores by aiming the light gun at a light and just keep shooting at the light.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or put a magnifying glass in front of the light gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the other trick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Works like a charm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: GunCon Time Crisis 3, coming to the PlayStation 3 very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: and another thing that was announced for PlayStation... Wake me up when they have point blank, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: For PlayStation 3 and for the 360, Soul Calibur 4, because we knew that Soul Calibur Legends couldn't be possibly the only game coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Soul Calibur 4 will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: They claim that's going to be 60 frames per second.
[SPEAKER_03]: I read somewhere 90 frames per second, which would be stupid, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: And then also that it's going to possibly be 1080p.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing, apparently, everybody's been talking about certain characters getting boob upgrades in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a fucking game, folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the teaser video that they had for it didn't really reveal too much because it was just still shots, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm just glad, you know, I know most games we joke about are obvious that they're coming, like Silent Hill 5, Final Fantasy 14 someday, you know, and all these other series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't 100% for sure that there was going to be another Soul Calibur game, because I got sworn they said with this last one, that's it, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the fact that, you know, the arcade release came later.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a comment on Sony's website saying that Soul Calibur 3 was exclusive for PS2 and any future Soul Calibur games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was wondering, what's the decision, what happened with the decision with Soul Calibur 4 being multi-console now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you see what happened is that Microsoft actually sold consoles, so that's why the decision was made to go multi-platform, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could be the 4 million console leave that they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or there's this whole rumor thing, I mean, because Sony or the fanboys are writing the hate mail right now, but also look at this, is that
[SPEAKER_04]: Namco, and you know, you'll see this throughout some other stories you may hear tonight or may not, is that Namco and Microsoft are starting to be in bed together, you might notice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, if you look at some of the decisions they've made recently and some of the things, I mean, not that they've abandoned PlayStation 3, but look at like, you know, Ace Combat and some of these other things, you know, Namco's kind of, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: with the Dreamcast thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the Dreamcast fishing rod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rod caliber.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just told that story like last time we had a show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but every time I think of Soul Calibur, I think of Rod Calibur and how great it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need a new fishing controller for more Rod Calibur fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think about Ivy and how great she is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think about trying to play Soul Calibur on the DDR pad on Dreamcast and the only analog button was like the Konami logo.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're tapping your fingers like you want to say something, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not tapping my fingers because I want to sing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He has a nervous twitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because I'm on my third Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't drink by yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't drink lots of water.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and please don't drink lots of water and not pee.
[SPEAKER_02]: And don't sit on the ground drinking nothing but, what, vodka and orange juice?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's your disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else on Soul Calibur?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, the Rod Calibur?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, the DDR pad on Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's almost as bizarre as someone trying to perform Shoryuken on a Street Fighter with the DDR pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seen it happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seen it done.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually is much easier to do that with the DDR pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try some of those Xbox Live Arcade games I didn't like.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try Nova Drone with the DDR pad and see if it's more fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe if I drink a few more it'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have an excellent idea for some of these crappy games out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's an excellent idea for...
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Skeet shooting?
[SPEAKER_03]: For the ultimate endurance test.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Janai's in chat and says, all video games are shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play with a jump rope.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might be listening to the wrong show, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, Microsoft would say jump in, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: HitStun says you can kind of play Street Fighter on a 2DX controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just can't go left.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just be player one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess so, and hope that player two never thinks to jump over you or else you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know what else to tell you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those who are keeping up with the PS1 games that were to be coming out on the PSN, PlayStation Store, or whatever the hell they're calling it, we have Crash Bandicoot, Wipeout, Medieval, Jumping Flash, and Syphon Filter that will be available on, looks like next Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, no, is it this Friday?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, take that back, next Friday, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will be available for PS3 and PSP, but you can only buy them from the PS3 store.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm guessing that's for the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the UK, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: My apologies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also going to be available is on 22nd June, there will be Calling All Cars and Super Stardust HD on June 29th.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard Calling All Cars sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take that, Dave Jeff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't like to say that anything sucks until I've actually either seen it in play or have played it myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think I'm going to pass judgment before I play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I actually do that a lot, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wrote off Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, I will never like that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't liked a first-person shooter since Quake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I actually played it at, get this, my friend's wedding reception.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had a Halo-themed wedding reception.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's brilliant.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they had TVs all land together and played Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually had a cake with Master Chief on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was the first time I ever played Halo, and I had a blast.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't always judge by looking, but some of the time you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the time you really can.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already know why I can't play Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because of the motion sickness thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX 360 SAINTS ROW
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadowrun also coming out in Japan and some other games coming to the Asian region such as Vampire Reign also I want to point out Def Jam Icon also comes out from EA on the Xbox 360 all on June 21st also coming out on the Nintendo Wii on June 21st is Hajime no Ippo Revolution which looks to be another type of anime based video game oh no it's a sports title it's a boxing title yeah it's actually what it is so first
[SPEAKER_04]: Something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Combo
[SPEAKER_04]: That's F-U-U-U-N Super Combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: This actually just looks like a Neo Geo compilation of some of the games there that SNK put out previously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet they're pretty fun!
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet they are fun!
[SPEAKER_02]: It won't be fun unless Psycho Soldier is one of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots and lots of SNK loving this week in Japan, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also a King of Fighters thing coming out, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, if you're on the DS...
[SPEAKER_04]: Have I Got News For You.
[SPEAKER_04]: This could be the game of the year right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello Kitty, No Gatuchi Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Koi No Doki Doki Trouble is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the box is beautifully pink with Hello Kitty wearing a bunny suit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think she's confused.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this is made by Rocket Company, not SNK.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom vs. SNK Cardfighter
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 2, The Adventures of Darwin
[SPEAKER_03]: On Xbox 360, we have Dirt coming out, which is an awesome off-road racing game, so definitely check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: PSP, PQ2, remember those old IQ games, this one should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hot Brain is going to be coming out on the PSP, another brain training sim.
[SPEAKER_03]: Puzzlescape,
[SPEAKER_03]: Another puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dungeon Maker, Hunting Ground.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting role-playing game with a little bit of sim aspects in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: On PlayStation 3, you got a big, fat nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rainbow Six Vegas was going to be coming out this week, but once again, it's been delayed yet another week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii, Resident Evil 4 Wii Edition is going to be making its way out, so that's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the DS, Time Ace, which is that Konami game that we played that's, I guess, sequel to Time Pilot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was the only one that kind of pointed that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, Zen Goku, or Zen Doku is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet another...
[SPEAKER_03]: Cidoku Game, SimCity DS, Rob, possibly a game that you might want to pick up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still have World of Warcraft to worry about on top of all the other new crap I've got.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too many games, too many games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even Christmas yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Transformers game is coming out a little bit early for the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have both the Autobots and Decepticons games going to be heading your way.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there is more than meets the eye to these games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally on PC, Dirt is also coming out as well as the Hitman Trilogy.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're actually putting out, yet again, Wheel of Fortune, Jeopardy, and The Sims Pet Stories will be making its way out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goodie, goodie.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I went to the new Fry's Electronics they built out in Roseville, which is all, you know, train themed out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very train-alicious.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a cute store.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the Sacramento Fry's is unlike any other Fry's because it doesn't have a theme, but all the other Fry's around the world have themes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, the point is, I was looking at computer games just randomly because I was thinking about maybe buying a new computer game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was actually, I don't know why, I was tempted for like half a second to get the Lord of the Rings MMO, even though I know it's like, I'm like, oh, I kind of want to try it for no good reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was looking at computer games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: One entire shelf, almost like two actually, dedicated to The Sims and all their spin-off series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it is one of the best-selling games ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder how many shelves are dedicated to the Tycoon series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even want to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about some different release dates?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: For our friends in the UK, coming out on the 22nd, we have Calling All Cars, like I said earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: HotPixel, Hour of Victory, Kirby Mouse Attack, Mario Party 8, Metroid Prime Pinball, Monster Madness, Pac-Man Rally, Sega Presents Touch Dart, and Cosmic Family.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metroid Prime Pinball just now?
[SPEAKER_04]: You poor kids over in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not that that game was like that great, but seriously, that game came out here what, like six months ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: They get flat out before I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I want flat out for the 360 so I can launch my driver through the window and into things.
[SPEAKER_04]: They get one game early and, you know, they're bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, they get Tomb Raider early.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you excited about Tomb Raider?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about gaming on the Mac, shall we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because...
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't always get to talk about this, and Loki usually has a field day with this topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, there was a pretty big keynote done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I've been drinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been a keynote done by Steve Jobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Worldwide Developers Conference did a keynote, and he talked about at the keynote that there are going to be... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was very professional, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get sneezed, but there's going to be coughing all over the Macintosh computers.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, here's what's really going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: They announced at the conference that Apple is going to be teaming up with EA and Electronic Arts is actually going to be putting out some of their games onto the Macs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Command & Conquer 3, Need for Speed Carbon, Harry Potter, and Madden & Tiger Woods 08.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming on the Mac.
[SPEAKER_04]: About fucking time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think they've had some games before this, but EA is definitely stepping it up a notch on the Macintosh, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another thing that's being shown off as well is ID's Tech 5 engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be their fifth generation 3D engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might remember them from such games as Quake 4, Doom 3, and all those other fun things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, they said that their new engine will also be able to run on Mac OS X. So that's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you're actually going to get some pretty decent games on the Mac, finally.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's also, it says, not being built with Microsoft's DirectX 10, which makes sense because, you know, not everyone wants to have Vista either.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Could this be like the next great engine that everybody wants to license?
[SPEAKER_03]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Doom 3, the Doom 3 engine was, I mean, Quake 4 engine had a lot of things going for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Quake 4, I think, ran on the Doom 3 engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, it could be the next big engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if it does things that Unreal can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Personally, I think Crysis is going to be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That engine is going to be nuts as far as the amount of detail that's in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they have a real high bar to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: PC, PC, PC, PC, PC
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it looks like Capcom is going to start releasing titles through Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be putting out PC versions of Lost Planet, Onimusha 3, Devil May Cry 3, Special Edition, and Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I add for matching service to that, just because I think it's funny?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, but I did not know that the Puzzle Fighter game was coming to the computers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or did I just miss that in the initial announcement?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says here that Capcom PC releases are going to be made available through Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I might add that their fucking Street Fighter 2 HD game looks fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that they've set the bar pretty high for
[SPEAKER_03]: Any new 2D fighting games coming out?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would love to see Guilty Gear in that much detail.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does look pretty hot, but it's going to do the same thing that Pac-Man CE did to Pac-Man on Xbox Live Arcade, is it's going to piss you off that you bought the first one.
[SPEAKER_04]: When the Street Fighter 2 HD version comes out, it's an arcade release, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to make you mad that you ever bought the Championship Edition release that came out last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have every other version, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you are a computer gamer, then you certainly know the series Monkey Island.
[SPEAKER_04]: You remember this series of games, Monkey Island?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about pirates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, going around LucasArts is rumblings of a fifth Monkey Island game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fifth Monkey Island game is coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know some of the guys who worked on the music compositions for the original PC Classics, and they say that it's currently being planned amidst rumors.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, LucasArts has so many things on its belt right now, including a Wii title that is yet to be named.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't expect any revitalations of its classic graphic adventures until 2008 at the earliest.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's coming from RumorReporter.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, this is a game that needs to be made into a movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Monkey Island series.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, with Sam and Max doing as well as it's doing critically, I mean, there's no reason why they shouldn't bring this back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it would be kind of interesting to see it on a console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although these games will always kind of be PC games to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, we talked about it a while back that, you know, Playboy was going to be coming to Second Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they finally opened their doors in a
[SPEAKER_03]: Fun little bunny-shaped island.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what can you find possibly on the Playboy Island, you may ask?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, plenty of bunny paraphernalia from its site, playboy.com and shopthebunny.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fake women.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, fake women.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll be able to buy avatars or merchandise for your avatars and also for, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: Like fake bunny shirts and fake bunny ears?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you can buy real merchandise that can get shipped to your house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: So slash Playboy instead of slash pizza.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, they're going to have characters running around dressed up like the classic bunnies.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, I guess they're going to be also doing other events and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Events?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pool party!
[SPEAKER_03]: Fake pool party.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was reading some of the comments on the story, and it was kind of funny, because they were like, I'm just going to fake bomb this place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, RawSteelUT read my mind in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you throw cocks at the Playboy models?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wipe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, the cock-throwing story in Second Life was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what if it was like four months old?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I actually played Second Life, I would want to throw some cocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on, what am I going to do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sit around and pretend I'm at the Playboy Mansion?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would build the massive cock launcher.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be a giant cannon.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all it would do.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should have sent DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, it was fucking lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was at the Playboy Mansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was at the Playboy Mansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, it's for the goddamn, was it the Professional Gaming League?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're trying to make gaming, they're putting it on TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to watch people play games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I fucking hate that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to play games or play games against other people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to have people watch me play games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So instead of watching basketball on TV, why not go play basketball?
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's why I don't watch sports on TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you're just weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's a lot of people out there that do enjoy watching other people play games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, don't you have friends that will come over and sit on the couch and watch you play?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't really want to play themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just will watch you play.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one ever comes over to watch me play.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Nellie hates watching me play games.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's like, I want to watch TV instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you do this to some extent, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You've told stories on the show before when you and Dan were gaming together that you would help him through Resident Evil, but you would just be kind of content in watching him, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So would it be fair to say some people are okay with just watching people play games?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can go ahead and start up their professional gaming league.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be like the fucking XFL.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be around for a couple years, and then it will fade into dust.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like it should, because no one wants to watch this shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously, people, gamers don't even watch... We were actually playing together.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember that stupid show on G4 Arena, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, granted, it had an interesting idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's watch gamers play games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sucked really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's watching people play games.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem with Arena was just the way the show was kind of formulated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, Rockstar or something like that so I can watch you play some stupid game that I could be playing right now and win $50,000 and go, I'm fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me make my own keyboard brand and sell it for uber money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you done?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're such a dick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear to God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, RossDLUT brings up an excellent point.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about Starcade?
[SPEAKER_03]: Starcade was awesome and you watched other people play games or Nick Arcade for that matter those games rocked bring that shit back I would love to see that that's good but fucking watching clan members or whatever fucking play multiplayer games and shit that's kind of boring but I'd be down for like an 80's style show or something where it's just people facing off in the arcades like their forefathers did so you will watch people play games under the right circumstances
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll play arcade games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Liar.
Liar.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Liar is not the right word.
[SPEAKER_02]: The word I'm thinking of starts with an H. Homosexual?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hypocrite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hypocrite.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Rob, that's just you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: That show's not on TV anymore, so fuck that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: and M60... Oh no, I guess GS68 said it first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hentai?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that the word you were thinking of?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear Rob... Speaking of hentai, DarkSakura likes to surf the internet every week for yaoiboyfun.com and I don't know what she's looking at, but she likes to... Oh yes, explicit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you going to YaoiCon?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura's website of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's talk about a little bit of Yaoi.
[SPEAKER_02]: for those of you guys who don't know what yaoi is it's art that is you explain it DarkSakura I can't it's man on man action imagine like the uber sweet sappy you know typical heterosexual relationship and then change the gender of one of them to male okay
[SPEAKER_04]: Good definition.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as I understand it, Yaoi is not made for gay men.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not gay porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not gay anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's made for straight girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yaoi is made for girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I get asked all the time, because Yaoi is man-on-man action, are you going YaoiCon?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I say, okay, well as a gay man, the last place I want to be on the planet is a hotel full of horny straight women.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stop asking me if I'm going to go to YowieCon, because the answer is no.
[SPEAKER_04]: YuriCon, maybe, because I love my lesbians.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love my lesbians.
[SPEAKER_04]: Might go to YuriCon, but I don't know about YowieCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry for the aside, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I apologize for cutting into your precious website of the week time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We needed to have some YowieChat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we do your website of the week now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm just playing with this stupid thing anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, the website of the week is FallingSandGame.com, which I have no idea what the purpose of this game is for anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's really stupid, and all I'm doing is just watching it do shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's a game from the same people who do Cat with Bo Golf or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, but I have no idea what I'm supposed to be doing other than drawing lines and trying to make this thing destroy my sandslides.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that thing that's running around on the outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're supposed to hit it with sand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this like Yoshi's Touch and Go?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been hitting it with sand, and it's not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you sure this game is fun?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it explodes.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have one that's also with slugs, and you have to pour salt on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate slugs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually slug-phobic, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: You now know what my deepest fear is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Slugs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And snails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I keep pouring sand on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's the type of sand I'm using.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grossant I want the sea monkey to gain Or that I can flush them down the toilet That's the only thing missing from Sims 2 Pets Funerals?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, flushing animals down the toilet Funerals!
[SPEAKER_04]: Fish funerals!
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember when I had fish?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is fantastic I prefer to call them funerals It's just like, what the hell is this crap?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, give that URL one more time
[SPEAKER_02]: FallingSandGame.com Dude, I just set the ball of sand on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I move on?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you finished?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up with you people tonight and not being able to finish in a reasonable amount of time?
[SPEAKER_02]: I am paying attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm playing with the Sand Game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I talk about BlizzCon while you're playing with the Sand Game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm a little upset about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: As you know, I've been gone for the past two weeks, and during that time, tickets for BlizzCon went on sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I actually was going to go to BlizzCon this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I get home and find out that the tickets went on sale June 13th, and then promptly sold out on June 15th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, tickets for BlizzCon 2007 already sold out.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you haven't heard, it's August 3rd and 4th at the Anaheim Convention Center.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, if you go, you're supposed to get all this free stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I, however, will not be going, and I'm a little bit bitter about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to cry?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, I'm not going to cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to get angsty.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what happens on this show when people get angsty?
[SPEAKER_04]: FUs of the week time.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, start us off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to get the information out of my purse because I'm going to tell people exactly where the fuck I went.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you to the idiot at Quiznos.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted my sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: I specifically wanted a Philly cheesesteak sandwich on whole wheat bread with no mayonnaise and no sauce on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just meat and cheese and onions on wheat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I didn't want it burned either, I want it toasted.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the guy's like, I'm like, okay, I want two goats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you being served by Ozzy Osbourne?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I was being served by a moron.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I was like, okay, dude, I want a Philly cheesesteak.
[SPEAKER_02]: No mayonnaise.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he starts putting mayonnaise, and I'm like, dude, I said no mayonnaise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he puts it in.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I get it, and he's like, okay, prime ribs.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I said Philly cheesesteak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay, I'll go add cheese.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he rings it up as... I was like, dude, okay, first of all, you bring me up as a prime rib.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a different price.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's like, oh, well, this is cheaper, so I'll just charge you for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, fine, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So finally, I just ended up saying, where's your manager?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the manager's only here in the morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so it's Quiznos number 1129 on...
[SPEAKER_02]: What is that road that's off of Zinfandel?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not White Rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just call it off of Zinfandel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zinfandel and 50.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's off of Zinfandel near 50, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Across the street from Target and Cheezer's Pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Olsen, it's Olsen Drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Olsen, I used to work on that road.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, it's on Olsen in Rancho Cambodia.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the guy's name was, I can't pronounce it, but it's A-K-O-B.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't ever let this guy make you a sandwich because he'll burn it!
[SPEAKER_02]: You saw my sandwich, Rob!
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty burnt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just came back from Philadelphia and you can't get cheesesteaks anywhere else like you can there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a reason they are Philly cheesesteaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything else is suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: But dude, I have never had such idiotic service anywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, I can understand, you know, missing it once.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the dude wasn't even freaking listening to me anytime I said something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, I want a small drink.
[SPEAKER_02]: He gives me a fucking large cup.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, dude, small.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, maybe he was high.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can tell him somebody's high.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was not red-eyed.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was not stealing the cheese out of the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just was speaking in a whisper and not listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was looking off into space and like, dude, I don't care how much you hate your job, you can at least do it right, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thank you, DarkSakura, for your very specific and directed angst tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: FD of the Week goes to Christopher's desk for being rotted.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is really foul.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I had to put a cup over the giant pile of rot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's literally, there's, like, stuff growing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm creating a wall with cans.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have enough yet, so I have to drink a couple more cans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FD of the Week goes to myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the Target that's across the street from said Quiznos because I was there and I was buying some diet soda.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, the IBC root beer I'm consuming right now that's mixed with Malibu.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was buying that and as I was pulling it off the shelf, it got caught on the cream soda next to it and so all the IBC cream soda went all over the floor and there was breaking glass everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: It made a beautiful noise, but F you to myself for being such a klutz.
[SPEAKER_04]: Old you fucking cream soda sucks, see?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, uh, explicit, any FUs tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see, um, an FU to having a flat tire during the road while I was trying to go to my cousin's graduation.
[SPEAKER_01]: I brought a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Luckily, I came into the party rather than not being able to make it.
[SPEAKER_01]: FU goes to pretty much everybody keeps overrating the over 9,000 joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the over 9,000 joke, dare I ask?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, if you go to YouTube, just type in over 9000 up at Google.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it a Dragon Ball Z thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I have seen it.
[SPEAKER_04]: His power level is over 9000!
[SPEAKER_04]: DMN linked me to something or sent us a song or something and I wanted to poke him in the eye with a fork.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so I know what you're talking about now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hear that almost every freaking day.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, let's see, if it goes to my coworkers for trying to make me break New Year's resolution, I'm not sure if you guys will know that the New Year's resolution I gave up for the whole year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dare I ask?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not erections again, is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gave up sex or masturbating?
[SPEAKER_04]: Masturbation.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gave up masturbating for a whole year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you having sex with women at least?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, sadly no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, you're gonna die.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should just get a hooker.
[SPEAKER_04]: For real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, you're a brave man, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see, another F you goes to everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still talking about the 300 Sparta joke.
[SPEAKER_01]: Combined with a Chuck Norris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I got a shirt that says, This is Zelda!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was actually funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I got that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was good times.
[SPEAKER_01]: F you to some of the kids in Sadgun for asking me for money.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, if you... I don't know, I'm not sure how much money these kids spend on a con.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially with their, like, $110 swords and their $50 Naruto jacket, etc., etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, God, we're gonna be starting on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see, and... Well, that's all for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always like how he always leaves it with, that's all for now, and then he'll be back, like, in a year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's some FUs I've collected over the past year that I'd like to share with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, actually, actually, I found something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I found something just for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just for you, Jonas.
[SPEAKER_05]: for $9,000!
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that one of the most god-awful things you've ever heard?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was made by DMN.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, gee, didn't see that coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll send you the MP3 later, Jonas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we get back to games, please?
[SPEAKER_03]: So something kind of cool came down to the Xbox Live video marketplace, and once I saw it, I thought, well, I don't know, I had to watch it, but I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, the Xbox Live marketplace, among other things, got a whole bunch of anime.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty awesome, including Guyver, Trinity Blood, Gunslinger Girl, Speedgrapher, Basilick,
[SPEAKER_03]: Sayuki, Kitty Grade, The Count of Monte Cristo, Desert Punk, Last Exile, Rumbling Hearts, Galaxy Railways, Gilgamesh, and Lupin the Third Part 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it also got Akira, and Akira in HD, which is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: So definitely worth checking out, especially if you're an anime fan, because that's one of the best anime movies I think of all time.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I believe Lady Death was also on there in HD so that's something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then beyond all that National Geographic shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you got National Geographic Adventure and yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So watch some Akira in HD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I tell you a secret?
[SPEAKER_04]: Most people assume that because I do this show, I watch a ton of anime, which is so not true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never seen Akira.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just haven't.
[SPEAKER_02]: The manga's better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't watch the anime.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: The anime is fucking awesome, and you know why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I started a fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember going to this place called Steamers or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a coffee shop slash video rental place.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like one of the...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fucking awesome movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the main characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's got like a character read the manga it's got a character that looks like Louis Anderson so you gotta that is true you gotta watch it and he kinda sounds like I hate Louis Anderson you're not selling me this but he gets killed oh spoiler and 50 and 50 year old children can we please move on he's like old Louis Anderson can we finish part A tonight at some point and the clowns if old Louis Anderson oh yeah the clowns if old Louis Anderson could like do you know psychokinetic shit that's fucking awesome
[SPEAKER_04]: Has this show really lasted five years, somehow?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not yet!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, it could all end tonight, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crash!
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting close.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, can we talk about something else, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Read the manga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut the fuck up and read a story.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know that Castlevania film that was supposed to be done by Paul W.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anderson?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he said, fuck y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, I'm working on other projects.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's remaking Death Race.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's more priority over Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, the one that they are getting to replace him is Sylvain White, who brought us such classics as Stomp the Yard and I'll Always Know What You Did Last Summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Such great American cinema classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: he is quoted saying most of the vampire films have been present or set in the future from Blade to Underworld and I was attracted to the chance to make a dark epic period movie that almost had an anime feel to it well there's Castlevania right the fuck there Van Helsing?
[SPEAKER_03]: anybody?
[SPEAKER_03]: yeah but that wasn't a good movie it just had Hugh Jackman being sexy and that's it but it had vampires and it was a period piece but it was a bad movie what about Bram Stoker's Dracula?
[SPEAKER_02]: that was sexy oh my god
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Interview with a Vampire?
[SPEAKER_04]: That movie was so hot, I would make love to it if I could.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that was sort of multiple... It was part period, part present, part... Part just, like, gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a gay movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I disrespected making out all over the place.
[SPEAKER_03]: For real.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a good movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: He probably just doesn't watch a lot of those classic films, you know, because he's in a whole other, you know, decade now, so... Who watches any of that stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say that maybe he might have some... I mean, if he gets the imagery off, then that'll be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what's also interesting that he's going to be directing is Ronan, Frank Miller.
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as it's not Paul W.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anderson or Revol.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need someone else to make fun of for making crappy movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone has to start off somewhere, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he did do I'll Always Know What You Did Last Summer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a springboard, I'll say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to try to have some faith because you know me and my Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will withhold judgment until the film is done.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's only fair, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody deserves a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo.
[SPEAKER_02]: You said yourself that you passed judgment on Halo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you learned your lesson, Bob?
[SPEAKER_04]: I so got pwned just now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you learned your lesson?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'll never learn my lesson.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haven't you learned that after five years?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, but I'm not going to tell.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll always know where Jigglypuff is hiding.
[SPEAKER_04]: and now I think it's about time to say goodbye to part A of Orange Lounge Radio we're going to take a quick break and we'll be back after a little break with more of Orange Lounge Radio for those of you guys listening live here on Sunday night you get part B just in a few minutes but for those of you guys listening to us on our audio archive or podcast feed you just have to wait a couple days we'll be back right after this with more of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.