Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
This week you got your Apex and my Fortnite
From downtown, in my rage
Your Mario and my little big planet
And your VR and my Switch
We've read through the fools and hope it's all legit
To bring you tonight's news starting right now on the show
Where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
Welcome back to another week of the show
Where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio tonight
Live with episode number 771
For this April the 7th of 2019
My name is Rob Roberts
And joining me in studio
DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
I'm so full
You're full?
Yeah
Of those cookies that you brought to the studio tonight
Well I meant to save one
But I ate it
She was going to give us a cookie
But she ate it
They came out black
Or gray
Because I made raspberry and blackberry puree
And when I added it to the batter
It turned gray and got really sticky
So I had to add more flour
So I don't know if I'm going to make them again
Because the first bite's like sugar cookie and then raspberry flavor
It turned out good though
It did but I like my sugar cookies
But I'm not doing any more dandelion cookies this season either
Speaking of our raspberry cookies
Would you allow the Twitch folks to see the back of your head
Because it's a very lovely red color
This isn't raspberry though
I know it's a little lighter than raspberry
But I like the color
This is flamingo
This is orange and peach
You can't really see
This is where my head was shaved
Well and for the podcast listeners
They can't see anything anyway
Sucks to be you
I didn't say that they suck
I said it sucks to be them
Since they can't see the gloriousity
Of my you know
My hair
Well if you want to see the gloriousity of hair
You can tune in live every Sunday night at Twitch TV
My follicular glory
Is that a word? Follicular?
Let me do my plug be quiet
Twitch TV slash vog network
Every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific
9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
More information and other great podcasts
At vog network dot com
Other things you can see on Twitch
It's a word
Follicular
Can I introduce our third host please?
Alright over there by my side
Did you just catch a Pokemon here?
Techmaster Loki
Live on air
Is there something good on the house I should be paying attention to?
No I just have to get rid of all these
Great and whatever
Oh like the quest you have to make so many
No I just have so many of them
I'm taking out my inventory space and normally I just throw them away
So you know might as well
Gotcha you got too many balls
Robin he's throwing away his blue balls
Too many balls
I don't want to know about yellow balls
Over in our chat
Over at Twitch TV slash vog network
Because again we tape live on Sunday nights
And you guys can join us in our chat room
Bobby Black Wolf suggesting that somebody could make a clip
Of the hair thing and then
Cause yeah there are clips of our show
And Bobby's show
We have a little archive cause that's a little something special
You can see it free of course when we broadcast live on Sunday
But you can subscribe using your
Twitch Prime subscription or any of the
Twitch subscription offers they have there
And you will get access
To the complete video library so you can watch
A video episode if you want
Audio only of course is free as it's always been
For coming up on 17 years
But the clips that people make
Are free
So you can see little like 30 second clips of our show
Some people clip random things too
I think some people just accidentally clip the button
Cause they'll be like these random I'm like why did somebody
Clip that it's just us I mean
It's not like yeah but there's
Also clips of things that are like
You know funny moments or like when
Smoosh came on camera that one night or whatever
So things happen
It's part of the magic of doing Twitch since
We did move over in December
From Shoutcast where we were beforehand
Anyway let's get
Into our kickoff topic tonight let's talk about
Let's talk about anniversaries
It's a little bit different of a kickoff topic
Usually we would talk about you know some
New gaming story or what's
Going on in the news and there is a little bit going on in the
Gaming news this week although it's probably slowed down
A little bit from last
Week because of
You know there's no PAX this week
Or GDC I think everything's calming down a little bit
But we do have a big anniversary
That we're looking at this week and that is
Final Fantasy 6
Celebrating it's 25th anniversary
Now of course I'm sure
Many of you guys that consume
Gaming podcasts are probably aware at this
Point that here in the US
We received Final Fantasy 6
As Final Fantasy 3
So sometimes this is called Final Fantasy 3 US
We received it as that but
This is in the true Final Fantasy
Canon it's the 6th game and
25 years ago on April
2nd so this week in
1994 Final Fantasy
6 was released in Japan
We got it a little bit later because
Back then you know it wasn't
Such a global economy
The internet had not yet taken off
I think the internet was probably still government in 94
I don't think you could do internet on Prodigy
Or AOL that stuff yet
94? Not yet
Almost there right? No you had AOL
Remember I met Dan
In my first year on AOL
In 93, 94 was
AOL 1.5 which was the DOS based
I thought it was more like after I graduated high school in 96
But I think it was still
We can say it was still very niche and not a lot of people were
I was in college
But anyway
Regardless Final Fantasy 6 came out
25 years ago and obviously
A lot of people
Remember this game very fondly
Although we sometimes joke about
Super Nintendo releases and
What's better Super Metroid or
Chrono Trigger or
We razzed maybe other games
Of Final Fantasy series like you guys know I have my
Issues of Final Fantasy 8 and so forth
All that tongue and cheek
Talk aside I think
Generally most people regard this
As especially in
Our age group of gamers
And that's an important footnote to make
You know the late 30's early 40's
Probably a good range outside of that too
I think there's a generation almost that would consider
Even if maybe Final Fantasy 6 isn't
Your favorite game
It's probably one of your favorite
Games if you're a role play
Person if you're more of a sports gamer
Maybe it's not in your list but I know a lot
Of people that would be Final Fantasy 10
If you're a sports game oh for Blitzball
Heck yeah come on San Arc and Abe's yeah right
But anyway
I think this game certainly left an impact
On a lot of people
Dark Sakura you know since you were
On the internet earlier and I know you're a big retro
Gamer and a big gamer girl
All the way back in college and so forth
What was your memories with
Final Fantasy 6?
Pretending to have the flu for a week so I could beat it
After I rented it
So you rented the game
You didn't even I rented it and you held on to it
For an entire week that's a lot of late fees
No I
Renewed my rental the place that we were renting our
Video games from you could rent for a week oh that's
Oh nice and so cause I wasn't running through
Blockbuster we were doing like little mom and pops
Yeah I rented cause I worked for
Mom and pops I usually rented through there too but
Yeah but I
Played the shit out of it
And I actually
Started over after the
Minecart level and then
Just started completely over and just
Zoomed right up till then and then
Got through it I don't know why I think it was
Just that motion sickness thing I've had cause I had
I just couldn't do it at all
Got so pissed that I put it away for a day
Went back started over and beat the
Whole game in the rest of the week and
It was absolutely amazing and then I
Finally got my own copy
I remember
Watching a friend in high school
Play it because you know my family
Was pretty middle class so it's like
We didn't really get the games when they first
Came out or that was a real treat like when I got
Mortal Kombat on Mortal Monday or whatever
It was that was a freaking treat cause
I usually didn't get games on the release day so I didn't get
Final Fantasy 3 I didn't even I somehow didn't
Even realize the game was coming out and I was over at a
Friends house one day and
We were about to do I used to do
D&D in high school so we were about to do a D&D
Thing and I walk in and they're playing
I'm like oh my gosh this
Is like Final Fantasy 2
But because remember I didn't I wasn't
As aware of what was going on in Japan and everything
I'm like this is Final Fantasy 2 but like
Like oh my gosh I'm just like watching
Like dumbfounded the entire time because
There's like the mechs and the different
I think he was at the point in the game where you
Had Edgar and Sabin and
So he was showing off how you could put like in the
Controller input cause remember with Sabin it's like
He did a little Hadouken and he would actually do
Was it that was one move?
I think so. You know there was like the controller input moves
And it was like oh my gosh it's like a
Fighting game not really but you know
When you're 13 you're thinking those types of things right
It's a fighting game and then
Of course Edgar had the tools right
So he had like the chainsaw
And the so it was like
Yeah the autocrossbow the gas
Thing the bio weapon or whatever
And so it was like getting to see all that for the first
Time was like oh my gosh it's so cool
And so like I knew I had to have it and so I
You know begged and I ugly begged
I was like what did they get? So finally
For Christmas that year I got that game
And I just I played it like
Every single day until I beat it
I think part of me as a
Kid is still a little more
Fond of Final Fantasy 2 or what
Would be 4 of course in canon
Just because that was like the first one
I played and especially like the
Story from start to finish
Because I don't know why but Final Fantasy
6's ending
Was always a little weirder to me
Like that I think it's
Let me kind of rephrase this
Because I think it's something I've grown to appreciate
In my older years
As I did versus when I would have first
Played through this game you know
Many years ago when I was like
Is that I seem to remember
Actually no I would have been ordering 13
Because this game was out when I was in high school and it's
What 25 years ago so I was more like 15, 16
But I didn't
Like the way like at the end you
Split up into the 3 parties
And he had to kind of go through that way
And then like everybody
Kind of had like a little piece of an
Ending and then like if you didn't have
Somebody you wouldn't see their piece
Because there's somebody I didn't
Oh I think it was Shadow I didn't have Shadow
You have to wait for him
Well right but I didn't know that
Wait for his late diva ass
Right so I didn't know that when I was
A teenager actually you know the
As a teenager do you know what I remember
About Final Fantasy 6
Like something I interpreted in the script
That like nobody else took away from it
And I know this is wrong but when I first
Played the game I thought that
One of the flashback scenes with
Realm and
What was the older guys name
Her grandfather
Whose name I can't remember in the moment but somebody will
Yell it out in chat shortly
I thought that Shadow was Realms mom
Notice I didn't say dad
I said mom
I thought that was like the twist
Because ninja why not a female ninja
Thank you strago
So why not a female ninja
And I don't know what it was in the script if there was like a
Pronoun I misread or something I don't know but I thought
Like for years
That Shadow was Realms mom
Until somebody was like
No no no like it's actually
Maybe her dad but it's not really said
I would have
I'm now going to head canon that it's her mom
Because we don't really know
If Shadow is actually a dude
Ultros was her mom
Alright what are you
You played through this game right
Yeah I rented it from Blockbuster
I did I think
I'm pretty sure I did I know I didn't own it
But I had it long enough to play through it and beat it
And I did
And it was great
I think I rented it multiple times
And just
Everything about it was fantastic and I must have
Played it like
Over the course of a weekend or something to finish it but
In a weekend
I remember that game took like 60 hours
To beat or something I don't know
But it was yeah I was
I just remember the end on it
But I don't know
How long it took me to do it but
It was fun
So if y'all have an SNES classic
I mean that's probably the easiest way to play this game now
Well let's talk a little bit about you know
Because to tie this into some more recent news
And things we've been talking about on the show more recently
You know we seem to think
That we might be standing on
Looking at the future of gaming
Where things are going to go more streaming
And so forth
And it's not like you know Super Nintendos are gonna suddenly
Wilt up and die and those things
Especially can take a beating right
Well I mean that's just what
They're pushing for console
Gaming and stuff but it doesn't mean that anybody's actually
It doesn't mean it's gonna take off
You know like they may say that
We wanna go this route but if no one buys
The system or no one pays into it
They're not gonna continue with it
So I'm not really worried
That it's going streaming because
There's still PC
There's still retro
You know if you don't like what
The new game's coming out on your streaming
Platform or if it's just
Not gonna work because you don't have the bandwidth
Or the bandwidth caps
For it then
I'm sure you'll find ways around it
When we're looking at 25
Years from now do you think
The only way people are going to be able to experience
Final Fantasy 6 is
By finding
Grandma at that point or Grandpa's old
Super Nintendo and playing
The actual cartridge or do you think
No emulators come on
So emulators
All of a sudden they're gonna find a way
To wipe those off the internet this time
I guess that's true I don't
Maybe because I think of the full experience
As plopping down in front of the TV
With a controller but you're right
Why can't you do an emulator on the TV thanks
To the
Little computers in a box and the USB
Stick which name escapes me at the moment
Raspberry Pi
And all those things
And I'm sure that technology's gonna just get even more
Yeah they're gonna get more powerful
And it's just gonna be
You'll be able to play all those old games
That you want
Just because there's new games coming out
Doesn't mean we have to only play those new games
Otherwise we wouldn't be remastering
Borderlands 1
Or doing all this stuff
I think it's just
Good games are gonna be good games no matter what
And that's why everyone's saying
Well it's all gonna go the streamy route
But indies
Can't necessarily afford to maybe
Be on those streaming platforms so they're gonna do
Things differently
Unless there was a do it yourself solution
Like YouTube
There will be ways
To put yourself on different
Platforms but it doesn't mean that's the only
Way to do it and they're gonna
Fill the void of so it's not gonna be
That this is gonna be the only
Way you do it it's only gonna be streaming
You're not really gonna purchase anything you're only gonna have
Licensing to it or something maybe the
Wrong thing to say is the only way but
Especially again you know not to repeat this conversation
Too much when we go look at the film industry
I think and we see like a lot of it is
Netflix and these sorts of things now maybe
The primary consumption method is
Streaming and physical
Blu-rays and DVDs are more
Collectible keepsake they're more
Collectibles they're more the secondary way to
Do things right I guess you could
Do it that way but if it's gonna be like
You know the film industry that we're gonna
Have Square Enix's streaming service
We're gonna have Nintendo
Streaming service Microsoft streaming service
Sony EA Activision
All of them wanting their own I think
I think especially on the TV I think things are gonna
Break with that eventually I think you're gonna
See mergers and things you know
Oh you're gonna see piracy is what you're gonna see
Because people are gonna get tired of it
Lots of great comments in our chat
Over at twitch.tv slash vog network
And Bobby Blackwolf saying
Google wants to dumb down
Your computer enough to make it a dumb terminal
Where the actual computing power is in a server
Farm so the new computers of the future
Wouldn't have the horse power to run an emulator
Well a super
Nintendo emulator in this day and age can run on your
Phone you know what I mean but I get what
You're saying they're kind of tongue in cheek when it comes to Stadia
And things no I get what they're trying to do too
They're lowering the cost of computing
For like people to get
Into that so like say I don't want
To drop several thousand dollars on whatever
I can buy a Chromebook or well
And also something we we really
Always need to be aware of is that we're
In the United States we're in California
Computers and being able to go pick one up
Is kind of a part of our culture but you go
To many other countries throughout the
World and computers are
Not something that's just
Assumed everybody has in fact
It's a rarity you don't see computers but I'm
Never gonna buy a Chromebook for
Like playing games that's never
Gonna be a thought that ever goes through
My mind because if I'm gonna build a
PC to play games on whether it be
Buying a laptop or something it's gonna have
The horse power to play games I'm not gonna
Well I'll just buy a Chromebook
Because it essentially does nothing without
You know Google you know
So I just
I would never do that but
There's other people that Chromebooks are
A good option like for example I have a
Co-worker that is retiring and she
Wants a computer that can she can check email
And do Facebook and I'm like
Chromebook is your way to go because
That's all that shit does
That was that was my mom when she was still
With us is that she just
Wanted to do email and she wanted to
Be able to look at her kids on Facebook
That's all she yeah and so for that I mean
And she's like well maybe I should get a Mac
Even email I feel like is
Starting to fade away it doesn't seem
Like email is going away in favor of things like
I hate to say it Facebook Messenger but Facebook
Messenger is huge but I also see
Other I feel like things like Telegram
And some of those are starting to gain a lot of speed too
Well I don't think
Email is not going anywhere but
I think that
You know for there's a market
Physical mail is not going anywhere either
But like the only thing that I welcome
Getting in the physical mail anymore is
Packages like stuff I bought on the internet
That's it it's true yeah
But I don't know
I just think that it's not going to be
They want you to
Be convinced that this is going to be the next
Big thing because they want the investors
To be excited about it and they want
People to be excited about so they jump into
It but let's just see what it actually
Is by the time it actually comes
Out and how wonderful it is because
If you may remember not that long ago
When they were talking about the PlayStation
3 or I think it was the PlayStation 3
That it was going to be you know
1080p
Full native 1080p 120
Frames per second it's just going to be this
Monster of a system that was going to be super
It just it fucking wasn't so it's like
The same thing with
They overhype everything
And then it comes out and then they have to lower their
Lower your expectations to what it actually
Can do so let's just wait and see what
It can actually do before we
You know start predicting where the industry
Is going because who gives a shit where the industry
Is going we're just going to go with it
Dialing back to Final Fantasy 6 a little bit
Since that was what this is originally about
I would love to see this game remade
Well it has been Loki
Well I meant remade like
I meant remade in sense like Final Fantasy 7
Is being remade type of thing
Oh you want to see it but I don't know if it would
I don't know if you can ever like
Lightning strike twice with
The Final Fantasy 6 like you know obviously
The recent mobile
Support they did was not good
Or I would even take
A new Final Fantasy game
Done in the style of Final Fantasy 6
We don't need 3D polygons
In like real time battles and shit like that
Just you know drop
Down because that doesn't cost
As much to develop
Didn't they kind of do that with the Final Fantasy 15
Damn it I can't remember the name of it
But it was basically like it was like a
Earlier throwback
Well they also did the after years for Final Fantasy 4
So that was like that
And if you got that on the WiiWare it was like
It was like you were playing Final Fantasy 2
Slash 4 like graphics
There was some good comments so I want to make sure
I got a couple other of these because
ActDeft in our chatroom said that eventually
And I lost the original comment but he had made the point
That oh yeah games eventually will fall
In the public domain too
So after so many years
You're not really pirating the game anymore
Because it's in the public domain
But it doesn't get really complicated though
Unfortunately the game was made in Japan
But I guess since it was put out in the US
As Final Fantasy 3 I guess there's
A certain term
But you can thank Disney for continuing to
Push that term back
Because Mickey Mouse
Mickey Mouse should have been public domain by now
But he's not
So kind of interesting how that all works
Well it's because he's also their trademark
So you got trademark issues too
But Bobby Blackwolf
Pointing out the new Dragon Quest
Does that if you'd played that on 3DS
It had the top screen and bottom screen
And I think with the whole
Switch port they're doing something with that too
Obviously it's not top screen and bottom screen but like a button
To switch between the two
So some people do dig their retro modes
Dragon Quest is a pretty good game as well
So
Yeah Questbuster says
I wanted that 16 bit Final Fantasy
13 that Square Enix made
A trailer of to explain the story
TigerClawnChat says
Some games will get in the public domain
But some of the more bigger ones they will continue to make games
For those as long as they are around
You know I'm almost starting to feel like about
Video game remakes though kind of finishing up
That thought as I am some of the movie remakes
Like some of them can be really good
But a lot of them
Are not good and something like okay like the
Borderlands remaster where they just basically
Went in and put out
4k textures and didn't really change the game
I would consider that more like a
Criterion collection
Release of an old movie
They're not trying to redo the movie
It's not a remake it's a remaster
Exactly
They did change a few things
A lot of video game remakes are kind of
Not Resident Evil 2 though
That was freaking amazing
There's a few diamonds in the rough and I liked
Blaster Master Zero even though other people
Had their problem with it and I would say not
Every movie remake was bad
Although most of them are I'm trying to think of a good
Movie remake
The new stars born was incredible
So you know
It's not Barbara
Or Judy Garland
I kind of thought it was better
There were as many motorcycle accidents in it as there
Was in the previous version
There's no way I'm going to answer that question
I actually think that the Total Recall remake
Which is actually I think off the original
Story
Honestly it's arguably a better
Movie than the Arnold one
Even if it doesn't have the cult following
The original one did
Not Spielberg
Miniseries, Stephen King
Miniseries, some people swear that the
Miniseries they did on The Shining is actually better than
The movie because it was more faithful to the book
Stephen King actually signed off on
The Shining
Well Stephen King also signed off on the end of
The Mist and that was a poor decision
That's true too
But then they made The Mist a TV show
Isn't The Mist a TV show now I think
I thought I heard something about
Not that I watch TV anyway
I know I so rarely do anymore these days
And then what else
Every Animal Crossing new game has been good
The It, some people
The It
It's just It
Versus the miniseries
It's not Tim Curry
I don't mean to
Go down this rabbit hole
I don't mean to go down this rabbit hole of remakes
Someday when computer technology
Is good enough
To resurrect
You know
Movie actor Tim Curry
He's not dead
I understand he's not dead but
To the point where mobility is limited
Mobility is you know
He's not what he used to be unfortunately
But he's a national treasure
International treasure
I want the new Dune to be good
Because I saw the
Four hour original
Because I knew someone who
Remember we talked about Betamaxes earlier
Someone had it taped on Betamax
Funny enough Questbuster and chat
Is talking exactly about the Dune thing right now
Sci-fi did their own Dune series
And it was actually pretty good
The series is good but it lacks the epic music of Tangerine Dream
That was in the movie
That's how some people feel about Legend
To tie it back to Tim Curry
Legend
I was telling you actually somebody on the phone
I will always play six degrees of Tim Curry
On this show
I will always play
Order of Magic was also done by Jon Pappadou
Well, we tried to get everything set up
Dan couldn't find the crap we needed
but then we decided
we might be playing something on the Saturn instead
because we want to go through
all of our Konami collections
and just sit and bore the shit out of people with Parodius
and Salamander
and maybe some weird RPGs
that we have to have a translation FAQ for
that we're going to speak our own dialogue for
like View 10 a game
Hi, in another universe I turn into a car
if everyone has seen the Utena movie
that must be the awesome universe
Utena turns into
spoiler, she turns into a pink Batmobile
and she and Anthe drive off through the city
it's weird
and then they're naked on the chassis
of the pink Batmobile
as they drive off into their lesbian sunset
that is literally the ending of the Utena movie
okay
right?
ah, jeez
but anyway, we've been kind of on this
old Konami shooter kick
so that's kind of what we're going to do
we watched through different playthroughs of Parodius
and the collection that we
no, it's not the collection we have
the PSP version
is the one where they replaced
um
crap, what song was it?
it was like a pop song that was in the
pattern version and they switched it out
for a remix of
Brilliant to You
because we were trying to figure out which one had Brilliant to You in it
and it was
I think Ocean Berry Parodius
for the PSP
so
anyway
Bright Man says a pink lesbian Batmobile
that's not something I thought I would hear about
have you heard this show?
well, we've done it all
now we have pink Batmobile lesbians
show Michelle
or Tamar
anyway
so that's really been about the
extent of us making plans
and just getting shit together
Dan kept thinking we wanted to play
on the CRT, I'm like why would we play
Saturn on CRT when it's
you know
HDMI
whatevs!
moving on, Loki, how was your gaming week?
um, I played not a lot
of stuff this week but I did start off the
week by trying to transcribe more
edits I was missing off of my DDR machine
and I got through 18 of them
before I decided to try to transfer
them to my system and
you see the problem is I'm using a brand new
editing tool
I used to use one called DDR Edit Max
and it's old, it only ran
on XP and out of
Visual Basic 6
runtime
which doesn't work in
Windows 10, so I found
thanks to the Wayback Machine
DDR Edit Max 2
that actually does work
but
there's a problem is that something's
wrong with the edit
files themselves and
the machine does not recognize them
or doesn't recognize most of them
it recognized one of them
and I don't know why one works
and the rest don't
so I've been
digging through them through
hex editors going back to my
edit FAQ that thank god I made
a long ass time ago because
it's actually helped me trying to read this shit
which I found out a bunch of new stuff
with it as well and I've been
updating it as I go but I
still haven't gotten any of it to work correctly
because something is fucked up
in the header and I'm not sure what
I need to figure out how to fix it
because there's some really awesome edits
I want to play so that was
about most of my week
and then I decided
to check
to see how much well because I
saw the Labo
VR kits coming out this
following week so I was like okay well
it seems so soon like
yeah let's see how much the other
Labo kits are because I know they're coming down in prices
and stuff so I found the robot kit for
$29.99
it actually ended up getting I think for $25
after I think I had a
coupon or something on there but
$25 for the robot kit I was like
can't beat it for that price that's kind of worth it
so I went ahead and picked that up
so I've been building that I started that today
and then I pre-ordered
the VR kit that will be coming next week
because my kids like
playing with the VR stuff and I hate
having to set up the Playstation VR for them
all the time so I was like well I'll just
build this and they can shove their
head in the butt of a bird
so
so we'll be doing that
and then
what else I played a little bit of Ingress
today just because I was
because I was
trying to report a
pokestop for being in the wrong
spot and
you can't do that in Pokemon Go and
apparently I can't do it in Ingress either but
you have to download Scanner Redacted and you can still do it
there which is the 1.0
because they had it was
the arcade creek trail and they had the
lizard marked there which there is a lizard
it's a big cement lizard but it was
several like tens of feet
away from where it actually is
it's in a completely wrong spot so
I was going to report it
but I did
Download the Scanner Redacted app and since you made
your account before Prime
you can still now if you're a brand new agent
you can't use Scanner Redacted because
they're trying to prevent people making new accounts
to spoof and things but since you had an existing account
you can do it yeah so
I may get around to that or I just may not
give a shit but
it was in the right spot at one
time so it's like it got moved I don't know
how that's shenanigans
it's awfully
conveniently close to a
mobile home park where maybe someone's
living in and
you know couch portaling
send me info on that portal we'll get it fixed
but anyway so yeah I did that and
I played Pokemon Go a little bit because
yeah so I'm going
to be I wanted to and like
I must have been half asleep last night when
I decided to order I ordered another
docking station for my
switch because I was like I want to take it apart
and I'm going to use this to build
and then of course my dumb brain today
is like you idiot you can't
you can't hack that apart to make it
allow you to stream
from handheld mode because the damn thing's gonna
think it's docked and it's not going to work so
that's kind of the frustration
because I wanted to like actually
do some streaming from the
VR thing to show like what it looks like
but you can't because
fucking switch
can't stream in handheld mode
so
what are you going to do?
So yeah
I guess I'll just have to find something else to do instead
and play some Borderlands
alright yeah that's it
My gaming week so I actually
officiated my first wedding
yesterday so
I do weddings now if you're curious
at least in California
I'm sure it's probably not that hard to do in other states
but so that
took up a lot of my time this weekend however
I have been playing some other games
including Beat Saber I
played a little bit this week because I had not
gotten around yet to the official volume
one DLC pack and they
put out that what's that
crab song whatever that April Fools
thing was like a year ago it was like this crab song
that they put in Beat Saber
that you can play
I also like the coloring in it because they use
blue and green as the colors instead of the blue and red
that most songs do
so yeah that was fun I liked
playing that so I played a little bit of that
and then I played some of the DLC songs because I downloaded that
because I have Beat Saber on PlayStation 4
so I was playing some of those songs and
you know just enjoying
expanding the original library of songs
not that the songs are bad but now
they're starting to sort them out a little bit too so like
instead of just having a big song list
I have like official volume one
soundtrack add on
songs or whatever it's called and then like
DLC one and so on and so on
so yeah I've been playing that
and then I've been playing Final Fantasy 14
just a little bit kind of got sucked back into that
after the Stormblood story patch and for no
good reason I pushed my
White Mage all the way to level 70 so that's my
fourth job at max level behind
Astrologian Bard and Red Mage
so now I have Astrologian Bard, Red Mage, White Mage all
at 70 no tank at 70 yet
and I don't know if I'll bother taking a tank that high
because I'm not that big a fan of tanking
but I guess if anything I like Dark Knight
of the tanks but we'll see
so did you want to say something on?
I actually just remembered the other
thing I was going to do for gaming is I'm going to go back to
Star Trek Online. Oh yeah
I'm going to cancel the wow and everything and go back to Star Trek Online
I'd be curious how that game kind of
sizes up now compared to when it was first out
They've been incorporating more characters and
have from the TV series and
have the actors back
as voice actors. Oh that's cool.
So I didn't mean to derail your segment
but I thought that since you're talking about MMOs
that might be curious too. That's not the first time.
And I do it to you too. Alright.
Dark Tetsuya in chat says oh speaking of Diablo 3
Rob I sent you something on Switch. I apologize
I haven't checked Diablo 3 on Switch in a long time
but I should probably get on that. It would be nice
to roll a season 16 character
but one more game that I played this week
that I think is kind of a big deal IDK
I played Borderlands which you know
is not a game I've played. I've played it before
but I haven't played a lot of it
but I downloaded the remaster
because I had it on Steam
anyway, the original, and if you had
the original game of the year edition
which I'm sure a lot of people bought for like 5 or 10 bucks
Yeah I just saw what was it
the pre-sequel and stuff was discounted
I'm like oh I should buy the pre-sequel
and I looked at my library and I'm like oh I already have it
So I looked at my library
and now there's Borderlands GOTY
and then there was sure enough Borderlands GOTY
Enhanced and I was like cool
I downloaded the Enhanced one and
originally it wanted to set my configuration
for 1080p and I was like
no I know my video card can do better than that
it was doing ultra
settings at 1080p so I kicked it down to
high settings on 2K
obviously my video card's not quite
good enough to do full 4K but it's 2K
and that works. The game runs very smoothly
and it looks really good
on PC. The art
style of the, you know how Borderlands has the very
strong outlines in a lot of
the art that it does. It really pops
you know in that high resolution
It is funny though because you definitely
notice the parts of the game
that aren't in 2K or 4K
namely anything pre-rendered
so like the little introduction videos
so I've played through the intro of the game
and I did the first boss or whatever
Nine, what is it? Nine Tails?
No Nine Toes
So I've killed Nine Toes and when it did
the whole like introduction
it suddenly switches to a video and you can
tell like there's like it looks
kind of a little more grainy and not
quite the same and I was like oh okay
but you know obviously that's a very minor
complaint it's not even really a complaint
because the game is how old but it's
fun to explore it again and I feel
like in some ways I've gotten a little
better at shooters on the PC
and I think because I remember I used
to be very much like I only wanted to do
shooters with a controller because of
stuff like Halo that I you know
had grown up on or whatever but thanks
to things like Overwatch and other
shooters I've been playing on PC like I feel
very comfortable playing Borderlands on
PC with keyboard and mouse
so I remember how it was the opposite in Final Fantasy
11 where I played everything on a controller
including my macros as a healer
Well you know in Final Fantasy 14
some people play controller on
computer and it's totally
like but that game was kind of built for
a controller not so much 11 a little bit
well no a little bit because it was on
the Playstation 2 in Japan and not everybody
had that you know yeah and
honestly for the longest time I was
strict to controller
I mean Rob came
and saw me play using my little shoulder buttons
for my macros and yeah it works but
I don't know it's kind of funny
how people kind of turn around on what they play on
It does yeah yeah um let's see
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says I think
Borderlands still has an aim assist on
PC which helped me that is
true the aim assist is still there obviously
I'm using it no shame in that I
the nine toes guy killed me once
because he has two little ads
or whatever and so I had to do him
do that fight does he have nine toes
apparently he has nine toes and three balls
that's what the intro says there's a lot of
there's a lot of straight
bro humor in the game
in Borderlands that I just
kind of go whatever
I find it more questionable if he had
a camel toe so
anyway but whatever I think the
game is it's fun to play I like
the questing system feels like an MMO
really so it's kind of yeah it's fun
so I'll probably play some more of it I want to play
some more of it and see you know where the story goes
and I because I've never
really touched the second game and you know
if I really enjoy it maybe I'll even buy the
third game when it comes out so
I'm definitely buying the third game but I want to let
y'all know I finally am getting around and I played
a little bit of Borderlands before but it was just like I'm terrible
at shooters this is bad but I don't know
I'm approaching this with some
more years of gaming of different types
under my belt and I'm kind of like into it right now
and it looks very nice with the enhanced version
so um kudos
so far so
Bobby Blackwell says will you buy the third
game in September or in April
um I'm not going to buy the third game unless
I actually make it through the first two
isn't that fair? Three
well I,
do you have to play pre-sequel? Pre-sequel's
pretty fun Is it? Alright
well then I guess I have three to play so
I don't know I haven't played
pre-sequel yet
well let's I guess we need to get into the
news a little bit and talk about why Bobby
is asking that question uh real quick
this is where I usually plug our social media
so follow us on Twitter slash
or excuse me at OLR we're also on
Facebook facebook.com slash orange lounge
radio we are no longer on Google Plus
Google Plus is officially dead rest
in peace uh alright let's
get to the news starting off with
the big decision when to buy Borderlands
right? Yeah so Borderlands
uh they did a second because you may remember
the original announcement that they did at PAX East
they had more details coming
you know next week
and so the more details that were coming
it's going to be
an exclusive
game to the Epic Games Store for six months
it's going to be launching September 13th
and then you'll be able to buy it elsewhere
April 2020
and it's also going to be out on
PlayStation 4 and Xbox One
and of course
a lot of people aren't very happy about this
mainly because the Epic Store
is very bare bones
and is missing a lot of the things
that you would expect
from a storefront including you know being able
to um
put stuff in a shopping cart
and you know I don't even know
do they have friends list? I mean they have friends list
but they don't have a lot of most of
the bare modes things I would say
it is bare bones but also I would
say it's it's progressed since
it first came out they're still updating it
and who knows where we're going to be in September
September's still a ways out
so of course since quickly though
I can understand the frustration though where it's like
I have Borderlands 1 and 2 on
Steam and now I'm going to have to go
to this store to get Borderlands 3
and it's you know going to be a little bit different
of course tell that to all the Bayonetta
fans right?
I have to buy a Wii U or a
Switch if I want to play Bayonetta 2
even if I play the first Bayonetta
Xbox 360 or wherever
the multitude of places where the first Bayonetta came out
it's on PC now
not not Bayonetta 2
the first Bayonetta is but not Bayonetta 2
gotta get a Switch
because the Epic Games Store is still so bare bones
that there is no way to leave reviews
on any game there
people have turned to Steam to go
express their frustrations by review
bombing of course the other Borderlands
games and you know Steam is very
fond of that happening so
yeah
Steam is really not getting a lot of good news
with this because not only do they not get the game
but then now all the users are going to
shit on the store for Borderlands
1 and 2 right
so that sucks but I know that
they had talked about ways to
prevent review bombing so we'll see
how that ends up working out but
I mean I don't know like
yeah it's annoying
that the only thing Epic's doing
right now seems like to try to drive
people to their platform well a couple things
I guess they're lowering the price
which is why or the cut that they
take which is why these big game companies are
kind of going their way because I'm sure they're
getting money thrown at them
plus they're also getting more
of more profit off of everything
so of course they want to make as much
money as possible
I think originally the plan was more
to try to drive you know indies to their
platform but
whatever it is what it is
the free games they give away
is nothing to buy
no that's nice and it's
to me it's kind of like you play
and stuff like that or like even
EA services
Origin you just have to have
it for certain games whether you like
it or not and I think this is kind of like this
if I want to play this game on PC at launch
I just have to
I already have Epic installed so it's not a big deal
to be honest I have Origin
you know love it or hate it
which it's come a long way but I
have Origin installed because that was the only
way I was going to be able to play Mass Effect Andromeda
on PC
as well as got a sweet deal
on Titanfall 2
you know there's just there's certain things that
you can only get on Origin that have to do with
EA BioWare and that type of thing
Can't you put like external games into it?
You have to have Origin for Apex
Can't you put external games into your Steam library
anyways because I thought they have ways to launch them
so I mean I'm sure that if this
isn't like any other game out there
you can have an executable that's straight
you don't have to launch it through the Epic
storefront I'm pretty sure
that you can just have an executable shortcut or something
The way that it works for
Origin is that it will
open when you have the link to
the game it will open
Origin and then open the game
but run it through Steam so that you can do your
screenshots and everything through the Steam platform
Oh wow. Because that's how
basically how I got all of my stuff
for my little effect which I've kind of let
fall to the wayside
Well the game's been out a long time now you've probably screen capped almost everything you can
I've had drama that's kept
me from posting and being sick and
family members dying and stuff
speaking of Mass Effect not to like
completely 180 this conversation but I noticed
Alan was like he was
reinstalling Mass Effect the other night and I'm like what's going on
he's like there's some new mod that came out that I want to check
out so I think they have like another new
graphics mod or something and so
now I see him because you know remember
Alan will get obsessed with one
game at a time. One game at a
time and um
It's nice to be able to have that kind of restraint
I don't have that kind of restraint
I know he's the complete polar opposite
so like Dark Souls has been his thing for a long time
Overwatch he still kind of plays off and on
this is the one that surprised me do you know what game
has been like his late like it's all he's been playing
lately? Dead Island
of like all the games in the universe
The first one? Yeah
I think it's a combination of the
series but mostly the first one
like that's what he's kind of been
into lately so yeah
I mean not to knock that game I know some of y'all are big
fans. By the way what ever happened
to Dead Island 2? Wasn't that like supposed to be out by now?
Uh I think Dead Island
2 already came out. No I don't think it ever did
there was like a Dead Island like
expansion for the
first game or something it was just built on the
first game. It still says it's upcoming on
wiki. Yeah they showed a trailer for Dead Island
2 like in 2014. Yeah I was like
I was like the last time I went to E3
Oh yeah. I saw that Dead Island 2 too.
That was a long time ago right?
Well there's a rumor on
this E3
like thing about with some pre-alpha footage
on it saying that
it's supposed to
the release date is going to be announced at E3
Well then they
have like a what was the other dead game
there was another dead bot not Dead by Dawn
but like there was a
oh like not a dead island but like a dead
free running game I can't remember the hell it's called
but they had like a couple sequels of that
I thought that was maybe
I don't know maybe
stop making zombie games because
I can't tell them apart okay?
Maybe you should stop doing that. I did not mean to
180 the conversation but we got on a tangent train
as we sometimes do. Let's have the
the chat brings back. Act F says
Dead Island Riptide no that was kind of that was
still it was like the first game
like after bit because you
just started at level 40 or you could import
characters to the first game it wasn't a true sequel
Dead Island Riptide was not the true sequel but
good point
The Break Man says is Dead Island any good
and Quest Buster says
it's good now it was pretty broken on release
and that's pretty much everything I've heard too and knowing Alan
he's probably modded the fuck out of the game
I'll bet you anything what got him on it there's probably
some graphic mod for the game
that got him into it
Maybe he should join up with Minecraft
Knowing Alan as well as I do
So YYR
is kind of fed up a little bit here
saying I'm just fed up with apps
and launchers I basically refuse to
play anything that would require me to download
an app or get another launcher
I have enough accounts I don't want anymore
since I play mostly niche stuff
I haven't really been affected by any of this yet
but if someone releases their game on the epic store
good for them but I'll never play it
Um
Isn't it I might be wrong I don't to be
honest I've never bought anything on the epic
store I have a nice collection of the free
stuff and fortnite that's about it
so I mean at least I bought things
I haven't bought anything yet on the epic
store personally but
do you
because we were just kind of talking about the
launcher loading in the background
if I get a game like
say super meat boy that I got for free
or whatever on the epic game store
if I just run that executable
doesn't it not go through the store
like maybe you don't have to use launcher I don't know
I can't remember I have it just I had it already
on there when I was trying out
development in unreal engine so
I already have it on there
for that um
and but I right now it's mainly
now it's just to grab the free
game of every couple weeks or whatever
that they put out and Bobby's correcting
me it does still launch the epic game store in the
background alright fair enough it's probably
must check to make
sure you bought it or something I don't know yeah
so I mean whatever I've
I haven't really purchased anything from
the epic game store I have looked at the new
game that they have from coffee scene studios
I may pick up that one
um but
so far I haven't purchased anything
from there alright
well let's move on and talk about
um what's going on
with the switch online retro
service so um
switch online uh has
been adding more NES games every
month and um
uh some of the latest
games will be coming to the switch um in
April of 2019 on
the 10th so what next week I think yeah
about three days uh they've announced
the next series of games that's going to come out which includes
punch out
not the Mike Tyson punch out cause obviously
the licensing stuff is gone although
I'm sure y'all heard about that tweet where Mike Tyson
was like why am I not in punch
out on this like I seriously don't
I don't think Mike Tyson knows
that he was taken out
of punch out a long time ago I don't
think he knows about Mr. Dream shh don't tell him
don't tell him I don't know
anyway he might bite Mr. Dream's ear off
uh also coming out Star
Soldier kind of a fun little shooter
and then Super Mario Brothers
The Lost Levels at least
that's what they're calling it here in the
US and so they actually are
giving it the little box you know that they kind
of created for Super Mario All-Stars
little square box but what's funny is
that when they showed the preview movie
they didn't bother to correct the title screen
or anything so when you launch it it's still just
Super Mario Brothers 2
obviously the Japanese version of these releases
same thing punch out Star Soldier
Super Mario Brothers 2 for them
but you know like if you launch
our Super Mario Brothers 2 in their
Famicom online it says Super Mario Brothers
USA they changed the title screen
they didn't they didn't do that here
so
because they actually did get it released to
Super Mario USA there later right
yeah so but anyway
that's not really the big news although it's certainly
a part of this as well as the the
question people might be asking is how long
is Nintendo going to keep going with this like
are they going to release every single NES game
and which honestly would be doubtful
due to licensing
and you know especially when
third parties develop the game where does
the money go and all that stuff so
um apparently what's happening
over in Hong Kong some leaflets for the
Switch online service were being distributed
and leaflets talk about what
the Switch online service includes because you know
they're trying to sell people on get your
you know online Nintendo subscription
so you can access the classic library
but apparently there's one little section with
fine print that says
eventually Nintendo will stop
adding new NES games to the
collection but obviously they're not
saying when or anything
like that but this it kind of already
has the internet riled up on oh
the Super Nintendo must be coming because
they're saying the Nintendo thing is ending
there's only a finite amount
of games on the Nintendo so eventually
yes it will end
and it could be
ending in three years
it doesn't mean it's going to end by the end
it's because we live in a world where people
are going to sue over the fact that Red Bull
doesn't give them wings so of course they have
to you know put the
put the disclaimer in there guess what
eventually we're not going to be adding
this was in Hong Kong I don't know if Hong Kong
has a sue happy culture like we have here
but but I get what you're saying
of course I get what you're saying you have to
you have to say the obvious things like
that because you're right people will sue well I've been paying
money every month where's my new games class
action lawsuit yeah
yeah anyway uh
dark to see in chat says well I assume they would
they were not going to end it like next month
but obviously they won't keep it going forever
honestly they would have made a lot more money if they
just uh virtual console
you think huh I know
well now especially that they just gave away a year
free with Amazon Prime obviously
Twitch and Amazon must be kicking them some money
but it's interesting they could have made a lot
more money a lot more
way all they just
seem happy I don't have to drop
the drop the cost
of the games down like you know cut down the amount
that they were charging for those because eight dollars
for a Super Nintendo game is just ridiculous but
cut that down to a point that it is like
very like four ninety
nine or something like that or you know
cut it down to where it's just like impulse by
people be eating that shit up
so Questbuster in chat says there's around
seven hundred or thirty officially licensed game
on the NES but
I mean you're assuming they're going to
I mean I don't think you specifically are assuming but like
they're not going to release all seven hundred thirty games
they're just not like the licensing on
too many games is too complicated for example
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
by Konami not going to come out
not going to happen because the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
licensing now is complicated
I don't think Konami owns the license anymore
they haven't for some time either EA has
or somebody else has it and that
I mean miracles happen because they did
release that arcade game on 360
when people didn't think that would happen but it's going to be
much harder for like a classic thing
that Nintendo kind of oversees for that to happen
I would say things like the
Guardian Legend as much as Dark
Sakura and myself and many of you stand that
game hard I just don't see that game
coming out because the license it's too complicated
who owns that game now? I think we figured
it out. Whoever owns
Bode Brund
well Bode Brund only published it
it's compile
we figured out the rights in the previous episode
it's so far like four times removed
now at this point and then I think I cried
yeah I might have cried
but you know again
miracles happen but they're just
not going to jump through hoops
for all seven hundred thirty games because
also let's be real some of them were pretty bad
some of those games were pretty bad
so maybe we don't need
all seven hundred and thirty but
yeah I think you know it's inevitable this is
going to end but I would say it's still going to be going at least
for a year I think the
thought is that you know as far as a Super
Nintendo online or something that does
seem like a very logical kind of next
step although
you know Loki to kind of build on your point
maybe they're going to have
the NES library be
Nesflix style
but maybe the Super Nintendo games
they plan to do piecemeal maybe
we're all assuming they'll be
assuming or did they say in
the earliest they did say in the
earliest press releases
that there would be Super Nintendo games didn't they
and the earliest earliest
materials about this online service
I'm trying to remember that far back
and they seem to remember that might have been a
I don't need
the Super Nintendo games to come out
because I have a Super SNES
Bobby's confirming what I just said they did say the earliest
ones absolutely did say that
well that's cool but I don't need it because
you only sold me your systems
you know you sold me that stuff already so
obviously I already have it and modded it
you know
SNES classic yeah exactly so I
don't need your you know extra
stuff Bobby points out
the early ones didn't even mention NES
games they only mentioned Super Nintendo games
so it would be interesting if they started
to dial back from that now but I kind of I don't think
they will I think most people kind of figure that
maybe when this
new Switch comes out or whatever they'll roll
out if rumors are true they'll
roll out the matching Super Nintendo library to
go with it who knows but we'll see
anyway that's to assume that the
Switch Online stays legal
right Narsakra I guess there's some interesting legal
things going on right there is that
basically in the UK the
competition and markets authority
has opened an investigation against Microsoft
Nintendo and Sony to check on
their online service practices to see
if they violate a consumer protection law
consumer law is a lot
more of a big thing
I guess in
Europe Australia
those general areas
but basically
they want to see if it's violating
those aspects of their consumer law they want to know
the auto renewal policies are fair
how easy it is to get a refund
or cancel it and whether or not the terms
of services
take more power out of the
customer's hand and put it into
the companies so basically
they want to make sure the laws are fair and
equal to both company and
consumer it's
actually part of a response to
a quote super complaint
on a loyalty penalty
which is basically the tendency for
some of the companies to punish
long standing customers by
making it difficult or
expensive to leave
and so they're
they said the investigation just started but they may
only take enforcement action
if they believe the companies are not being fair
you know
the biggest things that have indicated
this is becoming a problem is that Sony raised
prices for Playstation Plus
that there is
I mean just kind of like we were saying that there's no
guarantee that you're going to get
the same number of free
games or perks for
the cost that you're paying for it
and of course there is
auto renewal
you know for example
like what's going on now
with the Switch promotion for Twitch Prime
you have to
turn the auto renewal off after your time
period is up or you're going to get charged
and well
it's interesting because you know this is UK
law so a lot of our normal ways of
thinking don't really apply
necessarily but like I know this is a super
common tactic in the US like
when it comes to let's say Spotify
I'll pick on Spotify you get 99
cents for a month of Spotify right
but the whole trick is now they get your credit
card number they're going to auto bill you
unless you like turn it off
and heck there's tons of iPhone
and Android apps that do this too right they'll give away
a 7 day
preview of like the sleep
app that I use we'll do like a 7 day
preview of their mode but then
if you don't turn it off it will do an auto
renew so like I feel like in our
culture that's a thing like you got
it like we all know that's a gotcha
tactic in a lot of different places
right or a gym membership that's another
big one sign up for a gym membership
for 5 bucks but then after
30 days oh it's going to be the full you know
$50 a month or whatever it is right
but um yeah
it's the fact that it's UK law
I don't I can't put myself into the same
like shoes or whatever
so but some of our chatters think there
might be something here uh break man in chat says by
British laws I think they have a chance
I think Microsoft and Sony will lose this
but I don't know how it will affect us in America
well and I will tell you one thing too
just with some other companies
like for example with these
increased stringency of
encryption requirements and
uh customer control over
their personal online data
um because they became so
much stringent um overseas
that American companies are actually now
following suit to match those so that they don't have
to worry about what
are we doing different here what are we doing different
there you know it's
going to be universal it's why when you go on to all
these different websites now there's a huge
fucking thing that says by using
this website you agree to use cookies
here's our cookie policy that's because of
something that happened in the UK not here
so but we all
kind of get it too because
in the world wide web
you know it kind of has to apply
they set the bar at the most
stringent standard and then the rest of us kind of see
the effects of that exactly yeah
I think the auto renewal you know it's interesting because you know
it's a like when you get your free
PlayStation Plus games let's say
if you don't renew
and you're at the mercy of
Sony and everything I'm saying could apply
to Microsoft or I'm not picking on
Sony I'm just using them as an example
but um you know if you don't renew
um you don't get to play
those games anymore that you got for
free and that's part of the agreement but
you're kind of at the mercy of Sony
could kind of kick up the price of that
at any time they want to
well the same thing goes for Spotify subscription
or Pandora or Apple Music
it really is quite literally the same
thing it's just for games instead of listening
to music you know
it's really
no different I mean you know
Pandora could bump up their price or Spotify
could bump up their price and it's really
I
mean
it's like that ongoing
capitalist inflation cycle
where everything else increases
but your money does not so
it's all that
Akuma JP in chat says in Japan
we're trying to get rid of auto-subscribe
and fees for unsubscribe
I can't even believe there'd be like
fees for unsubscribing you know what I kind
of think is that I
the thing that frustrates me is that like to
get to unsubscribe from some
things you have to like call
in and the thing is only
open between like 9 am and 5
pm when a lot of people are working or whatever
so sometimes it's like really hard
to like cancel something because you can only
do it over the phone even though you can sign up for it
online so I kind of think
and I thought I heard something about the rules
moving this way or whatever is
that if you sign up for something
online you ought to be able to
cancel online as well
you shouldn't be able to sign up
and then not
like cancel the same way you signed
up they should only have cancellation
cancellation over the phone is the only option
if subscribing over the phone is the only
option that's the thing that I kind of disagree with
but I thought I heard something about laws
we're looking into that as well
so YYR in chat
says where are there fees for unsubscribing
it could be another part
you know Akuma JP is commenting from Japan
so maybe it's just not something we
have here but
well I have heard of things like early
termination agreements like cell phones
you sign up for a year
and then mortgages prepayment penalties
sure or
again
gyms right for some
deals you have to sign up for a year
and if you break it early you get a penalty
so but I get
that that's kind of you know
maybe we kind of sit here
going oh well doesn't everybody
know that but you know certain cultures
may have a different approach and I think
that's also what you're seeing here is that the UK
is starting to look at some things that maybe
we've just kind of come to accept as normal
in our culture and going huh should that
really be the way I don't know
so anyway
alright Sia Tabiri in chat
says Verizon will never let the
government stop that and Amazon
or Act Deft points out Amazon
used to have a cancellation fee for monthly
prime subscribers but they got rid
of that and then
the break man says
rollover contracts are a big no-no
in the UK as of the 2015 law
very interesting how all these
as the world gets more and more closer
together through the internet
all these laws in different places
kind of set different tones very interesting
anyway it's always about
consumer advocacy though that's very important
well let's move on for the sake of time
we're gonna go to our next topic Loki
yeah so this is kind of neat
so apparently Microsoft is rolling
the Xbox or they're giving you an
option to
have basically Xbox Live and Game Pass
as one big subscription
so apparently the plan
is to merge them into a $15
per month subscription called Xbox Game
Pass Ultimate
that'll basically give you both of those
services
at one cost now
apparently the annual of course
live gold membership is
$60 and 12 months of Game Pass is
$120 so that still
works out to $180 per year
so you're not really saving any money
in that way
but maybe $15
a month they're kind of
poising it in a way that
like hey you pay like 12 bucks a month
for Netflix or whatever and
it's not much more so
maybe that's how they're trying
to sell it when I first read the article
I was like oh this is what they're gonna start to move to
it's the only option I was like I've been saying this
they dropped the price down like maybe dropped it down
to like say $12.99 a month
or something like that and then
look see if you sign up for both
you save a little bit but
if you sign up for both
you pay for both that's not really much
of a deal
aren't you saying that only if you're paying for like live
on a year if you're paying live month to month you're still saving money
aren't you? Right but you're
always gonna be saving a month even just paying it for a
year so I
depends on how you want to do it
but I've been kind of sitting here going it's only
a matter of time before they just kind of
loop Game Pass and gold into the same thing
and this feels like a step in that direction
even though you know the finances and all that
get tricky and I do think
I do think you know they're not gonna
be able to easily
convince people to do this if they can't get
the price of Game Pass as low as the price of gold
maybe this could be per month
and then if they have like a year
subscription to this it's even less
you know maybe they could do something like that
I can understand that might be a little bit more
enticing because it's like oh hey you know I can get both these
services for less than I'm
you know paying for them
you month to month or something like that
I just don't see the advantage of just
putting the prices together
it's if you're doing it month to month
and YYR points out if you're paying month to month
$15 a month is a 25% savings
over subscribing to both individually
but if you're paying $60 a year then it's the same
price unless they get rid of gold
and just have that is this is your
only option I just I feel
like that you know I've been saying that for a long time
but maybe I know I know we're probably still
a little bit away from that but it'll be
very interesting to see I think at E3
what Microsoft does to push this further
are they saying this is going to be a thing at E3 or
sooner than that?
The thought was that it's supposed to be
this is rumor right? It's supposed to be out
around the time when the Xbox
One S all digital edition is revealed
the thought is so
that I think is supposed to happen in a few weeks
so I guess we'll hear about this before
E3. Alright
it'll be interesting if all this stuff kind of comes out
before E3.
Moving on to what's been kind of
an interesting back and forth this week
Kotaku ran a very
interesting piece on BioWare
that was really kind of a dragging and exposing
of some of the things that went on behind the scenes
at Anthem and the development
of Anthem and why Anthem may not
have turned out to be as
wonderful as it did. I'm not going to
really try to summarize the article if
you want to go read it you can. I would say
what I took away from this and maybe some of you in
the chat feel different but it really sounds
like they shifted
development in the last year
and a half which I feel like we
hear about games all the time and I would say
Final Fantasy XV was another one of those games
they just took the wheel and change
development in the last year and a half and
that's one of the reasons but it sounds like the biggest
reason Anthem had
problems was that they were forced to use the Frostbite
engine. It really sounds like that Frostbite
engine is not doing
BioWare any favors because it sounds
like I'm hearing a lot of the same
stuff out of what happened with
Mass Effect Andromeda and so on. Anyway
but the complicated
stuff that happened. So Kotaku
put out their story and then like what like 15 minutes
after the fact BioWare
put out a thing that
basically was like you know
we don't agree and it was
very kind of generic and didn't really
speak specifically to the piece like they knew it was
coming but they didn't know specifically what was
in it and obviously if Kotaku had asked
BioWare to comment on it then they probably knew it was
coming. Well a secondary
piece kind of came out and
Casey Hudson I believe wrote this piece
to something they sent to the whole
staff and of course emails
leaked from within what a shock
and part of the letter says
what we found out of bounds
was the naming of specific developers
as targets for public criticism
because Kotaku does try to kind of
draw this line of this particular
individual came in and the development kind of
shifted so it did kind of I did
find it to be maybe finger pointing a little bit
but I didn't me personally I didn't see
it as a negative I kind of felt like
it might be that this guy saw this
machine that was rolling in like all these different
directions and had to put it on
course because it was spiraling out of control
or something. It sounds like there's a lot
of other issues going into this that are
more complex than a three hour show can handle
but what's also interesting
is Kotaku kind of notes at the end of the letter
they said that
they've heard from a number of developers
who work or have worked at beloved
AAA game studios with messages like
replace BioWare with my
studio and it's the same story
and these are things like
crunch hours
just things
the left hand not knowing what the right hand is doing
rivalries between studios that are in
different cities and like all
of these things are just like really really
messy and
I don't know
I think we all have been sitting here going
the gaming industry is going to
crack under some of this at some point
and I don't know if it's the AAA
gaming that is going to be
looking at streaming as a primary thing that's
going to cause some things to crack or if
game developers do
cross that bridge and they
form a big game developer union
I mean Hollywood has unions
they need to unionize like
major Hollywood has Screen
Actors Guild, Writers Guild
I mean right so
it would be
sorry now it's SAG-AFTRA
the Screen Actors and the Play Actors
and voice actors
are part of that as well which
have affected gaming in the past
and they have very specific rules
they have to follow so anyway
I know that's a really kind of like controversial thing
but I think a lot of us are sitting here going
this whole like gaming crunch
time and the way games are being developed
it ain't working
y'all
and especially when you look at Anthem
some people are still defending
Anthem and having a good time playing it
and if you're having a good time with Anthem
go you, have fun
but I'm hearing some challenges about
what to do at the end of Anthem
and that it seems like it might be a little bit short sight
I feel like this is a broken record
there's so many of these games that have been in development
for years, well we just joked about
Dead Island 2 right?
they probably haven't started the real development
on Dead Island 2 yet
and they're going to crunch, crunch, crunch, crunch
to get it out by the end of a fiscal year
so
anyway
Kaijuto in chat says if they make a union
I hope they name it the multiplayer
unions don't really get
very cute names
it'll probably be something very, very plain
let's see
Act Def says
it's the people running the unions that
may be bad, unions aren't a bad thing
and devs should definitely form one
I don't know if the US has a similar law but in Mexico
you have the right to start a union
yeah you have the right to start a union, it's just
some companies will go so far
as to show you movies on your first day on why it's a bad idea
sometimes happens
so anyway
YYR in chat says and this is why I develop games
in my spare time and refuse to actually try to do it
for a living, sorry that you're all still waiting
for the new bungee ferret tossing but
it's not ready, and that's okay
YYR, when it's ready, it's ready
and that's cool, I mean you got new baby
and all that stuff, you're busy
it's fine, it's done
when it's done, right
just like we've gotten used to with a lot of blizzard games
just like we get used to with a lot of movies
it's done when it's done, right
and that's a-ok
so
what was I gonna say with the whole
that whole tangent
about the development needing to take its time
I lost my train of thought but
I think, you know, it's gonna get worse
in some ways when the graphics
are pushed even further
as we move into the Playstation 5
and the Xbox, you know, whatever the next Xbox
is, I don't know, I feel like something's gonna give
here, it's just
this industry really can't
keep going the way it's
going and people
need to be held accountable for some of these really
fucking bad decisions that happen
because I, from my perspective and looking
at all this, I feel like truly
the bottom line in this whole
thing on why these games are not
turning out as good as they could be
is that they're being forced to use the Frostbite engine
because of some type of company
you know, because EA, EA's making
them do it, like the real enemy
in this whole thing between
Mass Effect Andromeda and
maybe the next Dragon
Age and Anthem
is the Frostbite engine
so, you know what, EA
it is time to let that engine
go and if your developers
want to make a game in Unity, fucking let them
fucking let them
why are you, why are you tied, like you're
gonna go like that, do you want that Frostbite
engine to be the hill that you
die on? Cause
so far it's not looking good
Unless they have some sort of exclusivity
contract
and they're stuck to it
What I'm saying is that that contract is garbage
and it's sinking those games and they need to
end that contract or whatever it is
But companies don't think that way, they think of
immediate and not long term
Anyhow, let's move on
we got plenty more show to cover
Alright, well, how about
loot boxes?
How about no loot boxes?
Well, anyway
the Federal Trade Commission is going to
be holding a public workshop
on August 7th
2019 at the Constitution
Center in Washington D.C.
It will be webcast on the FTC's
website, but the workshop is called
Inside the Game, Unlocking Consumer
Issues Surrounding Loot Boxes
to quote
Examine consumer protection issues
related to video game loot boxes
End game rewards players can
buy while playing a video game
So this is what they want to do, they want to include
industry representatives, consumer advocates
trade associations, academics
and government officials to discuss
these following things. So it's the
end game transition landscape
including origin and
evolution of loot boxes and their role
in game play in the digital marketplace
and this is actually bullet points from
their thing
I was just going to say, Bobby is suggesting
this webcast should include one slide
with one word, don't
Research examining
consumer behavior including child and adolescent
behavior in the context of video games
and digital transactions
and a discussion of consumer awareness
and education about end game digital
transactions including the mechanics, marketing
and financial commitments associated
with loot boxes
They're also saying
that the public can
submit their input on those
topics by emailing lootbox
workshop at
ftc.gov up until
June 7th of this year
So there you go, you can send your email
subject, loot boxes, message, don't
There's also
an online
comment, forum
comment, forum on
the FTC
website which I will be linking in chat
Oh good!
But I'll just
go ahead and read it, it's regulations
dot gov slash
dot get question mark
D equals FTC
dash 2019 dash 0021
I imagine most of you will just Google
it. Whatever, I just said it
because it was a short one, it wasn't all crazy
But yeah,
basically you can
comment on the
document, there's nothing supporting right now
but the final
on that page is the document
for their
proposal on here for that workshop
and just taking a quick glance
over on it
Why does everything from the FTC
have to be in Microsoft Word format?
So basically
yeah, it's a lot of what I said
but it talks about what a loot box
is, why people
have concerns about it
and basically some of the goals of it
and again, it's for the public
I think it would be interesting to read this
and I might have to go in and do it later just to see how it's been
dumbed down for government officials
There's also a media contact listed in here
Fun
I imagine many of you are running
to the forum right now to simply post
don't
Does anyone enjoy loot boxes?
Sometimes they're kind of fun if you're guaranteed
something nice
I mean, I didn't mind it so much in
Mass Effect 3 multiplayer
but I got
kind of tired of it
I prefer being able to
win currency in my game
instead of getting a box for it
because that's 90% of
I saved my points and got stuff
instead of just paying into them
What are the people who will pay into it to get the biggest and bestest?
I like Enforza
where it's like you kind of have a wheel
that you spin but you'll get everything eventually
you know what I mean? If they want to
hand it out in a random order then fine
I don't know, but anyway
AkumaJP in chat says
free loot box I don't mind
when it's free and you get them as a part
of playing through the game
I think that's why a lot of people kind of give
Overwatch some slack because
Overwatch is kind of constantly handing out
free loot boxes between the holidays
and every time you level up and all that stuff
so I think that's why
some people kind of let that one slide
I don't know. Anyway, moving on
we still have some more gaming stories for you guys
Loki. Alright, well
something coming from yet another
battle royale game
but taking a page
out of Apex Legends
Fortnite has decided to add reboot vans
which apparently is very similar to
the respawn
beacons that you have in Apex Legends
but of course now they're just
kind of skinning it for
Fortnite so that's the new update that's going to be
coming very soon as well
to kind of mix up the game a little bit
and they kind of do something like
once a month anyways to kind of mix the game
up so I'm not surprised
that one game's curving
off of another game for
gameplay ideas
It's kind of interesting now to see how like
Fortnite that's been kind of leading things
it's kind of taken some cues now from
Apex which has Apex overtaken
Fortnite at this point or is it still kind of like a back
and forth? I've been watching the
Twitch rankings that closely and I know that's just one
representation
of how the games might actually be doing
when it comes to the money they're making
and so forth so yeah but
I mean I think it sounds interesting
I don't know I still just when it comes
to Fortnite like the building thing I just
I've never been able to wrap my head
around how the building works like what
like strategically how you like do that
in Fortnite because Fortnite has like no
tutorial and so I've never really been able to
figure out how to use that effectively
You can do the creative mode which
you know what's funny and a half later because I went to go look at the
Weezer thing at one point and like you know
I yeah the creative mode's kind of fun I
like that but then when I I don't know
what the building in combat
I don't know I haven't been able to wrap my head around that but the building
stuff isn't in Apex so
in some ways it's kind of easier I think
so yeah
Bobby Blackwell says
in Fortnite when you shoot someone they turn into
a 10 story building yeah
or they they try to hide themselves inside
a 10 story building so that you can't shoot them
I suppose alright anyway
one more story for you guys before we get to
the Classic Game of the Week and it has to do with some
Best Buy leaks so who
knows if they're true or not but
I know they're talking about some things
I think a lot of us have been waiting for
well anyway apparently these were on
internal employee terminals
suggesting that Persona 5
was about to get a
Switch release for 60 bucks
they didn't have a date on it
it just was in the system
you know how that goes somebody made a record in the system
you know how that goes remember Walmart Canada
and E3 last year yeah
Metroid Prime Trilogy was
another one and I think a lot of us have been kind of
asking oh when is that going to come out on Switch so that
might actually be a thing but then
the other surprise in there was
The Legend of Zelda
A Link to the Past
wait a minute wait a minute
that's the Super Nintendo game
why would the Super Nintendo game
be released by itself
unless
either Nintendo does plan to
piecemeal this despite
their earlier marketing about
the NES and the Super Nintendo
being separate or could
they since they're making
this Link's Awakening game
in a 3D environment
that looks a lot like A Link to the Past
but 3D could they
possibly maybe
be remaking
A Link to the Past as
well that's what some people are
theorizing with this how would you
feel about how would you guys feel about
A Link to the Past remake
in that
3D style that they're doing this Awakening
remake in
I mean
I need my pixels
I'm open to it like the Secret of Mana
remake was alright
but the original is still
like the one like if I'm like you've never
played Secret of Mana I'm gonna pull up the original
like the 3D remake was cool
in some ways but it also had issues when it first came out
I don't know if you guys remember the Secret of Mana
kind of had some issues when it first came out so
I don't know but Nintendo
usually does not
I would trust Nintendo's quality
a little bit more than probably anybody else
so anyway
let's see
Brakeman says I want a VR style
remake be careful what you ask
for let's see
Bobby Blackpool says what is the remake also
has Metroid and has a randomizer
you're on
but I don't think that's what's gonna happen although
god I wish Nintendo would go down that path
can you even imagine you know what I want
I want a new remix game
like NES remix and wasn't there
SNES remix at one point I remember
no there wasn't then I want an SNES
remix I want those games to come back
out those are fun anyway
alright let's move on to
the classic game of the week
every week here on the show Dark
Soccer steps in the gaming vault to find the game
that she thinks hey sticky
you guys should be checking out this classic
oh my god the cat threw up and you know
sometimes that's what I say in the vault
sometimes Dark Soccer will pick
pretty obscure Japanese titles you probably never
played like last week was one of those
titles right it wasn't very
yeah it was but this
this week she's picking a game
that I owned
this is a little bit more
one that you guys probably could play
honestly act deaf this goes out to you
what is the classic game of the week
actually finger trick
it is Kirby Superstar
because
it's so much fun I've decided that
my first tattoo might actually
be Kirby riding the star
it might be if I don't get my cherry blossom
but anyway
in PAL regions it was released as Kirby's
Fun Pack and it came out in
1996 so the
year I moved out here
the year I graduated high school
girl I should take that back
no I moved out here did I move out here in 96?
I don't remember
no I think I moved out here in 98
anyway whatever
anyway it was
developed by HAL Laboratories and published by Nintendo
for the Super Nintendo
and it was part of
the entire Kirby series
it basically was advertised
as featuring 8 games
7 short sub games
with all the same basic gameplay
and too many games
it was later released on Wii and Wii U
and there's an enhanced remake
called Kirby Superstar Ultra
that came out on the DS in 2008
also Nintendo
re-released Kirby Superstar in Japan
US and Europe
in November 2017 as part of the
Super NES Classic Edition
which I think I played
quite a bit of that during the time
anyway you play
as Kirby who can float
and inhale stuff and spit him out
if he swallows certain enemies
he gains their abilities and can use them
as his own
another feature of this
particular game is helpers
so when Kirby has an ability he can
transform it into a helper character
that the second player or computer can
control and certain abilities
like
crash or the mic cannot be
like crash or mic cannot be
turned into helpers
so you have to choose to give the helper
a form or revert them into a power
up in an emergency
so some of them
like wheelie allow Kirby to interact with
them during two player play
so
basically if it takes too much damage
then Kirby can grant it a new power
before it disappears and he has to create
a new one and if Kirby takes too much
damage he loses a life
so there are a few
the different ones in here are Spring Breeze
which is a simplified remake
of Kirby's Dream Land
but it has the Superstar enhancements in it
so basically you have to make it to a
castle to challenge King Dedede
who has stolen food from Dream Land
wah
and also float islands
in Castle Lola Will have emerged
and Kabula does not
appear and then
when you reach Castle Dedede you don't have
to do a boss rush to get to
King Dedede
Dynablade is an original
one where you have to stop Dynablade
which is a giant bird from
disturbing Dream Land's crops
it's all about food isn't it Kirby?
so you have four layers that you have to play and then you face off
against Dynablade and you have two secret
areas and many bosses that move around the world
map in this one
Gourmet Race, jeez even more food
so you have to race against King Dedede
while eating as much food as you can
so
you take
it takes place across three levels of different links
and whoever earns the most points by the end of all three levels
with a bonus point being the first to
finish each race
and so then you can choose to race
King Dedede or your ghost
to be the best at that
and the DS actually had multiplayer
functionality in this one
then we have the Great Cave Offensive which is
a metroidvania style game
where Kirby has to explore a cave for treasure
and so you have
sixty treasure chests
and you get a maximum score
of, it looks like
ninety-nine million
no, nine million nine hundred and ninety
nine, nine hundred and ninety points
and sixty treasures
it also has references to
other Nintendo games like the Triforce
screw attack
the helmet of Captain Falcon and
Mr. Saturn from Earthbound
and then you've got
other value
items that appear like in other
role playing games. We have the Revenge of
Meta Knight which basically has Kirby
trying to destroy Meta Knight's battleship
the Halberd before Meta Knight can
conquer Dreamland
you have a time limit and it will cost
you a life if it hits zero
and it is very apparently plot based
so then we also have Milky Way Wishes
which is the largest game in the collection
basically the sun and the moon
around planet Popstar
are fighting and a creature named
Marx tells Kirby that he must travel across
nine planets to restore a giant
wish granting comet
Nova, comet Clock Nova
so unlike this one
Kirby can't copy
the enemies
he can get copy essence's
deluxe and then he can choose a copy ability
from the list and then he has it through the game
also
beating Milky Way Wishes
grant you the arena sub game
and the arena is an endurance mode
that is a big boss rush, you fight basically
every boss, there are 26 bosses
in 19 rounds
and in between each round you have
a room with maximum tomatoes
five of them which can only be used
once each and then
two randomly selected pedestals will
give you certain powers
you can choose any of the powers at the beginning of the game
and then if you beat that you get the sound test
function so you can listen to all the music in the game
there are some sub games like Samurai Kirby
where it's a
timing based mini game
like quick draw from Kirby's adventure
where you have to
do the attack at just the right moment
wild gunman basically and then megaton
punch which is what I did yesterday
anyway you have to punch a crack
in the planet and you have to make a bigger crack
the point is crack rob
anyway
this is one of those games that had a special
chip for it, it's the SA-1 chip
and
with this particular
one it was basically just to
be able to
help with some of the computer generated imagery
like what was in the
introduction
they had some
other things that were planned
for the game and of course
Sakurai who also did give us Smash
Brothers
was developing the game using three different
design pillars as he said it
a two player co-op gameplay, beat em up
gameplay and an omnibus format
that you could use it to reach
an ending and actually it was
that last
sorry the two player co-op
I believe was requested by Miyamoto
and then
a couple of the other things
that were wanted to be in the game
was one called Kagero Mansion
which was a survival horror game
that leaves Kirby stuck in a mansion
with a cursed seal in his mouth
so he cannot use his
inhale or copy ability
and then
it was meant to be a little bit more
proactive in the gameplay but
they didn't want to
do it so basically
but when it was sold in Japan
it was sold in a package
resembling a wooden box with a seal
burnt off
like buying high priced sake or dishware
comes in one of those boxes, luxury items
so the design was supposed to be
like a luxury item box
so anyway
with the remake version
which came out in 2008 so it's still
under that 10 year thing
it has different modes
in it for Kirby Super Star Ultra
there's Revenge of the King which is a more
difficult version of Spring Breeze
where you fight a stronger King Dedede
which is Mask's Dedede
and in this one Kabula appears
and you
have to face using Starship Kirby
and you also have a Boss Rush
and they're all powered up
on top of that. Then you have Meta
Nightmare Ultra which you
control Meta Knight and he plays
through the levels on Spring Breeze, Dynablade
the Great Cave Offensive, Revenge
of Meta Knight, and Milky Way Wishes
and at the end of Milky Way Wishes instead of fighting
Marks he fights Galacta Knight
Helper to Hero
is also like an arena mode
but you play as a helper
and fight a new character
Wham Bam Jewel
True Arena is an enhanced arena
you've got all your extra bosses
in that one and then you have the sub games
Snack Tracks, Kirby Swipe
and Kirby on the Draw
which can be played up to 4 players
a local play. Anyway
it was pretty
pretty rad. People liked it and it
sold over 1 million copies in Japan
and it received fairly
favorable ratings and
a lot of people considered it one of the best games
in the franchise.
It got really great reviews
in EGM back then Electric Gaming Monthly
GamePro really
GamePro gave it a 5 out of 5
in sound and control and Fun Factor
got a 4.5 out of 5
and it was really considered just a
very charming and fun little game
Famitsu gave it 32 out of
and in 2008
Superstar Ultra became a Famitsu
Gold title
and that particular one
sold 1 million
21,000 copies in
Japan and was the 9th best selling
game of Japan in 2008
as of December 2008 it was the 5th best
selling Nintendo DS game in the US
and as far
as its legacy
some of the tracks
ended up in Super Smash Brothers
especially in the N64 and that was
the music from the Gourmet Race and Kirby's
theme song. It was on
Wii Virtual Console
and Wii U Virtual Console
like I said earlier
and it was included in Kirby's Dream Collection
that was released on the Wii
in celebration of the 20th anniversary
Metal Knights Battleship
the Halberd reappeared in
Kirby's Squeak Squad
Super Smash Brothers Brawl, Kirby's Epic Yarn
Super Smash Brothers for Wii U
and Kirby Planet Robobot
try that fist a little
it's not a tongue twister it's a
and then a stage based off
the Great Cave Offensive
shows up in Super Smash Brothers
for Wii U
that basically is just a reference back to them
of course it's included in the Super Nest classic
edition. So there you go
we got some koi b action
yes and it's a game that I
remember pretty fondly as well
I had this game, I loved the samurai game
the little wild gum and rip off was so much fun
I can't go
all
crazy
about
picking weird obscure shit no one's heard of
or that maybe five of us have heard of
I like the obscure stuff but I think
a good segment is a mixture of all of it
I am still thinking of getting the Kirby
on a star
because I said that when I lost
100 pounds I'd get ink
well now I've lost 116
I guess you still don't have ink
that's okay because I talked about getting a tattoo a long time ago
as well because I was
going to get a sound wave
here because thankfully
thanks to the long running history of this show
I have audio of my mom
because she was on the show so I wanted to get
you need to get the one of her going, Rob
well I wanted to get her
on my arm
and it's that whole little nerdy thing
where you can use the phone to play it and read it
and I realize that type of stuff won't be around forever
even though tattoos are but I still think like sound waves
the fact that it would be my mom and just the fact that
this shit here has been
a part of my life for so long there should be a
representation of that, you know, so
that's what I'm looking into doing
we'll have to go get matching
tattoos, no we wouldn't get matching tattoos
but sibling tattoos
anyway, does Agdeft have a Kirby tattoo?
I'd be curious about that
yeah I really want to know Agdeft, do you have a Kirby tattoo?
and where is it?
we're going to take a studio break real quick
but we're just going to throw it to a segment
I made earlier today, we're talking about classic
games, I've talked a lot on the show
before about the classic
Nintendo online library on the Switch
but I've talked about the
oh well maybe that's
something for the future
but I've talked about the Famicom
library and how there are some subtle differences
in some of the games and I thought it would be kind of
fun for this segment tonight to
show some of those subtle differences
here, so we will be right back
here on Orange Lounge
Radio, let's throw it to myself
earlier today
Hey everybody, it's Rob in the
office studio and I thought for our
OLR break tonight we could take a look at something
that I've talked a few times about on the show
but I haven't really shown here on the show
and I thought it would be a good thing for the midpoint
break, I've done a couple of livestreams
on my own personal channel that have
addressed this a little bit but what I wanted to show
tonight was the Nintendo Switch
online family computer classic console
or Famicom classic console
as opposed to the online library
for the NES that I think many of you
are used to, if you own
a Nintendo Switch you've probably fired up
this application and it shows you
all the classic games that you can play
and you can fire up whatever it is that you
want and you can play it, so
here's what it looks like right now
I think we're going to talk in tonight's show about some of the other
games that are coming soon, you can kind of see generally
what it looks like for those of you that don't own a Switch out there
you can pick whatever game it is
that you want to play and you just pretty much
go right into that game and you can hit the ground running
and play the game
but I want to take a look at the
Japanese version of this, the Famicom
which you can see right off the bat
had the very different controllers
it was a different system in Japan
and because it was a different system
there was also some different
types of peripherals, like they had a
disk based system if you weren't already aware
you could actually load
games based on a disk
kind of like computers back in the 80's
a lot of disk based stuff
well it's very easy since the Nintendo Switch is region free
it's very very easy to create a
Japanese account, you can go online
you create an account and just set it's
home as Japan somewhere
and then you can sign in on your
Switch with that account and you can go on to the
eShop and download this for free
and as long as you still have an online subscription
for your US account
or wherever it is you happen to be
it will work, the Japanese
stuff will work too because again
the Nintendo Switch is region free, it's just most people
don't think to make a Japanese
account to go on to the Japanese eShop
and download this, if you do do that
I notice sometimes I get
Japanese news updates and things
because I have both accounts on my Switch but
I don't mind at all actually
it's sometimes nice to see things on the other side of the pond
so let's fire up the Famicom version
of this and you don't have
to use, so you'll notice
if you have a Japanese account here, you don't have to use
the Japanese account, you can just use your regular account
in fact that would be the one you would want to use
because that's the one that actually
is paying for the Switch online service
which maybe you got free through the whole Amazon
deal lately, I don't know, but you only
need that Japanese account
to actually download the client from the
store, you'll see here, oh the
Japanese version looks very different because
again the boxes in Japan
very different and so it looks a little more jigsaw
puzzle here because of the fact
that all the
disks were different sizes and of course
there's a lot of special versions, different
software as well and all that fun stuff
and so you can kind of jump in and see some of the
big differences, for example let's fire up
Super Mario USA
right, which we all know is Super Mario Bros. 2
so it has kind of a different title
screen to it, otherwise
once you get into the game really it's pretty much the
same thing, it's just Super Mario Bros. 2
they just had that different screen that
went with it, so that one's a little bit like
whatever, there's not a lot of differences there
of course, one of the big big differences
is that Japan has been getting some games
that we haven't been getting in the US
for example, I don't believe this Yara
Kung Fu came out in the US
at all, this is based on a classic
arcade game, a really classic fighting
arcade game and yeah you can play
this which I don't think is available
in the US store at all
so, you know by downloading the Japanese
client, which again you have access to
and if you're paying for the US online you can just
create a Japanese account and go get it, you can check
out this game if you want, that's not
the only one
however there, you could also get Fire Emblem
which I know is a series a lot of people
are paying attention to now
but the original original was on
the NES and so that's what this game
is, unfortunately this one's a little
harder to play because as you see you're
gonna have to know some Japanese
in order to kind of make your way around the game
but I'm sure there's lots of FAQs
online that'll help you get through the game
because obviously, you know, people have
wanted to play this before so there's
fan translations and all that good stuff
obviously you can't translate the ROM itself
but there's some good text guides and things
that can walk you through the game and when in doubt
I'm sure a lot of YouTubes or other Twitch streamers
that are playing the game as well could also
help out with things like that, so this bottom option
will always take you back out to the main menu
also some other interesting differences, Blaster
Master, completely different game
in Japan, so it has like a completely
different screen here, Metafight right?
When you start the game, so you remember the story
in the US is like, oh you're gonna go rescue
your frog so you have this, you know
Sophia, the big
car that you're driving through the cave
right? You've seen that sequence at the beginning of Blaster Master?
Yeah, all in Japan? No.
Different story. It's not a cave.
It's like this laboratory thing.
Completely different story going on in that game
there, so that's kind of another like
little interesting difference. But one of the things
that I think gets really interesting is when you get
into some of these games that were on the
Disk System, the Famicom Disk System
because some of the sound
is slightly different because the
Famicom Disk System again had that extra
sound chip, so the versions
that are actually emulated here on
the Famicom library are
the Disk System versions. So for example
let's go to a game that I know everybody
knows, so where is it down here? Here we go.
The Hyrule Fantasy, right? The Legend of Zelda
and you can see that little logo with the little
yellow guy there for the Disk System, okay?
So that shows you that The Legend of Zelda was
a disk game and the way they translated that
when this game came out in the US was they
used the battery pack, but let's take a look at some of the
differences. So
it's very subtle
but if you can kind of hear the theme music
in the background, I'll shut up for a minute.
Little chimes.
There's some extra stuff in it, right?
Because there was a different sound
processing system on the
Famicom with the Disk System
versus the NES. So it sounded like a different
font as well that they used in that version.
So I can just go in real quick here as well.
I think I already set up a file. Now you have
to actually wait. The downside to using
the Disk System is it emulates the
loading times as well.
So you have to sit through the loading times
to actually get into the game.
But once you do,
it's pretty much the same game you remember from before.
But let me go pick up the sword,
okay?
And it is in Japanese
so he doesn't say
what he usually says.
It's dangerous to go alone, right?
But now, listen carefully when I fire the sword
because I have the full health.
Kind of a very
different sort of noise it makes there when you fire
that off, right? So some subtle
differences. Again, at the end
of the day, it's pretty much the same game
but there are some differences.
Now, some of these differences on the other
Disk System games get more so. Like if I
were to go over to Metroid,
okay, so here's Metroid.
And again, if you listen
very carefully, you can hear an extra kind of
bass track in the background
music here. But if I actually get into the game,
okay, look at this. You don't remember
this from the NES version of Metroid
because this was
on the Disk System so it had a file menu very
similar to what you had
with The Legend of Zelda because
Metroid came out first in the US
and that was their password
pack. That's why there were the silver
boxes. This and Kid Icarus
were the password pack series. So they
used passwords at first to sort
of emulate a little bit what they
were doing with the
sorry, I hit the mic. With the Disk
Systems before. So if I actually start the game
here and it actually, you know, it'll load here a little bit
and then
you'll hear it. Loading, loading, loading.
Now loading.
Lots of loading for these games.
That's, again, the downside to the Japanese
ones is that you have to actually emulate
that disk loading. Here we go.
I think it'll start here after this.
You kind of notice like, kind of like
an extra horn noise in there a little bit.
Probably. Oh, and I actually
I picked a pile that I actually already played so I can't
even go pick up the item now because I've already played this
character a little bit. Whoops. That's alright.
You can still hear like, some
of those subtle differences a little bit.
And when I get hit, like that little owl noise
is slightly, slightly different.
Newer releases.
I mentioned Kid Icarus as well
and I think we'll go there.
So again,
a screen with multiple files
just like you'd have in the other
disk games so
it wants a name but I don't really have
one so we'll just give it a fake name there.
And
start the game.
all those loading screens.
There we go.
And I think
for the most part the audio
is very similar in this game.
But I think when you get
hit
I want to say I noticed
a big difference when he, like
if you die or whatever. Maybe to do that
I might have to just do a falling death here.
Oh, maybe it was the Grim Reaper guy.
Let me see if I can just run up to him real fast
this first level.
Let's be real, it's not hard to die in Kid Icarus.
This game is very hard.
Some of those games you have to really kind of remember
your way through.
Okay, let's see.
So there's the harp that turns everybody
into hammers.
Kind of makes a little bit of a different noise instead of just
like a tick tock.
Ooh, I really went the wrong way on that.
I'm really not supposed to go to the right, that's okay.
Alright, there's one of the death guys.
Oh no!
Did you hear that little extra
backing track there? Wow, I wasn't
trying to die there, but you know, fail.
I did it anyway. Alright.
Anyway, I think that's enough
of a tour. A little quick break tonight.
But you know, I just thought for those of you that have
played Nintendo Switch and maybe haven't played around with it,
it's kind of just fun to look at some of the differences
between the Japanese releases and the American
releases. And again, you know, even though
you might be like, well, whatever with the extra sound,
you do have some of those extra games.
And now it's going the other way
too with this last month that we had
we had the Star
Tropics release in the U.S. that they didn't get
in Japan. So you know what? If you happen
to be one of those few Japanese listeners
that's participating with Orange Lounge Radio tonight,
maybe there's something to go in the other way
as well if you want to check out Star Tropics for the first time.
So there's that. Anyway,
just a little bit of a tour there of the differences
and I'll be curious if any of you guys
check it out this week. Be sure to send me a tweet
at MrRobRoberts if you decide
oh, this segment kind of
inspired you to go into the Famicom
library and check some of the things out there.
But for now, we will head back to the studio.
Enjoying that. YYR is like noticing
a lot of the differences that I'm pointing out there
and talking about maybe making a
switch online just
to check that out. And Brakeman
made some funny comments in our chat at
Twitch.tv slash OLR going, the music
I grew up with and loved was
watered down. My whole reality has been
shattered. Gee, thanks, OLR.
It's all perspective. I mean,
sure, maybe it was missing some of
the tracks there because it had
like one less chip or something.
But perspective a little bit,
those loading times in Metroid
were pretty bad and that didn't exist
when it was in a cartridge form.
There are some pros and cons and
like I said, I'd be curious if somebody like
AkumaJP or maybe one of our other listeners in
Japan would be curious about
exploring it the other way to see
what we always complain about and maybe
hear what the watered down audio sounds like or
check out StarTropics or some of those things
I was addressing there in the video.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Other comments in chat here. MetalMayham
says, admittedly, I never had Kid Icarus on the nest.
It's a hard game, but it's definitely
worth playing. It's a fun game.
So, Brakeman said that was a really fun segment.
OrangeRite says, Joy Mech Fight
is worth the time to make the Japanese
account alone. Yeah, why not? I mean,
part of the reason I want to highlight that is
I know I always talk about it, but like, those of you that
are already subscribing to Switch Online, which is
a ton of people at this point with the Twitch Prime
add-on now, you know, you
can go peek at some of those differences. Again,
it kind of takes a special type of gaming
nerd to appreciate a lot of those differences. I think
for the most part, they're all going to be very subtle and you'll just
be like, oh, there's really the same game.
But there's at least those couple extra games, like Joy Mech
Fight and so on. So, anyway,
all that being said, I think we
will get back into some
news and our show and the rest of what we got
to talk about tonight. So, let's do some rapid
fire news. Loki, I believe, starting
us off. There's some ridiculous stuff that you'll
find out there on the internet, including
screenshots, or I should say a
photographs of Gabe Newell
in China,
pimping out
some underwear. Well, apparently
some Chinese company that sells underwear
has used his likeness
on the cover of these
packages, and it's funny because
You know, when I think of underwear model,
I don't always think of Gabe Newell,
but I appreciate that we're being
body positive and featuring all sorts of
different, except the picture is him fully
clothed, to be clear.
The picture is Gabe Newell
fully clothed. He's wearing a bra on his head,
like Travis, being Queen
Amidala.
No, no, none of that. Are they selling
boxers or briefs? That's the important question.
Apparently, they appear to be
boxer briefs. Broccoli?
No, boxer briefs.
Although, the way
they actually have it listed, it's
large brief.
It's 5XL.
Oh, okay.
That's just probably the box the person picked up.
So, alright.
Interesting. Congrats, Gabe Newell,
CEO, underwear model.
But are they three-packs
is what I have to see. It's only a two-pack.
Oh, okay. Can't get to the
three-pack. No.
Apparently, so, yeah.
At least they respect that part of the
Newell. I'm so glad we talk
about such important elements of GameCo.
I'm so glad for all the stories we bumped tonight so we
could cover that one. Hey, you know what?
Can you not get enough of Hideo
Kojima? Well, guess what?
Soon, you'll be able to get him in other
mediums as well, including
a brand new show that's gonna be
on Prime Video. So,
Hideo Kojima has apparently
a cameo in
this new crime series. It's coming out
Too Old to Die Young.
And he's actually featured in the
trailer very
extremely briefly.
But you can check it out.
And it looks
interesting. I don't know what the series is about
but it's
the music
they have the retro
was it like the
retro waves music in the actual
series? Plus it just kind of
I don't know, very dark and stylistic
so it looks neat. And that
seems like something that he would get himself
involved in. So
check it out since I have Prime
Video and I don't use it for anything.
Alright. Get on it.
Alright. Moving on
April Fools was this past week
which, you know, I'm kind of over
all the dumb things people do on that day.
But once in a while, like video games
will put out like a little extra thing for
April Fools Day that ends up being like a permanent thing.
For example, I talked earlier in the show, Beat Saber
had that crab song and that's like there
now. Yeah, a full time thing. Well,
also, here's another one. So if you're a Rage 2
player, then they
unleashed a new announcer pack
featuring Tim Kitsrow
who is the announcer from NBA
Jam and NFL Blitz.
So if you want the guy from downtown
if you want that in
Rage 2, yes, that is
really something that is available.
If you pre-order Rage 2, you
get the He's On Fire cheat code
DLC pack.
And that will have the commentary for
the actions that you perform in the game.
It looked hilarious. Yeah, it looked hilarious
in the trailer. And that's a real thing.
So I like it when the April Fools jokes are
like legit, like actual things
that are just, they're just stupid and you turn them on
in office as you need to.
Now y'all know I love me some Civilization 6
right? In the Civilization series.
I think this is really cool is that
now if you link your 2K
account, you can actually
play Civilization 6 with cross
save support. So you can
start a game on the PC,
save it, and pick it up on the Switch.
Cool. Pretty cool. Yeah.
Cross save as opposed
to just like a cross play type of thing.
So that's pretty neat. So anyway, that was a recent update
that just came out. No April Fools joke there.
Where you can save a game
on the PC and you can pick it up on the
Switch. Again, you have to have a 2K
account to basically
facilitate the cross save. So
yeah, yet another game company account
you get to make. Woohoo. But that's kind of
a neat thing there. So do remember that
the original, or excuse me, the Switch
version of Civ 6 is the original
with no expansions.
So keep that in mind for your Civ 6
game. That's an important thing is that if you have
a Civ 6 game with all the expansions
oops, you can't actually transfer that file.
So do keep that in mind
with this. But I think that's pretty cool.
It's kind of one of those things that like now they announced
and I'm like, oh, that really should have been there
the whole time. How about that?
Anyway, DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
Well coming out is going to be
Konami's Arcade Archives
series.
And the game that's going to be added to that is
Time Pilot. That's going to be coming
out on April 11th, 2019.
Basically you go through time rescuing other
pilots. Apparently in 2001 we were supposed to have UFOs.
I love Time Pilot.
But it is actually saying it's going
to be the first of their classic
arcade titles to join that. So that's pretty cool.
It'll be on PS4
and Switch in Japan on April 11th.
It will be 823 yen.
A game that was
prominently featured on
Nick Arcade.
I was going to say StarCade.
StarCade had this game all the time.
Anyway, also the game
Power Rangers Battle for the Grid
is going to have some free DLC characters
and more content.
Enway has revealed
three characters coming out.
That's going to be Dragon Armor Trini
rest in peace.
Udonna and
Cenozoic Blue Ranger
are going to be out with no other
cost and that they are
hard at work on packing more content
into the game.
They are giving the
fans what they want. All six of them.
There's more fans than that.
Alright.
Well go go Power Rangers.
I heard what you did there.
I know. It was intentional. Let's travel around
the world and check out some games that are coming out
real soon starting in the US.
We have a few things this week.
Phoenix Wright Ace Attorney Trilogy
on PC, the Nintendo Switch,
PlayStation 4, and Xbox One.
We have Shovel Knight
Showdown on PC,
Mac, and Linux.
Wii U, Nintendo Switch,
PlayStation 4, and Xbox One.
Zanki Zero
Last Beginning on PC
and PlayStation 4.
Earth Defense Force Iron Rain on
PlayStation 4.
Nintendo Labo Toy-Con 4
VR Kit is coming out this week
on the Switch. And last but not least
Konami Arcade Classics
PC, Switch, PlayStation 4,
and Xbox One.
Which if I'm not mistaken has Time Pilot
in it as well. So it's a little weird
that Arcade Archives is doing one for 8 bucks
when it's part of a collection that's going to be
20 bucks. So this is a little weird
but okay.
You gotta choose how you want to consume your
Time Pilot I suppose.
So I'm traveling over to Japan. It's a little bit lighter in Japan
this week. I don't know if that's because gold weeks
at the end of the month or some of those budget things
that Loki talked about in the last episode. Who knows
maybe all of that coming into play. But the only release
really on the PlayStation 4 this week is
V-Rally 4 that is out on April
11th. Over on the Nintendo
Switch, oh a little bit a bigger deal
on the Switch. Not only is V-Rally 4 also
out on the Switch, but the Final Fantasy
X and X-2 HD Remaster
hits the Switch on April 11th.
So that's kind of a big deal. So that is happening
this week as well. But that's
really it as far as like big notable releases go.
Dark Sakura, what about the UK? Two things
on the 8th.
Dangerous Driving and
Zanki Zero Last
Beginning. That's
it.
Alright I think Dangerous Driving was
supposed to be coming out here too but I must have missed
out on the list. But it is. Okay.
It's Burnout Paradise or it's basically
Burnout. Yes but the
team kind of doing a new game right? Yeah.
It's basically Burnout.
It's like yeah. Burnout Take Down
basically but not. That team is
in the UK so maybe it is coming out there first.
Right. Yeah so maybe they do get it first
for a change. Who knows.
Anyway. The
Final Fantasy X stuff won't be out until next week.
Yeah it's Japan's getting it
first. That sometimes happens. Of course.
Alright. Well I mean honestly.
I mean what can they do for us?
If you really
wanted to play those remasters right now
it's out on Playstation 4 and PC.
It's just the Switch versions you have to wait on.
Anyway. Alright.
Let's go to the mail bag
because every week you guys send us
emails at participate at
orangelandradio.com
and why are you laughing?
Because there's nothing in there. There's no email.
Nobody sent us any emails to participate.
Someone trying to scam us did.
Those don't count. Spam emails don't count. I deleted it
and bypassed the trash. So participate
at orangelandradio.com if you
want to send us an email in a future week but
since y'all didn't send us emails you know what that means.
Fuck off. No.
It means I get to have an excuse to
talk to Dark Soccer about Drag Race.
Season 11. So.
I need to watch the last episode but it's already been spoiled
for me in the most delightful of manners. Well you don't have to
spoil it here but who are you rooting for on
Drag Race Season 11? I'm rooting for that
little romance budding between Miss
Vanjie and Brooklyn
Heights. Even straight
people know Miss Vanjie. Even
straight people do.
That was the most meme-able thing that's ever come out of
the show. I'm actually
Evie Oddly is my top favorite.
My second favorite would be
Brooklyn Heights.
And my third favorite is actually
kind of a tie between Miss Vanjie just
because I love her. I mean I love
her terrible. Get these cookies!
Yeah. And I love her talking.
And Nina West.
Yeah I love Nina West. I like
the campy queens. Yeah I love the campy queens.
My favorite is Evie Oddly for sure.
I think she's going to go all the way to the end.
Nina West I really like too.
She's going to be here locally in a couple weeks. I kind of want to go
see that show. I think it'll be a lot of fun.
Yeah I'm like you. I love a campy queen.
But as far as like a glamour queen goes I think
Acuria Chanel Davenport
has been bringing a lot of great stuff to the runway. I do
but I really like Plastique Tiara
and I would like to have another Asian queen
somewhere in the top. Yeah.
I mean that isn't you know the
an
imitatable uh
Raja. And not this bitch on
this season. Oh yeah.
Her. Her. Her and Silky
can go fuck right off. The other one I wanted to
fuck off is gone. What did you say is in town tonight?
Somebody's downtown tonight from the show.
He said. I lost it because it was
on my Facebook. Oh
it was I remember it was Trinity. It's not even from the
season. Yeah Trinity the Tuck. Your current
one of your current fucking half
reigning. One of our local queens
is um performing with her. Oh fun!
That's good. Support your local queens.
I want to tell everyone right now I'm going to
give one more shout out and this is to
a Facebook page
that everyone must follow.
It's called Possum Core.
Okay. And it's nothing but adorable
little freaking possums.
Alright well moving away from the mail
bag saying. Possums! I
did neglect to ask you because you're talking about
plugs. Did you have a podcast you want to plug this week?
Um. I guess we can do that here too.
Game Buoy.
Heck yeah. Game Buoy.
Our pals at Game Buoy. I'm trying
to do like non-vogue ones but
no one gave me a submission this week. The girl
can't help it. And they just came back. They just came back
from a hiatus. Welcome back. Welcome
Buoyak. Yeah. Game
Buoyak. Keep us afloat.
Aye aye.
We don't want to you know
Other nautical terms. Yes.
Will you be our star to guide us in the
gaming news
realm with opinions. Possums!
Yes. We don't want to sink
by not knowing
all the gaming news that's not on our
radar. Dude I am posting this freaking adorable possum in chat.
Alright. Anyway. Let's move
on. Alright. Back to gaming news. And
Loki what do you want to talk about in gaming news tonight?
So I just mentioned during
our release dates that the VR
Joy-Con set is coming
out for Labo.
And to go along with that they
released a video this week announcing that
hey not only are you going to be able to use the stuff
that's in those sets with
this but you'll be able to use the VR
goggles that you create with it
with other games. So
on April
25th they're going to
add support to
Super Mario Odyssey and
Zelda Breath of the Wild.
So the way this is going to work in Mario
Odyssey you're going to have a few different
levels or mini challenges
they call them. Where
basically it's all in 3D but you're kind of
watching from like a
kind of a fixed camera type thing.
So you're going to do that.
So they're just videos basically?
No you actually play it. Oh you're playing it
but it's a fixed camera. Yeah so it's like a fixed
camera type thing. Gotcha. But then
in Breath of the Wild though it's actually
going to be full on like
a VR first
person view I guess. Or
VR support
throughout the entire game except for the pre-rendered
cutscenes which won't be in VR.
But apparently you'll
be able to turn that option
or turn that on in the options menu
to get full VR support
for the game. I can't imagine playing through
that entire game in VR though especially because there's no
there's no way to strap it to your head. You have to hold
it. There is not a way to
strap it to your head. You have to basically hold
it up because it's
basically just the
the actual switch
just inside some cardboard and you have to hold it up
because it's weighted. So you
can't really strap it to your head because it'd be pretty damn
uncomfortable.
It's not exactly well thought
out for like playing a long game
like that but I can see the Mario
thing is a neat idea. It's a cute novelty.
It is a cute novelty
but yeah it'd be nice if they had straps to actually
strap it to your head but
I can't see how that would be comfortable
in any way being that it is just a piece of cardboard.
You have to like not only hold it up but like
the joy cons are there too because and Bobby's
pointing out it tracks your head movement that way
you have to control it up here.
Yeah you're holding it like this.
It doesn't sound comfortable at all.
It's going to be very uncomfortable.
That's the type of thing where it's like I will give that three minutes
max and then I'll be over it.
I'll play the Mario Odyssey levels
Yeah the Mario Odyssey one looks good.
It'll be very short but
It's like I'll turn it on just to see
Hyrule in VR. Ooh that's neat.
Okay done.
That's about all I would be able to tolerate of that as well.
For sure.
Well I want the full report
next week on the VR thing.
Yeah well I'm putting together the robot
one now so I mean that'll be fun.
But yeah the VR one is
coming on Friday when it releases
because I ordered it through Amazon.
I want to know all the details on that so
alright. Well moving on let's talk about
you know for VR beginning
something else is ending
sort of. Starlink is
going away a little bit. Well obviously
they can't like shut down the game. If you've already
bought the game you obviously can still
play it however
Ubisoft has mentioned no more physical toys
will be made for the game so
the toys to life things. They were clearing that shit out at
Target a few weeks ago.
Yeah and honestly like
Nintendo kind of treated this like it was
a Star Fox game so I kind of forgot
it was a toys to life
game I just kind of thought it was a
oh somebody like made
put Star Fox in a not Star Fox
game and now it's sort of Star Fox. I can't believe it's not
Star Fox. It's just yeah I don't know
it's a neat idea but
eh. Now to be clear
the game is still being supported because
pilots, spaceships, weapons there's going to be a
spring update that's going to add more of that but it's
all digital which maybe
some people are going to enjoy is that it seems like all
these things they had planned for future toys
eh. Well that's you know
funny enough that you mentioned that because that's actually how
they treated the PC version of
Disney
Infinity was it was all digital
you had cards you could put codes in you get
like with the actual well originally I think it was the
mobile they had a mobile game too I think
so you put in codes that came with the actual
characters to unlock
the digital ones but of course you know
now there's ways to you know cheat
that but it was all
now I think if you buy the games it just comes
with all of the characters that they had released
with that so
I don't know that's the only bad thing about those toys
to life stuff is like
eh. It's
it has to be really something
you want to collect because those things are
pretty big like the Arwing thing I could see
that would be pretty cool for someone to put on a shelf
but like all the other things
I don't know that's a bit
much. Alright
now the company did make a statement
the developers of the game made a statement
you don't usually hear them be very frank about what's
going on but the statement says despite
the immense and continuous support from our players
the sales for Starlink Battle for Atlas
fell below expectations
consequently we recently made the decision
to not release any additional physical toys
for the spring update and in the future
not often you hear a company being very upfront
where it's like well didn't sell enough of them
so the end
so it's kind of a sad reality
I guess so that's what happens when you guys
try to jump into the toy toys
life stuff too late in the game I mean
come on it'll be so up to you
maybe it'll work a little better for him digitally
we'll see but I
still need to play the game myself just because I
was curious about the whole Star Fox
you know obviously I would play on the Switch so I could see all that
go check out the clearance stuff
because those games I think were
the toys themselves were like five bucks
so like a big thing and I was like
maybe I should get some of these and I'm like I'm never going to play this
why am I going to buy this stuff
alright moving on Dark Sakura what do you have for us
I got some stuff
so Jackbox Party Pack
is coming in Q4 2019
but at any rate
they did
something kind of different
they do
we know that it's going to be called
trivia murder party minigame
from 2016
it's going to be returning
and that it's going to give us five games
per collection and maybe four more
and one with a new concept
so
at any rate it also did like a
really weird kind of
trailer with people wearing sheets
in a forest labeled ghosts
like what is this
it's going to
at any rate be
PC, PS4, Xbox One
Switch and Apple TV and iPad
so
hopefully it'll be
pretty good
we'll see
I don't know do you think you're going to
begin to this one?
I haven't gotten any of the other Jackbox games
although didn't they give one away
I think Epic Store had one
for free didn't they?
I don't remember
I'm trying to look at this weird
I don't have enough friends to play those with
so that's the problem
oh you have at least three
not that they want to play with me anytime
oh no
I do have the Jackbox Party Pack
I grabbed that
it was one of the free Epic games
that they had on there
I did get that
by the way The Witness is free right now
so check that out
well at any rate
I don't know if the weird
trailer is enough
it's kind of like people are banking in
on this kind of
oddity related
I don't know Trivia Murder Party was awesome
so I'm down for a sequel
but I wonder what type of new theme they're going to be able to do
what was the t-shirt one that they had
I don't remember
I don't really play a whole bunch of it myself
I just remember the last time I played it
was over at a Halloween party
well
well at any rate
sometime later in the year
we're going to have it
so we will see it when we see it
sounds awesome
anything else?
so we're having a microphone issue
and I can't tell which mic it is
it's all of the mics
they're all bad
I'm terrible
Radio Shack Ghosts
well we didn't get these from Radio Shack did we?
well it's still Radio Shack Ghosts
you know Dan worked for Radio Shack
and did he confirm that it's full of ghosts?
no
I think the ghosts were like possessing
but they used to play like the
chill station from
on Sirius
so every time I go in
Loki's unplugged for a minute I want to see if the chat says it's Loki's mic
I'm trying to diagnose which mic is having the issues
I don't need a mic
I talk loud enough to be picked up by all of them
and it's please
says I think it's Loki's mic
interesting so they say they keep hearing static
on their end
it's live radio
these things happen
it is not the Mac Mini
so I'm curious
if they're saying it's gone away
has it gone away at this point?
because I just unplugged Loki so if it's Loki's mic
the noise should have gone away
it's gone away so it's Loki's mic
don't make me sing
I'm going to sub his mic out for another chord real quick
well Loki's got a story to do
well nobody has a hot mic but you
I do
so this is the Dark Sakura Hour
and I'm going to go ahead and do my story for reasons
well I don't have another story
so I'm going to think of a story
and yesterday
you know that Burrito Week
National Burrito Day was last week
and Dan and I went out and got burritos
at Freebirds
and I ended up being
it was super good but they had
that alternate
meat thing, Rob, I'm just going to read your story
because fuck it
okay
Rob's story is this
there is a working Mario maker
inside LittleBigPlanet 3
apparently
players in LittleBigPlanet 3
have
basically made their own version
it's so weird
because it looks actually completely right
so they can do
blocks, pipes, coins and elements
of Super Mario Brothers
it's not
and someone actually tried to recreate
the level
so they did the demo
of Super Mario Maker running in
LittleBigPlanet and it actually looks
pretty legit, I mean
some of the stuff is a little different
this is actually kind of
kind of cool
well it's amazing what they can do with LittleBigPlanet 3
and so I can only imagine what we're going to be able to do
when we actually get
he's actually talking quietly
so I'm impressed
different
different cable
same story
talking
talking in the yellow
so yeah it would be interesting to see
what actually is going to happen when Dreams comes out
because you can do a ton more stuff in Dreams
than you can in LittleBigPlanet 3
so I'm very curious to see what they
can do with that full on Mario Maker
in that one
but it looked neat, it's pretty impressive
I haven't played LittleBigPlanet 3
even though we got it free
even though you cosplayed Sackboy
that was a long time ago
in a galaxy far far away
namely Rob's Old House
ok so live fixing
on the air, apparently I
tech supported the issue, the chat is happy
don't know you'll piss off
the electronics union Rob
like Bobby says
alright anyway
let's try to move back and talk about
the Loki story that we missed tonight
so there's one more we were going to do there
so unfortunately
speedrun.com has
had to revert their rankings
back to their April 1st date
because apparently
they had a security breach
which left many of the
leaderboards at risk of tampering
and so because of that
they had to roll back their data
and so unfortunately some of
these records that people may have set
have been
removed, so they said
about 3 to 5
counts moderating
prominent boards
were compromised and this
cause is still
understood to be only a few
users using
or reusing passwords that were compromised from
other sites years ago
and so because of that
they had to unfortunately roll back their
database
so that sucks
that's why you need these unique
strong and unique
strong passwords, symbols
and record your shit
yes
alright
the video cassette recorder
like they had to do in the days
of Donkey Kong
alright well this is, sorry
it's been a little awkward trying to get to the end here
with all the sound issues but we're finally all worked out
I think this is going to come a point
when I have money
that I'm just going to
all new mics, all new cords
why not, we got a new mixing board
these mics were
graciously donated by Brad
from Pod Culture but that was a few years
ago at this point so I think our system
might have just kind of lived its life
so we might have to end up getting some new stuff
we'll see very soon
anyway
let's get to our listener
round table, so we're actually going to
open up our Discord server
if you want to join the green room over on
Discord at the VOG Network Discord
which is vognetwork.com slash Discord
we're going to be taking some calls here
or if you have a question on chat
or something you want to ask you can ask
away in chat, while I get that all set up
is there anything that you
want to add here for Last Minute Stories
Loki?
I don't
have anything
other than I have to say
one thing I didn't mention as part of my gaming week
the whole Labo thing
one of the things I like the best about
the Labo software right now
is the music in those
building menus, it's fantastic
it's some really
really
energetic
kind of jazzy tunes that they've got going on
there, so I really like the menu
that's like Wii U or Wii
Shop music type stuff
really, really good stuff
I dig that and also just like
some of the joking around
because a lot of the stuff you have to do the same shit over and over
now look, isn't that
relaxing to fold these creases
and stuff like that
it's kind of
I got a humor to it, like I really wanted my kids
I really wanted my kids to
put this shit together, but they didn't want to
do any of it, so I'm like
do it, do it, do it, is it done yet?
I'm like, I just opened the box
it's not done yet, you see the stack of
cardboard here, Jesus Christ
alright, I know
we got one person waiting in the green room
so let's get to it, hello, you are on
Orange Lawn Radio, who's this?
Yeah, this is Metal Mayhem
Hey Metal Mayhem, what's on your mind buddy?
No, hold on
just a very broad topic
for you guys tonight
seeing as that we're
all pretty much with the
same age range
within a couple of years and we've been gaming
for quite a long time
I have a
general question for
the three of you
is there
even though
gaming magazines haven't been around
for roughly about ten years
give or take, because
that kind of killed off
gaming mags for better
or for worse
have there been any
in the past
that you
bought on a
regular basis
either at the newsstand or through subscription
so gaming magazines
what like gaming magazines were you guys
all into, like and what did you actually
subscribe to or consume
DarkSakura, did you have any magazines
that you got on a regular basis?
Not really, I would just go steal them from the grocery store
You stole magazines?
Yeah, like GamePro and EGM
Oh my gosh, we have a criminal
in our midst
I admit to it, they can't prove it, just me saying so
doesn't mean I actually did it
You just said it to look cool, even though stealing
is wrong, don't do it
Don't steal from the magazine rack in your grocery
store
Honestly, I had a subscription
in Nintendo Power for a long
time, I think I finally let it go when I went off to
college, but I had the very first issue in Nintendo Power
I wish I hadn't thrown it away, I didn't realize
how valuable that thing would be
But I subscribed to Nintendo Power for a long
time, and that was certainly a go-to magazine
I like EGM, I picked that up a lot
Honestly, it was the type of thing
the grocery store used to have
a magazine section, which is where a lot
of gaming cards are now, and so like
every time we went to the grocery store, I would kind of be able
to be like, can I get GamePro?
So I would kind of like
catch up on a video game magazine
that way, and so I kind of rotated through
all of them. I remember once
GamePro had this thing where
like, you could be an
editor or something, it was like they were gonna
have a team of 75 winners
that were like editors, and I ended up getting
picked, like they sent me a thing that was like
I got picked, I won the thing because I
had to send a little thing in writing or whatever, and then
nothing ever came of it
I never got anything else but the whole
congratulations, you got picked to do nothing
Alright, I guess I get to sit there and look fabulous
So there was that
Because we have
no editors here
They do nothing
Yeah, I guess they went under after that
To do a throwback, even though it's not necessarily
100% video gaming
I also remember, I was a big Commodore 64
enthusiast back in the day
because that was the computer that was in my family
so I loved those Compute Gazette
magazines that you could type the programs
in the back and like make your own stuff
I loved that stuff, and so there was
a lot of classic computing magazines I really
got into as well, VG&CE
Video Games Computer Entertainment was another one
Loadstar
was that only a disc thing, or was that
actually, I think it was actually a magazine for a short time
Logie, what about you? What about you and magazines?
I did subscribe
to Nintendo Power
and GamePro
and then I used to pick
up a lot at the stores, especially when I had
like, I had
my own PC at that time
so like my first PC
I would pick up PC Gamer
because they had the discs with like
full games in them sometimes
and so I would pick those up just for the games
and I used
to like also some of the import magazines
for different
things, because usually they had like
I don't know
Oh, the official PlayStation magazine
OPM, I did subscribe
to that as well, also for the demo discs
because that was awesome
Actually, there was a magazine that Dan and I
were subscribing to for a while
We were subscribing to Retro Gamer
Oh, and the
Xbox game magazine, also for the demo discs
Notice
the trend here, demo discs
that will get me to subscribe to your magazine
Demo discs
are a good thing. Metal Mayhem, what about you
real quick?
Well, I
personally didn't subscribe to it
particularly my father did, but
my father
multi-year subscription to
Nintendo Power
and this is before
future publishing
or whatever the name of the company is to go over
and
to a certain extent that
magazine was alright, but eventually it kind of
dawned on me that, hey
Nintendo's running this magazine
naturally, they're in the business of
selling games, they're not going to say, hey
our games are crap, don't buy them
it's Nintendo Power
So, like, eventually
It's that moment when you're younger
that you realize everything you loved
was advertising
Yeah, so
eventually I started going to
the magazine
I also started getting all the magazines
I initially started getting
game foam, which I loved
and then like
Loki, I started getting
an official
PlayStation Magazine once I got
a PlayStation 1
I got that for the demo
mostly, but I ended up liking the magazine
itself
and eventually when I got a 360
I got an
OXM as well for the demo disc
and I ended up liking the magazine
as well
Yeah, I used to love those official PlayStation Magazine demo discs
I think if you still have, I think some of those demo discs
are kind of collectibles at this point
Well, there was some that was pretty awesome
like the official Xbox magazine, they actually had
DLC for free on there, I remember
for Oblivion they had
a few Oblivion DLC packs
that were free in there, I was like, sweet
Yeah, it was awesome
Anyway, Middle Mayhem is a great question
I'm going to let you go so we can get some more calls
but great question, and happy reading
Alright, have a nice day
You too, take care
What's kind of cool is they had a demo in one of them
for Timeshift, the Atari
version of Timeshift because
they had changed publishers
at one time for that game, so they had
a demo that was of a game that never
came out, and they released later on
another demo for the actual version that came out
that was from another publisher altogether
Alright, well let me
go to another call here
Hi, you're on Orange Town Radio, who's this?
Hey, what's going on everybody?
Hey, Rama, how you doing?
Not too much, I'm a little stuffed from dinner
and getting ready for a brand new work week
You know, and I learned tonight, I thought
only Bobby and I had privileges to
drag and drop people into other channels, but apparently
you do too
And you see, the funny thing is, I didn't
even realize, because I
barely used Discord on my phone
and I'm like, okay, this is it, I didn't
realize, so like, wait, why is this locked
I was like, oh, oh
oh, and I was like, my bad,
Rob, my bad
So for those that don't know, because you can't see it
behind the scenes, you can't see the Discord activity
but during that last call with Metal Mayhem
like, Rama kept dropping into the channel
and I was like, okay, Rama, I get it
you want to be on the show, but like, you need to, like
I don't want background noise coming through, I'm like, you need to go wait
like everybody else, you know, and I keep
dragging and dropping him back in the channel
and then suddenly he disappeared
so I don't know if Rama, you dropped off, or Bobby
saw what was going on and was like, I'll show him
or what
No, I realized
after the fact that I looked in the room
I was like, restricted channel, wait, that's not
the green room, oh damn, whoops
Oh, oh, Bobby
said he revoked your access
what, what, what, it's like you
you were in the room and then the sirens started going off
woo woo woo
intruder alert, intruder alert
Well, I look at it
this way, if something happens
I have my papers, I'm good
I know, I know, alright
all that joking aside, uh, what's
on your mind tonight, buddy?
Alright, I wanna talk about something in regards to
a comment you made last week
that I agree with you about
Okay, good, you agree with me
sure, what is that?
The 3D Zeldas
Oh, oh, when I
gave my hot take, the Ocarina of Time
and stuff, like, you guys, you guys
hyped those games up a lot
I will say
this, I got a Nintendo 64
just for Ocarina
of Time, I saved up my money
I got the console, I got the
game, a few hours into this
game, I'm like, what the hell is this?
I felt like I got ripped
off, woo, okay?
I don't know if I would go
that strong with it, but I, I
personally, I think Breath of the Wild is the best
3D Zelda they've ever made
and I don't know if that's just because
you know, maybe now I'm kinda more used to 3D
games, I've just accepted it as that's where we're
at, whereas, you know, when the Nintendo 64
was brand new, I was still, you know
I was kinda like, all these, these polygons are
so bulky, they're just like shapes
floating out there, and you know, all that type of stuff
I mean
I do enjoy my fair share of 3D
games, I just
I just couldn't get into it, I'm like
I prefer my top
slash 2D Zelda games, now I
did play Breath of the Wild, and I did
like that, and
that game did one thing the other 3D
games did not do, it
actually mapped the button so Link could
jump
Oh man, yeah
I, I wish, uh
yeah, that, that's uh
Link being able to jump is important
Yeah
I mean, this is a 3D game, he should be able to
like jump over, so I'm like, there
what do you mean, he can't
you know what, forget it
forget it, I'm like, nope
I, I, you know what, I even said
you know, I'm gonna give Ocarina
Time another shot, so I went out
and got it on 3DS
I played it through
two hours in, I gave it the Mako
shot, I'm like here, you can have this, I don't
want it, I will play my 2D
Zeldas till I can't play them anymore
What, what do you think about the whole
um, the announcement
or well, either the rumor I guess
that Legend of Zelda
Link to the Past might be getting like
a 3D style
remake in the vein of the Link's
Awakening remake, uh, what do you think
about that, like a 2D game kind of going to that
sub 3D type
of thing, what do you, what do you make of all that?
Um, I don't know
if you saw my reaction, but when
Nintendo announced uh, Link's Awakening
for the Switch, my,
I pretty much said, fuck
I have to get a Switch now, fuck, I have to get a
Switch now, it's like, there were
reasons why I needed, I was gonna get a Switch
Yeah, um, I, you know, and we were talking
earlier about how like the Secret of Mana remake
you know, was kind of like a little bit hit and miss
but I, I kind of expect a certain quality
out of Nintendo, and so I think this
um, Link to the, you know, this Link's Awakening
for sure, but maybe even Link to the Past
is gonna be pretty, pretty
cool, it's gonna be up to a certain level, so I'm excited
about it
Alright, for some reason
I've lost your audio, are you still there with us, Rama?
Um,
Okay, if you can hear us, we can't
hear you, I don't know if maybe
Bobby's messing around with some permissions
live on air or what, but for some reason
we lost you, Rama, but thank you so much for the call
uh, and we'll talk to you next time, or everybody
should be listening to Anime Jam Session Tuesday night
here on the Voice Geeks Network
Uh, meanwhile, I've got one more person
waiting, so let me bring this person in, hopefully this
person can talk, hi, you're on Orange Town's
Radio, who's this?
Hey, good, oh, we can't hear you
So that wasn't me
What's up, buddy?
Hi, how are you?
Yeah, it's been a while
Uh, yeah, obviously you've noticed
I haven't been on like
for god knows how long
Probably more than a year, year and a half
Everything's good, uh, just settling
in to my new digs
I've been here for over
a year now
I mean, if you see the, yeah
I'm finally out of the city, I'm
excited about it
I'm in Westchester now, so
all things, you know, settling
in with my fiance and all
So, um, yeah, I just
uh, went to PAX last weekend
How was that?
Uh, hit or miss
Mostly, Thursday was probably the least
crowded day, I was actually able
to go to the show floor most, you know
hit up most of the booths, or a good
chunk of the booths
But it was mostly me just flying
and like, you know, just
But it was mostly me just flying and like
in Thrustmaster's booth
because they had DCS World in VR
And, you know
I love flying games, and I
won a headset because I shot
down, I shot down two
Russian aircraft on an F-18
uh, simulator
with their fancy $500 joystick
Oooh
That's like, that reminds me of the time
uh, it was years ago, it was when
Final Fantasy XI was being
shown at E3
It wasn't new though, it was already out
Maybe it was the year they were showing on 360, I don't remember
It was the first or second year I was ever at E3
But anyway, long story short, um, I won
some like, I think it was like a Ballista competition
or something like the PVTP they were doing
I won some type of Final Fantasy XI thing, my team of eight
and then they spun a wheel to see
which person got to pick their prize first
and they thought for sure people would pick
the Nobuyamatsu CDs first
that were signed, but I was like, no
they were giving away a full on brand new motherboard
you remember that?
It was a motherboard processor thing
and I got that at E3
and that ended up being
the show computer later on
uh, at some point
so it was kind of funny the way that all worked out
so anyway
Yeah, so, I mean, there was a lot of like
VR, most of the past couple of years
PAX has been mostly VR now
like, I don't know if you noticed
but a lot of uh
just lots of demo boosts
especially Facebook
you know, and their Oculus
their Oculus booths
like, literally capped almost every day
after Thursday
I have to admit, I haven't been to PAX
in a little while because uh
you may have caught some of the shade I was throwing last week
but our feathers were ruffled a few years ago
and I wasn't super impressed with the show anyway
so I just haven't spent the money to go back in a while
um, I've been tempted to go to another one
but I would be curious to see
like, what it would
look like, and plus
honestly, like, a lot of my money
like, a lot of my convention money, I do DragonCon now
and I try to get to other, like, smaller conventions
so it's just, it's been hard to swing PAX
as well on top of all that, but never say never
Yeah
I mean, you're not missing much
all it is, is just like, it's a lot more
like, esports, uh
uh, you know, it's a lot more esports related
now, like, most of the boosts either
whether it's like, you know
Twitch or Discord, they have
boots over there, apparently
Facebook with, uh, Facebook Live
and Oculus, obviously, so it's a lot
more, it's a heavy emphasis on
esports now, and just streaming
So, so it's like
So go ahead
I mean, I haven't gotten to that game yet
of whole, of streaming, I know
friends of mine who are definitely in that, uh
in Twitch, with their own channels and all
but, you know
that's what I've seen, it's like, either that
or TableTop
Yes, I believe we're doing a Twitch show right now
Um
But anyway, uh
So I, I kinda drug you into the conversation
about PAX and everything, but is there, is there something
you actually wanted to talk about tonight?
Um, let me see
Uh, I don't
Uh, other than, uh
Try to remember
Like, I've been reading here and there, like
I guess most of it is
just like, people, you know
I remember, like
out of this whole, uh
Me Too movement and the fact that actually
an incident similar to that happened last weekend
in PAX East, where
believe it or not, uh
Magic the Gathering player got, like
one of the top players basically got dropped
out of the tournament
last minute because, uh, a lot of
uh, long story short, a lot of things
came out about his misogyny
and other nasty things
about women that he's, uh, the way he's treated
them, and so
Yeah, and that, they didn't want that
I, I haven't heard a lot of what's going on
but it sounds like the company, uh
didn't want to take the risk that this individual would win
and then some of that
is gonna reflect on them
because whoever wins that tournament is gonna
basically end up being an ambassador for the brand
and if there's a lot of these things that could
drag that down, you know
uh, I can see why the company wants
to make sure that doesn't happen
Right, I mean, that's, that was
I mean, I get it, like, you know
and then recalling, like, other
I guess nowadays, it's like
you know, Twitch is
or, or, or just having exposure
in general just exposes you
you know, it
it scrutinizes all your actions that you make
like, it, if you were a dick
before streaming, then
chances are, you're walking on a tight
rope, basically
with your behavior, unless you change it
and, you know, obviously
with sponsorships and all
it's, you're putting yourself in a
precarious position where
any action that you may have done behind
the scenes before, you know
before streaming or becoming a
streamer, which I can't even believe that's
a profession now, and
and it's just like, you
you do things, it's your behavior
that ends up reflecting poorly
like, I don't know if you heard about this one
uh, you know, a couple of months back
where this streamer was playing Fortnite
and he was beating on the, on his
uh, I think it was his wife
or a significant other, while on the
stream, like literally being, like
off camera, just like beating the crap
out of, you know
just because he just, like he was
he was getting nagged by her and then he
was like, the way he's reacting
okay, so that's really gross and not something, I mean
it's, that's a gross, gross
incident, sure
yeah, it is, it's bad, it's
and it, and the thing is like
Twitch only gave him a slap on the wrist
initially, until people
called Twitch out for the fact that
he wasn't, his channel
wasn't suspended permanently after two weeks
well, he also got arrested too
yeah, that too
but the fact of the matter is that Twitch gave him
like, you know, Twitch really
gave him a slap on the wrist initially
it wasn't until like, you know
public pressure
you know what's interesting, you know what's interesting is that there was a story
this week, and it didn't make our short roll tonight, but it was
about something about how like, Mixer
is really trying to figure out
how can we like, differentiate ourselves
from Twitch, and one of the things that
Mixer is trying to put out there and kind of push
is that they want to be very much like an
anti-toxicity environment
and so they have some different rules
and was it, and you know, I, what's interesting
is that it would be interesting to see how Twitch
might ultimately respond to that, because I don't think
Twitch necessarily wants to be known as like, we love
toxicity, I don't think so, I think it's one
of those, you know, maybe, and I don't
I don't know enough about the situation, I don't want to
defend it, or either way, but maybe just Twitch
needed a minute to kind of assess like,
what do we do, because maybe we haven't been in the situation
before, we don't have a clear policy
let's hope Twitch has learned from that
and on that note, we talk about learning from
things, I think that
you know, when we talk about what people have done in their
past versus what they're doing now
I think a very important question to ask is
you know, we're considering, do we
cancel somebody over what they said 10 years
ago, and this whole thing, I think you're gonna
have to look at a situation like that and go, but it does sound like
the person like, wants to do better, are they
learning, are they apologizing, do they
realize why what they said was shitty
and now they're acting
differently, or do they
show that they don't give a fuck, and
that whole type of thing, and I think a lot of that
sometimes weighs into
how people might respond
to a particular situation
you know, obviously these issues
that you bring up are a way bigger
you know, cultural issue than probably something
we can really sink into in 3 hours
here on OLR, but you know
you are correct that we are moving
more and more into a time frame
where things are
documented, so why on
earth you'd want to
take physical action on your spouse
which why on earth you'd want to do that ever
is one question, but then to do that
in an environment where it's recorded
gross, even if it's a
joke, not funny, you know
it's like, what the hell, you know
I mean, if we're getting into the place where more and more
things are recorded, you have to kinda
make sure you're saying
good things, and being a good person
and putting positive stuff out there where you can
sociopaths don't care
well right, there's always gonna be a few bad eggs
but you know, I'm just
I don't know, I don't know, I mean
the way I see it is that we're at an age where
like, you know
probably like, like 10 years
ago you didn't have this type of scene
where people are making a living off
of just streaming and just playing Fortnite
for example, and then
it brings out the, you know
the bad elements, like you have certain
individuals who haven't
haven't been conditioned
to, you know
behave in a certain way, or they're
basically just assholes inherently
and as a result, you see their true colors
in the way they obsess over
what they're trying to do versus
you know, the other things that
kind of like, push them
to the brink and cause them to act out
differently in front of a
live studio, you know, live audience
from that, and we've, you know, hopefully moved on
and at the end of the day, trying to do
a positive thing, but anyway
Zaku is good to hear from you, and I'm glad to
hear you had a good time at PAX
ish, and I hope to
hear from you again, don't be a stranger
Yup, definitely
Take care buddy, have a good one
You too, bye
Alright, always good to hear from Zaku
here, so going to our
chat, let's see
Oh
Gosh, that's a really sick story, I don't even want to repeat
that story, it's really sick, alright, just what some
people do on
stream to maybe tug at people's heart
strings, and it's sad, because
then it like, ruins it for everybody else
It's just, blah, anyway
Alright, well trying to do good things here at Orange
Lounge Radio, we are the show where every gamer
has a voice, you know, as long as you're not
being a jerk and hurting
other people's feelings and stuff like that, you know, we
want positivity at the end of the day
Doesn't mean we can't be critical of the things
we love, like EA insisting
on using that Frostbite engine
It's a bad decision, it's not
you know, we can call
that out, but it's all
in how you do it and what you say when you do it
Anyway, hope
you guys enjoyed this episode of Orange Lounge Radio
and if you like what you heard here at Orange Lounge
Radio, please tell a friend or two
Help us spread the word, because we are the show where every gamer
has a voice, but
you know, we can only share those voices if they're
actually here to share with other people
So we encourage you to tell a friend
or five about the show
The hosts on Twitch, like if you put
VoG network on your auto host list, that goes a long way
Really appreciate that type of stuff
All the tweets, all that is great, and thank you guys
so much for helping to spread the word
So I think I'm gonna go around now
and get everybody's final thoughts for the night
Loki, you have a final thought for us tonight?
My final thought is
I'm going to build
the Labo thing this week and
I don't know, I'll
try to get my
edits to work, that's really what
it's been down to, it's like
I know how that format works more than
probably anybody, and
yet it's not working
It's frustrating, because it should work
It's just not
My final thought is
sorry for the mic issues, but the joys of live
radio and what we do here, thank you guys
for participating in our live little radio
program, and
I can't wait for the Harry Potter
game to come out already, Wizards Unite
My location-based
gaming is ready for one more
They haven't said when
I'm hoping the summer time, but
yeah, and
Darzaga, last but not least, your final thought
I'm happy that Star Trek Online plays on a Mac
and give me bursters
Alright, can do
That's gonna do it for another episode of Orange on Trado
Thank you guys again so much for tuning in and participating
We will see you back here in 7 days
over at twitch.tv slash vog network
or on the podcast feed
However you choose to enjoy this show, thank you so much
for being with us, and I hope you all have
a wonderful week. Good night everybody
See you next week
Thanks for watching!