Orange Lounge Radio
Who's the host?
Dark Sakura
Sky and Loco
Tonight, May 2nd, 2010
Is a 6 player 2D Castlevania game on the way
Bungie signs a new publishing deal
And is yet another sequel to Red Steel on the way
Orange Lounge Radio
Enough arguing about the graphics card in our chat room
Jeez, it's like all these wars
Can't we all just get along?
Oh hey, hello my friends and welcome to episode number 365 of Orange Lounge Radio
The video game talk show where every gamer has a voice
My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-host
The one, the only, the ultimate, the sometimes friendly
Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
Hi
But always
My headache's gone
But always ready to make guacamole
Oh my guacamole was really good
Oh my guacamole
Okay, I have to say something because
You know how I said two weeks ago, two or three weeks ago
That I was going to give up fast food altogether
While I decided to go semi-raw
Oh my guac
Not fully vegan because if I have an opportunity to have sashimi
Then I'm going to eat sashimi
But for the most part, the easiest way to do it
Is to go kind of raw vegan
And it's because I've had so many digestion problems
And so many other health issues
That I think this is the best way to see if it
It can't hurt, it can only help
I will say this, years and years ago
Probably about seven, eight years ago
The crazy psychic
I used to date someone who was vegan
Allegedly
And he really, really liked to cook
And I will tell you, and I don't like to cook
So I would eat whatever the vegan would make
Well yeah, because I will eat anything a vegan makes
Because you know, at worst case scenario
It's like tofu surprise
They're not going to go, surprise, it's brains of a cow
Or you know, something in the dish
Or Rocky Mountain oysters
Yeah, you always know, it's vegetables
Chat room, ask me what it is if you don't know
But I will say this
Between that and that was at the peak
Of me playing DDR during the tournaments
And that was when the orange bat stuff happened
When the show was born, etc, etc
I was never thinner
Now I'm fat
And the whole thing of it is
I really just stopped and looked at everything
That I was consuming
I was having a couple of sugar free Red Bulls a day
And coffee
And I was having trouble sleeping, duh
Gee, I wonder why
And I was really stressed out from work
And from my school projects
That a lot of other stuff had going on
So I just decided that it's time
That I stop putting this off
Stop putting this?
Yeah, stop putting this off
And just start doing something for myself
And yeah, and no
It's not like the crazy vegan type of people
Like, oh, organic food is the only kind of food you can eat
And all these have drugs in them
Meat is murder
Yeah, fuck PETA
However
I do think that
The belief would not be there
If there hadn't been some basis for it
So
I'm doing this for me
I'm not doing it for the bunnies
I'm doing it for the cows
Although I did find that corn fed cow
Makes me sick
Grass fed cow does not
How strange
Keep in mind they feed cows antibiotics
To make them digest corn
Because cows are not meant to eat corn
Neither are humans
Anyhow
Let me go
I gotta introduce everybody here
I'm sorry for going off on it
But I have to say right now
My headache has finally gone away
Let me also introduce the host
Voted least likely to go vegetarian
Of all the OLR hosts
Say hello to the one and only tech master Loki
I'll never go vegetarian
You'd have to give up your double downs
I don't eat the double downs anymore
It's not worth it
Seriously
It was just experiment to see if it was any good
And I see right through their scam
Of giving me two pieces of chicken
For a lot of money
Tonight I notice you've gone back to the old standard
Personal sized pizza
Wrong it was six parmesan twists
Oh okay I'm sorry
And it's because those are really delicious
But also vegetarian
No
Not true vegetarian
Because it's cheese and all that stuff
La ba ba ba
Whatever the cheese and egg
Labia what?
Octolavio or something
I don't know
I haven't researched my vegan terminology
I did have eggs this morning though
Because I went out to breakfast
Maybe someone in our chat room knows the vegan terminology
Chat.orangesolentrated.com
Because we do tape live every week at
All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
9 o'clock eastern right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
If you're listening to us live
Pull up a chair and join us in our chat room
Chat.orangelaungeradio.com
I know we talk a lot about food
On this show but we also talk about
Games once in a while it happens
It's been known to happen actually tonight is a very
Busy game news night so we have
Lots of game news to get into here in a little bit
Also a game tonight yay we're gonna
Do a game list list is coming up
Tonight part B exciting
You guys asked for a game last week so we're gonna do it tonight
We'll tell you the topic in a little while but first
How was your gaming week?
DarkSakura
I played more Babylonian Twins which is pretty fun
Super Street Fighter 4
Which Drury is mean and evil
And bad ass
Totally
And I played some pinball
And more
Espagaluda
Espagaluda 2
That's just kind of fun to say
Espagaluda
Let's talk more Super Street Fighter 4 cause I
Bought it this week too
What console did you guys get it on?
We have 360
At PS3 but you guys have the fight stick right?
Why are you giggling?
Cause
That's cool
You guys have the fight stick on 360 right?
Yeah good times
But we do have some news though about
GameCrazy
And I was gonna wait until later on in the show
To say it cause I got an email
Well I didn't show roll it because I didn't know if you wanted
To talk about it or not but go ahead and take the floor
I said I was gonna wait but meh
GameCrazy's gone out of business
So instead of my husband
Having 3 weeks of work he's got 13
Weeks of work so that's good
But at the same time
Bye bye GameCrazy
I know the rumors have been floating
Around the internet and I think the stories we've seen on the internet
Were a rumor but
It's true
We got confirmation a week ago
So
I'm more like a couple days ago
But for every door that closes another opens
Blah blah blah blah blah
It'll be okay
We're not worried I'll put it this way we're not worried
So it's all good we're not worried
It's just a bummer though that
An alternative to
You know Baron Von GameStop
Is now closing you know
It seems like they're just dropping like flies
Did you totally see the game trader store that's on
Antelope? And there's more local
We sell them yes and I know they have their
Logo that's a blatant rip off
Identical to GameStop
Seriously the same
The same freaking font
I don't mean to get local
On you guys but maybe there's like
One or two sacri- here there's the guy
We met in the line at Target that listens to the show
So somebody in Sac- he's even still listening
Some people in Sacramento are listening
There's also
Have you seen that place on Sunrise? Smashburger
Yes that too
Same font, same white and red
Color and everything but it's a burger joint
The font
Is not a condensed font
Close, close
It's different enough that they can't
You're weird
I know I noticed this stuff
By the way, by the way I know
I'm gonna take a picture and put it on the site
But this is the newspaper that I did
Oh it's all like
Actually printed on paper
It's a very- it's like I can get all my
Jewish news
Well it was for a fundraiser
The temple that I go to had a big fundraiser called All That Jazz
You were plugging in on the show a couple weeks ago
They wanted a newspaper to distribute
No OLR fans at the show
I didn't go
You know why I didn't go Rob
Cause guess who's sitting her happy butt
Here in this chair doing OLR
I'm sorry
That was me
Anyhow, by the way there are some alternatives
There's what, the game trader
Is that what they're called? Game trader or traitor
Traitor
There's also that fair game
Now I know the guys there
The guys at fair game are rad
Aren't they expanding? Cause there's the one over on
Fair Oaks and then there's one right by my house
In Rosemont
Not that I should be plugging where I live
The guys there though, I do think that they
Kinda overcharge a little bit on some of their stuff
But they have a friggin copy of Loom
For the turbo graphics
It's kind of hard to get stuff there
And they also do
Disc resurfacing
And
Xbox
Repairs
Quote
Let me go to chat
chat.orangelandrarity.com
Rama says with GameCrazy going out of business we only have GameStop left
There's a lawsuit in there somewhere
Monopoly?
Trust me there's people that want to make game stores all the time
And just like
Blockbuster closing a bunch of stores
And Hollywood closing a bunch of stores
Well Hollywood's definitely going to be closing a lot of stores
And the same with movie galleries and stuff
How that has sparked the independent
Video growth
Now you're gonna see
The independent
Game store growth go up a little bit
I mean GameCrazies are out there
Definitely not out there as heavily
As say GameStop
Right now but
There's always alternatives
Search them out
You're also forgetting GameStop's biggest competitor
In some ways is Walmart
Target
Best Buy
You know those are all big big game retailers
Now as far as the used game market goes
I don't know
But you always hear rumors about those companies maybe wanting to get into it
But it's just sad when
More stores like this close
Especially when it affects people we know
Very very well and so forth
I hope things go okay in that situation
Let us know if there's gonna be any good sales at least
Whatever silver lining
We can find in this tragic news
They are in the middle of liquidation
You know what they say, when life hands you lemons
Throw them back
Throw them against the wall, stomp on them, squish them
You know what, no no no
I like how Ron White puts it
To quote
When life gives you lemons, make lemonade
Or when life gives you lemons
Find someone who
Who gives potatoes and makes them
Put lemon vodka
Or something
I
I said it wrong
When life gives you lemons, make lemonade
And then go find someone whose life gave them vodka
Alright
Loki
How was your gaming week?
I don't even remember if we were still talking about that or not
Once in a while we talk about video games
Amongst the guacamole and the vodka
Ron White quotes gone horribly wrong
Yeah
I played a few things this week
I tried out some of the
Upcoming Xbox Live arcade games
I mean not anything I was really impressed with
Cause they're just like ports of old arcade games
Or semi-recent arcade games I guess
Racestorm HD
Kinda cool
I actually have Racestorm on my
My arcade cabinet at home
So
Honestly it's just slightly
Crisper graphics
And that's it but otherwise it plays
Pretty much exactly the same
And then Neo Geo Battle
Coliseum
It was okay I actually never played that in the arcade
And it was kinda neat to be able to
Play as one of the characters from
Metal Slug in a fighting game
Cause he uses his gun a lot
But
It was pretty cool so that should be coming out hopefully
Soon I know Racestorm I think we have it
In the show role I think later on
So that's also coming soon
Then other things
Play more Grand Theft Auto
Still trying to
Dominate that and
Played against one guy today who thought
I love these people that
I play against that
Think they're so good and gonna
Teach me a lesson and stuff
Then I get like a thousand
Oh yeah
No no seriously they're like
You better remember that
Yes you better remember that you got a lucky kill
On me after I chased you down through the entire
Damn city trying to kill you even though I
Was $1500 dollars ahead
Oh yes you're so cool that you got one kill on me
I guess that totally negates
Those other 15 I got on you
So you will remember that as the
One kill they got on you all day
And then you quit. Loser
And then
I actually went back to playing
A little bit more free mode because it is damn
Hard to get a ranked deathmatch game
Nowadays especially in
The Battle of Gay Tony so
Free mode's actually been pretty fun we've been running
Across a bunch of strange
People on there so
Definitely a good time
Waster
Other non Grand Theft Auto
Related stuff played some Marvel vs. Capcom
2 on my arcade cabinet
Because I'm very excited
About the sequel coming out so
Gotta get some of that
In
Hopefully the server bought back because that's
Awesome character to play as
And then
I think
I think that's it for right now because I know I've been
Playing a lot of stuff but I just can't remember all of it
Alright
Well last week I didn't play a whole lot of games
So you guys would be very proud of me that I made up for lost time
This week I played Super Street Fighter 4
I bought it on PS3 because as I mentioned
On the show a couple weeks ago
I don't think I play enough
Street Fighter to really justify the
Arcade stick purchase
But I am a fan enough of Street Fighter where I
Want to buy the upgraded version of
Street Fighter so I bought it on PS3 because I've
Decided I'm declaring war on that
D-pad on the 360 and I'm not
Gonna buy games on the
360 that
Rely on that D-pad so much because
It's just poop and they need to
Release a new controller I don't know why it's taking them so long
So the Playstation 3
What's frustrating is they did
At one time remember in Europe
They had the green one and they fixed the D-pad
Apparently
Why would you
They're waiting for Natal or something I don't know
No they're not waiting for anything why would you
Fix the problem and go
Well we're not gonna fix it forever we're just gonna
Fix it for this one run
I know there's people out there and especially
Xbox and so forth
Believe me I hate on all systems equally
That are gonna tell me that
You're just hating on Xbox
No it really made a difference
I noticed the difference in actually being able to pull off
Combos and certain controls and maneuvers
On the PS3 way easier
Than I was on the 360 so I'm just putting it
Out there that's a personal preference I suppose
And everybody has their own but I did notice
The difference right away in playing on the PS3
On that controller
But the game itself putting the console
Wars and so forth aside going to
The game itself I liked
It quite a lot I thought it was a very worthy
Upgrade and a good purchase you know
Street Fighter 4 as it was was a great
Game but this upgrade having all the
Characters unlocked from the start having
The extra 10 characters and some of the characters
Are awesome like Dark Soccer said
I love Juri as well she's awesome
I like playing her online she's a cheap
Mofo she is
And I love cheap Mofo as in Street Fighter
I was drawn
To her because you know when I was playing the game
Alan was saying like she doesn't look like she belongs
In Street Fighter what is this what is
Her she doesn't she doesn't fit
So I had to play as her and sure enough
She really kind of doesn't look like she belongs
In Street Fighter but she's cool
But I will tell you who I love
Is Guy that is
Oh I love Guy that's my favorite character to play
He's just fun and I like how
Like every you know parting shot
Of him is his butt
They have this thing with butts in Super Street Fighter 4
Have you noticed? No I mean
Surprise no I just
Really like playing as him because he can fly across
The screen and do all these cheap kick moves that I love
I love Guy did you play Cody?
No but I
Alan did and kicked my ass
He was throwing rocks at me and it was pissing me off
Yeah and picking up the knife and everything
I think Guy can use him too though
I tried playing Hakan and I thought
The Turkish oil wrestler
I thought he was kind of hokey I didn't like playing as him
But then again I'm not a big fan of the Zangief
T-Hawk type of characters
Well the whole point with him is that you're supposed to
Build up his oil
You know over and over and over and when he's really slick
Then you can do like all of these crazy moves
Yeah I know but
I don't have the patience
And I have to say though that
If you've ever seen Turkish oil wrestling
He's really glorifying it way too much
I have to tell you though
This is a huge accomplishment for me
I was playing matches online
Ranked matches and winning some
Like that's huge for me because I don't think
I ever won a single one on 360
But I won my first match on PS3
I'm not winning them all but I'm winning some
I gotta say
The skill match I'm getting
Is actually pretty good because
Like I will play a guy
And go for like five rounds if the game
Is configured that way and you know
Win narrowly and
There will be like another guy I was fighting back and forth
We just kept coming up against each other
Ranked matches and he won half and I won half
Like it's actually really matching me up pretty well
So I gotta uh
I gotta say that
Tigerclaw in chat says oh here's another thing guys
If you play as Guy or Cody in the car smasher bonus
Stage you get the oh my car
Easter egg, oh I thought that was normal
Because the first time I ever played that bonus stage
Was with Guy and I just thought
That was what was supposed to happen
But that makes sense because that happens in Final Fight too
Speaking of Final Fight
Alan and I decided just for the hell of it we would
Play through all of Final Fight
Double Impact version, the Final Fight game
And so we played through the whole game
The other night, it doesn't take that long
Maybe an hour at most so that was kind of fun to play
And so we went through that and
The other big big event
In my world is that I
Finally said I can't take it anymore
With my old graphics card
And I upgraded to a new video card
In my computer so
Finally WoW is running at top speed
60 frames a second is beautiful
Gorgeous but more importantly
I'm also able to play
Games on my PC that I wasn't able to
Play before because my graphics card
Was kind of shoddy and one of those big ones
Would be Dragon Age so I
Finally, because I bought Dragon Age during the Christmas
Sale when it was only like 30 bucks
But I was really having a hard time
Playing it because my old video card just couldn't
Handle it and for those of you that are asking
It was a 8, I originally
Had an ATI Radeon
I think in my computer
And so I decided
I don't want to restart the video card wars
That were starting at the beginning of the show but I thought
It would just be easier since my
Computer had come with an ATI card originally
Just to get another ATI card
Call that stupid logic if you want
Whatever I don't care the card I got works
I got an ATI Radeon
And there was a lot of drama trying to get the card
Installed because
Bless Alan's heart he knows how to do all that stuff
I could probably
Figure it out but this thing
Would have confused the hell out of me because this
Graphic card like takes up two slots
It's so big and has like
This gigantic fan on it and that would have
Confused me and then we had to actually
Go upgrade the power supply
Because it needs its own power source
And like it can't run on
The old power supply I had
So yeah thank god he knew how to recognize all this
Stuff because I would have just been lost and cried
You might have been able to get away with the old power supply
If you had the converter for it but
We just got a new supply it was like 30 bucks
And now it's like 600 watts
As opposed to 300 so it works great
Oh 300 yeah
So yeah no the card works great
I was able to play Dragon Age so I was playing that for a couple hours
Did a little bit of the
Warrior human beginning because Alan wanted to show me
Some stuff there and I was
Playing the mage opening a little bit earlier today
Which played so much better
But I understand this game is on
Consoles but man I can't
Imagine how it must control on consoles because on
The computer it's just so
Fluid and just makes sense
Especially for like somebody who's kind of been playing
WoW a long time like me so
I am considering checking out
Star Trek online just because Dark Soccer
Always never shuts up about it and
It's fun I know but here's the thing
There was a big sale on the store
Steam store this weekend I couldn't resist
I bought Guild Wars trilogy for 20 bucks
And you got to admit
It's not a bad deal for Guild Wars
Because Guild Wars is one of those games
You don't pay a monthly fee for it so I
Can buy it now and if I have the itch to play it
In like six months I can just say oh just fire
Up Guild Wars Did you overclock your graphics card
Once you got it? I don't think he did that
Oh he should it's simple
And it's extra
Oomph it runs beautifully
I'll tell you what Guild Wars looks gorgeous
I started playing the Prophecies
Campaign as a Paragon which you know
I had only I'm sorry no no
No Prophecies is the original so I was
Playing Nightfall whatever the newest one is
I played that as a
Paragon which is one of the new classes
They're kind of like Egyptian influenced it seems like
And so I was playing through the openings that it's
Gorgeous oh my gosh
Gorgeous looking stuff
So I didn't really play it enough
I mean both Dragon Age and Guild Wars I only
Spent a couple hours with so but I just
It's fun to be able to play PC games
Again and not have my computer crying out
In pain from it and what's also
Exciting and I just realized on the drive over
Here is that
Between that new card my quad core
My 8 gigs of ram I ain't gonna have a
Problem playing Final Fantasy 14 on my PC
Woo woo
So waiting for that baby test
Help
I need to upgrade my graphics cards because I have two of them
Running in SLI but they're like
8800 Radeon GTS
Do you want my old card? I don't know what's better
I have a power supply and an old video card
My card's way better than that
It's just a lot of stuff
Like if I were to go back and do it again
A lot of these games don't run
SLI and it's really disappointing
And I guess you don't really get that much benefit from it nowadays
But um
I don't know I've got two slots
To put graphics cards I almost feel obligated
To get two more but
Brad from Pod Culture
In chat says Sky didn't know it was on sale
You just sold me on it there you go
When you write NCsoft put
As heard on OLR
No but that's great no but I think the logic
Is fine because you know 20 bucks
For the three game series and no monthly fee
I mean that's a pretty darn good deal
Guild Wars isn't a bad game by any means
I don't think you'll play it forever
But I think you'll kind of go
It's one of those games you'll be like
You know I'm kind of bored of WoW and Star Trek
And Final Fantasy and all the other MMOs
I'm playing right now
Just fire up Guild Wars for the hell of it
What the hell is going on in Guild Wars these days
That's kind of how I've found it
I've played on and off for the past five years
Alright anyhow enough of our gaming weeks
Let's move on and get into some housekeeping tonight
I don't have a lot except for
I might not be here Memorial Day weekend
It looks like I might be taking a trip
So we might not have a show then
Pre-taped or something something
But that's the first time I'm also telling Jamie and Loki
Because I didn't think of it earlier
We'll see
Memorial Day weekend
Three day weekend so if you guys want to get away
I'm planning a trip it looks like
I probably won't be here
We'll see
It's not going to be an extravagant trip
Just a little getaway
Anyhow
More to come on that in the upcoming weeks
We'll let you know for sure what's going to happen
That's Memorial Day weekend
Which I imagine a lot of our listeners
A lot of them are probably going out of town
Anyhow
Also our Twitter
Twitter.com slash OLR and our Facebook
Of course is available too at Orange Lounge Radio
Join us there, friend us
Like our posts, share us, help us spread the word
Because we don't really have advertising dollars
Another place where we could really use help
iTunes and five star reviews on iTunes
Just look up Orange Lounge Radio in the iTunes store
And say a couple nice words about Orange Lounge Radio
We really appreciate
It really does go a long way
Because the more positive reviews you get
The higher you go up in the rankings
And you get a little more visibility
And it works
That's why a lot of podcasts you listen to
Want to get the reviews on iTunes
Because sometimes it's hard to stand out amongst the crowd
And I'll tell you what, it's tough
When you have G4 and IGN
And GameSpot and all these companies with
Limitless amounts of dollars
And budget to pour into advertising
It's hard to stand out amongst that
So we rely on the OL Army to help us out
Alright, let's actually get into some gaming news
We'll have to actually put down the guacamole
For a little bit, step away from the vegetables
And get into some actual gaming news
Loki, start us off tonight
I like to call this kind of like
I don't want to go on the same tangent
As we did last week, but
Kind of like Idols gives back
This is Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2
Gives back, I guess
Apparently with the new
Firmware or dashboard
That was out
At the beginning of April
On the Xbox 360
Comes with it some glitches
For some reason that work with
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2
Allowing certain arcade games
That you may have in trial form
To work as a full game
Instead, without having to pay
Any extra monies
Uh oh, uh oh
So here's how it works, and it couldn't be
Any simpler
Of course you have to have the latest dashboard
The 9199, the one that allows
You to have the USB support
Pop in your Modern Warfare 2 disk
Let the game load up to the main menu
Once you get to the main menu, hit the wonderful
Xbox guide button
That's on your controller
And it will pull up of course the old
Kind of blades
That you can select stuff
Go to quick launch
And choose the trial game of choice
To play it as a full version
Now this doesn't work on all games yet
And there's really just a small list that they have
So far that it works with
But I mean, hey, might as well try it on
Whatever
Some of the games that have been shown to work with it so far
Fatal Fury Special
Metal Slug 3
Samurai Shodown 2
And Metal Slug 7
All those of course being published by SNK
So maybe other SNK games
Might work as well
Let's see
And apparently also there might be
The King of Fighters 98 Ultimate Match
And Guru
Mark of Wolves
I might play on it as well
Okay, break this down for me
How smart do I have to be with my hacking cracking sense
To get this to work?
You don't have to hack anything
It's just part of the dashboard
It's basically, it's just a glitch
All you have to do is pop in your game
Modern Warfare 2
Put a button on your controller
And then select quick launch to
How does that happen?
I don't know
I don't know how you would figure it out either
That is really bad
It's not that we necessarily enjoy
Bringing these things to light
But I think it needs to be said
Like, oops
This is a huge flaw
And you can earn achievements on those games as well
Oh my gosh
I would imagine it's gonna get patched out at some point
But might as well enjoy it while it lasts
We need to introduce something new here on
Orange Lounge Radio called
The Dup Factor
That's right, the Dup Factor
And the Dup Factor would be
Days until the patch
DUP, Days Until Patch
Loki, what do you believe is the
Dup Factor?
I'm not sure because I don't think this is
This hasn't been published on like
Major blog sites or anything like that
Usually when it does hit those
Good thing no one listens to this show
Yeah it's a good thing
Once that happens they'll be like
Because
Obviously Microsoft doesn't read every forum
Out there so
It's hard to say
Yeah, so that's interesting
And if you don't happen to have
Mario Warfare 2 that's okay
Because there's other glitches that also involve
The 9199 dashboard
As well, a couple of the games
Were also found to be working
As full Xbox Live arcade
Games as well
Apparently
Some of them have to do
With
Like for example Worms
Is one of the games that actually works as a full
Xbox Live arcade game if you
Transfer it to a USB card
Because originally they did have
A version of Worms that came on a memory
Unit and it actually worked as a full game
As long as it was on a memory
Unit so you can try that as well
And that doesn't require any sort of game
Purchasing whatsoever
And apparently
Family Game Night has something else that
Works like that as well
But I'm not sure
What's involved with that one
But it's just interesting to see
That a lot of these glitches are out there
I put the dump factor at
7 days. I say by this time
Next week it's out
I think the
Red alarms are going off at
Microsoft as we speak
I just found out about it this week
This has been posted for about 3 weeks
Now so
Has anyone, what was the last posting
Date? The 22nd
So it may already
No
It nothings
No I think somebody would have said something in that little thread he's looking at
If that's the case
We would have seen a patch on the dashboard
Or we would have seen a patch for Call of Duty
I say 7 days
We'll see
Alright
Now Loki I'm sure you would not be taking
Advantage of a patch like this
Or if you have it's only for journalistic purposes
I don't really care
And honestly
Yeah it's just the SNK games
Well
Dude I have a JTAG console
I don't need this crap
Alright
Moving on to other stories
That aren't so shady
But more of a surprise I think in some ways
Nintendo Magazine in France
Apparently has confirmed the existence of
Red Steel 3
Apparently the series
Which as you know is kind of like a first person hack and slash
Type of thing
It's going to be a trilogy even though apparently the second game
Did not sell that well which you were talking about last week
On the show right Loki?
Red Steel 2 not doing so hot?
Well they were saying it wasn't doing hot
Because they only have data from like
You know what 10 days
Not that long
Well apparently the game is going to support
The Wii Vitality sensor
Oh god fail
Right there fail
I'm sorry
That's going to be awful okay
Absolutely awful because
What's the point at that
So how are you going to control the game now
Because you're going to have
Where are you going to plug the nunchuck into
And come up with some sort of splitter or something like that
For the Wii remote
I can't see how this is going to work
I don't know either
I don't write the news I just report it just so you know
Fail
That's all I got to say
I was looking for a clip of the old school DDR failed boys
To play
Behind that
There was a couple other things I wanted to say about this
It's supposed to
I guess this is just part of
If you think about it Red Steel 2
Supported the motion plus
Red Steel was kind of a launch
Title for the Wii
It would not be a surprise if this supports the Vitality sensor
Because it's just yet another add on
Of Nintendo's that Ubisoft is supporting
The only one that Red Steel really didn't
Get on was the balance board
To be honest
So
There you go even though Loki is not a big fan of it
Apparently Red Steel 3 with Vitality sensors
The Vitality sensor is retarded
I'm sorry it's absolutely retarded
Yeah it will be wonderful
For the Wii Relax game that comes out
And people will buy it because it's like
Oh look you can relax now
Now that Nintendo is helping you
How do you really know yet though
I mean all you've really heard about this
Is a concept you haven't seen it in motion yet
Maybe it will be neat
No it won't
That's like saying oh blood pressure
You know I get to take my blood pressure now
That's so exciting
I mean old people are like that
You know they go to the drug store
Take their blood pressure
Well I beg to differ
Who's buying the Wii
I actually beg to differ
Well they're not going to be playing Red Steel 3
I
Well this is someone who gets a blood test twice a year
And has her blood pressure checked regularly
So
Yeah but is it fun
If it keeps me alive
Yeah but I don't consider that fun
I had to have four MRIs
A couple years ago to keep me alive
But I wasn't exactly like gosh I wish I had one of these at home
It's a lot of fun
It's like a colonoscopy
Oh that helps you stay alive
Some people get off on that
The Wii virtual colon sensor
Thanks god
For when the Human Centipede video game comes out
I'm just saying though
Fun aside
I do want to say
They'll be illegitimate
And they did say there was like a subtitle
At least on the Human Centipede
That it makes it seem like it's going to be one of a series
So I'm like
That discussion on that movie
Has gotten far too much airtime
On the all news network
Let's move on to some more
Video game stories
I was actually putting something up for you Rob
What's that
Come and look at it
Is that Gaia?
Yes it is but so they put up an item called
Starmony
That's a little rainbow unicorn that says open your eyes
Loki's the rainbow unicorn fan
Not me
Who's the one that's always playing the rainbow unicorn game
That would be Loki
You need to put that on his wall
I'm going to post it on my Facebook later
But I thought it was funny
Anyway
So how about a story
How about something about Guitar Hero
I think
Is that
Activision is sending out the feelers
To see if people would be interested
In Red Hot Chili Peppers
Guitar Hero
I guess but aren't most of their songs
In like Rock Band or Guitar Hero
Already?
Isn't the whole Blood Sugar Sex Magic album
On Rock Band?
I think that it's
Supposed to also have an exclusive
For their new album
Oh
That's at least the speculation
But then again
You can get the whole thing of Blood Sugar Sex Magic
On Rock Band
But I mean
The Red Hot Chili Peppers were much more than one album
I mean they are
They're an important band
I've been listening to their stuff since George Clinton produced them
You know
P-Funk
Parliament
Multicolored dreads
They gotta be older
I think
40's at most
They've been doing it a long time
I was listening
Blood Sugar Sex Magic came out
When I was in high school
And I had already been listening to
Actually a song off of Mother's Milk
Was in Say Anything
So that's late 80's
I think they started in
84?
Well I mean if Green Day
Can have their own game
But Red Hot Chili Peppers is far more
Expansive than Green Day
I agree to an extent
Yeah
But
I think it's a good choice
For their own video game
I would look at it
I don't know if I'd pay $50 for it
But I'd look at it and I'd go oh neat I like these songs
You know
So
We'll see though I don't know
There's a part of me that goes I don't know Guitar Hero Van Halen
Was kind of poop
Yeah
They're better off sticking with Rock Band
Just putting out more content for Rock Band
We'll see
Well I'm just like
Cause I thought they were supposed to be
Cutting back
Well I guess they sort of have cut back on Guitar Hero a little bit
Cause we haven't had a game in like 6 months
Well not 6 months 4 months
Yeah 6 months
Is that counting DS versions and all that?
And yes
It does count DS versions and whatnot
And nothing I've seen
On the horizon yet until like
Fall
Which is good
So here's a rumor that's kind of interesting
We may have talked about it
A little bit before when it was
Discovered as a trademark
From Konami, Harmony of Despair
Well the
A trusted source as
Joisic puts it
Harmony of Despair
Is a 2D 6 player
Xbox Live arcade game
You'll get to play as some of the old
Characters or I guess main characters from a bunch
Of different games and it's supposed to kind of
Appear like
The Game Boy Advance or DS
Versions
Of the game so I guess like you know
Super NES type of thing
And you'll get to play
With a bunch of people at the same time
And they'll actually be able to zoom out
To show where everyone's at
And stuff like that so 6 player co-op
Castlevania sounds kind of fun actually
I feel like God has finally
Listened to me, thank you
Thank you Jesus
This is what I've been asking for
For how long now on this program
Give me a old school
2D new Castlevania
Game on my television
And this sounds sweet that it's gonna be like
6 player zoomy in out co-op stuff
Sounds kind of rad actually
Sounds way better than Judgment
And then when you're done with this Nintendo give us a new Metroid like this
And then when you're done with this
Konami can come back and give me a new Contra like this
No Frogger
Do not want Frogger
With 6 people
Unless it's an
Extreme Frogger
I gotta admit though this sounds very awesome
Like can you imagine being able to explore
The castle with multiple people at the same time
But how would that work because
There's gonna have to be some type of like
Random castle generator element
To it or something or else it's always gonna be the
Same damn game
Obviously this is a very
Early type of story and it's also rumor right
It's not confirmed
But maybe they're gonna have multiple castles
Or something like that or you'll be able to download
Extra castles later on
I really want more information on this soon
This sounds great
Or maybe that partner net site
Will leak everything like it always does
That would be wonderful too
I know what do you think your
Castlevania fan Dark Soccer would like to see?
Oh I'd be all over that heck yeah
We're gonna play 6 player heck yeah
Dude totally
That's right I'll whip you
But think about it I bet Dark Soccer
If they're talking about multiple characters
You'll get to be
You'll get to be Alucard
You'll get to be Maria
I bet hands down a lot of the famous Castlevania
I do remember they had
I would have to play
They had Alucard on the list
There was another site that covered it also
They had some more information but
I remember Alucard being on the list
Amae Satsuma in our chatroom
chat.orangelandstrategy.com says
I'd be fine with a 6 player Frogger
If I could play as a truck
That would be awesome
I want to play as a gator
That's like Frogger versus
Remember in Pacman versus you could be the ghost
That would be amazingly fun
Total side note
It's not on our show roll but I think this chatroom
Comment is worth reading Spyro in our chat says
Is there no more game room games being
Released now? You know they were supposed
To put out like Pitfall
And Super
Breakout I think were some of the big
Games this week and it got halted
The release just
Didn't end up happening
And there was actually a tweet
Over on god I can't believe I'm using
Twitter but the thing is
Game room did not have much of a good
Website behind it I mean I guess they have an official
Website but it kind of sucks
They don't have the greatest web presence I don't know
This thing was kind of set up to fail from the beginning
But on their Twitter which is
At live game room they say
First off they
Broke the news by
Retweeting Major Nelson
Just shows you how
It's totally burped excuse me
That's awesome
Professional radio
They broke the news by retweeting
Major Nelson saying
We're working to bring you additional game room titles
As soon as possible I'll let you know
The moment I have more details
And then they
Sent an at message to somebody
Saying there was a delay in the game pack release
We'll update when we've got more details
That's it
So I mean fail fail fail fail
I kind of regret
A couple weeks ago when I was
Reviewing game room on the show I said
Hey this is going to be better than
Virtual Console because at least you know
Although it has plenty of room for improvement
It's more than just straight up ports of the games
Well I mean
At least games are
Coming out for Virtual Console
It just
Irritates me because there was so
Much potential
Here
Can you imagine if they had
I'm sorry they have just crashed
And burned with
It's so frustrating
It's an awesome idea
Well they should have integrated it with
Like different Xbox Live
Arcade games so it wouldn't matter
That they're not putting out any because you could
Still use your Xbox Live arcade games
And have them in your arcade
And what not
And then here's the thing
SHJ100Matt says Seriously game room was supposed to be
Microsoft's answer to home
But it's just as much of a failure as home so far
That is
I don't know if I'm okay with the game room
Home comparisons
I think people assumed
It was going to be like home
Because you would be able to navigate around in the first person
Which was I don't think ever the case
I think Microsoft's always kind of strung you along
With the well maybe we'll implement that someday
Dude you can't even fucking release
A new pack for the game on time
You're not going to have the full
First person movement around like home
Ever
Prove me wrong please
I'm just irritated because the problem is
If this fails
Which it's starting to look more and more like it's going to
And how fucking disappointing is that
That we're never going to get any more packs for this game
At the rate we're going
You know whatever happened to like the 1000 games
If this thing fails
We're not going to see anything like it
Until maybe the next generation
Maybe
Maybe on Nintendo's Wii HD
Or whatever console they do after the Wii
Maybe they will finally say
Okay you can play the old NES games
Over the internet after you re-buy them
For five bucks a piece
Just irritates me
I am mad
Anyway
Rob
Deep breaths
As a retro game fan
You know I was really excited about
A lot that Game Room had to bring
And it didn't really suck
I mean there was a lot of promise with it
I mean yeah they could have had a little more
Hopefully
I'm just overreacting and this is all fixed
In a week I mean maybe they had problems
With the whole PC and I heard people
Were able to hack certain games in Game Room
Like a lot of the high scores on asteroids
Were faked so maybe for quality
Purposes they pulled it back
But when I hear about these layoffs
When I see crappy web support
You know for this
My hope fades more and more
I have a feeling that there's going to be all sorts of
Exploits
With it because it's in file form
And people have modded consoles
And they're going to hex edit crap
So that they can cheat in the games
It's going to script the leaderboards
Prove me wrong Microsoft please
Please I would love to get proven wrong on this
Meanwhile other news
PlayStation 3 and here's something
Else to rage about
Of course
We reported a couple weeks ago on the show
And I'm sure you read about it everywhere on the internet
You saw this first hand
They took out the other OS feature
On the PlayStation 3
They released a patch to do nothing
But remove a feature on the PlayStation 3
And I believe we said
Oh I wonder how long before somebody sues
Well days until suing
Would apparently be about two weeks
That's right about 14 days
Somebody sued
A class action lawsuit for removing
The PlayStation 3 support for other OS's
Anthony Ventura is the
Class action lawsuit filers name
The plaintiff
I'm a plaintiff
He filed a class action lawsuit against the company
Saying that it's a breach of contract
False advertising
And you know all this other big legal words
He says that the other OS function is extremely
Valuable
Although players are not forced to download the update
If you don't you can't access
The other features on your PlayStation
So you're either locked out over here
Or you're locked out over here
Apparently the amount is in excess
Of five million dollars
Is how much they're looking to get in damages
I don't know if it'll work
But it's interesting that somebody's actually
Filed the lawsuit over this
As I suspected somebody probably
Would in this too happy nation that we're in
I don't know what do you guys think
Will happen with this lawsuit
I don't know it'd be interesting to see
How it plays out
I'm interested because I have a system
That you know hasn't been updated yet
And I'm not planning on updating it
Because guess what I haven't bought any new games
For it since
LittleBigPlanet
I think the biggest kicker here is
Are they gonna be able to prove that this was
An advertised feature
That's gonna be tough
And I don't think they're gonna be able to get away with it
Maybe in other countries but not here
I don't remember that being advertised
It's not on a commercial or something
But they did advertise it coming out of E3
And that kind of stuff
It's a console it's not like you know
People didn't know it was there
But I do think it's kind of
Messed up
It's the whole kind of conspiracy part of it
Or I guess paranoia part of it
It's like if they're gonna take this out
Because some hacker or whatever
Found a way around
You know their copy protection
Which didn't really happen
I don't think anyone's actually found a way around
Their copy protection yet other than the fact that
They're starting to mess around
With Linux but
You know if that's the case
Then what if someone finds a way with
You know the Xbox or not Xbox
PlayStation 1 emulation or something like that
Or are they gonna remove that too
Or you know
Even on older consoles
That can play PlayStation 2 games what if they find a way with that
Are they gonna remove the PlayStation 2
You know backwards compatibility
I'm surprised they haven't
So I don't know
And yeah let's just say for example
That they decide later on
Hey you know what we're gonna start selling PlayStation 2 games
On the PlayStation Network
Now we're gonna remove your backwards compatibility
So you have to buy those games from us
Again
That would be kind of shady
And if you want to play your PlayStation 2 games
You can go buy one of our $99.99
PlayStation 2 slim systems
But at the same time
Let me play devil's advocate for a minute here
Because Rama says forget the lawsuit
People just trade in your PS3's
For something worthwhile
That chat coming from chat.orangestonsrated.com
Well I mean to play devil's advocate
You never could install Linux on a 360
You can't even get the web on your 360
I mean
You can now but
Well
Without legitimately
None of these features are possible
I mean you can still get the other OS feature
On your PlayStation 3 too if you know where to look
Right
Um
Not yet
Well it's being worked on or something
Anyway
Uh yeah I guess we'll see what develops with this
It'll be very interesting though because you know what happens
Is that if this guy wins
You'll all be able to get a check in the mail for like
Five whole dollars
Cause that's what happens with class action lawsuits
Or maybe they'll have to give out a free game or something
I don't know
Yeah but I mean what if that free game is like
Yaris 2 for the PS3 or something
It doesn't have to be a good game
Freeze free?
I don't know
There's some things that you couldn't even pay me to play for free
It's like bad
Anyway let's move on more gaming news Darcy
How about something happier? Yes happy happy joy joy
Cub Scouts!
I thought you said happier
Yeah okay I know little Mormons in training
Um sorry I didn't say that
I was in the Cub Scouts for a year
One whole year
I was in the Cub Scouts and the Boy Scouts
Never became a Mormon
In fact I
Just learned how to set fire to things and tie knots
I forgot the knots part
Oh if only they knew I was a gay in training
It's so awesome though
I mean seriously if you want to have fun as
You know in the Boy Scouts or something like that
Just buy the damn manual
Give it to your kid, have them read through it
That's all the information you need
The rest is just camping trips and pinewood car derby
That's all it really is
So about video games
That was awesome
I love how Dark Soccer is like
I swear to god I have news to report
Will you boys stop reminiscing about your stupid scout troops?
We build wooden cars
Just so you know
Anyway hi
So for the Cub Scouts
There's a new
A new badge available
Or sorry belt loop
Or whatever the crap that means
You can get a video game
Belt loop
I guess
I don't get a belt loop
I don't remember them having
I remember the badges
They actually could sew on and then there was the little
Patches, there were patches and there were badges
So now they have belt loops too whatever
They get more bling
It was pins back in my day
Yeah that's what I meant, pins
I remember they would flip the kid upside down
And put the pin on when the kid was upside down
And then like when you actually did
Whatever your parents could turn it right
Side up as if you weren't capable of just
Doing it yourself but
If you did you'd go to hell
I remember that part
You actually need to watch the episode
Of bullshit about scouting
You make John Smith cry
They took
Anyway I'm gonna
Can I tell you a true story? I'm sorry Dark Soccer
I know you have a legitimate gaming story here
Hey guess what? What? My mother
Carrot Pulled me out of Cub Scout
She didn't want me going anymore
You know why? True story
She didn't like the other kids in my troop
She thought all the other kids in my troop
And 10 years later
She told me this
All the other little kids in your troop
Were little assholes
I love your mom
And I didn't want you hanging out with those assholes
So Rob
I'm not saying that you might be listening to the show
I'm just saying that
The Roseville troop was a bunch of assholes
Allegedly
So the whole way to get
This video game belt loop
You have to complete three tasks
And I think this is actually a really positive thing
Explain why it's important to have a rating system
For video games
With an adult's help
Make a schedule to do things that include your
Chores, homework, video games
And you have to stick to schedule
And learn to play any video game that is approved
By your parent, guardian, or teacher
So I guess imagine babies might be on it or something
After you get the belt loop
Um
You earn a pin by
Completing five of nine tasks
Which would be
With your parents create a plan to buy a video game
That is right for your age group
That's hard
Compare two game systems
Explain the differences between the two
And good purchase
Or use of a game system
Play a video game with family members
In a family tournament
Teach an adult or friend how to play a video game
List at least five tips that would help someone
Who was learning how to play your favorite video game
Play an appropriate video game
With a friend for one hour
So no imagine babies
Play a video game that will help
Practice math, spelling, or other skills
To help you in your school work
Choose a game you might like to purchase
And compare the price at three different stores
To decide which one is the best deal
Include
Factors like return policy and warranty
And with an adult supervision
Install a gaming system
Um
Okay
I think it's good because it's encouraging
You know, family time
It could be good for parents
To demystify
Video games
Yeah, it's not a bad thing
I know we're sitting here and tee-heeing about it
But it's encouraging
What should be happening in the first place
Parents and kids to talk about
The kids hobby
Who would have thought
When I was a kid, my papa and I
My dad's father
We used to sit around playing Jackal
On Nintendo
On the big screen TV
Which is a war game where you shoot people
And run over them in a tank
And we played, get this
Abadox
Disgusting game at the time
I love Abadox for the record
I could imagine coming home from a Cub Scout meeting
And telling my mom
Hey mom, uh
I want to get this video game badge that they're giving away
So would you sit for me for an hour
While I install a video game system
And show you how to do it? She'd just be like
Where's the paper that I just signed?
Hahahaha
Well also, um
There, um
I think that that kind of also
You know, sort of discounts
The fact that a lot of these parents might have grown up
With video games too
You know, my mom and I used to play
Tetris together
And we used to play Super Mario Brothers
In all kinds of games and
Okay
Stop trying to smack the fly
With your pizza box
You're gonna fly on the loose in the studio
Keep in mind
It flew outside, it flew outside
Stay out
In two days it will be dead
Not if I can help it
I'll take that long
Flies really don't live longer than a few days
That's the comfort I take in that
They're going to die soon
Tangent Lounge Radio, back to the Cub Scouts please
I have carrots
They're delicious and raw
Cub Scouts!
They should program a game
I'm very disappointed, well that's a programming badge
Um, I'm very disappointed though
That not one of those little
I guess, uh
Achievements or requirements on that list
Is go to arcade
Well, cause there are no arcades
That's a myth
In some parts of the
States, there are no arcades
Well then, you know what, you don't really want that badge now
Do you?
Here's the thing, the only problem
I don't want to even like open this door
And go there, but you know, I live there
Uh, the only problem I have
With this badge, like I think it's a good thing
And it's encouraging the family to talk, yada yada yada
Is that this badge could go right next to your
Queer hating badge, because
You know, the Boy Scouts won't
You know the whole thing about how, you know
They won't let, um
Gay guys be Scout Masters and so forth
Because apparently
All gay guys know how to do
Is molest kids
They won't let them be Scouts
At all
I think at that age, you're kind of too
Young to know anyway, so I think
That arguments are relevant, like
Honestly, like, you know, how
Old are Boy Scouts, like 12 to like
15, like you just
Here, everything
Is, it's not even
An issue at that age, you know what I mean, if it is an issue
You're too young, just don't even
Think about that stuff, but um
You know, it does kind of
Irritate me that they don't really have
A good reason for
Justifying why
I don't know why homos
Will want to be involved with such an organization
That hates them, but if they do, they should
You know, get to do it. My problem is, why is this
Even a badge in the first place, because I thought
The Boy Scouts and Cub Scouts and whatever
Were all about, kind of like
The whole outdoors, you know
The Woodsmen, you know
Type mentality, where it's like learning
How to kind of, not really necessarily
Survive, but there are survival
Tools in there as well, and
You know, kind of, you know, how to be
Good, you know, participant
In your, you know
Social circle or whatever
You know, being a good community member, I thought that was
Really the values that they were
Trying to put forth, and this is kind of
Unnecessary, because like, I mean seriously
They're gonna have a badge for learning how to use windows
You know, or, look, I installed
The Mac today, or you know, I've
I don't know
I learned how to program my VCR
My TiVo badge, you know, and seriously
It's not really necessary
It's kind of just
Good that you know how to do that stuff
And good that you're spending time with your family
And that kind of thing, but
It doesn't need to be a badge
I think it's just being
Used as a convenient tool
To teach economics
Good shopping skills and family
I think it's just Boy Scouts trying to be hip
I think you're right
Because maybe the
Memberships are down or something
It's fine
Question, or I'm sorry, comment
From the chatroom, chat.org.org.com
Sharan in chat says, you don't need to be gay
To know how to molest children
No, you just have to know how to be a priest
Ohhhhh, and if that joke offended
You, guess what, now you know how
Offended I get when I hear
The rationalization for why gays
Can't be in Boy Scouts, and there
You have it
See, I offended people but to teach a lesson
Now you know how I feel
Alright
It is offensive, moving on
Release dates
Let's go to the US and see what games
Are gonna be coming out soon, Loki
Not much, this week is pretty light
And it's sad that one of the biggest
Games this week is actually
Iron Man 2
Of course, coming out on
Friday in theaters
You gotta have your typical movie tying game
But don't worry, Sega says that this game
Isn't crap like the last one
That's famous last
Words from people that make crappy ported
Or movie tying games
Other fun
Stuff coming out this week, Picross
3D
Picross, but it's in 3D form
And you make nice little cube animals
The Total War
Battle Pack, kind of a
Pre-release of the Total War games
Coming out on PC this week
Fat Princess Fistful of Cake
Making its way out on UMD
For the PSP, of course it's
I think already out on the PSP
In the PlayStation Network
Dance Sensation
Kind of
Trying to take advantage of the adjust
Dance craze, but
Purely aimed at girls
And Dementium 2
Out on DS, this would be the perfect
Game to purchase for that
Cup Scout badge
And
Also this week, the official
Xbox 360
USB Flash Sticks
These are hilarious
And I'm laughing at the prices
An 8GB
USB flash drive will cost you
$39.99 and
A 16GB flash drive
Will run you $69.99
I was just pricing these online
Because I'm planning on picking up an 8GB
And guess what, you can get them for about half the price
So really, thank you Microsoft
For still overcharging
It's not gonna work as well with
A USB stick
And that's it for this week
Let's head on over to Japan
And look at the Japanese releases
What's coming out on the Xbox 360
This week, really nothing, believe it or not
Not really anything coming out at all
On the Xbox 360 this week
Again, these are Japanese releases
And sometimes, you know, there's big variants
On the Playstation 3
Also not a lot coming out this week
I don't know what, is there like a holiday or something
Going on in Japan right now?
Golden Week
It's a big
No, no, no
If I remember right, Golden Week
Is when families go back to their hometowns
And
They visit with people, like everything's closed
I just know the 5th of May is Children's Day
Oh, maybe that explains
Where the holiday comes from in WoW
Because it's Children's Week in WoW right now
Yeah, I totally just made a Warcraft reference
Hey, Nintendo Wii, also nothing
This week, really, no releases till the 13th of May
Playstation 2
Nothing, DS, nothing
PSP, nothing
Nothing is coming out in Japan until the 13th
Okay, by the way, I found it
What's that?
It's a paid time off
On the work days
Some companies completely close down and give their employees
Time off, it's the longest vacation
Period of the year for many Japanese jobs
So, yeah
Wish we had that over here
I know, I want Golden Week, how about Golden Arches Week
We have FIFA World Cup
Soccer to look forward to when Golden Week's
Over, that's going to be a big release on the 13th
It's because there's
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
Holidays during
That period of time
Well, we get Cinco de Mayo over here
We don't get it off, do we?
Yay
Really, I don't think Cinco de Mayo is really
Actually an American holiday anyway
It's just one we kind of borrowed
From our neighbors to have an excuse to drink
Mexican food potluck day
Exactly
As if work needed another excuse to have a potluck
Alright
Let's move on
Okay, is there any holidays in the UK
Stopping video games this week?
Uh, no. I don't think so
Why don't they celebrate Cinco de Mayo?
Runaway 3
For DS
Runaway A Twisted Fate for PC
On the 7th, by the way
Sin and Punishment 2 for Wii
And What Did I Do to Deserve This, My Lord?
Dude, that's awesome that they're getting Sin and Punishment 2
Seeing as ours has been delayed
Yeah
On PSP and that's really it
Alright
A few more gaming stories for you guys
And then the classic game of the week
Where Dark Soccer is gonna dig through the vaults
And believe me, kids, she's diggin' this week
Loki
You may remember that Microsoft
Sue Datel over their unofficial
Max memory
Memory cards that they had out
Because they took
Little micro SD cards and allowed you to use them
On the
Xbox 360
Which now that I think of it, it's kind of funny
Because, um
They actually
Now that they've opened that up
You don't really need these memory cards
Talk about, uh
Sucking
Anyways, so
To kind of respond to
Datel's request
They filed an antitrust
Lawsuit against Microsoft
Pissed off that they weren't
Kind of playing on even
Playing ground here
And, um
Yeah, I kind of remember this whole
Back and forth from a couple weeks ago, yeah
Yeah, they're basically saying, um
That the
Claims that by
Datel
That they locked them out with a firmware update
And Microsoft has used its
Status as a platform holder to
Unlawfully prevent competition
Which, I can see that
Because there's a lot of
You know, um
A lot of first party, you know, products out there
But there's a lot of stuff that, you know, you have to get
Approval from Microsoft to build the release
Items for those systems
And I think that pretty much goes with any other system
But, seeing as the Wii
And, um, the
PlayStation 3 used kind of open
Storage formats, you know
The SD memory cards and USB
Memory sticks and stuff like that
Now Microsoft, um
You can see how that would be a problem
Since they were
Prior to the last firmware update
Only allowed to use
Either the hard drive or a
A memory stick
Memory unit from Microsoft
They're saying
Microsoft's motion to dismiss
Because they tried to dismiss it, it claimed that
The language in the additional terms and conditions
Clause of the Xbox 360
Product warranty, because everybody reads
That, um, barred the
Use of unauthorized peripherals
And the company, uh
Backed up its case by citing
Apple's, I guess, successful defense
Of its right to limit the use of
OS X to its own hardware
And the court rejected
Microsoft's motion to have
It dismissed, so it will
Apparently go to trial
Although, at this point
It's like, well
That's great and all, but
In the meantime, I'll just pop
In my USB memory stick
To, uh, save my games now
So that's gonna be kinda hard
To, uh, make the case
Now
Hmm
Well, I mean
Do you think there are, this is gonna be
One of those cases that gets dragged out
For years and years, or is it gonna get settled pretty
Quickly? What do you think?
Put on your legal expert
Hat
I think it probably gets
Probably gets settled, because
You know, really, yeah, it sucks that they
Made these devices, and
They got pulled from the market really
Quick. My thing is, though
Uh
It's gonna be difficult
Now to show any damages
Because
They weren't out that long, and
Now there are other options
Other than the memory units. In fact, they're not even
Making the memory units anymore
Um
So
I don't know, it's
It's hard, like, if they were
Yeah, they're not making them, because
Yeah, well they're not making them now, but if
If they were, like, to say, completely ignore
The time when they had just the memory units
Now that argument doesn't really hold
Um, but of course, you know
This took place before that update
But it almost makes you wonder if that update was
Partially in response to this
But, who knows
It just sucks for them, but
That's an interesting thought, because it did seem like that USB
Thing came out of nowhere, didn't it? I think they were
Worried that there was gonna be
Some sort of, uh, because
With this, you'll be able to
Access your files on your memory
Cards or whatever
And you might be able to cheat or something
Like, you know, edit your save games or something
Which, I can tell you right now, that wouldn't have
Stopped them, because it's very
Easy to do that if you have the right tools
Even easier now that they have USB support
It's like
A program in hex editing
Alright, we're gonna go ahead and move on
We got one more story for you guys
Before we get to the classic game of the week
And that story has to do with something
We sort of talked about last week
Don't know if you heard, but apparently
A leaked GameStop ad
Has revealed that a black Wii bundle
Is on its way
Who would have thought? I had never
Heard about this
Yes, this black Wii will contain a Wiimote
And MotionPlus, and Wii Sports, Wii Sports
Resorts, all for $200
However, it's supposed to be coming out
May 4th, which differs from an earlier
Report, but the interesting thing is that
I'm sorry, the
Ad is not supposed to go up until May 4th
But it got leaked, the debut of this system
I'm sorry, is May 9th
Which differs from the earlier report
Canada's supposed to get it on May 23rd
Which is interesting because May 23rd is the
Date that had originally been reported
And my source was not Canadian, thank you very much
So don't know what happened there
But could also be that
More is to come because Nintendo
Has yet to make any official announcement
You have to keep in mind, all of this is
Still rumor, it's just that now instead of
Some schmo on an internet radio show saying something
Now there's a picture to prove it
It's coming, whereas everybody outside of the
US is rolling their eyes and saying move on
With it, we already have the black Wii here
Well, it's news here
Anyhow, Nintendo is
Pissed
They commented actually on what's
Going on here, well no, they didn't comment
They made threats which caused
GameStop to comment
Here's an email
I love this because this whole email
Is about stop leaking stuff
And then the email gets leaked
That's my favorite, so here it is, here's the email
Let me read the email that went out to all the stores
As you know
There is a lot of rumor and speculation about various
New products and titles launching this year
One of these is the black Wii
Various blogs and internet sites
Are raising awareness about this product
GameStop stores and associates should not
Proliferate these rumors
Today you received pop, I guess that's what
POP, what is that?
Point of purchase advertising
Whatever
For your windows regarding the black Wii
Somehow a picture of this appeared on the internet
Somebody snapped it with her camera phone
It's not that hard to figure out
It may seem cool to be in the know
And feel compelled to share something like this
Nothing can be further from the truth
All activity like this does is hurt our reputation
With publishers and manufacturers
And potentially hurts our company
Until Nintendo decides to announce their product
There was capitalized, that's why I shouted it
There should be no discussion of it with customers
Period
If they ask, it's not appropriate to comment on
Speculation and rumor should be the answer
That's dumb
So in other words you should just confirm it
Just say I don't know
Here's an excuse that people will believe
I work at a game store, I don't know
Don't believe that
Anyway, the POP should be secured
In the back room and left there until further notice
Any violation of these will be treated
With the most aggressive consequences
I believe strongly in the field organization
But I am as disappointed as I have been
In my tenure here and how we are handling this
I am trusting that your professionalism
Will result in no further issues
I got two words for you, BITCH
PLEASE
Well here's the funny thing about it
If you didn't want news
On this to get out until May 4th
Then maybe you should have sent out the materials
I don't know, May 2nd?
I mean come on, if you're gonna pay these guys
Next to nothing
And let's face it, these employees at GameStop
Don't make enough money to shut up
Right?
I mean
You shouldn't be telling the whole world
That the Black Week is coming out if you don't want people to say
And I love how they put, oh it hurts
Our relationship with Nintendo
Yeah I'm sure Nintendo's gonna go
Oh we're not gonna ship product to our largest
Partner
Actually Loki, they did make that threat
Apparently that is the rumor going around
Nintendo did make the threat to pull all of its
Products from GameStop stories
You know what I have to say to Nintendo over that?
BITCH PLEASE
It would never happen
Never happen
What other game stores are there?
I mean
You're gonna just rely on Walmart
And Target and all that for your sales
I mean come on
That is an empty threat
If I've ever heard one
Maybe they'll send us a decent quantity of product then
Cause we service all the independent guys
And they seem to fuck us over all the time
I would love to see
The big gorilla in the corner
GameStop get fucked over once
Or twice
Yeah you're kinda sitting there going
Leak more, leak more, hee hee hee
It's not gonna do anything
GameStops leak information all the time
Not only do you leak information all the time
I'm sure that they're the source
Of a lot of the leaked games
That appear on the internet as well
So
Oh well
Things get leaked
Trust no one
God look at the music industry
I mean stuff
I mean CDs get leaked
Weeks before their release date on the internet
And you know what they say about
When something hits the internet, it's done
Everybody's got it now
Once it's been put on the internet
It is not coming off
Period
Anyhow
So yeah the black Wii is coming, big surprise
Five minutes of fame and an eternity on the internet
Well here's the thing, the only reason why
They probably didn't want it leaked
For the stupid reason anyways is
That's gonna hurt the sales of the Wii right now
Because people are like why the fuck am I gonna
Pay $1.99 for the Wii
When I can get the Wii with Wii Sports Resort
You know for the same price
But, but, but, but, but retailers
Are already doing that
We had a story a couple weeks ago about Walmart
Was already selling this as a bundle and I believe
Yeah they already have it
What's Nintendo's problem?
Bitch please
I don't know
All I can say is
That my Wii's been gathering dust for
Five months
I would love to see that meeting
Where somebody at GameStop says that to Reggie
Fils-Aime's face, bitch please
I still wanna borrow your Wii Fit
Maybe I wanna use it
If you're not using it
Yeah sure
Okay thank you
Anyhow let's move on
Spyro in chat says wait it's already here
Yeah that's my other thing is that like
In all the rest of the world
Like the UK and what doesn't even Canada
Have the Black Wii at this no no
Cause it's supposed to come out May 23rd
Pretty much everywhere but the US and Canada
Has already had the Black Wii
They'll announce it like tomorrow okay
I mean they're gonna make the announcement soon
It's retarded that they're not
Maybe on the 4th I don't know why they wait till Tuesday
But it's just gonna be an announcement
And whoopty shit
Okay seriously
Really a color change that's really
Gonna get people to buy the Wii
That didn't before I would buy it
But if only it were black
Going to comments from our chat room
Chat.orangelaungeradio.com
ActDeaf says to Nintendo, you mad?
Rama says
Is that sky getting sassy?
Mhmm
Frisbee says Nintendo
And Tigerclaw says
A Black Wii would be nice but it's not gonna
Hide all the dust it will collect turning it into a
White Wii ha should be more of like a
Grayish Wii but I get your point that's true
It's gonna be like the PS3's
Little dust magnets
Good times good times
Hey it's that part of the show where we're going
To speaking of dusty things we're gonna jump
Into Dark Sakura's vault
And pull out a video game
It's a classic
It's time to bring a game up from the
Vault of History and deem it as a
True classic that you kids need
To respect and adore and play some of
This week it's Dark Sakura's classic
Game of the week
Dark Sakura what game did you pick for us this week?
I picked a sequel
Rob
I picked Dodonpachi
Dodonpachi can't say I've
Heard of this game let's check it out what's Dodonpachi
You haven't heard of Dodonpachi?
I don't think so
We're like one of the classic cave shooters
As in the company that gave us
Es-ba-ba-ba-ba-luga whale
I'm sorry Es-ba-galuda
But I didn't play all of their games
Was this released in the US?
What system was this on?
I played Dodonpachi in the arcade
It was
Published by Atlas
But yeah
For systems it came out on
Let's see
I'm trying to remember
I think there was
Wasn't there
I don't remember if it was arcade only
It couldn't have been arcade only
Because I know that this
And I think that
Dodonpachi
Came out in the arcade
Only
Because I really don't remember
Playing this at home I've just had
Main ROMs
It was also on the Saturn
And the original Playstation
Now that I think about it
I think it's the Saturn version
I've never heard the easy web
I don't know what that is
Anyway
The original Dodonpachi
Was sort of like an 8 year training mission
Where you shoot all your friends to death
And then
There's another twist in this one
But I'm not going to really get much into it
But you have different fighters
You have your type A
Which is a narrow stream of shots
You have B
Which is a helicopter that has
Guns forward and side guns
And then type C
You've got different guns
Lasers, bombs, all kinds of different stuff
Different power ups
You get shot mode and laser mode
Different collectible items where you can get
Power to increase your
Guns and lasers
Bombs where you get more bombs
MP
Appears when you've lost all your lives
So when you continue you can pick that up
And you start back at full strength
Which is also in Espegaluda
And in
Another game
That's supposed to be even harder
Than that
I set a link aside
To get the name of it
You also
Now this is something else that
Totally incorporated into
Espegaluda
Later on is that you can get
Stars
For
Killing
A boss
An end boss
And their bullets are converted into stars
And you get 100 points
And then you get a giant star when you get 10,000 points
For a multi-part boss
And then
A pentagon
That gives you 300 points
But you only find them on the ground
And by the way the other game
That I am thinking of
Is
Mushihime Sama
Which is
Like bullet hell
Just watch the last boss
For that if you want your brain to explode
It's really freaking difficult
But I like my brain
You've also got a maximum
Mode in this
Where if you
Trigger a bomb when all of your bomb slots
Are full and then your
Score increases
By 220 points
Per 1 60th of a second
Yeah
And so you start off with a 2 multiplier
And you increase by 1 for every successive
Bomb collected in maximum mode
So it's pretty crazy
And you also have a get point system
Where you have a combo gauge
And you get
Increased number of points
From enemies larger hit counts
It's pretty complex
It's got other stuff so you've got different
Areas in the game
But area 7
You can only get to
By entering the second loop
Which is done by
Completing the first 6 areas on
1 credit
And doing any of these
Following requirements where you lose
2 lives
Or depending on which one you lose
For type A you have to have a maximum
Hit count of 270 hits
Type B 300 and type C 330
Or score at least 50 million points
At the end of area 6
Or collect all 13 B's
For 4 of the 6 areas
And the second loop has
The same areas
Same bosses
But you have many many many more bullets
And giant mechanical B's
Different
And then you get the actual
Real boss of the game
You've got different bonuses
So you get stuff for
Pentagon's getting the stars
Boss hits
No miss
In the second loop you get
10 million points for each
Reserve fighter
So you've got different endings too
If you don't get the
Second loop access
You're congratulated by the DonPachi Corps
For being brave
If you get everything
The mechanized aliens
Are your own comrades
Although
The
International release says it's a lost fleet
But
They're actually trying to stop
You
So
Once everything is done
They're all ordered
To kill you
And that's when you start the second loop
So going through it again
The whole point of DonPachi
Is to annihilate all the human
Beings in the world
Awesome
Pretty pretty crazy huh?
Yeah I'm looking at the screens of this
It's definitely bullet hell
God there's so many of these games
That's not even bad Rob
That is not even bad
It just goes to show I suck at these games
Because I would fail at this so miserably
I've been bouncing from YouTube to YouTube
This is like stage 2-3 I think
And yeah I would not beat this
Rob you need to find
The final boss
I believe SSJ100Matt actually linked that
In our chat room
It's very resourceful
Here it is the hardest video game boss ever
Let me fast forward a little bit here
This is nuts you don't need to fast forward all that much
It starts off hard
Isn't that gorgeous?
This is ridiculous
This is just retarded stupid
There's a video up of a person
No missing on it not getting hit
And keep in mind
The final boss in Escaluda on iPhone
Releases
Not quite as many bullets
The way these games work you can only get hit
In that little glowing spot right there
That's it
That's bullet hell
Ridiculous
And I like that it talks to you the whole time
Just like it does in Escaluda
Sorry
But yeah
Cave is evil
For throwing bullets up our noses
So yeah there was
A special version
The campaign version or DDP Blue Rom
That has
A very limited print
Of the game that was given to winners
At a Dodonpachi contest
That Cave had
It has
The same game it's harder and has a hyper mode
In it which
Actually shows up later in Dodonpachi
Dialjo
A blue title screen
Very very hard to get
And actually
One
There's actually two
That have confirmed to exist
That one of them belongs to
The
Current world holder for Dodonpachi
So
But yeah
There were of course
The other versions too
Like the Saturn and
PlayStation
I was trying to remember if it was Dodonpachi or Dodonpachi
And that game
I've only ever really played it in the arcade
Although I think I have it on Saturn
In one of my collections somewhere
But yeah, pretty crazy
And for the record
You want to play 2D games on the Saturn
They look better
Alright, there it is your classic video game of the week
Dodonpachi
Going to comments from our chat room
Shao Ran says
Bullet hell is all about patterns
Beauty, thought, and bullet hell
As there are no things superior to beauty and thought
Kevin DDR says
Sky 2-3 means
It's the second loop
You have to beat the game with certain conditions to even get to that
Well, that ain't happening
I'll tell you that
And then Shao Ran follows up and says
Yeah, once you get grazing down, bullet hell games aren't that hard
It's just about memorization
Just like any other old Japanese game
Frisbee says
Bullet hell is almost like a maze game
I guess I can see that
Just interesting
Alright, I'm just not very good at those games
Like, the last bullet hell game I played
Was the You Will Die
Which was by one of the other all games hosts
Making his own game on XNA
And I suck at it
Alright
Let's go do our break
We're going to take a quick break, we'll be right back
There's plenty more to come tonight
Listless, speaking of friends on all games
One of our podcasting buddies is going to join us
For Listless later
There was huge news out of Bungie this week
We're going to talk about that in the next segment
Final Fantasy 5 and Final Fantasy 6 remakes
Possibly, maybe
We'll see after a quick break
So stay tuned, don't go anywhere
We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody and welcome back to another episode
Of Orange Lounge Radio
It's part B of our show
Already in progress
On May 2nd of 2010
We have plenty more gaming news
To get to this hour
And Listless tonight
And I'll tell you the topic right now
What we're going to be doing tonight
What Capcom versus series should they do next
Or maybe I should actually say
Versus Capcom would be correct
Because you know, you've had Tatsunoko versus Capcom
Marvel versus Capcom
What should they do next
We're going to find out with the definitive list
In a few more minutes here at Orange Lounge Radio
But first we have some rapid quick
News, there's so much to talk about this week
We don't have time to talk about everything
But we can at least give some shout outs
To some other gaming news highlights this week
And as somebody in chat points out
I should say this real quick
ActDeaf says it's episode live 365
Because this is episode 365 of our show
Do not speak that name ever again
Just kidding
Remember we went to the live 365 awards
Good times, good times
We went twice
What? Hey what?
That's what I did during the live 365 awards
Oh yeah, when they, oh god
How could I forget when they forgot our name
When they were going over, yeah we got nominated
One year for live 365 station
Of the year, like that's a pretty big honor
Because there was what, like 11,000 stations on live 365
We were one of the five nominated
For station of the year, and when what's-her-name
Betty whatever was reading the
Nominees, she forgot OLR
And you just hear, and god
I wish I could find that recording, I think it's long
Gone in the recycle bin or whatever
But somebody actually had a recording
Because they played the award show live
And a bunch of our listeners were listening
And you could hear Loki in the background
She goes, we have all, or she goes
And the nominees are
Rockland, da da da, and whatever stations
And she goes, and the winner is, and you hear in the background
Hey!
No, it was funny, it was
Most unlikely to be on radio or something
Like that, and they had like an 80's station
Because you don't ever hear 80's
Stations on the radio
Ever. That's where we lost to the station that plays
Nothing but porn music all day long
Got nominated three
Years in a row for those fuckers, never won
One, oh well, thanks for trying
I got speakers. That's right, you won some type of like
Playing bingo. Bingo thing or something stupid
Alright, so yeah
That was good times, so
I really wish I had a recording of that
With Loki in the background, hey!
And then she goes, oh, oh yeah, yeah, and on orange
Orange, orange, orange, and we just gave each other
That look of, well, we didn't win
I'm outta here
Drove all this way for this
And then they drove up their fees
By like 300% and we
Got the fuck out, and now we're here at All Games
You know what, it worked out for the better, because coming over to
All Games, I think got us new listeners
Because, you know, we had
Kind of a cultish audience
And Scott Rubin and Bobby Blackwolf
And all the people at All Games had a bit of a cultish
Audience, so when we married these
Cults together, it was a good thing
It was a super cult
Yes, it was a super cult, uber cult
So thanks to all you little cultists
For sticking with us
Over the years, alright, back to some gaming news
Loki
Yes, so real quick, if you wanna be
Iron Man on Playstation
Home, it'll be a lot easier than having to
Steal a suit from Stark Enterprises
Yes, you can actually play, they have a little
Game where you can fly around
As Iron Man
And apparently it
Debuted earlier last week
On Thursday
Apparently
It was part of the Out
I'm surprised that they actually have
A space, but
Audi, I guess, has a space there
And they're teaming up with Paramount for that
No actual Iron Man themed space
I mean, it sort of is, but it's part of
Audi's
And then I guess, oh
That's funny
Unfortunately though, it is exclusive to the
European Playstation Network, so
That sucks for most of
Our listeners
This is kind of cool
Someone made a Flash game
That kind of crosses a bunch of
Different 8-bit game
Heroes with Super Mario Brothers
And it's called Super Mario Crossover
And it features such
Playable characters as, of course you can play as Mario
Why would you want to
Link, Mega Man, Samus,
Simon Belmont, and Bill from
Contra
And that is awesome
And I'll be playing that later instead of the
Unicorn game
And then finally, APB
Has been slated to be coming out now
On June 29th
And they also kind of talked a little bit about
How their pricing structure is going to go
As well, it's really cool
I like the way that they're doing it, I mean
I think it's going to be pretty sweet
Instead of paying a monthly fee
As you would with most MMOs, you pay for time
So for example, when you buy the game
You get 50 hours
And how you use that
Is up to you, if you play a lot
Great, if you don't play a lot
No big deal
And once those are up, you have the option to purchase
20 more hours for $7
Or you can do 30 days of unlimited access
For $10, or
90 days, or 180 day passes
As well, and they haven't given the prices on those
In addition to extra playtime
Oh, in addition, extra playtime
Can be earned through different accomplishments
In the game
So that's pretty awesome, and I have to say
You know, I don't really hop on the
MMO bandwagon
Because I don't have time to play games, but
If it's as a pain as I go
I'm interested
Definitely, especially since the game looks like
Grand Theft Auto, so
I'm all over that, and it's
And it's real time worlds, man
It's a crackdown, and I really am sad that they didn't
Do the second crackdown
Thank god, WoW doesn't charge by the hour
I'd be in debt
Well, I mean, they do have that option
Though, where you can buy unlimited access
For 30 days for $10
Which is still cheaper than WoW
So, it's not bad
Alright, well, here's a game that I think
Loki might be interested in, I think Dark Soccer
I don't know why, this seems like a Dark Soccer kind of game, too
THQ and Syfy
The TV network are getting together to make
A new game
Sadly, it's not a Caprica game, but what it is
It's a Ghost Hunters Academy game
Here's the problem I have with that
It's Ghost Hunters Academy, and they've done so many spinoffs
Of the Ghost Hunters show
It's retarded now
And they've become, they've sold out
Okay, they've sold out
And then jumped the shark
Bought a shark to jump over, I guess
Well, if you want to jump the shark with them
Ghost Hunters Academy is coming out for the iPhone and iPad, of course
And the DS
Is the game you get to try out
To be on the team
If you want to be a ghost hunter
Who wants to be a ghost hunter?
That's what the game's about
Just saying
By the way, no details about actual gameplay
Hopefully it plays like Ghostbusters
The old school game that was on
Commodore and NES
Don't cross the streams, Marshmallow Man, etc
Also, apparently
There's stuff afoot in the Mega Man universe
No surprise there
Mega Man's been having a little bit of a renaissance
Thanks to Mega Man 9 and Mega Man 10
Apparently there is a Mega Man universe
We talked about this before
But now we might know what this is actually connected to
Apparently
There was a little tease dropped in another podcast
Called Bit Transmission
And Seth Killen
Was the guest from Capcom
He said that Mega Man still has some surprises in store
For everybody
Quote, it's good, I don't want to say nobody has seen it coming
Somebody may have seen it coming
But it excited me and when I heard about the project
I was like, holy crap, that's rad
I actually haven't seen anything that's going on with the project right now
But the idea was exciting
This is still kicking around as a concept
But there are exciting ideas in the Mega Man space
It's a six player co-op
Xbox Live
2D game
And this week they're gonna be like
Shit, someone beat us to it
Damn it
MU Konami
We all know it would be Konami copying them
Oh, I went there
Hey look, no seriously, think about it
I don't want to say nobody has seen it coming
So here's my thought
And especially if the game is called Mega Man Universe
Is this finally
That game
Oh yes, that Mega Man game
With all
Of the robot bosses in it
At once
That'd be awesome
That would be so fucking awesome
That's more awesome than I think I can handle
I might just explode
We'll see
Meanwhile, this is also awesome and I didn't realize that
By the way, Dark Tetsuya
Oh, thanks to the lag
I just beat him to it
But he just said in chat
I'm calling it now, Mega Man Battle Royale
With all the bosses
I called it 30 seconds ago
Anyway, speaking of games
That sound really awesome
I'm going to pass out from how awesome it is
ModNation Racers is on its way out
I never did play the beta, so I don't know if it's actually that good
I got in the beta and never played it
You dumbass
I would have played it, I didn't get in the beta
I didn't try hard enough
I didn't realize the beta was coming out so soon
It's coming out at the end of May
There was a commercial for it on TV the other day
I'm seeing more and more Playstation commercials on TV
What's up with that?
Of course I've been watching more South Park
Maybe it's related, I don't know
Anyhow, in ModNation Racers
You will be able to play as Sackboy
Will be one of the racers in ModNation Racers
And if this surprises you
I don't know what rock you've been living under
Because this series has been getting all of these
Transplants from other Sony franchises
So this is kind of a duh
We don't know if it's part of a pre-order bonus or what
But probably it is
So there you go, there's a little teaser out there featuring Sackboy
And all that fun stuff
Dark Soccer, what you got for us?
I have some stuff, Rob
Which is as cool as every freaking Mega Man boss at once
Sims 3
Is coming to Playstation 3, Xbox 360
Wii, and DS this fall
EA is working on console versions
And should have different features
Like karma power
Depending on whether you can get lucky
Or have Epic fail
Yeah
Which actually still reminds me that I need to completely
Uninstall all my Sims 3 stuff
What?
I just spilled water all over myself
You're a big boy, Rob
I need a sippy cup
I could go get you one
He's getting wet over that news
Literally, I just got wet over the Mega Man news
I'll be right back, I need a towel
Okay
So also though, coming up for Rock Band
We have new download content
We have No Doubt Tragic Kingdom
To download
Which are
Basically all
We have the songs on there
Including different people
And ended on this
Happy now see you then 16
The climb tragic kingdom world go round
And you can do it
And then individual songs is
Orient the according to you and picture me broken
Dearest I'm so sorry
And then
We also have our UK
Download games
Just to mention what's coming out
We have Hamster Ball
For Playstation 3
Yeah, Hamster Ball
Which looks kind of Monkey Ball
Like to me
And then
Alpha Bounce
For DSiWare
500 points
Which just looks like a glorified
Arcanoid to me
The Will of Dr. Frankenstein
For WiiWare
And
It looks very Nintendo 64-ish
It's actually a cut down version
Of the island of Dr. Frankenstein
And then
We've got a few others
There's Earthworm Jim for DSiWare
500 points
Um, which you know
Freaking Earthworm Jim, so hey
I loved Earthworm Jim, it was cute
I loved how the titles, credits would burp
Sound like me earlier in the show tonight
We have Lead and Gold Gangs of the Wild
West, which is for Playstation Network
And Steam
That would do it
Alright, let's get into some Twitter topics
Every week we solicit your tweets
At Twitter.com slash OLR
And we like to pick some of our favorite tweets
And read them here on the show
So let's get into the tweets
I gotta admit, they're not always on topic
You guys, but uh
Whatever, we're flexible
Uh, let's see
Souture in Twitter
Says, uh, what I've been playing
Harvest Moon, hero of Leaf Valley
Fun, but frequent, those short
Loading screens. What do you think of Harvest Moon?
I tried to get into that series
On the GameCube, I think there was a game on the GameCube
I couldn't really get into it, I don't know
Like, I was just more into Animal Crossing
I wasn't, maybe it was too much
Fun with Cows!
Maybe it was too much micromanaging for me
I think it's one of those games I really need to give another shot
Like, I don't think I gave it a fair shot, to be honest
Fun with Cows!
No, you know, Jessica played it a whole bunch
When I would hangover
And I was just like, look, my cow loves me!
Okay
You know, Harvest Moon kind of strikes me as like a Facebook game
Like, I'm kind of surprised it's not on Facebook
Uh, I'm surprised
Especially with the success of what, uh, Farmville
Farmville? Like, seriously
Why are they not suing over this?
I don't know
Uh, let's see, more tweets
TheShadowSniper tweets us
OLR, you guys are awesome!
Do you agree?
No. Most days
I'm awesome every day, Rob
Uh, KnightsOfBlaze says
Here's Twitter topic for tonight
Blur or SplitSecond, which will be better?
SplitSecond
Tough. I haven't played the SplitSecond demo yet
SplitSecond looks awesome
Blur, I think, would be fun
Because people like playing online
But I don't really give a crap about online
So I'm all about SplitSecond
Plus, they have that new survival mode now
Which looks all sorts of awesome
So, that'd be the first game I'm gonna play
They may check out Blur later on
But both of them to me win the I don't care rating
They both look awesome to me
But I'm gonna say Blur just because it's the one
Loki didn't pick
So now it's officially a tie
I'll let Dan get whatever he wants to and then I'll go
Oh, that's neat
One for Blur, one for SplitSecond, one for I don't give a fuck
I mean, you have like
You have a game that looks like Burnout with explosions
Or you have, you know, Mario Kart meets
Project Gotham
It's tough
Both games look good actually
But we'll see, you know, a lot of it has to do with the controls too
Keep that in mind
So we'll see how they control
Blur controls pretty good, I'll check out SplitSecond soon
But I remember playing it at E3 last year and it was pretty cool
I wonder if they'll have the same damn demo this year
Oh no, the game will be out by E3 this year
Game's out pretty soon
Tigerclaw sends us a couple stories
I'll go ahead and read this one here
Because the other one I think Bobby got on his show
So let's talk about this one here
Um
Oh, I love this
This is so appropriate what Tigerclaw sent us
Apparently a couple of game testers
At Activision as identified
By one of the vending machines in the background
They had a speed eating competition
Of the KFC Double Down
Polishing it off in
57.97 seconds
That's just under a minute
Apparently it was sent
In some type of video over to Kotaku
Not yet verified by Twin Galaxies
LOL, so there it is
You can actually see the guys eating the Double Down
And um
These little bastards are skinny
That's what I don't like, like if I ate that Double Down
In 60 seconds, I would gain weight
These little bastards are still skinny
You guys can go to hell
Alright, uh
I'm just jealous
Let's see, um
Sponstwang says, can anyone make me
Anything OLR slash gamer
Related I can wear on my 5K race
In a couple of weeks
I'm already going to wear a Pokewalker
I don't know, Dark Soccer is the
Seamstress of the bunch
I can
Make you a keychain
I don't know if Misty
Is still in the business of making
OLR keychains and stuff
But you might want to try talking to Misty
Because I know she used to have some of that stuff
Like, you know, beaderies and necklaces
And things like that
Yeah, I've been talking about that for years
Nothing yet, nothing yet, maybe soon
Uh, let's see
DarkTetsuya wanted to give a big fat plug
To his new series on our website
I, uh, love this
New series that he came up with
I think it's a great addition to our website
It's called A Look Back
We kind of need to give it a better name though
A Look Back, I mean, don't get me wrong
The name suffices for what it is, it is a look back
But we need something a little more hardcore
Than a look back
You can look back, bitches
Maybe not
But anyway, regardless of what it's called
The system is really good
It's A Look Back, the MSX is the first in the series
And he talks about what the MSX was all about
Because, um, it's, uh
Cool because the MSX is a
Console we didn't get here
And so you can read a little more about it
So, that's kind of nice
BlackWolf suggests rear view mirror
I kind of like that
Let's see
I said he's not totally, um
I like that rose colored rear view mirror
Anyway, uh
Let's see, Blue Swim sends us
A tweet saying
Rob, are you going to get behind the
Bieber ruined Twitter trending topic
Happy that people are revolting
See, I'm just ahead of my time
Because I commented on that whole thing a couple weeks ago
About how I don't want to use Twitter anymore
Because I really can't justify using a site
That Justin Bieber is a trending topic
On every single day
I'm glad that people are finally revolting
Take back Twitter!
From Justin Bieber and all his frickin' mouthy fans
And, uh, there you have it
Those are Twitter topics for tonight
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
Or just ignore it
I can't ignore it
Because you got the Bieber fear
It's not in my nature
S2100Matt says the look back idea
Was actually his idea
Oh, my bad
Sorry, Matt
I hate the series
It just, you know, needs a more hardcore name
That's right
A look back to the extreme
A look back extreme mix
Alright
Anyhow, let's go on to a couple more stories here
Listless coming up in just a little bit
With a special guest, Loki
As I'm sure a lot of people thought
Maybe hell froze over earlier this week
But, um
Bungie has entered in a ten year partnership
With Activision
Um
Yeah, apparently they're gonna publish the next
Or all games based on, um, Bungie's
Next big action game universe
And, um
They're looking to publish on multiple
Platforms, so it's no longer gonna be, you know
Xbox exclusive anymore
And, um
It kinda makes you wonder
Bungie, have you not been reading the news?
I mean, seriously?
Yeah, but there's a huge difference, Loki
I think you made the mistake a lot of people are making
Activision did not buy
Bungie
Activision has a publishing deal with Bungie
Activision is basically getting free money out of this deal
I mean, all they're doing, they're putting out
You know, they'll do the marketing
They do everything outside the actual development of the game
Alright
That's what this agreement's all about
I honestly don't think this is a big deal
If Activision had bought Bungie, then yes
Oh my gosh, doom and gloom, Bungie, what are you smoking?
You all are high
But, it's just a publishing deal
I mean, they had to sign with somebody
They weren't gonna self-publish
And what's funny is, uh
Bungie's Harold Ryan looks like
Brendan Fraser, he even has that
Really creepy smile
I didn't realize Brendan Fraser had a creepy smile
Yeah, he's just creepy all around
Um, so yeah
So they're gonna be publishing their next game
They'll work out exactly what the next game is actually
Gonna be
But that will probably be coming up at E3
Probably at E3, and then
It's also probably gonna help with that void
Of people that
Hate on Activision right now, although
I can't imagine it's gonna really affect their sales that much
Including the Call of Duty franchise
Cause people bitch, but people still buy
It would be interesting to know about this agreement
If the Final Cut
Arrangement is still with Bungie
You know Final Cut, so to speak
Or if Activision gets to make changes to games they want to publish
I doubt that's in the agreement
Kinda Bungie, I imagine, got to do whatever the hell
They wanted with this
So I don't think this is gonna be bad news at all
I really don't
You know, and I've been as critical of Activision as the next guy
And so forth, but I just think this is just
Bungie had to sign with someone
And Activision makes as good of a sense as anyone else
If it had been EA
People would have still been like, oh my god
I can't believe it
It could have been Konami
Oh my god
Doesn't matter
I think Bungie just wanted to
Sign with somebody
You knew it was gonna be somebody here in the US
Cause they're a US development company
So it wasn't gonna be Konami or any of those
SNK or any of those overseas companies
It was gonna be an American company
And that pretty much leaves EA and Activision
Pick one
Alright, anyhow
Moving on, Square Enix
And one of the games they get requested about a lot
Is Final Fantasy 5 and Final Fantasy 6
On the DS
Cause you might remember they had an epic, epic remake
Of Final Fantasy 3
That was followed by an epic remake of Final Fantasy 4
When I say epic remake, they were done in the more 3D-ish
Style of the newer Final Fantasy games
Which is pretty awesome
So the big question on everybody's mind is
Where the hell is Final Fantasy 5
And really Final Fantasy 5 is just a stepping stone
To Final Fantasy 6
Because we want our opera scene in fully rendered 3D
Thank you very much
But apparently
It's not in development just yet
There was apparently a Twitter thing
Going on earlier this week
And one of the producers of Square Enix
Shinji Hashimoto
Was quoted on Twitter saying that
They are undecided about
A downloadable port of Second Densetsu 3
And the mobile RPG Everheart Odyssey
And then he also said
For Final Fantasy 5 and 6
There are technical issues as well
So at present these are also
Undecided
Not sure what those technical issues are
I wonder if it's space
It's a much shorter game than 5 and 6
And I wonder if they maybe have just maxed out
Those damn cartridges
I wouldn't think so
I don't think so
Well Amiga777
In chat says Square Enix spare us
The FMV theatrics and give us some awesome gameplay
I agree I would sacrifice
The full motion theatrics
For some uber 3D-ness
But I don't know
At the same time
I'm okay if they spend the resources just developing
Something new you know
Although I don't know I'm torn
Because the 3 and 4 remakes were pretty hot
But at the same time I'm not like
Ah they need to do 5 and 6
Or you know if you just want to I don't know
Port say for example 4, 5 and 6
Onto a DS cartridge
And don't even worry about upgrading it
I'd be fine with that
Maybe it's something they're going to do for the 3DS
Hmm?
I don't know
Alright guys well we
Are going to get into a segment here on the show
Called Listless
Yay Listless
Weee
And for tonight's Listless
We got to get one of our friends here on the phone
So we're going to make a little
Outbound call right now
Tonight's Listless topic what Capcom
Versus series should they do
Next
Does somebody want to explain Listless how Listless works
While I give our guest a call tonight
Well the way that it works
Is that we go around all of us
And we each pick a game
We pick 3 of them in
Order or pick a subject
You know something that we would like to be on the list
Not a game tonight but something
And then what happens is we leave it
To the chat room to pick
Um
Well we each take one off of the list
And then we leave it to the chat room to pick the winner
That's right so if you want to help
Vote for the winner and remember guys
This is the definitive list
If this list is written there's no arguing
It's done
It's the definitive list it's a highly scientific
Process but in order to play the game
We need 4 people so we're going to
Call up a special guest right now
Let me down the music here
While we give our guest a call here
Hopefully he's standing by I told him it would be 8 o'clock
Otherwise
We'll just open it up to somebody else on Skype
I suppose
One ringy dingy
Live radio it's fun two ringy dingys
Watch he's not going to pick up
Hello? Hi! Is this Jon?
Hi who's this? Oh my god
It's crazy radio guy hey Jon
Oh hey I totally forgot you were calling
Hi
You ass
What are you doing did I interrupt something?
Ladies and gentlemen
I have a bunch of friends from Securicon over and we're
Playing Halo and drinking
You might be a little pissy but I remembered the topic
For listless tonight
Well folks let me introduce
Because I didn't say who was coming on the show tonight
This is our good buddy Jon Breslull
From Undersedation Live
Saturday nights here at All Games Radio
What are you like 7 o'clock 8 o'clock
Midnight now?
8 o'clock Pacific 11 o'clock
Eastern
Did you know that one of your old co-hosts
Said that I sound like a straight version of you
Who is that? Jenna?
Or Jessica?
When was she on the show? Yeah Jessica
I haven't talked to her in years
She's actually, whenever I take off from
U.S.L. she's going to be hosting for me now
Oh wow
How come I wasn't invited to be a guest host?
I see how it is
Okay well you can bring that up with Travis
I will I will
I'm going to be my Star Trek Online character just to find Travis
And beat the shit out of him
Was Travis a human? I have to be a Klingon
I don't know I don't play Star Trek Online
I play WoW
I don't know because certain somebody named Travis
Took me off of Facebook
Travis Donovan you're a bitch
Punch him in the balls
That's always a good solution for Travis
You know what though?
Facebook does weird things
I've lost friends mysteriously
He may not have done that on purpose
If he did he's got some drama
Alright here we go
Let's do this
Hey tell the people in the background to shut up
We're trying to do a radio show
Hey people in the background please stop masturbating
Alright
How was Securicon by the way?
Did you have fun?
It was a lot of fun
I made a lot of friends
I made a lot more friends and it was just a great time
Wait you have friends?
Definitely look forward to 2011
Oh good times good times
Aren't we supposed to be playing a game online soon or something?
Was I what?
Never mind
I think I was talking about something I'm not supposed to talk about yet
Alright
Let's get into something else
Get into the list list
You know tonight's topic is
What Capcom vs series or should I say vs Capcom series
Should they do next?
We're going to go around and get your top 3 answers
Breslow we'll start with you
Your number 3 answer
What Capcom vs series should they do next?
I'm throwing the political card on here
Because I think this is the most important one
Since I get to go first
And I'm surprised I haven't done this
Capcom vs Midway
That would be fun
So like Mortal Kombat characters
Yeah so you'd have a bunch of Mortal Kombat characters
Against the Street Fighter characters and such
I think that would be awesome
I'm actually rewording your answer to be Midway vs Capcom
Because it's always something vs Capcom
Just so you know
That was attractive
By the way, logical answer coming from Breslow
I mean this episode is full of shockers tonight
Alright
Who wants to go next?
Dark Sakura what do you want to pick for your number 3 answer?
Um
McDonaldland vs Capcom
Mayor McCheese
And the Grimace
And the Fry Guys
I fucking love it
The Grimace
And
Birdie the Early Bird
Hello?
Whatever happened in the McDonaldland characters?
Breslow?
It's McDonaldland vs Capcom
Is what it is
Oh our stream
I want Mayor McCheese as the boss
Apparently our stream died
And our thing is trying to reconnect right now
But we're going to keep recording for podcast sake
Shit but now our chatters
Can't hear to vote
We're going to hope
The chatters right now are saying
The all games stream vs Capcom
Because apparently we shut down
Alright we're back up
Alright so far we have Midway vs Capcom
And McDonaldland vs Capcom
Alright Loki
What is your number 3 answer tonight?
I was trying to be slightly serious here
So this is kind of obscure
For people who don't remember
But Paul Robertson vs Capcom
And to explain
Who Paul Robertson is
He's the guy that did the animation
Pirate Baby's Cabana Street Fight
And then also
Yes that one
That animation was such an amazing thing
Exactly and like
Devil eyes and just like
All sorts of crazy ass 8 bit
Animation stuff so
That would be kind of cool
Okay fair enough
Paul Robertson vs Capcom
It's better than Pirate Baby's Cabana Street Fight
vs Capcom
Alright my number 3 answer
I have picked Saturday Night Live
vs Capcom
Because
I just won an excuse to
Beat the shit out of any character Chris Kattan
Who I never played
And you know I think some of it would be kind of cool
You know your favorite SNL
Like the coneheads and the guys that
Bob their heads to what is love
Baby don't hurt me
SNL vs Capcom is my number 3 answer
Did you like that answer Bresloh?
I did
I beat the crap out of all the crappy skits
They've done from like 97 to 2003
I know it would be fun
Alright
Anyhow your number 2 answer
Bresloh and just to catch the folks up joining us
Because the feed was down so far we have
Midway vs Capcom
McDonaldland vs Capcom
Paul Robertson vs Capcom
And Saturday Night Live vs Capcom
What is your
Number 2 answer
Bresloh?
How bad would you want?
Jesus vs Capcom
So Jesus vs Capcom
You're not going to make it just
The Bible?
Bible vs Capcom
So you can play like Moses
And Jesus
What character
God would be the end boss
Who would be the end boss?
God
God would be the end boss
Bible vs Capcom
I love some of these answers in chat
I'm just cracking up
Sarah your number 2 pick
It was actually something on the serious end
I picked
Arc System Works vs Capcom
As in Guilty Gear and Blaze Blue
Ah okay
So you want your Blaze Blue and all that stuff vs Capcom
And the fighting
The fighting systems
Are pretty similar too
So I think it would be fun
I want to have Strider hear you
vs the little bad guy
Alright
Let's see, Loki what is your number 2
answer tonight?
You know I had to change one of my answers
Because of your SNL thing
I got to top that
Although that would be my number 1 answer
Now it's going to be a semi serious one
Konami vs Capcom
Because they have a lot of good 8-bit characters
That would be pretty awesome to bring over
You have different Contra characters
Hell you can put
Frogger in there if you want
Castlevania
I mean that would be pretty awesome
Alright
I'm also going to go with the super freaking
Obviously I was going to do
See I don't know if this would
Well I'm going to go with a different one
Because I already have a list just in case mine gets taken
Mine was kind of a Konami thing
But I'll go ahead and go in a different direction
I'm going to do the completely obvious and probably stealing someone else's answer
And why hasn't anyone thought of this yet
Nintendo vs Capcom
Hello
I'm a jackass Ronald Roberts
I mean hello
Mario, Samus
Pit, all the like
Super Smash Brothers Melee characters vs Capcom
Hello why is this not happening
Duh
Alright
Sounds like I took your answer didn't I Breslull
You did
My bad, well do you have a backup answer
Because we're ready for your number 1 answer
So far, let me recap what you think
So far the list is Midway vs Capcom
McDonaldland vs Capcom
Paul Robertson vs Capcom
SNL vs Capcom
Bible vs Capcom
Ark System Works vs Capcom
Konami vs Capcom
Nintendo vs Capcom
Breslull what is your number 1 answer
All games vs Capcom
Would you be one of the fighters in
I would and so would you
Bitch slap people silly
What would my special move be
It would be to bitch slap people silly
What would Dark Sakura's
special move be
Um
Throwing Guinness bombs at people
And Loki
Um
Throwing his number 7
ranking at uh
GTA um
What's it called at everybody
Alright
Dark Sakura
It's time for your number 1
answer, what is your number 1 answer
Blank vs Capcom
Taito
Could you imagine Bud and Bob
Getting like
Hadoken
What would their special move be
They'd just trap the opponent in a bubble
Yeah and pop them
That might be fun
They'd have special attacks like the water
Bubble
Boom
We're recording this
Remember it's only porn if you tape it
John blow your rape whistle
Alright back to the show
Anything else you want to say about Taito vs Capcom
Rainbow Islands
Loki your number 1 answer please
My number 1 answer is
Very obvious considering the
SNL thing
It's Nick at Nite vs Capcom
And of course
It's awesome because you have a fighting
game with Bill Cosby
Will Smith
From the Fresh Prince of Bel Air
John shut the fuck up
You're interrupting a professionally done radio
show by raping me
I just want you to know this
This is a bad idea
Hey
Do you think you could stop getting your
asshole raped by a woman
In time to do this show here
Actually the worst part is I'm getting my
asshole raped by a man
That's nothing new
Loki
Nick at Nite vs Capcom
Yes and I think the golden
girls was on there one time so that would be
pretty awesome
The monkeys were on there and could you imagine that fight
That would be pretty awesome
As long as Bea Arthur is a character I'm fine
Would Bea Arthur be a character?
Sure then I'm fine
My number 1 answer
I'm gonna totally
Black Wolf says Cosby's ultra
servant puddin' pop
I'm gonna go with a very obvious number
one that I'm surprised nobody has said yet
but I'm gonna win myself a lot of fans with this
one and my number 1 answer
Whedonverse vs
Capcom thank you very much
Dr. Horrible, Buffy the Vampire Slayer
Firefly
and Firefly
Jane vs Capcom
Jane vs Capcom that would be
funny
Joss Whedonverse vs Capcom
And when he comes out the first thing he says is
you're damaging my calm
Tell me that would not sell
But we also need the blue
Like I'll be in my bunk
But we also need like a mid
boss to be like the blue hand guys
from you know
I just want Elijah
Deuceku from Dollhouse to be a character
cause she's hot
Anyhow oh you are not
booing me chat room F you
F you all
Alright Becky just said that you were made of
win thank you Becky
Alright see somebody loves me
ass alright and some of the
suggestions from chat that didn't make
the cut
What the fuck alright
Doctor Who vs Capcom
Let's see what else was suggested
here in chat Disney vs Capcom
Duck Island vs Capcom
Power Rangers vs Capcom
Cooking Mama vs Capcom
Capcom vs Capcom
Mavis Beacon vs Capcom
Coco vs
Capcom
Wow DC vs
Capcom alright
Anyhow it's time now it's too
late your suggestions didn't make the cut
I'm sorry chat room that's just it's the it's
one of life's tough lessons is that
sometimes your account
What?
I said it sucks for those guys I know sucks
to be them alright well at least they're not getting
raped alright uh Bresl
uh here it is for your recap
we're gonna go around and take one off the
list alright Bresl so listen carefully
cause I'm not gonna read this a million times
Midway vs Capcom
McDonaldland vs Capcom
Paul Robertson vs Capcom
SNL vs Capcom
Bible vs Capcom
Arc System Works vs Capcom
Konami vs Capcom
Nintendo vs Capcom
All Games vs Capcom
and Whedon vs Capcom
Bresl which one of these
is not worthy of the list?
Nintendo vs Capcom
Oh you whore
why not
it'd be hard to go multiplatform
because it would turn into the Capcom characters
have to do button combinations and then you could
just stamp Falcon Punch
with the Nintendo characters
I suppose I will accept that logic
but you're still an asshole alright
Dark Sakura you're next
which one of these is not worthy of the list?
Bible vs Capcom
oh you just
just
not feeling Jesus
as a playable character huh?
I don't really give a crap about
Jesus in the game
alright fair enough
Loki which one of these is not worthy of the list?
uh
I'm gonna have to go with Midway vs Capcom
just because
you know I've seen the
Coogan videos with the
Mortal Kombat characters vs Street Fighter
it looks weird okay
I guess they could reanimate them
but it would just be weird
and besides Midway
is no longer around so
that's true it would be kinda hard to get the licensing wouldn't it
alright as far as me
which one of these is not worthy of the list?
I'm gonna have to say Paul Robertson vs Capcom
too obscure
too obscure sorry Loki
I'm sure it was funny but too obscure
see there's more coming in
Rob's Mom vs Capcom
Atlas vs Capcom
Fallout 3 vs Capcom
Prop 8 vs Capcom
alright
wait wait
the hall of presidents vs Capcom
animatronic
presidents vs Capcom
alright guys it is now
your time to vote
you are gonna place a vote via private message
to Sky with your number 1 and
number 2 answers please label them
number 1 and number 2 answers here's the list
McDonaldland vs Capcom
SNL vs Capcom
Arc System Works vs Capcom
Konami vs Capcom
Taito vs Capcom
Nick at Nite vs Capcom
and Whedon vs Capcom
John thanks so much for playing with us tonight
but we should let you go so you can get played with
some more by the folks there at your house
do you have anything last
you wanna say to our listeners tonight
press plugs
press plugs and into usl every saturday night
here on all games at 8 o'clock pacific
11 o'clock eastern
and if you're not listening to orange launch
radio live you're a terrible human being
well
thank you press lol
oh hey Rob I got one more thing to say
uh oh yeah
hold on
he just hung up
that was his last thing to say
I bet he thought that was funny
well I hope you get your
butthole torn open by that guy
alright let's move on
wow
I think that was the first on air rape that we had
going on during a fun happy say
I don't think that was the first on air rape
this show is on air rape
that's true we do kind of rape gaming news
every week
back in the day when we used to broadcast live
during some of those DDR parties
yeah that was
on air rape and I think that's where
big black cock came into play
alright
please more gaming news
darksagras save us
for call of duty fans
actually the next one coming out
has been named
it's call of duty
black ops coming out on
the 9th of November 2010
that's at least the European date
and they've confirmed co-op
for it so
you can play with your buddies together
killing people
and that's actually one
that I would be interested in I think
checking out is a black ops
game you know
instead of you know full on face front combo
you know combat you have
to be sneaky like solid snake
so
I
well I'm sure the fans
are just
all they're saying is it's a
Treyarch call of duty
so
um
alright so apparently
this is kind of interesting and scary at the same time
red faction
a wonderful
you know kind of sci-fi
action game from
Q and volition is being
turned into a TV
movie the problem is
it's being produced by sci-fi
the same folks that brought us
what was it
mega shark versus
giant octopus or whatever the hell
it was that's
scary I'm sorry how is this
a problem
I believe you just called
this a problem because it's gonna
suck the problem is the rumor I
heard that sci-fi is like picking up wrestling
and stuff now and they're not gonna do those movies
anymore that's a problem
they're all just
blending together every station does
not need wrestling okay
unless they're dressing up like space
aliens or people from
battle star galactica it does not
need to be on sci-fi there is nothing
science fiction about wrestling except for the plot
um
what the hell is that
watch the shark
through the plane
ah yes
it is so
this looks so fake I love it
condor airlines
and they had a
image or whatever a little picture
that someone made that talked about what
it would take physics wise for
the shark to do that it was just
retarded
ah yes high production
value right there
holy shit
that's the kind of stuff you make
in like high school how dare someone
try to take this from me
shark eating a
plane how dare you try to take that out of
my life anyways
so they're gonna be doing
possibly um
an ongoing series
as well if the movie does well so it's
expected to be um
coming out early 2011
and um
we'll see how it turns out cause
most movies that are based on video
games kinda suck and this one's
done by sci-fi who puts out movies that
pretty much always suck so
I don't know it's like um
a convergence of suck
a convergence of suck really
yes alright uh
well we'll see what happens uh good thing
they're not making a movie out of this but uh
cause I think it would be kinda boring but apparently
somebody has beat Bejeweled 2
yes who knew that Bejeweled 2
was beatable I sure didn't but Bejeweled 2
got beaten this week after
three years
that's right this guy Mike
Lady? Ladi? Ladi?
he probably gets called Lady poor guy
Mike Ladi I'm gonna say it's Ladi
uh apparently uh beat
Bejeweled 2 he played the same game
for 2205
hours and 51 minutes that
was a score of 2
billion 147 million
so on and so on points apparently
that's the point where the score display
just went to black and there's actually
a YouTube of it that's up um
and PopCap just said hey
you beat it they didn't
want to acknowledge that the game broke they were just like
you beat it congrats
it's the Bejeweled kill screen
yeah it's basically what it is the Bejeweled kill screen and you can
actually see
PopCap actually put up the video themselves
exactly what that took
and I think they put the picture
of the kill screen here
or not cause maybe PopCap
didn't want to show their game breaking
I don't know
that was just like a little promotional video
it was all happy go lucky
yay Bejeweled were awesome
play us on Facebook
well somebody broke it so yes a kill screen
is achievable in Bejeweled 2 but 3 years
seriously
3 years is a long time
I know right
and that was all time when he was supposed to be working
mailbag
every week you send us emails
mailbagatorangelaungeradio.com
darksacra might read them on air
and she might decide to say screw you guys I'm not reading emails this week
I'm reading them
alright yay we caught her in a good mood
hello Orange Lounge Radio
Haseo here to rant a bit
first I'm sorry for spelling errors due to the use of
Vicodin after surgery involving
knee dislocation dude sorry
but you misspelled Vicodin
you know what though I would say
being on Vicodin is an acceptable excuse
for bad grammar dude when you're on Vicodin you don't
care
we're going to give them a pass
second I was really just saying that to be
a smartass second the whole Activision
bullshit starting with this whole
Infinity Ward leaving the company
Infinity Ward left Activision
and they as we already
know are the creators of Call of Duty
now according to G4 and their
the feed service
they say that the next Call of Duty games will be called
Call of Duty Black Ops comes out this fall
what the hell is Activision thinking?
especially when the Infinity Ward founders left and
35 other team members quit oh and did I mention
they are suing Activision for up to
500 million
for reasons untold to me
now Activision as stupid as they are
they have the Bungie
they have Bungie the creators of Halo
sign a 10 year contract what the hell
lastly three questions
one would it be illegal
to infect my aunts computer with a virus
to teach her a lesson?
how would I go about that?
well she's a bitch I mean
no I'm not trying to cripple it only trying to
burst her I'm not to blame for the
fucking it up bubble like a warning virus
switch her default browser
to Internet Explorer I think that will pretty much do it
I thought it would do it
have her use yahoo mail
just switch her homepage to
two girls one cup
or lemon party
two
is there a way to hack a copy of Final Fantasy 12
like you hacked 13
or do you know of a cheat I've beaten it over a year ago
and I want to replay for story
cause Loki's a big cheater
at 13 so can you cheat at 12?
12 I'm not sure
if there's a way to hack set at the
save I mean maybe
I'm sure there is
three
you just need a game genie
is there a way to hack an imported
UMD and change the text to English?
no
but yeah back to the
Final Fantasy 12 thing because it's on Playstation 2
you could probably just get like a game shark or
approach and replay or something like that
if you don't want to cheat in the game
why did
Bobby Blackwolf in chat just say two girls
one cup versus Capcom?
because he's trying to mess with
our brains I think the cup wins
thanks for reading my email
and if you don't what the fuck people
your loyal listener Hasia Sumiragawa
Sumiragawa
made me
I was just thinking of the cup winning
whoever wins we all lose
this is Robert M. I don't mean
to sound like one of those one-knit fanboys
but since it came out I'm pretty obsessed with WarioWare
DIY even though I'm currently somewhat
stagnant at creating new games in it
for some reason I actually had a dream
where one of my micro games set
a record for in-game sales
which somehow made the Orange Knowledge
Radio show roll I remember
Loki saying he didn't get it meaning the game
and all of you were
as all you did was tap and a character
moves up slightly
this somehow leads to a kernel of thought would you like to
see a series of OLR dream game micro
games or would you of course
prefer these concepts in a more substantial
more readily accessible less handheld
format I imagine having puzzle
slots or what they play snap
available in my warehouse might be
confusing to other people
in my in-game friends list have a good
show I think we'll take it in whatever format
we can get it yeah I know I'll take it wherever I can get it
but I think what they play dot com snap would
be very I mean because what was what
they play dot com snap supposed to be was just like what
two gay guys having sex holding
a dismembered head shouting fuck wasn't that the whole
and you take pictures of it like Pokemon
snap yeah and if you if you're kind of
like sitting at your radio right now in disgust
um it has to do with a poll
that what they play dot com ran like a
year ago about the most offensive game
most offensive thing in video games
and like I think homos and games was like
more offensive than dismembered heads or something
um so we suggested that they
should make a game about it called what they play dot com
snap uh go read about it in
the OLR wiki it's it's all there
this next email just made me
snort hard
hi OLR as usual thank you for
supporting yyr games OLR is awesome
and so is everyone who listens to it
as a show under mat
relayed your game request discussed
during the last weeks show apparently you have requested
a game based on the golden girls yes
yes please oh my god yes
after spending many hours sweating countless
buckets and crumbling hundreds of pieces
of paper before tossing them in the general
direction of a wastebasket I'm prepared to
unveil the following concept the golden girls
death squad
the golden girls death squad will be a four player
cooperative twin stick shooter
each player will assume the likeness of either
Dorothy, Rose, Blanche or Sophia
and battle an advancing army of terrorist robots
and balding perverted old men in full
180p high definition I'm sorry
I'm about to explode from awesomeness
Rob needs to go change his mantis
I do
you'll use the left stick to maneuver each
girl's technologically advanced mechanical
wheelchair each wheelchair
is equipped with its own unique weaponry
just as each girl is equipped with wisecracks
and quips taken straight from the popular TV
show voiced by the original actresses
spoken dialogue varies with context
when you get close to an enemy you'll hear Dorothy cry
have you lost your head? as she chops off their
head with an axe
each of the game's seven levels
Rob's red in the
face this is beautiful
each of the seven levels
are loosely based on the show's seven seasons
boss enemies will include Dorothy's cheating husband
Stanley evil palette swapped versions
of the main characters and the
leader of a cult named high cholesterol
fortunately you will have rocket
launchers nuclear bombs exploding calcium
supplements as part of your wheelchair arsenal
the game will feature
four player simultaneous drop in drop out
play over xbox live
60 frames per second animation simple and
responsive controls motion capture versions of the
show's actresses and a driving
rock and electronic soundtrack featuring
a hard drum and bass mix of the show's
opening theme thank you for being a friend
development of the game will commence immediately upon
our receipt of the rights to the golden girl's license
um you can help me get that for free right
the budget currently allocated for
the development of this game consists of
the four dollars in my wallet I'd hate to
use it on licensing when I can pick up a sandwich
instead oh wait I think I just
sold a copy of falling now my budget
is 470 wait what you have to pay
tax on sandwiches crap
oh well little bitch oh well please look
forward to the upcoming release of sharpshooter
the announcement of future yyr game titles all my
love erin that is
the pinnacle of awesome email
you did yeah first off
you get a gold medal
for awesome email that's an official
olr gold star they don't get handed out
very often you just won one sir
even if that was the biggest
tease I've ever heard in my life dude
here it is you don't have to
get the licensing you just call
it grandma's got guns
and
it would sell billions
quick poll in chat how
many of you would play a game called grandma's
got guns
also
I want to throw this out here
everybody should buy falling and
what's this other game snake 360
and the other one sharpshooter buy them
all immediately when they come out they're
like a dollar so I mean what like
three dollars maybe four I don't remember how much maybe
snake 360 is more whatever it's like
less than 10 for all these games
and if you buy these games
then we will guilt him into
making grandma's got guns
there you go and just so you know
I just want Aaron to hear the quick results of our poll
in chat me yes
me grandma versus cap
com fuck yeah yes
yes me fuck yeah hi
yes I haven't seen a
no yet dude
if I made a game with zombies in it can
sell millions of copies how about I made
a game with grandma in it
you
know you want to do it
alright
am I getting pathetic
is this turning into a baking and groveling
a bit too much I don't know I just really want to see
my grandma game
alright you're so funny
I know okay
this one is from Robaba
about test drive
unlimited 2 I was a big
fan of the original test drive unlimited
and we had an ol army clubhouse
joystick shows the demo reel here
um
it doesn't look like lost islands oahu setting
at least not for the video it does
look a lot more types
of driving events but the character models are
sims 2 ish still it releases
in fall amongst the big titles so I hope
it does well I never did get to play my 5000
miles in the first one I remember
test drive that was a pretty neat game
um it's
taken him long enough to kind of put out news of a sequel
I don't know I'll play it if it's good
but it's going to be tough because there's so many racing
games coming out that I'm so interested in
you know but um well that'll be
I'll be a ways out by the way
that's it going back
to the email
from yyr act def says
you can call it golden age
grannies killing spree
this is great the prize has to still be cheesecake
yes
grannies with a z
I made a game with grannies in it
alright there was our mail bag
and now it's time
imagine grannies
I know this is a little
outside of the box for you I know this is
not a retro game or inspired
by you know other stuff but I'm telling you
instant cash machine
alright lets get into the fus of the week
f u to um
caffeine withdrawal headaches
they stink
yeah
low key
um
I guess
f u to my neighbors
pushes for still being alive even after
I dumped a half gallon of weed
killer on them
damn you weeds
oh I will kill them
um
I don't really have much of an f u of the week
I'm again in fairly good spirits
I will say f u to me being such a procrastinator
cause I procrastinated
on something big time I really should have got taken
care of a lot sooner but whatever
hey you know what life goes on
alright
there's worse things that could happen in the world
lets move on
we got a couple more stories for you guys
then the listless results
and then the skype line
and listless by the way I will say this about listless
this doesn't happen very often in listless
but every single answer
tonight got at least one vote
every single answer usually something gets shut out
but it's going to be a close one tonight
so hopefully you guys all voted if not
you got like 30 seconds left
loki what do you got for us
while we wrap these up stop playing that game
what are you playing now
yes you are you're playing that freaking
contra in castlevania meet
super mario brothers and all that crap
alright
well this is appropriate I guess
or not I don't know
it's of course you know a parody game
and only in
japan of course created by
joe jin circle studio
s super strip
fighter 4 is a
18 and up parody fighting
game with 15 brawlers
and skimpy outfits and apparently
there's also one big fat geek dude in there as well
and um
I guess it has parodies of
fighters from king of fighters
tekken virtual fighter
street fighter you name it and of course
um each character
has their own special abilities
for example rana
who is covered in massage oil which she uses
to rub on herself on the
other fighters and uh
slip past their punches
um or they have um some other people
who throw vibrators
and what not but it's um
a game where they basically get
uh
they get uh
their clothes ripped off as they're fighting
so awesome
only playable
in japan I'm afraid
oh what a big surprise
a game like that is never going to come out here
what a shock
but they have some screenshots and it's uh
interesting I guess
amaze satsuma in our chat room says
super strip fighter isn't that called
dead or alive
ba dum bum ba dum bum merrimay is a comedian here at
olr
orange lounge radio of course as you know started
about a little game called
adr and the other types of music games that were out there
in a series called bamani
well guess what the bamani series is still alive
so we want to take our last story
tonight to show you guys
one of the new bamani series
that's coming out well we're not going to show you because it's a radio show
but we're going to talk about it it's called reflect
beat that's right a brand new game of the bamani
series called reflect beat is apparently
location testing
what is going on here it's a
multi touch space touch screen
I guess up to five simultaneous
touches will register on the screen it's a two player
player game it's two machines
linked together if there's no second player you can play
against the CPU it's made
at a wide screen and what happens is that
player one has a red colored bar across the bottom
of the screen and player two has a blue colored bar
across the bottom of their screen and what happens
is that at the start of the game the music begins
and a ring shaped note appears at the center of the
screen the note travels from the center to
the player's bottom bar the
player touches the bottom bar when
and where ever the note
meets the bar to the beat of the music
if you hit it then it changes
to the color of the player and bounces right
back to the opponent the rate
at which it will move will depend on the music
so if it's a slow BPM then
the note will move slowly and so on and so on
there's hold notes, chain notes
and so forth they say it's also
a lot like boom boom rocket
if you've ever played that on xbox live with the whole
bar and the exploding fireworks
some of the songs in the game there's
a remix of star mine 7 7
a song called
juicy I'll leave that to
your imagination and silence so on
and so on so reflect beat a new
game in the bamani series
there's even some pictures that are posted around there
on the internets so you can see what this game looks
like it kinda
looks like dj max technica
a little bit that's what I was totally thinking
when I saw it I was thinking I wonder if
I wonder if they're stealing the
idea a little bit there isn't that funny how that
works out konami steal a music
game idea rock revolution
what alright
whatever
there it is we don't
write it we just record it reflect beat
probably never coming to an arcade near
you unless you live in japan alright
let's get to the list
list results yes the
list list results and who won
tonight's list list
as you know tonight was
all about what versus capcom
game would you like to see next
and we had a lot of votes
in our chat room
and in the
end only one could win
but
for fun we'll read you the top three
the number three capcom game
you want to see the most
weed inverse versus
capcom that's right
buffy will be staking morgan before too long
number two
all games versus capcom
well
you know what that means we're gonna all get to be our
own little fighting game characters the number
one answer for what you wanted
to see the definitive versus capcom
game you want to see next
no surprise to this audience
konami versus capcom is
the number one answer tonight konami versus
capcom there it is
the definitive list
i actually had on my original
list silent hill versus capcom
but i took it off when somebody said konami
but i do think it would be
pretty awesome to have pyramid head as a character
pyramid head versus chun li
be awesome
alright so there it is your
top three list tonight and that's it
no disputing it's a done deal no more
arguing fanboys sit down shut up
it's done we've put it through the scientific
process alright
anyhow the skype line
is now open 1877
game olr or our username on skype is
orange lounge radio if you wish to give us a call
and talk about anything you've heard
about on the show tonight or i suppose
anything else if you want
alright uh loki you have any last minute
stories or are you just gonna play your little uh
capcom well i wasn't playing this game but
uh right yeah i'm sure
there's stuff i could talk about here let's see
um
uh
uh yes uh
hi
the record of uh agris war apparently
it's too hot for gamestop uh they've
decided to put it behind the counter like
porno
and uh if
apparently they said uh this was actually an
email that went out to the stores
uh please place record of agris war
limited edition behind the cash wrap
um if a
customer inquires about the game let the
customer know you have it in stock what's so bad
about it it has like
suggested pictures on the outside
sorry we picked up a call hi you're on
orange launch radio who's this
this is ds master
alright dark
sakura yell disconnect
dark
sakura vetoed that call
awww sorry
sir alright uh
you are not you're right i'm not
877 game olr username
on skype is orange lounge radio unless you're
ds master then you just don't want to call in
alright
um
let's see what other fun stuff can we talk
about here oh this is kind of neat i tried
this a little bit earlier this week but it
crashed my computer but instant
action it's a game service
that um they sell a bunch
of different pc games they actually have
a new thing now where you can embed
game demos into web
pages so say for example
the example shown
the secret of monkey island special edition
you can embed a 20 minute
free trial into a web page
and get the test it out
fortunately when i did that on my work computer
it crashed
i don't blame the website i blame my
computer because it sucks
it's too bad
um
some games that are going to be coming out
later um in the month
uh raystorm hd is supposed to be
making its way out on may 5th
as well as xeno clash
um and then of course uh
those are both on xbox live arcade
rocket knight uh the remake
there is supposed to be making its way out on
may 12th on xbox live arcade
and steam and then may 18th
on the playstation network so that's kind of cool
i don't know
and um
yeah that's pretty much it
what is up
with skype like last week
nobody wanted to call
like
wow and now they're too busy playing super
mario what is up like i like
a couple weeks ago
we were getting like seven calls at once
it was insane freaking call us
people
dark soccer is already mad
now i know
maybe they're afraid we're going to hang up on them too
we're not going to hang up on you unless you're ds master
alright let's see what's going on
you know what's so funny
a phone call was coming in and
the minute dark soccer said that it disappeared
laughing
alright i don't know
are we just going to sit here and wait
see if
i don't want people to call us
please
don't make me use the little girl voice
somebody is offering to call in
dammit call
well hold on maybe we'll get a call here in a minute
just be nice see now a phone number
now a call is coming in
hi you're on orange laundry who's this
hey this is ssj100 matt
hey ssj100 matt
hi
thank you for not being ds master
how are you
i'm doing very good
so tell us
i know you're kind of buds with yyr
erin you know the guy behind
snake 360 falling all that fun
stuff and who sent us the gold star email tonight
is he serious
or is he just fucking with us
um
i plead the fifth
ahhh
you're killing me look i'm just saying
go back to him and say hey
you don't have to make it a golden girls game
it's grandmas got guns
well let me tell you something
when you were reading the email
with all the comments i texted him saying hey
people want this game
he hasn't texted you back
alright fair enough
you tried you get an A for effort
alright
well uh what else is on your mind tonight
what kind of video games you been playing this week
actually i called in
to do a giveaway right this very second
holy crap i want a gimme gimme gimme
gimme
what is it what are you giving away tonight
actually you know what i'm giving away
is uh back at
pack east i was given a
an avatar download
code
now what you know
it's an avatar hoodie
it's a packs east avatar hoodie even i didn't get one of those
you're gonna give it away to a listener
yes i'm gonna give it away to a listener
god i hope ds master wins it
just to make you mad alright
well how you gonna give this away
i'm gonna do a quick trivia question
on a game that just came out
uh that meanwhile we are actually
battling with uh afterburner climax
ooo ok fair enough
and uh what if somebody knows the answer
i assume they're gonna uh what send you a private message
in chat or something
no they're just gonna spam chat
oh spam chat ok first
to yell out in chat and then we'll see who won
cause you're watching chat right now alright
what is the question
alright the question is
u-sazuki is the creator
of afterburner
now afterburner made an appearance
in another u-sazuki
game which game is that
go
alright i wish i need some like
suspenseful music here while this uh
jeopardy
i don't have jeopardy
chuck norris
is not the answer bobby blackwolf
no no no afterburner is playable
in this game so i'm giving you another hit
alright well i don't have
the theme song to jeopardy or anything like that
but i do have this for game show music
people need to be more specific
they almost have the answer
there's like four people shouted out
chenmue uh daytona usa
bayonetta
chenmue oh
ok got it
ok
i cheated
no i didn't cheat these all be more specific
i'm like chenmue 2
loki you are not eligible you are a host of this
program do another question
you need to do another question
loki keep your hands together
play your stupid game
new question new question hold on
i'm gonna put new question
no you
what
you know i did not expect loki to ruin it
i know loki ruins everything
god loki
i'll help you come up with a new question
you want a new question
yeah you know what yeah come up with a new question
alright
i know matt now look how much you've upset matt
you need to apologize
no no you didn't upset me you know the thing was
i didn't it was my fault cause i just saw the answer
i said chenmue 2
and then i saw loki next to him i'm like shit
shit
alright
here you go
according to my
source that i'm looking at right now
what type
of airplane do you
fly in afterburner
that's a good question
right? yeah there you go
what type of plane
do you fly in afterburner
a big plane
will not work
a boat
you're not on a boat
what type of plane do you fly in
afterburner
a shark oh oh oh oh
dark tetsu you got it it's an f14
tomcat there you go
there you go dark tetsu you got it
and there you go even though he's sort of
on olr staff at least he's not one of the hosts
of the freaking show
so there you go
dark tetsu you wins
congrats dt
applause for dt he's a winner
the rest of you i'm sorry you lose
alright
well we love giveaways
go ahead
i said we love giveaways so thank you so much
matt for calling in and giving stuff away
we really appreciate it anything else on your mind
you want to share tonight with us
um bye
uh afterburner climax
try to beat my game
afterburner climax
try to beat my score i need to get it
i totally forgot it came out i was so busy
having sand in my vagina over game room
and then playing stuff on my
uh new video card that i totally forgot about
afterburner so i need to check it out
alright well uh
s2100 matt you have a wonderful
wonderful week and uh thanks so much for
giving away free shit on our show we appreciate it
yep alright take care buddy
yep take care
alright free stuff
on the show free stuff speech
dar tetsuya speech
alright um
we'll take more calls 1877
game olr our username on skype is
orange lounge radio do we run out of last minute stories
lowkey
ones that i wanted to talk about there's just you know
well how about the ones you didn't want to talk about
i don't want to talk about them
okay fine um
i wasn't paying
let's let's go to the b-sides tonight
let's go to the b-side stories and see
uh what uh what's going on there
the b-side no you got saved by a phone
call hi you're on orange launch radio who's this
good evening oh
you olr
good evening uh how are you
oh and why else peter
well
when the fuck did i get
a german accent oh
oh well i don't know
well how are you
and your german accent this fine week
uh i'm just fine
well kind of got you
well what's on your mind and what do we owe the phone call to
uh
sims 3 that's
annoying that when it
walks up
are you how do you feel
about sims 3 coming to consoles
i uh say almost
uh j and
them kind
uh well
uh well it's gonna be
it's gonna be get
dumbed down and
which is boo hoo
but here's the other thing though
is that well uh
the uh well
and lucky us for us hardcore
sims players the new
expansions expansion
set ambitions
will hit
the pc before we get sims
3 on the console
hmm
uh yeah because sims 3 on the console is gonna probably
be a ways out especially if we're just hearing about it now
you know i haven't heard dark soccer talk about sims 3
in a long time i've actually been sitting here
installing my sims 3 oh it did all the talk
about it tonight well no um
because what's been going on is because i have
a lot of mods in my game
i have to completely reinstall
and delete my registries
so yeah and it decided to fart on me
so uh
i have a question dark sakura actually
how do you um
the registry
erasing
what the hell how do you do that
how do you do that
since well um
because my
current problem in sim 3 is that
well my school
building is borked
they can
be in the school building for like
2 minutes and then
they uh
it just stops i don't know
i have no idea
that's something that you're probably gonna have to
check on the sims 3 forum for
yeah
i've never had that problem so i don't
know how to help with it
what's supposed to be coming in this next sims 3
expansion what's the
big thing that they're going to do with this
uh
like they were they are
apparently they're gonna make
a move that
to make
make a move on those
those players that
never leave the sims
the sim creator
or uh
the or the uh
like where they
just build lots
and never play the actual sims game
well if they're happy doing
that i don't understand why they're gonna ruin
that get out and play the game
dammit
yeah well but
it's like never mind really so
it's
it's interesting though you know there's a lot going on
in um i don't wanna
compare the sims 3 to wow but i will
uh there's a lot going on
in wow right now where they're really changing up the game
and they're changing it in some big big ways
and it's kind of causing the player base to
have some rabble rabble although blizzard
changes big shit with every patch
and everything works out just fine but i guess the big
thing that's causing rabble rabble is that
now the 10 man and 25 man
raids are gonna share the same lockout
so if you're in one of those raiding guilds that does 10
mans and 25 mans every week you're gonna have to pick
one or the other not gonna be able
not gonna be able to do both anymore
we all have to do different raids or something like that
same loot and everything
it's gonna be very interesting they're saying oh it's gonna kill 25
man raiding so you know
big changes to the game but sometimes it works out for the better
so in a way and you know i'm relating
this back to sims 3 i promise
you know if they're gonna change some of the core elements of the game
maybe it's just because they kind of
see the habits of the players right now and
they kind of want to course people into
looking at this whole other part of the game that they've
developed that nobody's looking at
and also
a thing that's apparently
coming with the new expansion is that
there's gonna be apparently
natural disasters
coming
now there you go
there
we have something really interesting
now that kind of reminds me
if that would happen
because well the
optimal would be if they
made a
well what's the
season
i think it's actually called
the seasons
expansion that they made for sims 2
since well
since i'm like a snow person i would
love to have my sims
playing in snow
but here's the problem
is that
your cure
even though the problem that i would have
with that is that my current sims
house is
not is
not exactly a winter
house because they would
would freeze if so
were the case if you have to have walls around
everything since i'm like
i'm having like one bed here
one bed there all the all in the opening
i have to say
though this expansion where they want to
add like natural disasters
kind of reminds me of the roots of the sim
series which would be sim city
which is kind of the game that started it all
because remember you could have natural disasters in sim city
like your nuclear power plant blowing up
or godzilla attacks the city
good times
indeed good times
alright well akiripper we're gonna let you go and
go to wrap up the show but thank you
so much for your call and have fun simsing
away i hope the expansion works out ok
for you
alright take care buddy
alright
we'll go ahead and wrap up there that'll be our last call
tonight because we want to go and wrap stuff up
and get to our
after birth the part of the show that's
not podcast
nothing to you see you got to join us
for a live show to know what that's all about
but don't worry you're not missing too much
we wouldn't do that to you but we want to get to
that and wrap things up and get out of here tonight
but first we got to thank all you guys for listening
tonight were there any other last
minute stories though before i get to that loki real quick
no dark sakura nothing
alright then let me take an opportunity to say
thank you guys so much for downloading our show and
tuning into us or tuning into us live however you
choose to listen to olr we really appreciate
the support and really thank you guys so much
for you know taking the time out with us every
week to support olr
you know all we ask just tell a friend
or two about the show help us spread the word
about our little program we really appreciate all
the support um but let's go around
and get everybody's final thought dark sakura
your final thought tonight this is a pain
in the ass to uninstall
my final thought is
new video card yay
dragon age yay loki your final thought
um
with the power of hot swapping
i will once again be able to play my crazy
grand theft auto games yay
alright thank you guys
so much for listening to our show
we're going to be back next week to do it all again
more news more chatters
more stuff more antics it'll be a
good time thank you guys so much for downloading
our show that's it right
nothing else i guess we'll see you next week
have a good one everybody
see you next week