Orange Lounge Radio
Digital Hosts
Dark Sakura
Sky and the Low Crew
Tonight, May 16th, 2010
EA gets set to sell a controversial new online pass
More details are forming on Mega Man Online
and Steam gives away a game totally free
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends and welcome to episode number 367 of Orange Lounge Radio
The video game talk show where every gamer has a voice
My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-hosts
First on up, the one, the only, the fabulous, Dark Sakura
Here's my impression of Rob earlier
What?
What episode number is this?
Okay, no. Okay, before we went on air, because you know, I wanted to have the episode number down
Because I lost count like three years ago, longer than that, where we were at with the show
You know I have to give you a hard time
So I said, what episode number are we on? Just kind of like a rhetorical question
Like I'm actually going to look it up, like I don't expect Dark Sakura or Loki to know it
And Jamie in the background, she's all, 69
I said 50 million
Oh did you? I thought you said 69
You said 69
I thought you said 69
I totally thought she said 69 too
I said 50 million
Alright so it's episode number 69 of Orange
Actually in two weeks, no three weeks, because there's not going to be a show in a couple weeks
But the show after Labor Day will be episode number 369
Brought to you by the multiples of three
That's right
Oh that is weird, 369
Alright anyhow
Also the other voice you hear over there, the one and only tech master Loki
Hello
Who's favorite game by the way, is that Rainbow Unicorn game
It is not
That's all you ever play on this program is Rainbow Unicorn
That's not what I play
I played the werewolf ice cream man one not too long ago
How dare I
And I played the, was it the Mario crossover game the other week
I just didn't have the link for the Mario crossover game because I was going to play that
That was actually pretty awesome with the Contra guys blowing up all the blocks
I do have the link to the Unicorn game but that's about all I have right now
Alright also joining us tonight, you guys in our chat room because we do tape live every week at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com at 6 o'clock Pacific right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
If you are listening to us live please pull up a chair and join us in our chat room at chat.orangelaungeradio.com
We're going to move into a little bit of how was your gaming week
That's how we always start off the show
First off Dark Sakura, I understand, school's out for summer
Yay
Well I'm going to school in the summer
Oh never mind then
Well but I make it to skip pre-algebra
Well who
Because for some reason ARC's website just let me sign up for algebra in the fall
And I was going to do like the self study thing in the summer because it's freaking pre-algebra so whatever
So I may only be taking history this summer but that means I graduate
Wow
In the fall
With my AA
My AA
Your alcoholics anonymous
AA
Alright
So you'll actually have time to actually play games again, it'll be great
I've been playing games though
Alright well tell us a little bit about your gaming week
Even though I've had like my final projects and crap due
I played, well I downloaded something for free that we'll be talking about later because everybody freaking downloaded it
I was having a wait in the damn queue
And then I played that stupid gay ass unicorn game
Excuse you
No that's what it's called
Oh okay
Well you have to have the ass to make your unicorn be extra gay or something I don't know
Wait wait wait wait you're not talking about
No the one on Steam
Oh you played the Pink Anus game
Anus that was it
Yes
I thought, I was thinking of the hand he called
Oh gosh what was the name of it
Magic Stone or Legend of Magic Stone or something
Okay yes
I got as far as looking in the stable and I was like this is crap and turned it off
Just so those you know catching up with OLR
It's also very Engrishy
Who haven't heard the past few episodes
There's a game on Steam and it was Alan that brought it to our attention
Where in the, it's like something like about a mystical unicorn or whatever
And you see in the screenshots like there's like a crafting screen or something
And one of the materials you use is A-E-N-U-S it's anus but it's pink
So it's the magical unicorn with pink anus game
And Dark Sakura bought it cause she's a consumer whore
And hell
But no like I tried to, it's really like a click and drag type stuff to use things
And I was like this is like a big bad flash game
You can groom his hooves
And he was a little cult when you first got him
And now he's a golden unicorn with sparklies falling out of his butt
At least that's what it looked like
I put up a screen capture somewhere I think on my Twitter or something
You make everybody want to play this game very badly
Here's my review
Pink sparkles out of a unicorn's anus
It's anus
A-E-N-U-S
Anus
My anus is bleeding
Or would it be
It would be emus cause the neod
Anyway and then and then and then and then and then and then and then
I know you can't have it cause you can't spell your
Sorry
Um
Then um
I played other stuff
Yeah I played more um
Beluga whale
I'm sorry S-B-G-B
And um
I played um well well we've been
Well I was watching Dan play Alan Wake
And here's our review of it
Um
Max Payne meets Silent Hill
The end
It's actually not that bad
And then um
Oh god we played some other stuff too
Oh yeah I went to Pinagogo
So I played pinball
Isn't that like a big convention type thing for pinball?
It's in Dixon
Oh nevermind
Well no it was a pretty big event for pinball folks
Just to describe Dixon
Like if you're driving between Sacramento which is OLR headquarters
And you know the capital of California
And if you're driving between Sacramento and San Francisco which is where all the fun things are
Dixon is kind of like the pink anus of that drive
It's like
Sorry the pink anus
You look over and you see a gas station
A Mary's pizza shack and farms
That's about it
And fruit stand
And fruit
I went to the Yolo fruit stand yesterday but anyway
So yeah um I got
I also
And I forget this every year because I've been to like four Pinagogos now
I'm allergic to the town of Dixon
No seriously
No I'm being absolutely serious
Okay
Every time I've been to Dixon
I end up getting some type of weird heat stroke
My allergies get like
You know how allergic I am to dogs
It gets that bad
I swear
I took two doses of Benadryl Sudafed and Zyrtec
And I was taking local honey
And giving myself shots
And you name it for allergies I was doing
I was snorting crap
I was still like super you know
Eyedrops my eyeballs were floating
And it was just like not
It was not beautiful
I felt like that my eyeballs were the size of like
Double the size of my head
And so I went and sat in the car
Texted Dan I'm sick
I kept hiding in the bathroom because it was in a place with air conditioning
And um playing Final Fantasy 2
Sitting on the floor of the bathroom at the Dixon Mayfair
Sounds like fun
Sounds like the sophistication being sucked right out of you
And that's why you're having all those you know
Complications and stuff
Just like sorry you're too sophisticated for here
And well I finally ended up going and sat out in the car
So I could turn on the air conditioner
And filter out the pollen
Because you know we run the AC in my car
No pollen gets in you know
And so I was doing that long enough to get everything settled down
So I could take some more stuff
And so finally I get to where I'm feeling better
I drink some vitamin water I'm feeling good
And then Dan texts me so do you want to go home?
Yes
And not to not to not to say anything bad about the uh
Pina Gogo
Because it's a great event
But if you have hay fever
If you've got allergies to nature to grass
Um don't go unless you bring your own plastic bubble
And then it makes the plastic bubbles really can't play pinball very well in them
So I just totally wouldn't you know
I would say um a gas mask could work
You could actually play the gas mask on that would work
But as far as what I played um
I played uh Back to the Future
And I played Revenge from Mars
Which is one of the pinball 2000
And um I played F14 Tomcat
I was going for mostly the mid 80s to early 90s era of pinball
You know just kind of get into it
And I played this 80s
It's like a mullet era of pinball
Well I was going to say speaking of that
I played a pinball machine called Punk
And it had like the you know
Looked like uh pictures from uh
What was that movie with Nicolas Cage
And Valley Girl
You know and all the
The guys on the on the play field
Looked like Duran Duran
And it was kind of funny
Even though they weren't very punk they had that hair though
But um and eyeliner
Um and that one was actually pretty fun
For an old school you know
Earlier era of pinball
And there was a Beatles pinball there
I took a picture to send to Tiara
I didn't realize they made a Beatles pinball game
Kind of random
And um there was like a Spiderman
And the Ted Nugent one
I love the picture from the Ted Nugent one
Because he's there with his hair
And the guitar and the guitar's a gun
And he's shooting out of his guitar gun
And I was like rock on Ted
Huge anyway
And so uh I was
And my other thing and I know I'm going off on this
Is I was actually so caught up
Because me being the big design
Freaking nerd that I am
I was going around taking pictures of
Of interesting design
Of like cool pictures and neat you know
Early 80's late 70's style art
And
So I'll put some of the pictures up
They're on my phone
Yeah you're a nerd yeah
But I did play other games
Well I said I played Final Fantasy II didn't I?
Yes while you're on the bathroom floor
Crying and sobbing because of your allergies
I wasn't crying
And um
Yeah I played some Star Trek Online
Fun
I'm sure I played something else
Oh yeah I started playing Braid
And then I
Kind of remembered that I had to do other things like homework
I'm done with my finals
I love how you sum it up
I started to play this game
But then I was like oh god I have something better to do
Bye
No it wasn't something better to do
It was something responsible to do
Rob
Screw that growing up
So you're Robba and our other one is Robba
I know I know
Alright Loki I don't know if you can top
Dark Sakura's adventures in Dickson
Pinball and Final Fantasy II on the bathroom floor
While she's trying to recover from allergies
But you want to try?
I didn't go to Dickson
That's already an improvement right there
Let's see
I played
I played a lot of things that
Have yet to come out
Including APB
I've been playing the beta of that and I love it
Because it's just like
To me it's like crossing Saints Row with
Free Mode and Grand Theft Auto 4
You kind of
Do what you need to do
You have different missions
I guess this would be the tutorial portion of the game
They have you go
Spray graffiti
And break
Some stuff
And then eventually at the seal stuff
In the course later on as it's going on
You'll gain
More notoriety and
They'll have more enforcers
Coming at you
And the enforcers of course are played by
People online as well
So you can play
Both the villains and
Kind of the heroes I guess in the game
I'm playing of course as one of the gang bangers
Because that's fun
Lots of customization
In the character creator
It's just nuts
How much customization is in there
The clothing though you don't really have a lot of options
At first you have to kind of buy that stuff
Or unlock it later on
When you finish different missions
Same with cars and what not
But I'm really digging it
I might go back to
That as an MMO but we'll see
I kind of like the fact though that
The way they have their
Pay scale for it
Basically you pay it as you go
So for someone like me that doesn't
Necessarily get a lot of time
To dedicate to MMOs or stuff like that
It wouldn't be so bad because
You know the time I'm not playing it
I'm not actually losing out on anything
Because you pay for the hours that you
Want to use
It sounds good to me
I may try it
I have to upgrade my computer though too
So it might be a little bit
Other fun stuff
I happened to get a copy of
Red Dead Redemption a little early
So I've been playing that
And I love the game
Not a big surprise because it's a little bit like Grand Theft Auto
But for me
A lot of it's been like Oregon Trail
Extreme
Nice
It's a hunting portion of Oregon Trail
Because in the game you make money
You can hunt stuff and skin them
And take the meat and the skins
Or whatever
But you could only carry 100 pounds back to the wagon?
Oh no I was able to kill a lot of things
I don't know about 100 pounds worth of skins
Did you know in that game you can skin a horse?
I did not know that
Yes you can skin a horse
Because I got through with this one mission
Where I had to go
Kill some gang members
Kind of hiding in this house
And so we killed them
Captured them or whatever
And all their horses were left around
And I'm like I can't ride six horses
What am I going to do with this?
So I killed them all and skinned them
And sold their skins
For $2 each
And then I saw Onward Dills running around
Breaking news
PETA hates Red Dead Redemption
Oh I'm sure they will
You can kill all sorts of creatures out there
I haven't found the bears yet though
But it's really cool
And the fact that the game looks a lot better
Than Grand Theft Auto
Just a few years
And the amount of improvements in the engine
It's just amazing
Definitely worth picking up though
Then another game I was quite excited to check out
Was Split Second
And really digging that
I love how crazy the races are in the game
And just
I didn't play a whole lot of it
So I got to play some of the one track
That they had I think at E3
The airport
That's just the demo
I didn't play a lot of it
But I love the game
It's awesome
I was playing the demo
I'm not cool like you
You can get all these early games
In the know or whatever
I was playing the split second demo myself
It was as fun as I remember at E3
It was still the same game
That was probably
Funny enough probably my game of show
Last E3
Last E3 was not a huge year for me
But that was probably the best thing I played at the show
So I'm excited that game is finally coming out
Like Tuesday right?
And I'm looking forward to
I'm going to try some of the multiplayer in Red Dead
When it does come out
Because they do have a lot of neat multiplayer options in there
But at the same time I'm also working on
Doing another edited
Modded Grand Theft Auto game
I have some maps now
But there's specific rules you have to follow
As far as getting stuff to work
And stuff that normally works on the PC version
Doesn't work on the console version or whatnot
But um
Oh yeah
I got to play some of the listeners
During this week's
Grand Theft Auto games
Oh finally some listeners took you up on the challenge
That was fun
And then of course
More Grand Theft Auto
I think that's really
Did you school the listeners?
Or did they school you?
I school them, I school everybody I play
And so humble
Well the only times I lose
It seems lately is when I get
Cocky and just start messing around
And then I get to the point where
They get too close and one of them gets lucky
Killing and I'm unable
To make it across the map to kill somebody
So I don't do that anymore
But no
I'm actually like ranked
67 now so I'm
Going up there trying to
Make as close to number one as possible
Moving on up, moving on up
Alright congratulations
Hey this is episode 367
Of OLR and you're number 67 on Grand Theft Auto
Hey how about that
And I did pick up 3D.GameHeroes
But I haven't played
Then we'll move to my gaming week
Because I did play 3D.GameHeroes
I picked that up as well and you know I was kind of
Motivated by the price point of just $40
It kind of seemed like a bargain to me
So I decided to pick up the game and I didn't know much about the game
Okay here's how clueless I was about the game
I thought it was kind of like a game editor
Type of game where you would get to make your own little
Adventure games
No that's not what it is so
Let's take a step back and talk about what
3D.GameHeroes actually is
It's basically a gigantic rip off
Of The Legend of Zelda
But that's cool you know like
The Legend of Zelda was a great game
It's kind of fascinating that they're getting
Away with it but hey if Nintendo
Is not going to do anything why not
Now you know when I say rip off
There's some clear parity going on here
They've changed just enough
So it's not really a rip off of Zelda like for example
You don't have hearts
You have apples
What is he called? Kidneys
That'd be funny
That's I guess maybe the core
Part of the customization of 3D.GameHeroes
Is that your hero can be anything you want
You actually have a mode where you can
Go in and edit
The default guy I guess you could say like
The person in slot number one in the character edit
Mode looks like the dude from Dragon Warrior
So I don't
Know what you're supposed to like I'm 12
So I give all my characters like 3 year old
Names I name my character vulva
So I don't know what the normal
Character name is shut up
Alan and I picked
Out a good name
Save us vulva
Save us from the evil empire
So
Yeah I don't remember what his name is
Usually
Somebody in chat will probably yell it out
But whatever it doesn't matter what his name is
The game
The game is like this giant love letter
From guys our age but in Japan
Because I know it was developed over there
Who kind of miss what gaming used to be
I mean if you think about the concept
Of this game
The story is that there's this
Where everybody stopped visiting
It and it got old because
You know just people didn't care about
It anymore so their big idea was
To go 3D to change
The world I mean that
There's kind of like this really
Hidden bitter subtext there about how
Everything is 3D in this day and age
And why can't our games be 2D anymore
So and it's just loaded
With references to old 8-bit games
Mostly Zelda but there's other stuff
In there as well that's really funny
Including more current games
Because from software the developer
They made this other great Playstation 3
Game that came out a little while ago
Called Demon Souls and there's
Actually this room in the game where
If you walk in the right spot
It says there's a message on the ground
Here something like that it says
Do you want to recommend this message?
Yes it says somewhere someone got healed
That's funny if you've played
Demon Souls if you haven't
It makes no fucking sense you're just like
What is this randomness but
Whatever but then there's a chick right next
To it and you find white sticky stuff in front of her
Which is also a Demon Souls reference
But it sounds like
Porno which is really funny
Because there's a lot of parts in this game
That really push the envelope
Of an E10 rating but it's funny
Like there's a whore
In the game you pay her to
Do the fruit fruit with you or whatever they call it
And the fufu
I don't know what it is and that's
You do the fufu
But then you wake up and it's her dad
I kid you not
I kid you not spoiler
So anyway
You know what
It's 40 bucks
The game has flaws yes it has
Flaws there's slow down
In some of the dungeons because the water
Effect that they do in the game is so
Over the top and there's a lot in this
Game that's really over the top like
I don't know the size of your sword
When you have a full health bar like takes up
The entire screen
As long as you don't get it
I was making all kinds of inappropriate jokes
Yeah
It's funny it's really over the top there's a lot
That's very over the top about this game
And they decide for whatever reason
To do the water effects really over the top
And it causes
Slow down in one of the dungeons
And it's like okay folks
This is the PlayStation
The government bought PlayStation 3
Where's your cell processor now
Exactly
It's like this game
And to be honest there's really nothing
About 3D Dot Game Heroes
That deserves to be on the PlayStation 3
This game could have been on the PS2
I mean yes it has trophies
And yes it's widescreen but
I think there were a handful of widescreen
Games on the PS2 as well and
That's really it
I mean graphically
You're not getting that much more oomph
On the PS3
But I'm okay with it and they give it a pass
Because again you're charging me
About the cost of a PS2 game
You know 40 bucks
And it's you know still a good time
And at the end you just have to evaluate
Did I have fun yes or no
And I had fun playing the game
Despite it's flaws
So I wouldn't give the game like an A++
But I'd give it a good like solid
It's silly
Especially if you're a gamer in that age bracket
Late 20's early 30's
Or even if you're a younger gamer
That knows your retro gaming history
Then you're gonna get a kick out of this
And get some lols
And I don't think it made our
Show roll but
They have some really cool custom characters
You can download off of their
The 3D Dot Game Heroes Hall of Heroes
Website
Including they have a little arcade game you can play as
Little girl Cthulhu
Um
Chickens
Well yeah one of the default characters in the game
Is Santa Claus so I mean that's funny
You're Santa Claus going around with a giant sword
Ha ha
The only kind of weak thing
I guess is that that's where the
Customization kind of ends
And I guess maybe with LittleBigPlanet
Being the big thing on PS3 I was hoping
For a little more
I don't know maybe I'm just being greedy
I thought there was gonna be a little more to customize here
Maybe in the sequel
And I hope there is a sequel
You know what
Something just occurred to me that I should do
I need to get RPG Maker for PC
You should
And do Orange Dodge Radio
The RPG
Is that gonna be your little project while you don't have school?
You should do that it'd be fun
Well I've got clients that I'm working for but
You know what I'm gonna leave it now
Whoever's in the chat room who wants to work with me on this
Or three years ago or three maybe
I know that Dark Dead 2 was working on something at one time
No somebody did like a text adventure
Yeah we had a text adventure
It was really funny
I don't even know where I can get a copy of that anymore
I got it somewhere
If I can find it I'll share it
Yeah I
Again you know
I'm nitpicking a little bit with 3D.GameHeroes
Overall if you wanna play
Like if you're sitting there going
Gosh I wish they would make another 2D Zelda game
That I could like play on my TV
Here you go
This game was like made for you
Enjoy. Eat it up. Get a big spoon
They have like a little big
Planet Sackboy type thing
In there called Ragdoll
It's one of the custom characters that someone made
Looks just like a little pixelated
It's just kind of a bummer that that's like
The hero is like the only thing you can change
You know what I mean?
Weren't you kind of hoping there would be like a little more
Just a little more customizability to this
Oh well
But you know what? 40 bucks. Hard to complain
SirDuckTape. Yes someone made a roll of duct tape
Alright look other games in my gaming week
I don't wanna drag this out too long
Cause we're already almost a half hour into the show
And haven't even touched gaming news yet
But I just wanted to say really quick some of the stuff I've been playing
World of Warcraft of course cause I'm addicted
And play some Game Room this week
Cause you know they're back on the ball
With getting the releases out so hooray for that
I think I talked on the show last week about Pitfall
And nearly missing the top 20 right?
I tried to do like a perfect run of the game
And you know what gets me in Pitfall
And why I can't do it?
It's the scorpions and the hidden passage
Like I have no problem
If I just run
Straight from right to left or run to the left
I can like get through 20 minutes
Running straight and not die once
And that's how I got like a score of like 85,000
But the minute I have to go into the tunnels
The scorpions eat my face
Like that's the problem I'm having on old school Pitfall
But there were also some new games this week
And one of them was Oink and I bought that game
And you've probably heard me talk about this game before
Because it was out on the 2600
And I don't think people really know this game
It was an Activision game kind of based on the story
Of the three little pigs and I think the best
Way I've heard it described anywhere
It's a reverse breakout
There's a wolf that's trying to blast the bricks
And you're trying to put the bricks back in place
Before he can blast through them to get you
And Oink is out on Game Room this week
And so I was spending some time playing this
And I just saw this before the show tonight
Bobby, the gentleman who does the show before us
On all games, the Bobby Blackwell show
Actually put a tweet out there on his tweeter
And he put, why pay $3 for Sky's favorite 2600 game?
Actually I wouldn't say it's my favorite 2600 game
But it's, I think maybe like Kaboom or Pitfall 2 would be my favorite 2600 game
But it's my most underrated
And I think most underappreciated 2600 game
When I can get the cartridge for $1
Buy it on Game Room, I'll probably buy it on Game Room anyway
And sure enough he sends a picture of Oink
Running on his TV with the Atari 2600 hooked up
I think that's a lot of people's chief complaint
About Game Room and I get that
I get that complaint
Although do keep in mind it's pretty awesome
With Oink when you go like
Gosh the best score I can get in this game is 1800
And this game is really hard
How do these people get like scores of 5000 and stuff?
Oh I can go up, fire up their replay and look at it
I mean those are like features you can't get in a dollar
Cartridge and leaderboards and challenges
And some of this other stuff
You know, does it justify the increased cost?
I don't know, it really depends on how much these games
Mean to you and so forth
There's a lot, yeah and I already did my Game Room
Tangent a couple weeks ago
I'm trying very hard not to repeat it
There's a lot of potential with Microsoft Game Room
And I really hope that potential is realized
I'm hoping E3 is gonna drop a Whopper on us
I really want them to come out at that press conference
At E3 and go
We're gonna release a Whopper of a game
On Game Room this week and it's out
Right now, go get it
And so I don't know what that game is
But hopefully something really cool
Like something not from the early early 80s
Like something
I don't know, I don't know what game that could be
Galaxian 3
I don't know what it'll be
But hopefully something they'll kind of put out
And it'll take Game Room to that next level
Where it's not just Atari 2600
And old old old old old stuff from the 80s
We'll see though
My gut tells me
Here's my bet
Quote unquote
It's gonna be a Capcom game
From their like
Street Fighter 2-ish era
When they were using that hardware
So I'm gonna play
The CPS 1 and 2
I'm gonna just
guesstimate with no
Nothing to back this up whatsoever
Cause there's already the rumors
That Capcom games are gonna make their way
Like the Mega Man fighting game
And some of that stuff is gonna make their way
To the Rock Battle
Cause Capcom supported Ultra K
In the past
So there's no reason why they wouldn't jump in on this
I'm gonna just speculate
Original Street Fighter 1
Street Fighter 1 will be the big
E3 Game Room release
I have nothing to base that off of
But half fanboyism
Half, I've been doing this show for long enough
That I feel like I start to understand the patterns
In some companies
Take it or leave it
And also in Game Room this week
Keystone Capers was released
And I played a crap ton of that
Alright, I'll stop talking about my gaming week now
We are officially a half hour into the show and haven't talked about
I've been playing a lot of Super Street Fighter 2
I got my ass handed to me in Super Street Fighter 4
This weekend
I was playing and I got schooled
And it just reminded me what a terrible
Street Fighter player I am
I was playing Super Street Fighter 2 on my
Arcade cabinet
It was fun
Go into our chat room
I think some folks are speculating what the game could be
That's released at Game Room
Or released at E3 for Game Room
SSJ100Matt speculates
Oonga Boonga will be the game
Dear Lord no
BlackWolf
Our good pal Bobby BlackWolf says
Miss Nude World USA
Oh I wish
And BlackWolf also says
Remember no online multiplayer
In Game Room so it doesn't make much sense
To do a fighting game
Well to be fair sir, it really didn't make much sense
To put combat or outlaw there
Either then for those same reasons
I mean combat is
Is pointless
If you don't have someone to play it with
And yet you're supposed to invite someone over
They get on the second controller
So you could basically cheat for the high score on that one
Donovan speculates
Custer's Revenge will be the big game that's released
You know I just
I just don't think that's going to happen
A few people in the chat talking about Kangaroo
ActDeft in chat says if Game Room releases
Kangaroo I'll buy it on release
I do want to warn you though
If they release Kongo Bongo
Which I don't know, for some reason Kangaroo makes me think
Of Donkey Kong which makes me think of Kongo Bongo
Because they were all kind of
Trying to one up each other
Kongo Bongo is on the Sega Genesis
Uber collection
Be careful if Sega games start showing up
On Game Room because a lot of them
Are on that collection
Don't get swindled
Alright let's move on to some
Actual gaming news for heaven's sakes
Housekeeping, join us on Twitter
Twitter.com slash o-l-r, join us on Facebook
Orange Lawns Radio, yada yada
Blah blah blah gaming news, Loki
So Activision
Apparently is taking some
Lessons that they
Possibly have learned from
Lawsuits and what not
They are dropping celebrities from the next Guitar Hero
Game so you will not see any
You know
Dead Kurt Cobain's or whatever
Singing
Well to be fair, Kurt Cobain was not
Portrayed as dead in the game because I think
If he was that would have been a whole other issue
That would have been a whole other issue
You just got he's on the stage
No head
Zombie Kurt Cobain
So yeah, so they're basically
Their claim is
They're going back to the basics
This is coming from the latest issue of the official
Xbox Magazine
Some of the old Guitar Hero
Characters, the ones that were actually unique to
The game are coming back and you'll
Be able to recruit
Characters by playing their song sets
And once you do that you can also
Unlock their alter egos
So for example Lars would become
Like warrior Lars
And that will allow you to
Get a
Times six multiplier
Quick play
I guess is being revamped
Of course
The DLC from
Guitar Hero 5 and before that
It will be compatible with Guitar Hero 6
They're doing
I guess streaker's momentum
Do or die are now available in
Online competitive modes
New power challenges
Queen, kiss
Black Sabbath, they're confirmed to be
In the game, I guess quest mode will
Feature Gene Simmons as a narrator
Because he needs money
Does he have a
TV show, does he get money from that
Well, he's freaking Gene Simmons
All he has to do is go in a freak show and
Stick out his tongue, you know what though, he was on the Celebrity
Apprentice and that's, you know
If you're resorting to going, Joan Rivers
Was on the Celebrity Apprentice
And that's Joan Rivers, her career's kind
Of not gone
Now she's got a movie coming out and all this stuff
A couple years ago
They claim there's going to be a bigger focus on rock and roll
Right
Focus on rock and roll
Well I'm glad they're making a bigger focus
On rock and roll and not, I don't know
Making money
Why do I just have this feeling, like I'm not trying to be negative
Or be a fanboy or whatever, but why do I just have
This feeling that in E3
We're going to see Rock Band 3 and it's just going to
Blow this shit out of the water
Like it's just going to annihilate Guitar Hero
Let me play this way
Um
I don't really
Give a crap about, I mean look at
Look at Guitar Hero 5, what exactly did
Guitar Hero 5 do that was that
Great over Guitar Hero World Tour
Nothing really
I mean it was pretty much, hey look
We have new songs
Yeah? Yeah?
How about we throw in
Or throw in Van Halen
Eh, two games to press one
Is that the first game with the whole
You can do four singers if you want
And four guitarists and all that stuff
Wow that's awesome, we're going to put
Four drummers in my house, yeah cause
That makes sense
Um
I don't know, it sounds dumb
And this one doesn't sound that great to me
But you know what, I'm kind of biased because
I don't really care for the Guitar Hero series really
Once I had Rock Band 2 it was just like
I don't really care
You know I've got all these download songs
That I need to buy another game
Rock Band 3, I'm going to kind of consider it
The same thing unless I see them doing
Something really unique with it
Although I do have faith in harmonics that they're
Going to actually put something out decent
That's going to be
Different enough from the last game
So, props to them for that
But, I mean look at like the Guitar Hero
Um, their song creator
And stuff that they had in game, that was supposed to be
Like this huge feature and everyone's kind of like
Eh, whatever
You know, so
We'll see, I mean
We don't know a lot about it yet
But, I'm not expecting much
Just like with DJ Hero 2
I'm not expecting much
New songs, that's about it
Which could be a good thing, because if you set the expectation bar really low
Then, you know, they have the potential to really
Overcome that, whereas I think the
Expectation bar with Rock Band 3
Is really high, at least for me
Like, I'm expecting this game to really blow me
Out of the water, because they've had a couple years
To kind of perfect it now
They didn't do a Rock Band game last year, you know what I mean
Well, okay, yeah, they had the Beatles
But you saw the progression from Rock Band 2
To the Beatles interface, so you're kind of
Yeah, and like, was this
You know, the Green Day Rock Band stuff, I mean that's basically
Just Beatles being reskinned
With Green Day stuff, and it's
You know, it's basically like a track pack
But there is a lot of songs in the game
And, you know, just like
Guitar Hero Metallica or Aerosmith
Or something like that, I really don't give a crap about
Green Day Rock Band
I guess even the same could have been said about Lego Rock Band
Yet I purchased it anyway
Although Lego Rock Band had a really good setlist
So I did like that, but
You know, I basically dumped the songs in the game
And then sold it back, so
Whatever
I don't know, it'll be
Interesting to see what happens
Hopefully we'll, you know, obviously we're gonna know more
After E3
Alright, well let's move on talking about some other
Big, big news that landed this week
I just had everybody talking, and this is one of those things
That I don't think is gonna be news to you guys
But I wanna take some time out
To talk about it and get folks' thoughts here in studio
And those of you in chat room, and that is
EA's big announcement this week
At what exactly they mean
When they're talking about Project
$10, and the deal is
That Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11
Which is gonna be the first game that has this
Enabled, it's coming out June 8th
So just a couple weeks here
The EA Sports games for PS3 and
Xbox 360 will include a title
Specific online pass
This will enable you to do
Online services, features, and bonus
Content, however if your code
Has already been redeemed, meaning
You bought the game used, you
Got it on Gamefly, or borrowed
It from a friend, then you
Can get an additional online pass
For $10
Of course you get a 7 day free
Trial, so I guess if you rent it from
Gamefly, you'll at least get that
It's gonna depend
What it is, depending on the game you have
But EA has mentioned that
It will be, it could include
Meaning it probably will include
Basic online multiplayer
That could also include group and league features
Roster and playbook updates
Downloads, of like
The user based stuff
Tournament support, and so forth
So that's the direction
They're going in, where now if you
Get this game used, you're gonna have to pay an extra
$10 if you're gonna want to enable it online
Not the first time
We've really seen something like this
Ever happen
Right? Because you know, there's been
Other games that have charged
You know, the
Money for extra stuff, you know
If you wanna redeem the code, but it's interesting now
That you're talking about what I think a lot
Of people have come to take for granted online
And that is basic, head to head
Online matches. Dark
Sakura, what do you think?
About the whole
Project $10 thing, where you know
Folks are now having to pay
$10 if they wanna play their sports
Game online
That's
I understand
The logic behind it
What I think
It's not really gonna
I think
People expect for online play
Just to be a given, you know?
Yeah
So yeah, it kinda sucks
You feel like to some extent you're getting nickel and dimed
But it's tough because
Like
Well at least if you buy the game new
It's included, whatever
So if you're buying the game new, nothing really changes for you
I guess the difficult part for me
Is that
I see the logic behind it
And it's hard for me to argue with it
Because yeah, game developers kinda lose a little money
On the used market, this is a way for them to make it back
Whatever
So
Is that I already pay for Xbox Live
That's what I was about to say
You know, you pay for these services already
If they really
Wanted it to be
Something they could make more money on
They should just have like
I don't know
More download packs
They're not losing any money
Either off of used sales
If you think about it
If I sell my game used to somebody
Out there that's, you know, floating around
You know, it's not like
I copied my copy
And now there's two people playing
A game that you paid for once
It's just still one person playing
And so it is kind of
A dick move to do this
And you know what, the fact that they haven't dropped the price of their game
You know, it's still
Kinda messed up
What's even dumber, the whole thing
Was that GameStop was actually quoted
They were like, yeah we think this is a great idea
The quote you're thinking of
CEO Dan DeMatteo
I think says this
GameStop is excited to partner with such a
Forward thinking publisher as Electronic Arts
This relationship allows us to
Capitalize on our investments
To market and sell downloadable content
Online as well as through our
Network of stores worldwide
Are you kissing or sucking over there?
Here's the thing I think
Is because they're probably
Getting other back end deals for this stuff
Like for example, if you look at Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11
On GameStop's website
You get a $10 off future order
When you purchase Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11
The $10 coupon code
Will be emailed
When the order ships
So basically they're getting some sort of kickback money
That they're passing out to their customers to make it more
Appealing to them to buy the new game
Well yeah
And I want to say this too
DarkTetsuya in our chatroom at chat.orangelandraday.com says
So then the game itself will only cost
$59.99 new, right EA?
Right? No
It's still going to cost $59.99
Or let's just say $60
Because unless you live in Oregon or one of those other states with no sales tax
You're going to pay $60 plus for it
The thing to keep in mind though
This won't affect you if you're buying your games new
Because you get your free code
With the game and you know since it's new
That no one's used it, etc, etc
So you know that you're good
That means
Isn't GameStop going to have to alter their policy now
That they're not going to take returns on these games anymore?
No they will take the returns on the games
It's just like you know
Download content that would be coming with the game
You know they do this a lot now
Where they're bundling in some DLC
Like a coupon or something like that for
You know the first piece of DLC for free
Or like some in-game hat or something like that
That you get for free
Just to entice people to buy new games
But the thing for me
And you know I don't know
Because I don't play sports games a lot
You know I wouldn't care
For me if I were to buy Tiger Woods
That I couldn't play online
I wouldn't buy Tiger Woods
Well that too yeah
The only thing that bothers me about this
Yeah I don't play a lot of these sports games
Either so there's a lot of me that goes
Nah nah nah doesn't affect me
But I do worry about the precedent
This is going to set for the future
Because EA does make other games I do play
And granted I buy most of my games
Used or I mean sorry new
So a lot of this won't affect me anyway
I do use Gamefly a little bit
But probably these are not the type of games
I would be getting
I worry about the precedent it sets
And the part that kind of irritates me
Is that I feel like I'm being double dipped
I'm paying for Xbox Live
And now you want me to pay for this as well
If it's used that I have a problem with
It's weird like I will admit
I am weird this is weird
I don't have a problem with it on PlayStation
It's free there's not a lot for me to complain
About there you can't say like
Oh well you know it's wrong for them
To charge you to use their servers and all
That stuff when
You know you're not really paying anything for
It in the first place and if you want to use these features
Then you know I get it but I thought
That's what I was already paying for on Xbox Live
I understand that EA
Uses their own servers and I understand
That it's kind of separate like that
But then does that mean that the restriction
Will be removed where I no longer need an
Xbox Live Gold account to play these online
If that's the case
Then okay I guess
That it's the same as the PlayStation
And I can't really argue but otherwise I feel
Like I'm being charged twice
Do you seriously think that Microsoft is gonna
Let an online service go without
Going through Xbox Live?
Yes Final Fantasy 11
That is different I think
When you're dealing with Square
Well this is EA
Okay well here's the thing
I don't think that EA is in
Squares
They made the exception because Final Fantasy 11
Was built to be on the PS2
And Microsoft wanted a piece of that
They wanted it they thought it was gonna be
Probably the bigger thing than it really ended up being
What have you so they made an exception
But it just goes to show an exception
Can be made
But I think that also
It was the fact that
They would be getting something that no one
Would have ever expected to be on one of their systems
So
That was I think to get
Really to get into the market share
They're going to get EA games
Anyway
EA would be completely
Just butt-tarded
To not put out a game on
Xbox 360 I mean
There's it They're doing a lot of stuff
In this project $10 they have the way
That they changed the DLC the way
They kind of give it to you
In Mass Effect 2
You know this is not the first company
To try this they did the same thing with
SOCOM on the PSP to try to
You know
Curtail people buying the used game
But
My problem is
Basically like GameStop
You know their money is made and used product
And
They've been ballsy enough
Before to make you know publishers
Pay for shelf space and stuff like that
Why can't they be ballsy now they go
We think this is a stupid idea
What's EA going to do
Oh we're going to stop selling our games to your stores
They're not going to take a cut that big
I mean they may try to
Make that bluff
But I mean if you call them on it they're not going to do anything
And even if they did
You know what I've seen Blockbuster
Blockbuster or Movie Gallery or somebody
You know they stopped carrying
A certain vendor's
Product for quite a while
And just basically saying
Well if you don't want to play by our rules
Then we're just going to stop carrying your product
And it hit them big time and they ended up
Kind of settling with them
Okay let me go check because there's lots and lots
And lots of chatty chat comments I want to read here
And most of it's coming from Bobby
He definitely has a lot to say on this
BobbyBlackWolf in chat
You're ripped off if you buy the game used for $55
Then you'd have to pay $65
To get the game plus online
But buying the game used for $40
And buying the $10 online is still
More than buying the game new
And EA still gets a tiny bit of money
So you win, you got a cheaper game
EA wins, they get money to pay their SysAdmins
And GameStop wins because you bought a used game from them
Okay I want to stop there because
I get what you're saying
And I'm like 95% with you
But the soccer moms
Buying the games for these kids
Lose because they don't understand
That there's a hidden $10 fee that's going to come with this
And you know what else
Sucks too?
EA, they shut down their servers after some time
So you paid for the money
You paid the extra money to play this game online
And then it's not there
If all of that is disclosed in the agreement
I'm borderline comfortable with it
And then
There's kind of like a little bit of back and forth
Between BlackWolf and ToaGak
And some stuff here
BlackWolf says Phantasy Star Online also doesn't
Require a gold subscription
Any game that has it's own monthly fee
Does not require the Xbox Live gold
And ToaGak was trying to recall
A game that required them both
Couldn't think of one and Bobby says
Oh you can't remember haha
Well this $10 is not a monthly fee though
It's just a one time fee
To do the game for the duration
And you do get the 70 trials
So you can try it out
If the online is really not something that you care for
Then you don't have to do it
The other thing I was thinking of
And I'm sure that they've thought of this
And they don't have SystemLink in the game anymore
You can use tunneling services
To actually play online with other people
So you can use that
It basically acts like
It's a SystemLink game but you're playing it over
The internet like you did with the GameCube
And stuff like that with Mario Kart
Again, I don't know
I'm just a little worried like
What happens next
Like if this ends up being acceptable
Then what happens next
You know
They get you for $10 here
And you know, I don't know
They're not losing money left and right either
I mean this kind of stuff
And it's an experiment for them
They're just saying, huh, what can we get away with
It's just like the $15 map packs
For Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2
What can we get away with
$15, let's see if people buy this
Oh, people are buying this like crazy
Let's release another map pack for $15
I mean it's just
If people are going to buy this stuff left and right
And just not even think about it
There's going to be a lot of people that decide
Hey, we're going to buy this game used
Better off if you really want to get this game cheaper
Don't buy it used
Just wait for the drop in price and buy it new
And I guess
The moral of the story, if you will
Is so we can kind of move on with some other news
If you don't like it, don't buy it
Don't say you're going to
Don't be one of those left for dead
Two petitioners
That sign the petition against the game
And then are caught on Steam playing the game
The day it comes out
If you are really against this
Don't buy it and mean it
How about
Something a little bit more
Possibly encouraging
Or maybe face palming
Maybe a little bit
Walmart
Actually is
Going to be back in the
Used game
Business
They're going to be working with Game Trade
A startup services provider
With a lease to test
Their little game trade stores
In different Walmart places
There's only about five of them
But it's going to be previously owned games
Movies
Hardware
Basically you get store credit or cash
So yeah
They're going to be
I guess what GameStop was
For used games
Only Walmart
Well they didn't really get out of
The used game market
The company going under that was doing their kiosk
Kind of
They didn't have a choice
So they're kind of trying the same thing again
I don't think they launched it full
Steam
While that company was working with them
DVD Play
I don't remember ever seeing used games at Walmart
They were in test locations
Test locations of a new company
E-Play is what it was
They were doing it with Best Buy
And they went out of business
So now this new company
Coming out trying to do the same thing
We'll see what happens there
It's a tough market to compete in
But granted
Used games, there's not a lot of kiosks
Out there for that stuff
It could catch on
It might be neat
I just worry about those things
There's too many ways to exploit them
I don't know
With competitions dwindling
It's nice to see
I guess GameStop is going to have a little competitor
Because competition is good
Especially when news like this comes out
And there might be a $10 hidden surcharge
On your used games
It's nice that
There's going to be a little competition there
But I just don't think I like that
That competition is Walmart
Well, I mean
Walmart does everything else
Do we really need them in this too?
You know, money gets tight
And you need to buy dinner
You can always trade in your game
And buy dinner with the coupon
Or the store credit that you get
That's always good
Hard to argue with that, okay
At least there's that option
But as far as
As far as trading in stuff
I don't know
Really what they need
Out there is a website
And this would be pretty impossible to get
GameStop to be sharing what their trading prices are
But if there was a website to
Compare trading prices based on
Title per these different places
That would be kind of cool
But once again, they're not going to give that information out
No, I don't think they're going to give that out either
You know, and
The other kind of little worry I have
Is that there's going to be a lot of Walmart employees
That are going to get taken advantage of
Because, you know, one thing about GameStop
Is that most, and it really depends on
Which one you're going to, but most of them
Are going to hire people that are at least somewhat game savvy
Again, depends on the store
But I would worry that a place like Walmart
Isn't going to really care
And there's going to be a lot of people to get taken advantage of
And buy back games that are
All scratchy
Yucky and codes are used
Here's the problem though, Rob, with that
It's a kiosk
It's a machine
How does the machine know what games are in good condition and what aren't
It tries to read them
It reads this
It checks them
To see if they're able to be read
The problem is, though
You could trick the machine by using
Some sort of burn disk or something like that
And it might help you
Tell the difference between it
Of course, then you have your credit card
But, once again, it's also easy
To buy a, you know
A prepaid credit card
And you can do the same thing
Put whatever, you know, person's name
Social on there that you want
And do it and you can get away with the money
You should be telling people how to do this on the show
I'm just saying, hey, I think, you know
I work out the flaws
If you thought of it, somebody a little more shady
Has definitely already thought of it
So, it, I mean, but
Then again, not everybody's thinking that way
So, you could probably
Factor that in
But, um
It'll be interesting to see
Hey, who thought, you know, renting DVDs from a kiosk
Was going to take off
Not a lot of people did
Still not going to make me stop shopping at Target
Over Walmart
But, hey, you know what, though
If it takes off at Walmart, who says that Target's not going to do it
And, you know, if this company is anything like
ePlay was, they could easily have
The same damn kiosk
It just, you know, branded with the Target stuff
And it would be the same service right there
And they could double dip, basically, in the market
And there's nothing really stopping them from doing that
Unless they sign some sort of weird contract for it
Which they very well might have
Very true
We'll see what happens
Um, so there's some rumors now regarding
When, uh, the PlayStation Move
And Natal's going to be launched
Um, the rumor is that
PlayStation Move is supposed to launch in September
This is coming from Jason Bradbury
The host of Britain's
The Gadget Show
Apparently, he's proclaiming
That the PlayStation Move controller
Will take, uh, be released
In September
On his Twitter account
Another thing I was meaning to say
September for PlayStation Move, I'm sure of it
Can't say why, just September 2010
I
Well, I mean, if I was a betting man
That's a pretty good bet
It's gonna be this fall, okay
You know it's fall
And you know it's before Black Friday
It must, must, must be before Black Friday
So what does that really leave?
October, November, and maybe September
Here's how you know when
Uh, the PlayStation Move is scheduled
To come out, is you look at the titles that are
Supporting the PlayStation Move and where they're
Sitting as far as releases go
And everything that I've seen so far is pointing
To November, which makes sense because that's when
They seem to launch new consoles and whatnot
Um, so I would be betting
November
So, we'll see
So you are going to go against the British guy
From Gadgets or whatever
I don't know who the fuck Jason Bradbury is
From the Gadgets show
Good for you, you think something
I think you should challenge Jason Bradbury
To a throwdown
A throwdown?
A hoedown throwdown
Whatever, I could be like Michael Patcher
And say random shit, and if I'm right
I'm a genius, if I'm wrong, no one will remember
So, whatever
I'm an analyst!
We should just start calling you an analyst
We need to have a segment on the show, analyst Loki
No, but I'm serious
Wait
I'm serious though, like look at
Look at IPET
IPET is supporting the Playstation move
And that's supposed to be coming out in the fall
Lord of the Rings, Eragon's Quest
Whatever is supposed to be coming out in the fall
As well, because that's now supporting
The move on the Playstation 3
Um
LittleBigPlanet 2 will probably be coming out
Like this fall, I'm guessing
It's all going to be around the same time
Um
I just, I don't know about September
I guess it could be September
If you think about it, because
They are starting to support games now
With the Playstation move stuff
So, you know, publishers have access to it
And I guess they could do that
But I would be more willing to bet it's going to be
Closer to Christmas
Just to catch in on that holiday buying madness
You know, we'll see
Now see, where's that story going to be on all the
Game blogs tomorrow, that
World renowned, years long
Running, game analist, Loki
Has predicted on
Some little
Crappy web show
Just like this other thing
The gadget show or whatever
That move is coming out in November
He is sure of it, folks
He is sure of it
Let me just put it this way, okay
This goes, you know, both against me and against him
Just because we're hosts of a show
Doesn't mean we know what we're talking about
I mean, so, you know
Just because he hosts a TV show
Does not mean he knows exactly when
The Playstation move is coming out
It's a good guess, fourth quarter, duh
It's going to be coming out fourth quarter, so
Whenever that is, if it's September, great
It'll be nice and early
But, you know, from what I've seen
Their major Sony releases
Have either been in November or October
October like last year, for example
Because he had Uncharted 2
Um
God, there was other Sony titles last year
But LittleBigPlanet was also
In October as well
Although Resistance 2, I believe
Was in
November, so
It's all around that same time
They have release schedules
What about Natal, then?
Okay, Project Natal
What does our analysts think about Project Natal?
They're saying that it's going to be releasing
In October
This is according to
Microsoft's
Saudi vendor
He's not even really working for
Microsoft
Although they
Quote him as working with Microsoft
Apparently G4 has said that
Said Bilal
Tariq
There's a source you can trust
Is not a Microsoft employee
He is a vendor employed through a
Third party company on behalf of Microsoft
A subsidiary in
Saudi Arabia
And uh
Pardon me, pardon me. Can I do just a quick
This is a very important poll
We need to do in
Chat, okay? And I realize
Our audience is biased
But I still think this is a question worth asking
So quick poll in chat
Who do you trust more?
G4
Or
Analist Loki
Or Loki
Ready go
Well I agree, I don't think he's an employee
They're just saying
That they're reporting that he's not an employee
Okay, but he was the one
Apparently that was saying that
We will be in position to confirm the day after
E3, which is in June
But definitely it's going to be October 2010
And we will have it in Saudi Arabia
For sure
I don't think it's going to be definitely in
October
And once again it's because all the major
Stuff that's been released
Is usually around that November time
Now granted they could do
The fall update early, it's going to be
Timed with the fall update basically
You're going to have the fall update slightly
Before
This is launched, just like
When they did the avatars, the new
Xbox experience, whatever
They had
Their new scenic game come out slightly
Before
This new update came out
So you kind of look at what the games are
What games are supporting Natal and stuff
And what their release schedule is going to be like
And you can kind of guess when
Natal is going to come out
And if at E3
They're going to be showing off Gears of War 3
Which obviously is not coming out until next year I guess
But maybe another
Fourth quarter title is going to be really big
I'm guessing it's going to be
Around the November timeframe
September would be too early
I mean they're saying in October
So the end of October would sound
Right
Let's go to the results of our quick poll chat
And our chatroom, chat.ornsonshooter.com
Who do you trust more, G4 or Loki?
We have Loki, Natalist Loki
I trust Bananaman, Loki for sure
Homer Simpson, Natalist Loki
Natalist Loki
I trust the bird because the bird is the word
Well everybody said
About the bird
Yeah, stop it
Let's see
Loki
At least he mentions games I work on
We all trust Loki because we all love Secret Club
Natalist Loki over anything
Although anything is better than G4
I don't know, G4 has hotness
G4 has Ninja Challenge
That is a good point
G4 does have Ninja Challenge
Loki, not the OLR, the Norse god
I've trusted Loki with my life before
Or budget at least
And there you go
I'd be willing to bet that we'll find out
Probably before it's released
I mean, well
Obviously we're going to find out before it's released
But we were going to find out before
They announce it, let me put it that way
Alright
Well, do you think you know
A catchphrase that ought to be
In the next NBA Jam
If you have the next Boomshakalaka
If you know
Boomshakalaka, he's on fire
If you have the next
Catchphrase for NBA Jam
They want to know
EA Sports has come out
Oh, this means you'll have to pay $10 to play it online
EA Sports has come out and said
That they're doing
This whole little contest about
The next catchphrase in NBA Jam
Of course it's taking place on Facebook
Go to facebook.com slash NBA Jam
And you can submit your entries
Up until May 19th
9am pacific time
That doesn't give you much time
On the top 64 entries
And the one with the highest votes
Will be immortalized in
The game
Now they say the entries must be
Associated with one of the following actions
In the game
Dunks, assists, alley oops
Blocks, 3 point shots
2 point field goal
On fire shots, steals
Shot clock violations, rebounds
Miss shots
Catchphrases should avoid a reference to specific
NBA players and they must not contain
Pornography, illicit content and must be
Appropriate for audiences 13 years of age
I listened to the
Ad for that
Dan played it the other day, I was like
Dude, it's the guy
AlphaCananagram suggests
And Boom Goes the Dynamite
That's a great
YouTube clip by the way, if you've never seen it
I think that should be in the game
Boom Goes the Dynamite
I don't know, I'm thinking that maybe they could
You know, do something with
The bird
No, no
SSJ100Matt
Saying that we should have an OLR catchphrase
In it, I don't know, what OLR catchphrase
Would lend itself to basketball
I don't know, like ferret
That doesn't really work, exterminate
Can you really, I mean that's really a Doctor Who
Thing that we just kind of stole
What other OLR catchphrases do we have?
I don't know, do we have other catchphrases?
Your mom
There's Rob Rob Rob Rob What
I don't know
I don't think that'll do it
Some other folks are saying
That they should try to sneak in an
OLR reference into the catchphrases
I really don't know what that
OLR catchphrase would be
Ferret
Duck Island, okay
Duck Island might work
He made that shot all the way from
Duck Island
They'd be like, what?
He's not coming in from Duck Island
No, how about no
It's just J100 Matt
Says friend your butt
He'll friend your butt
Dunk
No, that won't work either
Cause that might not be appropriate for audiences
Under 13, alright
Maybe that'll be a future-less list, I don't know
Although the contest will be over by then, we'll see
Look at him
Paddle those balls
No
That ain't appropriate
But it did make me laugh
It did make me laugh
Alright
Let's move on with some more news
And of course release dates coming up
And the classic game of the week at some point tonight
Well how about something that isn't crappy
There's a Castlevania
game coming out on the iPhone, Rob
OMG what?
Yeah
It's a
Encore of the night
Which is really
It's gonna be hard to control, right
Puzzle game
It's like
When I looked at it, I was like
Oh, it's Puzzle Fighter and Puzzle Quest
So
Yeah, so basically the little screen capture on here
is Alucard playing against one of the fish guys
Who hangs out in Dracula's basement
But it could be fun
I think I'm gonna try it out, you know
But it also looks like it's timed
Each of your little matches is timed
Because there's an hourglass
But why can't they just
Or maybe when the timer runs out
Something bad happens
Like the fish guy
Takes a big poop or something, I don't know
And eats your face
And poops your face
Yes
It could be cool
I
I guess
I like puzzle games, I like Castlevania
It's all in the price
By the way, some more suggestions for the NBA Jam
Thing from our chat, and I gotta say this is my favorite
So far from SSG100 Matt
D-d-d-d-dongle
That's a good one
I might be saying this wrong
Shez-ro
Shez-ro says double down
You know, like in reference to Loki's
Least favorite KFC food
Alright, let's move on to some release dates
We're gonna travel around the world and look at some
Release dates, Loki
We're gonna look at some release dates
No, it doesn't really work for
NBA Jam
No, it doesn't
Yeah, actually some good stuff coming up this week
Kind of the
Big push for
Games until
Memorial Day, woo
July, July is like that
But this week though we have SplitSecond coming out on
Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
Highly recommend picking that up, it's actually pretty awesome
Oh, and also on PC apparently
Shrek Forever After
for the little tykes, of course the new
Tie-in game with that movie that
Thankfully is done
No more Shrek movies, thank you
They'll be coming out on Playstation 3
Xbox 360
Wii, DS, and PSP
Prince of Persia
The Forgotten Sands
Making its way out on Playstation 3, Xbox 360
Wii and DS and PSP
The PSP version
Is supposed to be 2D and then they're also
Re-releasing Prince of Persia
Sands of Time on Playstation 2
In case you haven't picked that up and feel
Festive with the movie coming out and everything
The game I'm
Definitely gonna be playing
A lot this week, Red Dead Redemption
Coming out on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
This week
City Builder
Coming out on the Wii until the Forgotten
About game that no one will be picking up
Attack of the Movies
3D, it's a parody
Of a bunch of movies including Terminator
And you know
Alien, Mummy
It's got 3D glasses and you can play
It is an on-rails
Shooter game and what makes it
Even more bizarre is it's coming out on
360 as well, how the fuck is that
Gonna work
With the analog sticks I guess
Horrible decision
And then of course Alan Wake making its way
Out on Xbox 360
And they're also doing the limited edition
For that this week as well
And that's
Basically it
It's just J100 Matt in our chat room
That play was better than a DS
Master email
Oh I'm sorry, how did I miss this
I must have scrolled too quickly
Imagine Animal Doctor Care Center on DS
And then a better game
Blue Dragon Awaken Shadows
Come out on DS as well
Blue Dragon
I got a good one
He's on, FIRED
Rob
That's the slow Rob
And of course one week from today
Super Mario Galaxy 2
Going to Japan and looking at the release dates
On the Xbox 360, Lost Planet 2
Senko no Ronde Duo
Comes out on the Xbox 360 as well
That is
An updated version of an old game
That's now on the Xbox 360
New graphics and everything
Tropico 3 also, again these are Japanese
Release dates and the Xbox 360 is getting
A whole little bundle for Lost Planet 2
There you go
Going over to the Playstation 3 and looking at
What's coming out there
Another Lost Planet 2
The port for the PS3 is coming out there
World Soccer winning 11 2010
Aoki Samurai no Chosen
Comes out there as well
There's also a brand new
Hori Pad if you want to check that out
If you are into the Japanese peripherals
You can look at that
On the Nintendo Wii this week, not a lot
World Soccer winning 11 2010 comes out this week
Next week, just so you know, is the Japanese
Release of Red Steel 2
They don't have that game yet
On the Playstation 2
Tier Nanog is getting a price reduction
Coming out, there's also a port of World Soccer
Winning 11 2010 and a few games
In the Lucien Bees series
There's Evil Violet and Justice Yellow
So I'm guessing those are like Pokemon
E types of games
On the Nintendo DS, Captain Tsubasa
Gekitou no Kiseki
Comes out this week
That is a soccer type of game
I guess with all the winning 11, the DS wants in on the action
It's also a manga
Different game, oh is it, is it a soccer manga type of thing?
Yeah
And then coming out on the PSP
Heganni no Rekinjutsushi
Full Metal Alchemist
Yakuzoku no Hiei
Yes, it's a Full Metal Alchemist game
On the PSP
As to what type of game it is
I think you actually kind of get to play
As Ed and Al
You get to
I don't know if it's like a
Kind of like a little 3D adventure game
With a lot of cut scenes and dialogue
So it's a
I think it'll do Full Metal Alchemist fans
Some justice there, so check that out
On the PSP this week in Japan
Those are Japanese release dates
In the UK
We have on the 18th Dragon Age
Origins, Darkspawn Chronicles
On the 21st
Mud Nation Racers, Morphex
Prince of Persia, The Forgotten Sands
All Star Karate
Red Dead Redemption
and Rooms the Main Building
Oh yeah, and Split Second Velocity
Busy week
Yep
Alright
More gaming news and then the classic game of the week
Coming right up and
Dark Sakura, I'm not going to spoil what the game is
This week, but she just picked a game where she's like
Yeah, pretty much everyone
Says this is a classic
So we'll get to that in a little bit
To put it a little bit more
It's a game that
Dan and I played a lot of when we first
Got together
It has sentimental value
Alright, we'll get to that in just a moment, Loki
Apparently, you know, we kind of alluded to this
A little bit last week when we were talking about
Mega Man Universe
The trademark that was filed by Capcom
Recently
Well, it's been announced that
Capcom is working on an MMO
Called Mega Man Online
And according to
GameSpot, they're saying it's being
co-developed by Korea's
NeoWiz Games
They're responsible for EA Sports
FIFA Online
And
Possibly
Possibly might be related to the Mega Man
Universe game
Well, maybe it's
Could be different names, different regions
Yeah
You never know
I don't know
That's kind of neat
I don't know what they're really going to do for a Mega Man Online game
But it'll be pretty awesome, I'm sure
I'm going to kind of approach this with a big
Huh
It's just kind of like
How would a Mega Man Online game
Work?
But then I think about Mega Man Legends
And I'm like, huh
This could be interesting
I'm not sure how yet
Or imagine if you're not really playing as Mega Man
But imagine if you got to be like your own
Robot Master boss
That'd be kind of rad, actually
I don't know, there's just
Things that make you go hmm
There's definitely a big hmm factor with this
I don't know, I don't know what to think
I'll need to see screenshots or something
Do you think you'll get to see more of this at E3?
It might be a little early, but
That'd be kind of neat if they announced something
Very cool
Alright, well we'll see what happens
With Mega Man Online
DarkSakura, do you like the idea
Of Mega Man going online, or is it
Enough of the freaking MMOs already?
It's a good idea
Yay for whoever wants to play it
Good for them
Ask Star Trek Online, dude
Even if you got to be a Robot Master boss
There's no Robot Master boss you'd want to be
Well
No
Alright
It's Sakura Woman
Loki could finally have Pizza Man
For reals
That reference is about 5 years old on this show
Pizza Man
I think there's a clip of that
Let me tell you how old that reference is
There's a clip of that on our
MySpace
Oh, we were talking about the Mega Man 2
Sound effect thing
Yeah, there you go, you got it
Alright, one more story for you guys
We were talking about music games a little bit earlier
In the show, it's very interesting
Because apparently there are rumors
If you want to believe this Swedish retailer
Webhallen
They are believing that a Pearl Jam
Rock band is in the
Works
Apparently some box art has leaked out
Although this could be one of those mock ups
To get you to pre-order things
MTV is saying up and down
They have not announced anything besides
Green Day Rock Band and Rock Band 3
But they are quick to say
We have a great relationship with Pearl Jam
And hope to have many of their more awesome music in the game
In the future
Hmm
Here's where I have a problem with this right now
They've
Given it a Peggy rating on the box art
This early
The fact that they haven't even announced the game yet
It would not have a rating
It would be rating pending
Very good point
It's fake
Wishful thinking basically
I mean, I don't know
I kind of go, okay, yeah, I could see Pearl Jam
Getting their own rock band
We've talked about this on the show before
There's only certain bands that can have a rock band
Not every band
Is worthy of having a rock band game
Dedicated to them, but Pearl Jam, okay
There was a survey that came out
That was asking people what dedicated rock band
Games would you like to see, which artists
Would you want to see have their game
And Pearl Jam was on the list
So I think it's a little bit wishful thinking
It's kind of like how
With, you know, even if you look at GameStop's
Website and stuff like that
There's a bunch of listings for games
Like pilot wings for the Wii and stuff like that
Stuff that doesn't exist
That they're taking pre-orders on
Just in case, you know
That kind of stuff
That rock band ABBA, that's the one I want
By the way, apparently
Yeah, they are doing
That little test right now
But there's also some news about how well these games
Are selling
The NPD group is saying that Guitar Hero Van Halen
Only sold 94,000 copies
Which kind of makes it a poop
However, it's hard to say
Does that count the free ones that went out?
Because that sort of would
Kind of screw those numbers, wouldn't it?
It's copies sold
So I would imagine, yes it does
Well to put it in perspective, Guitar Hero Aerosmith
Sold 2.7 million copies
Guitar Hero Metallica
Sold 1 million copies
Beetle Rock Band, 1.2 million copies
Guitar Hero Aerosmith
Sold twice as many
As Beetle's rock band
Well, think about it though, Guitar Hero Aerosmith
Was first, it was the first
Kind of, you know
One group exclusive
Game that came out, and it seems like the numbers
Have slowly gone down since then
And the Van Halen just kind of pooped
You know, it didn't do much, but it's hard to say
Because again, they were given that away for free
Can you really trust that number? I don't know
It'll be very interesting to see how the
Guitar Hero Green Day sells
You know what's also not accounted for in here
I'm sorry, did I say Guitar Hero Green Day?
I meant Rock Band Green Day
What's also not accounted for in here is the
ACDC Rock Band game that came out
I don't see that in here anywhere
It was like a live ACDC game, it was exclusive to
Walmart for a little while, but then it wasn't
I don't see numbers for that anywhere in here
Because there's no numbers for that
Probably, and just for reference
On the Peggy website
There is no listing for that new Rock Band game
If it had a rating, it would be listed on there
See? Analist Loki
Squelching the rumors
Right here at Orange Lounge Radio
Alright
Just out of curiosity though, if they did
Do a band based game
A one band game, is there any band you'd want to see?
No
Dark Soccer, any bands you think are deserving of their full
Rock Band game?
Electric Light Orchestra!
Sorry, I've been on an ELO kick lately
ABBA Rock Band, you think I'm kidding?
Radiohead Rock Band
I would be down with a Radiohead Rock Band actually
But I just don't see Radiohead as the type of band
That would want to be a part of that
And you know
I know they said, oh well on the Rock Band Network
It could happen
I would like to see some drum based tracks
Come out on Rock Band
Like, you know, get some Pendulum in there
Something like that
I mean that would be pretty cool
With some guitar stuff in there
I guess it would be really difficult to do on drums
But it would be neat to see
Bobby Blackwolf in our chat room
He's getting a lot of comments tonight
But he's saying some good stuff
Well that was a track pack
It wasn't actually a separate game
It wasn't listed as a separate game, it was a track pack
Yes but Bobby, technically you can play it by itself
Therefore it is kind of a separate game
I get what he's saying though
It's in the vein of those country packs
And the things they sold individually
But yeah, I thought of it as a separate game
Could you buy the ACDC stuff?
You can buy it and play it by itself
I didn't think you could buy it from within Rock Band
No, you can't buy it within Rock Band
You can buy the track pack
You can buy it by itself or dump it into your game
Donovan's suggesting Village People Rock Band
Blackwolf again says
I'd like to see Rush or U2
Funny T-Man says
Golden Girls Rock Band
There you go
It could be the Betty White version of
Thank You for Being a Friend from Saturday Night Live a couple weeks ago
Anyhow, let's get into
Speaking of old classics
Because when doesn't the Golden Girls seem to come up on this show lately?
Old classics!
Because I want to be Betty White when I grow up
Dark Soccer likes to dig through the gaming vault
And find a game that she says
Hey, hey, listen
Hey, listen
You kids ought to be playing this game
It's the classic video game of the week
And I think though this week
She's managed to pick a game that
Most people have played
But if you haven't
What the hell? Seriously
Where the hell have you been?
Let's get to it
Dark Soccer, what is the classic game of the week?
Super Mario 64
Yeah, this
I have to say
This is one of my favorite ever
Nintendo 64 games
Probably one of my favorite
It's up there in my list of favorites
It was, you know
The first real dive
Into 3D for Mario
And it was one of those games
That controller just seemed to be made for
But I love the music
Can you turn it up for a minute?
I love the early level
I also love that you can go up to
A sleeping piranha plant
And punch him in the face
Cause look, he's about to do it here too
But that was like, there were just so many
Little fun things, you know, you could do the wall jump
You could also glitch the game hardcore
And just beat it right from the very get go
If you were really good at the wall jump
See, he punched the piranha plant in the face
Sure did, in the face
Mario's hardcore like that
He's a thug
At any rate
The game starts off
At Princess Peach's castle
And she writes him a letter
And says, I baked you a cake
Even though I'm a princess and have servants
To do it for me
I think it was also the first game in the US
Where we got her name as being Peach
If you think about it though, she is a princess
She could take credit for what her servants did
And their, you know
I baked this for you
By me, I mean I own these servants that made it for you
I want to say she was actually Peach
In Mario 3
I think, well I know Mario Kart
Was on Super Nintendo and that was before this
I'm pretty sure Mario 3 called her Peach
At any rate
You go through
The entire game
And it's kind of neat because
Not only is it
The different levels you have to go through
You have 8 different ways of going through
A lot of these levels
You have to beat them in different ways
So it was very innovative
And a good way to reuse
Levels in different means
And that theme kept coming back in later
3D Mario games
Like in Sunshine and I think in Galaxy
You had different ways of beating the levels
And that was pretty cool
You could get different things like the Metal Cap
Where you turn like into
Shiney crue Mario
Like bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang
Bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang
There. How's that
Yes
And you can find a pink Bob-omb Buddy
Wooo. He's pink
and there were you also had coins that you used for your life so and you know
you could also you know there was like I said the wall jump you could do a triple
jump you can flip you can do all kinds of extra stuff but it actually started
off as Super Mario FX when Miyamoto is working on Star Fox so it was originally
gonna be a Super FX game for the SNES but it couldn't quite reach what he
wanted to do so basically he I think I think he pulled an avatar on this dusted
it off out of a drawer decided oh technologists caught up let's do it and
then I love the sliding levels too you just fell down a hole though and you
you can move the camera around and it does have a fairly set path you can go
but you can just run around and do stuff and explore and even if you're like
trying to beat a certain way if like if you're doing a certain mission that has
you beat the level a certain way you can actually do it the other way you know if
you just decide to do that but it's it's really just you know pretty cool and
also the music and it was done by Koji Kondo who is one of my personal heroes
and it was one of the first ones that had Charles Martinet to do the voice
he's so cool he's so cool he was cool to meet you know so yeah it's I think in
that list of one of you know best games ever and dude punching a piranha plant
in the face you know grabbing Koop you know Bowser by the tail and swinging
them around and throwing them off a building you know Mario turned into a
thug in this game and also if you want to see something incredibly fun go on
YouTube and just watch speed runs but now the the really interesting thing
with this game for me is that Dan and I we spent because he had a Nintendo 64
we know we don't we didn't actually have nearly the collection that we do now
when we first moved in together we had maybe about 20 video game systems then
maybe 15 something like that and you know I moved out here with like my Super
Nintendo and stuff but he had a Nintendo 64 and we just played the stew out of
this game and you know we put the rumble pack and we had a lot of fun it was just
really really cool and I actually have the Nintendo DS one it's actually a
little harder to play but you know you place Yoshi Luigi and Wario and it looks
a little bit better and it's got minigames and multiplayer mode and it's
pretty good there is there was a direct sequel plan for the Nintendo 64 double D
and Miyamoto it started at 97 and it was gonna be released in 99 but because the
64 double D didn't make it my husband just decided to pop his head in the door
and said that the movie he was watching was awesome what movie were they
watching kick-ass no kick-ass good times but because 64 double D pretty much
flopped it we basically got Super Mario sunshine on the Gamecube and then we got
Super Mario Galaxy of course we're getting into the Super Mario Galaxy so
this game has a special place in my heart that and when you win the game
peach makes you a cake like she promised good for her all right well there it is
your classic game of the week Super Mario 64 now I want to give a quick
counter opinion this is not my favorite Mario game in the series I did not like
the transition to 3d very much I understand a lot of people are all
excited about it but I don't know I I had a really hard time with this game
after the awesomeness that were the Super Nintendo Mario games I don't know
the switch to 3d never felt right for me but oddly enough I was okay with Mario
Sunshine I know that makes me weird I'm all sorts of weird but whatever all
right anyhow our weirdo Rob I am weird it's fine it's fine I'm ideal with it
okay anyhow let's go ahead and take a break here at Orange Lounge Radio we got
more gaming news we want to get to in part B tonight we haven't gotten to yet
in fact you know the huge news about a free game that's available we're gonna
get to I mean I'm sure everybody's already downloaded it but if you haven't
we'll tell you more about it in a minute plus movie news movies turning into
games games turning into movies lots of news like that and a little more Red
Dead Redemption and rapid-fire news and your calls when we come back with more
of Orange Lounge Radio welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on this
Sunday May the 16th of 2010 where we are taping the 357th episode no 67th yeah I
lost count I was talking about that earlier in the show 367th episode of our
show as we do every week at all games radio www.allgames.com live here on
Sunday nights we've talked about a lot of different news in part 8 tonight
talking about you know EA's controversial new $10 thing talking
about used games at Walmart and our gaming weeks were quite long tonight
everybody's doing something Dark Sakura went to Pinagogo and I was playing 3d
game heroes and look you still playing Grand Theft Auto that's all right good
times all right speaking of Loki he's gonna start off some quick news topics
before we get back into some longer discussion so quick quick what's on your
mind tonight Loki ah yes apparently there is another dance game coming to
the Wii and funny enough this actually has a tie back into one of the shows
that I wasn't a part of but Rob had hosted while back and it's a kids bop
dance party the video game you might ask how did that even you know the fuck did
that come up on olr I don't even remember it wasn't on olr it was on
vanilla sky because I wanted to spin off shows yeah oh oh god yes oh yeah we had
the kids bop thing yes the kids bop trivia game where if you got the trivia
question wrong the volume of this song that was my favorite games we ever did
where if you got the trivia questions wrong the kids bop music got louder yes
and it would distract you from getting future and see they should make a real
game show out of that I'm a genius I invented that game all by myself the
game will be launching September 21st will feature 24 contemporary hits as
they put it in quotes there including and if you haven't heard of kids bop
it's basically kids singing you know popular songs so imagine all your
favorite and not so favorite songs and like from a top 40 radio station just
kind of like thrown down the garbage disposal and that's like a kid's music
yes the Benny Hill theme came up inadvertently oops the Benny Hill theme
unfortunately not part of the kids bop dance party video game you know it's
funny total mistake did intend for that music to play but somehow fitting yes
such songs in this will be of course Lady Gaga's paparazzi Michael Jackson's
thriller thanks get the party started and yeah it's gonna include a free play
challenge dance-off shop and dress-up modes and it will feature two players
that can dance cooperatively or go to head-to-head lame but not really my
target demographic but then again just dance sold million copies so what do I
know about games I guess apparently nothing if you are a collector of such
odd game peripherals as I don't know the chainsaw controller for Resident Evil
or I guess in this case Dragon Quest it's gonna be getting its own Dragon
Quest monsters battle road victory it's a Wii game that was a port of an arcade
game that's based on collectible cards but the actual controller like the
arcade has two giant buttons and a giant sword that looks like it's basically the
sword in the stone that you have to interact with as well the controller
will cost the 12,800 yen of the equivalent of $137 US and will be out in
Japan this summer so if you're a big collector of odd peripherals this will
be coming to you from Hori and then finally of course we've been hearing
about a lot of cameos of characters in lost planet 2 including you know Dom
from Gears of War well now of course you know Sony's got to have their characters
in there as well not really making it in for the launch but there will be some
free download content coming out soon that will include the Helghast
characters from the Killzone series that you'll be able to play as in lost
planet 2 and they have a few different versions of those that you get to play
as so those will be available for free on the PlayStation Network in June can I
pitch a dream game to you guys real quick and all our dream game possible I
just want to pitch it to you guys and see what you guys think okay the crew
from Kidz Bop meets Gwar
that'd be weird and I don't know like maybe could be like a point-and-click
type of game like in the vein of you know Sam & Max and those types of games
where like the you play as the the folks from Gwar and you're trying to find the
people from Kidz Bop and like corrupt them and or murder them I will one-up
that okay okay I'll one up that please we need to launch a new CD series called
Gwar Bop they basically take score and have saying all these different
temporary hits as they put it hey hey I I'd play that I would do good stuff
alright and then we'll make it come full circle and put it out of the game alright
so possibly coming to a PC near you alright moving on let's talk about some
other quick news halo 2 yes there were still some holdouts playing halo 2
online you might remember there were guys that were refusing to pull their
neck connection and what's kind of weird is that Microsoft you would think would
have just like like put the ban hammer down on them a long time ago but they
kind of thought it was funny and they they let it go like as long as they
could hold out their connections and so forth and the last man standing was
Apache and for sir was the gamertag and he was finally removed he says he was
kicked off but you know kicked off could mean that his Comcast connection sucks
balls because that's what's been happening to me on World of Warcraft
these past couple weeks tech came to my house and everything said he couldn't
find anything wrong like yeah I guess I'm just fucking crazy yeah that's just
our crappy service it's a feature so anyhow whatever I so he finally got
booted whether it was by Microsoft or his cable provider who knows but it was
at 11 o'clock or just before 11 o'clock pacific time may 10th 2010 he was out of
halo 2 which means that's it for the original Xbox Live that was the official
last connection on Xbox Live rest in pieces who that could be like the tag
line for war versus kid Bob surezo in chat suggests I kids bought versus
Capcom I remember that from a couple weeks ago yes you can now play Gameboy
games on your nest yes your actual NES that's right not not talking about the
Super Gameboy that was for the Super Nintendo no it's a device that was
created by this guy on the Nintendo age forums who calls himself bunny boy it's
called retro vision and you plug the car into the Nintendo put your Gameboy game
in there and you're good to go this is even more awesome it has the
expansion port on it too so you can use your Gameboy printer remember the
Gameboy printer what a worthless piece of shit that thing was huh huh didn't
they have like a hidden DJ game in that though the the printer software the what
software the printer software that came with the actual printer does it I don't
remember yeah there's a little like game in there or I don't know one I didn't
pay for one all right I just remember seeing the features and I thought gee
that was stupid can I put my own receipts on it oh that might be good I
don't know I game room updates there's now we have to start covering these two
we got rock band releases virtual console releases now we have game room
releases as well this week you missed battle zone Canyon bomber Keystone
capers for the 2600 Canyon bomber is also the 2600 version not the arcade
version mega zone for the arcade night driver for the Atari 2600 oink for the
2600 and soccer for the Intellivision interesting thing about game room the
game packs that you're downloading are actually two weeks worth of games it's
just that half of them stay locked for a week so if you downloaded you know
something that was in last week's pack like pitfall you already had this week's
pack waiting to go interesting huh although you would have should have been
able to guess that because games pack one and two are like 15 games apiece so
game pack three rolls around and it's you know another 50 megabytes it's
actually 15 more games go figure well some of the games have been announced
for the next pack that is coming out and that is going to be coming out on May
19th because it looks like what is that Wednesday is gonna be game room day yeah
asteroids for the arcade you know we already have asteroids deluxe but you
get original asteroids this time demons two diamonds was a 2600 game that's
coming out this week as well Grand Prix from Activision shark shark space duel
it was an arcade game it was kind of like a souped-up asteroids I guess you
could say probably I think the biggest release this week stampede is coming out
this week on the 2600 oh I have fond memories of stampede we went to the
classic gaming Expo I participated in like the official stampede scoreboard
that twin galaxies was doing I think I got like next to last place I'm that
good at stampede time pilot is also coming out May 19th but time pilots
already available on Xbox Live just so you know for five bucks and you get the
souped-up version so if you want to buy time pilot for game room that's on you
but you'll get the opportunity this week to buy it all over again if you want
it's all about money that's right Monday Monday Monday and speaking of all about
money how about our rock band releases for the week as yay what is wrong with
my computer well where do I begin I'm just kidding
seriously it frees up or something no it's opening 50,000 windows when I'm
trying to yikes spam spam spam no lose weight increase your penis yes it's no
because it's completely screwing up now so all right that's fine I'll go to some
chat room comments chat that orange on trade calm salacious pop says demons and
diamonds was a paddle game though with it was a big twisty knob paddle and
trackball for game room please I somewhat agree although I don't think at
the end of the day I would be able to justify buying a trackball for my Xbox
because I know it costs like 30 to 40 bucks and what am I gonna play with it
Crystal Castles whoo I don't know although you know in theory they do they
do need to have better support for that so it's a prey hack that together playing
Crystal Castles on the joystick or the little Xbox 360 controller just just it
stinks it stinks all right so we have I've got everything pulled up now I had
to basically reload it all our rock band download content actually is pretty cool
we've got a Grateful Dead pack which includes beat it on down the line
Cumberland blues scarlet begonias throwing stones touch of gray and US
blues and then two songs by the smithereens and I like the smithereens
is one of my groups I really liked when I was in high school is a girl like you
and only a memory those are both really good songs for some project new town
news their big event is going to have a Cirque du Soleil performance you Cirque
du Soleil but it'll be on June 13th so look forward to feats of flexibility or
as my friend calls it Cirque du Soguet I know right and then Bayonetta the
director Kamiya Hideki he basically doesn't like that there's a Bayonetta
doujinshi like hentai doujinshi about Bayonetta getting getting it on well I
mean she's kind of sexy that means you've got a popular product hi the more
you know I I have personally Sega should be fucking excited that they have like a
new franchise here you know what I mean well I mean trust me you go to cons and
see how much Final Fantasy 7 doujin there were you know I've got a ton
myself of other series that I won't need I actually have some Final Fantasy 7
doujinshi doesn't everyone this interesting um but um and I have a few
roni kenshin ones too but anyway um he's basically quoted saying it seems
there's pornographic doujinshi based off Bayonetta there are fans who will resent
that and I hardly think those responsible hold any love for the game
dude get get your head out your butt dude um there was though Chris is it
dalen or dalen there's a quote from him and I actually like this and this is
actually a point that I've had with you know some of these games that guys can
go and get outfits for their female characters and you know I always laughed
that WrestleMania was like dress-up for for boys you know because they could
customize their wrestler and you know but um the quote saying guys tell
themselves they shouldn't listen to fashion they're terrified if they spend
enough time playing as Bayonetta being Bayonetta and witnessing the power of
her high heels and endless tresses well at some point they'll stop objectifying
her they want to be her she won't invite our gaze as much as grip it until she
sucked us into a vortex of overpowering femininity I like that a vortex of
overpowering femininity that should be on the box can we get an iTunes review
for our show that says that
boo power a vortex of overpowering feminine is that what they're calling
her bits now it's a vortex all right some other gaming news and of course
we'll get to the skype line the mailbag and all that fun stuff in just a little
bit but some other new stories first starting off with Loki yes you know it's
like every week we hear about another game franchise being turned into a movie
and each one you was perceived with more of a eye roll than the next well this
shouldn't be a surprise rollercoaster tycoon is now becoming a movie thanks to
Sony pictures what how does that even work it's just gonna be a movie about
people liking theme parks and building theme parks it'll be some stupid plot
like you know rollercoaster park a versus be like some scandal it's it's
gonna be like Wall Street but cute and about theme parks right can be awful
awful I don't know what anybody really want to watch rollercoaster tycoon I
don't know well it's being developed as a live-action CGI hybrid at Sony
pictures animation is it gonna be in 3d I'll probably and I guess it's being
worked on by Harold as worked the director of the upcoming karate kid
remake he will be taking an executive producer role alright before we get to
more news I am completely forgot to do like a segment that we usually do on the
show with Twitter topics oops we should do those now Twitter topics every week
you send us your tweets at twitter.com slash OLR and we read some of our
favorite tweets live on air here if I remember to do them all right let's see
let's do this story isn't that ironic Tiger Claw actually tweeted us that
rollercoaster tycoon story but he also tweeted this one so I'll do this one
this has to do with video game injuries you somebody like gotta like bloody nose
thing that's gross I'm looking sorry this is a great radio I'm looking at a
pictures linked at asylum calm healing this on Twitter here what the hell
happened here I guess these guys got injured it was Call of Duty modern
warfare 2 and he was playing against a few friends and his mother asked him to
get his daughter's PJs wait so your mother had to tell you to get your
daughter's boy all right so that he didn't realize that the Xbox Live
headset was wrapped around his chairs arm so when he got up quickly BAM the
wire got caught and the head smashed right into my Mac which was sitting on a
stereo a few feet off the ground ow so he got up quickly and BAM hit his head
that looks hurtful so he went to the hospital and thanks to him I love this
but a few hours later he was online fragging again thanks to a real-life
painkiller perk prescribed by the doctor
thank you like it in all right there you go thank you Tiger Claw 305 on Twitter
for sending us that link tweets from blue swim here Twitter question what
franchise that hasn't had a game yet during the current generation would you
like to see get a modern game what game that hasn't gotten a modern game yet
during this generation would you like to see get a game well there's always the
good old standby the Guardian legend I mean hello or kid Icarus there's always
a lot of people clamoring to get a new kid Icarus game a new fantasy zone yeah
okay that's fair the adventures of opa we got afterburner there's like a new
afterburner with a crime and a lot of the old stuff is new again and maybe
finally release planet Harrier here's here's my number one answer though in
all honesty blue swim especially if you want to go just to the last generation
of something we haven't seen yet f0 k thanks that's the one game I really
would like to see a new one of except unfortunately I think if I really want
to like a new f-zero game it's going to have to be on the Xbox or the
PlayStation 3 and that's not gonna happen 30 tried it there and it sucked
did they you remember is that a game from koei I put wipeout wipeout HD is
kind of fun it's cool mmm Sega in our chat room says Star Fox that's a good
one too but it has to be actual Star Fox not the adventures or what the hell was
that I'm gonna get what the hell what the hell fuck adventures yeah star
fucking adventures all right let's see also blue swim wants to give an FYI hey
did you know that Amazon is giving a $20 gaming credit on your next order when
you buy Super Mario Galaxy 2 from them no I did not know that but I probably
won't be buying Mario Galaxy 2 my Wii isn't even hooked up right now it is not
gonna get hooked up again until Metroid other M comes out I'm telling you right
now unless Mario Galaxy 2 like I play it at someone else's house and I'm like oh
my god I'm missing out oh my god but there's just so many other games coming
out right now between blur and split-second you know and all these
other racing games that I'm just like you know what yeah hey Rob a buzz in
chat and suggests the adventures of Lolo and yes I'm serious hey Lolo was actually
a pretty freaking rad NES game that never really got a new version you know
what else was on the old-school NES that I don't remember ever seeing later was
and I bet Jamie would know more about this but she left the room real quick
my lawn secret castle remember that game yeah good times did they ever do a sequel
I think they did do like one sequel a little what little one dark tissue wants
to plug the latest retro review rear view all about the x68000 it's on our
website at orange lounge radio.com check it out retro rear view actual content on
orange I saw an actual game review on there too I know what's this about like
wait this is in our side of my community awesome we don't have to do anything
all right I'd rather reviews on there but it's by the time I get around to
putting a review up there it's too late oh shit excellent in chat room excellent
choice star tropics 3 how about that I'll be amazing that should be what 3d
dot game heroes just rips off an X should be star tropics that was a great
game all right hey entertainment also sends us this tweet call of duty has
been making money off multiplayer practically since the launch of the 360
but they sell products EAS P is a service sure why don't I link read this
one Tiger Claw 305 sends us another Twitter topic it's a link from MTV
multiplayer blog apparently cliffy B has said that mass effect let me read this
quote quote the thing that was cool is that mass effect is kind of an RPG for
me with the cover-based shooting I think there's a reason why it's been
successful because gamers love gears God get your just take your ego and shove
it up your ass here's something like that I would like to thank myself for
making Mass Effect 2 such a great game because if I put my game out no one
would know first-person shooters are in the window epic first-person shooters
you know I I'm sorry with all due respect I'm awesome I'm not gonna read
the rest of stories I don't give a shit what he thinks yes I'm also awesome
thank you Tiger Claw for trying but I'll just tell you in a nutshell he says mass
effect is the Star Wars for the new generation I'm the Dane Cook oh you know
what no no what you are like the episode 2 of this generation the Yoda fight was
cool but come on get over yourself all right although I gotta say with all due
respect to Cliffy be the shadow complex on Xbox Live Arcade was pretty fucking
rat I gotta say I gotta say shadow runner in chat says Cliffy needs to suck
sucking to quit sucking his own dot dot dot you know what um let's see here and
last tweet I'm gonna read here from Jay Jugo says scare so in chat that's how I
say it scares oh I should have known that oh well whatever scares oh thanks
you for mentioning the double down this is my first live olr show so far so epic
and also wants to send a quick thank you to Jamie for your pick for the classic
game of the week oh well you're quite welcome woot there you go those are the
Twitter topics I'm sorry for ignoring you for one whole story you know I just
remembered and this is totally random I don't even know why I just remember this
but I saw earlier this weekend like huh that's not my should mention on the show
because we talked about it before and we kind of were hoping they would come to
other platforms remember that game that I kind of hated because it was basically
a ripoff of House of the Dead Rock of the Dead it was a game that you know it's
like typing of the dead but you use your guitar controller to I remember that
it's coming up this fall but it's actually not just coming out in the Wii
this time it's actually gonna be coming on 360 and PlayStation 3 as well as the
Wii well done is it please tell me it's a budget title please please uh I don't
remember I don't remember that part but still called Rock of the Dead so called
Rock of the Dead awesome look and I realize you guys are saying like you
know I and I seem to remember when Rock of the Dead first came up on this show a
lot of people were saying lawsuit it's gonna be a lawsuit but like seriously
after playing 3d game heroes it's a parody that's all they have to say it's
a parody and we're like Loki when you play 3d game heroes and dark Sakura if
you do at some point you know you really should check it out because it'll tickle
your retro funny bone tell me it's not just a complete effing ripoff oh I can
tell that without playing it but that's okay I'm fine that Zelda's a good game
it needs to be ripped off more often hey there was already new topia all right
huge news this week everybody's been talking about this and you know we got
to say something about this to steam for the Mac came out this week it included
57 games at launch including torchlight that's actually game I played a little
bit of this week I like me some torchlight was out there for 10 bucks on
steam for the Mac but the best deal of all free free game portal free zero
dollars free nothing may tell May 24th and they didn't want the Mac users to
have all the fun there because if they only gave it away for free on the Mac
you'd have people like Loki that would be like that's my Loki impression that
they didn't give it out for free on the PC although I'll bet Loki didn't
download it nope but you really should it is really a great game but I you know
we all know what the trick is here it's a it's an asshole game at this point
it's a great game and you should do it if you've never played it you need to
play it but the trick is it's kind of the Trojan horse to get steam on your
computer because once steam is on your computer then you're gonna see these
sales civilization three complete edition one dollar and 25 cents buy it
that's what's been getting me well I said when when loom went down to four
bucks you know I was on that yeah and you and dark soccer look dark soccer she
even bought the pink anus game I did by the penis game and you know what it's
crap but she bought it and that's all they care about at the end of the day
yeah it's it's read ratings please people SSJ 100 Matt says can't get any
cheaper than free unless you're Yaris mmm true SAG in our term says they needed
to demonstrate the steam play concept so it's free on both platforms absolutely
it's kind of the Trojan horse but you know it it it's a win-win situation you
win because you get a free game and you don't get like I in and to reference the
other chat comment you don't get some crappy free game you get a great game of
the year caliber game for free but the trade-off is they win because they just
installed your thing on your computer so you're not tempted to go get you know
direct-to-drive or the windows gaming platform which granted I know is not on
the Mac but you know you know what I mean same thing they get that on your
computer and then you're seeing all the sales and you're like oh shit I can get
torchlight for $10 maybe I should get that so there you go all of that's
available on the Mac some of the other games you might want to check out that
are available on the Mac right now braid let's see is a big one some of the
Indiana Jones games loom you can play on the Mac now yes salmon max devil's
playhouse tales monkey island season 1 torchlight which I definitely recommend
if you liked if you even just like thought Diablo 2 was kind of cool you
should get torchlight it's pretty much the same fucking game and have a better
set for which of course you know I have a big boner for all things civilization
so I'm excited that the Mac fans can play that on steam well I think that was
I think sit for was already available on the Mac I could be wrong all right more
news mailbag coming up in a little bit to dark Sakura yes more stuff um this is
about the rating system in Australia there is and actually so fairly I would
have to say a big percentage approves that there should be 98% actually said
that there should be an r18 plus rating so we're thinking where things are
restricted to 18 and over it's been proposed before but now it's like that
that's what the people want so who knows but that's there's actually though some
from other special interest groups though that were saying that only 53%
actually approve of it but numbers lie statistics can be budged it's funny you
talk about statistics because some of the interesting chat comments I'm
reading right now about the whole steam thing you know they're a little delayed
so we get comments from the last story say is saying now we'll have stats for
how many Mac users will buy games or to clarify publicly accessible stats for
Mac users who will buy games interesting some other comments Robert M says I've
been anticipating torchlight for quite some time but didn't want to invest in
Windows 7 and partitioning for boot camp donovan says he'll wait for Diablo 3
yourself but I think torchlights pretty good deal with the one thing torchlight
is missing is multiplayer but seriously it's like 10 bucks that's that's great
it's a great deal for a single-player game really is anyhow alright so moving
on with some more news stories looking yes so it's interesting because you
know there's already been screenshots people are not really screenshots but
people taking pictures of you know Red Dead Redemption because it's been coming
in early to a few different stores and one of the screenshots or I should say
box shots that they got of the game on PlayStation 3 shows that there's some
exclusive content included for the PlayStation 3 version now I mean not
trying to sound biased or anything it doesn't sound all that wonderful but
here's what you get you get Solomon's Solomon's folly gang hideout which is
basically kind of a safe house in the game and then you also get the Walton
gang outfit the Walton gang is the kind of villain in the game and John boy yes
this is exclusive for the PlayStation 3 not quite as wonderful as you know
exclusive download content like that was on Grand Theft Auto episodes from Liberty
City but you know maybe this stuff will come out later on as you know something
paid for on the Xbox 360 I know there is some more free download content coming
out later on so who knows but hey anything extra is kind of good so you
know if you're getting on the ps3 there's a little bonus for you who know
that it might be enough to sway some people even if it's like a little you
never know people that have both I know it's not that big a deal there's like
other there's tons of outfits you can get in the game and lots of different
things you can find safe houses and stuff I don't really know if this stuff
is really gonna do it for you but whatever if that's me if you really want
to get into both systems you're not sure which one maybe that's way all right
some other news coming out this week how many of y'all have seen the movie cube
there's a little in my love cube too but not the original cube no I like the
first one but the second one I okay I'm just to go say a little bit about it
it's it's an indie film and describe what cube is about but you gotta start
with the first one with the first one these people basically wake up in
different rooms that are all there's a hatch above a hatch below and a hatch on
each wall and it starts off with a pretty gory death because some of the
rooms are trapped and so as it goes they they each run into each other as they go
through the cube and find out that each of them has a specific skill some people
have been left with their glasses some people have been left with you know
something in their pocket there's a crazy lady and her skill is being crazy
no she was a doctor right yeah the doctor but um but it's it's that you
know these people are stuck in in the cube and their whole point is trying to
figure out the way out and basically while they're moving from room to room
they all know they had they didn't have what the cube 2 was one with crazy lady
the first one had the autistic boy yes they they basically find out that the
rooms are moving mm-hmm and then G spoiler that's why it's all I just like
it's like over 10 years old this point and that and that basically the autistic
boy is some sort of savant with numbers and figures out that it's like prime
numbers go into the right room and they figure out which way the rooms are going
to be that lead to the exit right where the exit is so it's all and now cube 2 I
love it because it's called hyper cube meaning a tesseract wait it's not
electric boogaloo no I mean I like that one because I love theoretical physics I
I don't have the brain for the math or anything I just love reading about it
wait so the cube was like traveling through time and space as well exactly
Wow the fourth dimension being time Wow so and it had like this really weird
ending and also the cube 2 inspired a whole mod for a half-life when they're
a cube zero at some point you were a cute cute the third one was cube zero
which is like a prequel and it was crap okay well how would you like to play a
video game based off cube she's raising her hand it might actually happen
believe it or not it's an interview that Vin Vincenzo is his name Vincenzo Natali
he was the director of the game and he was talking to MTV about the game the
film splice which is an upcoming movie that he did they for whatever reason
asked him about cube if he ever wanted to revisit the universe he said I would
very much like to do a cube game I'd love to do a game when I was writing it
with my writing partner we were saying to each other are we writing a film are
we writing a game it's always been amazing to me that no one has attempted
to turn it into a game I would very much like to do that that's how I would like
to get back into the cube world I guess that's true because there was the mod
right there's the mod based on hypercube he probably hasn't seen it and someone
actually recreated the end of the movie in using Gary's mod it does have a real
creepster ending to it actually the whole movie is kind of a downer and then
like like it really leaves you with more questions than you start the movie with
but it wasn't a bad movie it was just kind of like the fuck look that was my
reaction at the end was like the well it is what and it's it's a movie that I
think everyone needs to see at least once you know the movie that leaves you
talking and for a low-budget movie it was intelligently done I think it's
definitely one that's a thinker too so would it be a low-budget game well given
that you probably only need to make you know one environment over and over and
true well you know when they did when they did how they made the movie cheap
when they seriously is the same room and they turned them around and when they
did cube to they it was also relatively expensive they just had those white
walls of different lights behind them he's easy yeah it you don't nobody has
to bother by the way with the third movie it's SSJ 100 Matt is suggesting
Jamie if you like theoretical physics I would tell you to check out the movie
what the bleep do we know I've heard of that movie I don't want me to see it
actually you might have to like Netflix that or something all right in the
meantime though Jamie has no time to Netflix because she has to dive into the
mailbag and read your emails mailbag orange lounge radio.com every week you
guys send us emails to our mailbag and dark soccer will jump in read if you
possibly criticize their grammar and then we'll answer your questions here on
the show again that's mailbag at orange lounge radio.com although more and more
people have been submitting them through the website recently I guess there's a
forum you can fill out deep man does deep man makes the magic happen on the
website and he made it magical where people send us bleeps through the
website now only in dragon boy is actually dragon boy 69 is actually
sending us a tech support question and I have to read this because I think I
don't know if look you'll laugh I'm not sure if you can assist me with my issue
I have an iMac and just attempted to sign up to your site however when trying
to log in it goes to white screen with the words invalid token is this because
I'm on an iMac thank you in advance for any help you can provide me this matter
um no I don't think it's because you're on an iMac just well we'll help you
later I've seen the website do that before and I think it's because a lot of
people hit it at once sometimes like believe it or not we're kind of popular
use Firefox not Safari also just reload or use your back button and try to log
in again usually it will kind of work itself out if it keeps doing it to you
come back after like an hour we honestly don't know what causes it unfortunately
our website is a popular target for spammers and when they clog up the pipes
with their poop then it kind of prevents the rest of us from logging in but it
has nothing to do with the fact that you're on an iMac as far as we know the
websites worked on a Mac for me before it wasn't an iMac granted all right
hello olr I look forward to your show every week I do have a couple of
questions for olr what Sega model 1 or 2 or model 3 arcade games urgently needs
an Xbox Live conversion I'm really looking forward to Daytona USA or scud
race is it cut is it called super GT in the US I think so also I think super
hang-on needs a good update like Sega did to outrun I would agree with that
are you guys okay yeah that's the first one what do you think would make a good
release if they had some sort of gun control or any of the gun games would be
good like gun blade or even you know house of the dead or some that kind of
stuff planet Harrier that's Hikari that I don't care planet Harrier um can we
get doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo no I'm kidding actually that wouldn't be
bad I mean you could even have steering wheel support maybe it wouldn't have
drawing that would be cool are you guys planning on a new show for foreign
listeners after the mishaps of your previous effort that's right wasn't the
the euro show when the last computer just finally died it exploded yeah that's
right let's pick a date we will have to do that but it's gonna have to be like
in June at least yeah it's gonna be something it'll have to be at least June
because next week I'm gonna literally be running in here at the last second
because I'm going on a trip but and the weekend after by the way we won't be
here Memorial Day weekend we will not be here at least I won't be here and I
think that that's gonna be getting some shush I'm going to Oregon on it on a
getaway so we're doing that and so I'm not gonna be here and I imagine a lot of
listeners are probably gonna be doing their vacations and stuff too so we'll
we'll not be here Memorial Day weekend but sometime either a June maybe July
maybe like 4th of July weekend or something cuz I'll be a long weekend too
we can do something we could do something or we should plan it around
a major holiday you know what we should do is the 4th of July weekend just start
at 8 in the morning and then finish late at night although Bobby will probably
want to do a show somewhere in there I figure something out we also need to do
another like roadshow good times roadshow and last question to dark
Sakura why are there no more robbed floods I really miss them okay you I
don't know rubber rubber rubber rubber rubber rubber rubber rubber rubber
making a show nearly every week it's a real relief to listen to olr your
light-hearted view on things is very welcome in a world that's way too
serious thank you very much for a breeze from Belgium PS was my spelling and
grammar okay you didn't put a question mark at the end of okay other than that
spot on but he's from Belgium so he gets a little they have question marks in
Belgium alright funny I question a question from our chat room wetu in our
chat room asks what is Memorial Day for I don't know if maybe he's Canadian or
from a foreign country or maybe one of the Americans that doesn't know the
difference here it is quickly in the u.s. there's two holidays around the Armed
Services one is Memorial Day one is Veterans Day Memorial Day is a day to
honor those that have been lost serving the country in the Armed Forces and you
know most notably wars like Vietnam World War two etc memorial is for those
that have passed away veterans is to honor oh and what who wants to clarify
from New Zealand Veterans Day is the day that is that's in November and that's
the day to honor those that are still serving or you know alive and used to
serve you know a veteran so one for those that have passed away one for
those that are still alive basically in other words Memorial Day would be like
for my papa mm-hmm and my grandfather and Veterans Day would be like for my
brother but both days great sales at Macy's tell me I'm wrong tell me I'm
wrong I just read back a message from Becky said I made her snort by saying
there's question marks in Belgium there are indeed question marks in Belgium
you're right okay um this one comes I'm just gonna say from Laco and cuz they
didn't put any other name it's been well since I've had a chance to email you
guys last time Loki had turned me under earth defense force on 360 what Oh still
playing by the way my question is in regards to the zombie talk from last
week you guys talked about what music would kill zombies to but where would
you set up HQ my roommate and I have argued between a super Walmart a mall
and a Costco PS sorry if the grammar is bad had a 14-hour work day and typing in
the dark so that I do not wake the wife good husband and and by the way I only
give people a hard time they're really really really crappy where would I set
up shop sorry I was flooding the chat room because they needed a they needed
a spanking what was the question here it's we talked about what music we would
kill zombies to but where would we set up HQ my roommate and I wouldn't argued
as super Walmart a mall or Costco well dead rising was set in a mall and I
guess that did pretty well for Frank West say an amusement park like
zombieland that would be fun or a museum might be fun too and especially scary
and who'd look for me in a museum it's the zoo Fort Knox
oh good good guess area 51 or the equivalent of wherever it is video 54 so
you can get your club on and kill zombies my mom's house the space shuttle
try to get me up here zombies Rob Rob why are there zombies outside Rob Rob
get rid of the zombies do you know this neighborhood has already gone to hell
why are there zombies out front Rob she would annoy them away it would be great
here zombies would never make it in the south especially out in the rural south
just because of how many people have freaking guns probably be some good
eating the New Orleans anyway Oh Rob uh no not Rob above Rob above us send us an
email yeah okay here we go I listen to your conversation about the black we
bundle leak in quotes the correspondence between an 10 on GameStop sounded
totally fake ie viral marketing Nintendo bad dog that leak totally advertised our
new bundle a very convenient week before release GameStop we fired the guy I
will never do it again unless you ask us to again and did okay but just this once
well played also Nintendo knows after all these years how to prevent this type
of leak sending the promo standees every week ahead of time sounded intentional
Rob above yep probably was and the more and more I hear about it the more and
more I think it was just kind of like one of those like leaks to actually get
people talking about the black we can I read some chat comments because these
are pretty funny do it all right Donovan suggested these are all about the
zombies and where would you set up shop one of my buddies from Alabama by the
way hi Donovan my old school buddy I keep thinking it's Travis Donovan
Donovan from under station live but he wouldn't listen to his one of my mate
one of my major geek buddies and one of the people responsible for making me a
bigger nerd then I literally he's a geek if he's listening to this show well a
hearty hello heart as California as California kids have done a good job of
corrupting Jamie just you know also some comments about my mother's house zeba
says they're gross Rob and Tigerclaw follows that up with yes guy and if your
mom sees you shoot a zombie she'd be like Rob that's gross rock you go outside
right now and clean that up Rob I like your mom Rob Roberts what do you think
you tell that that's not really my name but yeah we should call my mom next week
and ask her what she would do if zombies showed up at her house salacious pop
says lol the notoriously violent elitist bouncers of studio 54 are a great
anti-zombie tool you look like shit you can't get in sorry come back with some
hot girls and try again well they wouldn't even let the hot people in
they're just like you random random random the zombies would have to be
carrying cocaine to get in basically yeah zombies don't need cocaine they're
already act like crackheads yeah you know what just popped in my head though
with the word crackhead and zombie mmm zombie Whitney Houston okay so the next
email we actually got a decent number of emails by the way yeah you're all our I
know I probably don't think your average demographic being a 31 year old male
carpenter but I have to tell you something I love Wednesdays and
Thursdays you know why because that's usually the time you release your
current podcast and I get to fix someone's house while listening to you
guys Wow please please please keep on doing this show another seven years or
at least until Loki is number one in GTA thanks for all you do serious turtle and
by the way dude you're totally are okay I'm 34 I'm 31 in college working at hell
on earth I mean a job Jesus was a carpenter yeah you could totally be our
Jesus there you go are you Jewish yay Jesus email and any of this listens to
ol are no that's horrible and sex Rob you should be ashamed of yourself kidding
my mother would have told that joke probably my mother would be ashamed of
you and this you know my mom my mom this is what you know my mom probably would
have Rob you shouldn't say that rock she's like secretly laughing she was
thinking that my mom would probably try to stifle the giggles you know like you
do when you're at church exactly actually that was me at church
tackling my giggles I'm sitting in your own pew no usually I was sneaking out
and going to hang out in the church library to read like the real stuff
anyway all I know you might might you know and I I don't want to get all
religious see on the show but I will see super book that was my show growing up
super book flying house that was it all right actually and for the record I did
used to sneak out of church and hang out in the church library reading like well
would you go to hell for that though I don't think you would because like
you're still like doing churchy things well because no at the tender age of 10
years old and and this you know I'm not making it any type of a secret I'm
converting to to Judaism eventually mm-hmm I I was sort of like these were
translated from Greek wasn't it written in Hebrew and then going out in the
library and look everything up so that was me anyway
on the 700 Club Rob I know I know and I was a kid it was totally old-school
anime you know if you think about it like you know it's some pretty badass
shit happens in that cartoon you know this guy's just like splitting the ocean
in half like you know transformers didn't do that shit it's totally
old-school anime all right anyway um I'm over it God everybody everybody gets too
too tense when it comes to religious topics have fun I just stopped just I
have to be in boy drag and I can salacious pop I need dark soccer to
dress in boy drag so she can sneak into the rabbi school and read the Torah
this needs to happen and sing father can you hear me I could do that anyway if I
wanted to be a rabbi all right let's move on let's move on I couldn't be an
Orthodox rabbi but look two things you shouldn't talk about on a video game
podcast politics and religion yet we do them both that's what makes our show so
special what more emails hi guys this is just a quick note to thank you for
sending out Mother's Day wishes to we gaming moms your show is a welcome
distraction from corporate tedium every week not to mention no and the mention
of Mother's Day made it all the sweeter I'm one of those they grew up on video
games still place today and believes that parents should be gaming with their
children rather than shaking their heads over it keep up the good work
veggie wolf good yay parents your children an extra special Mother's Day
at Mother's Day is every day for you lady you you deserve okay no that's a
good attitude Rob you need to I'm gonna link this to you so that we can we can
play it okay because she sends another email that says of course right after I
sent the last message I heard the question about a good song for zombie
killing so I am going to copy this link location and by the way while Dark
Sakura sending that over to me a salacious pop is clarifying that was the
plot to Yentl that he was trying to get you a Barbra Streisand I know I haven't
seen Yentl which I know I'm supposed to see either have I bad gay you know what
we know we're not having a Barbra Streisand night vetoed no I'm talking
about watching if we're gonna watch like things that involve cross-dressing Rob
let's watch Yentl and Victor Victoria no let's watch Priscilla Queen of the
desert I need to see Yentl you really don't all right here's the video that
your email or sent who it contains content of an adult nature hooray oh I
can't believe
oh is the zombie killing music she's actually sent the songs let me see me
get the link
this is funny cuz he's running over people with a lock or great radio I'm
watching a video and laughing at it oh this is the actual song the world's
combined harvester should be like the new email do we have more emails oh good
read the email to this song I'm gonna have to find that song now we need to
use that for we need to do that for our ridiculous news okay ever since I
started listening to internet radio almost ten years ago I have always
dreamed about listening to shoutcast net stations in my car when I found first
came out I was excited to learn that it can play streaming radio however I
didn't have the money to get one a couple months ago I finally decided that
I wanted to purchase one with some of my tax return money after I heard about the
supposed 4g version of the iPhone being found at a bar I was hesitant to buy
knowing that this version may be released very soon since I haven't heard
anything new about it in a while I don't know what I should do do you think this
leak is delaying the 4g version to come out or do you think was just a marketing
employed by Apple we're going to hear more about it very soon I just don't
want to buy the 3gs and then a couple months later see a 4g version release
and screw me over your fellow gamer girl Ziba well I bought a 3g a couple months
ago rumor is Job's was pissed and like called gizmodo himself that's one of the
latest rumors that was on the blogs this week but whatever believe it or not I
don't care the fact is fact Apple will release information about a new phone in
June so my suggestion if you think you can hold off until June the end of June
which is only about a month away at this point if you can hold off like one month
you're in good shape you'll be fine and then you'll you'll have a better idea
what to expect the only other suggestion I really have is that keep in mind that
iPhones not your only option you know they do have like two wraps I think for
blackberries and the droid I mean the other phones have them too I don't know
I wasn't feeling the song for mailbag music we're gonna have to we'll find a
purpose for it on the show though it's a good song okay and that's it we're gonna
find a use for that somewhere yeah by the way you know I was so distracted
earlier in part a hmm it's because I was reading a friend's live journal and she
had pictures up of what's it root root beat the the new Bimani game Oh you beat
you beat yeah and it looked very cubicle it looks oh oh yeah our friend Japan is
that that was um yeah you beat is kind of one of those games I'd like to play
at some point where they testing it in the US and then they just kind of stopped
I guess I don't know well she listed as do beat or maybe it's you as in like the
the Spanish J I don't know um I I would say that there might be a chance at e3
sometimes if Konami's got a lot of Bimani games they want to show they'll
roll out a lot of machines at e3 supernova they did they brought they
brought a beat me to DX machine in 2006 I think it was six sometimes they'll
bring them to e3 for awareness I don't know why it started show but the Japanese
games it was distorted yeah they brought to e3 one year and that was the new game
that was on Japan yeah so we'll see but you beat I don't think is and it's not
juby because I know but a lot of people because it's juby go juby I've seen
people spell it both ways and besides that I would I wouldn't have known if I
hadn't if I hadn't seen the Kana for it so but it's yeah yeah I'd like to check
it out at some point but probably never will oh yeah and they actually called it
in the limited location test they actually called it in dark to see it
clarifies in chat you beat with like a you and that's not a bad name for a game
but it could be taken many ways so you beat what we're 12 all right this is the
part of the show where we get a little bit angsty because I don't know we've
just been that way for eight years so deal with it it's the F use the week
if he goes to allergies and the city of Dixon namely they're pollen
locate after you too bad CD dumps
I don't know like overall I've had a pretty good week but in the past couple
days like like mother nature or whoever has it out for me out there was just
kind of like I'm gonna kick you in the balls but actually you know what all
things considered things could be a lot worse and I don't have it so bad so I'm
not that angsty but I will say an F you know there was something that it ticked
me off the other day and I was like that's gonna be my F you the week on oil
I ride now I can't remember what it was so I guess they didn't make me that
angsty F you to the fact that I still don't go out and buy a new car okay I've
been saying I'm gonna do it for like a year and I still have it if you to
myself all right let's get into a couple more stories and then oh god your calls
1877 game olr after a couple more stories here the skype line will be open
at orange lounge radio on skype or 1877 game olr but at first a couple more
stories looking I'm sure with infinity war going there not really going there
separate ways but they're kind of dissolving if you know what I mean I'm
sure they're going to treat the call of duty franchise with the utmost respect
although you kind of wonder with all these different domain names that
they're registering and I'm sure a lot of it's just to kind of make sure that
people aren't squatting on the moon the domains but a little bit kind of weird
okay like for example they have registered different variations for
quality including Call of Duty future warfare advanced warfare secret warfare
and space warfare as well as those same names with two and three appended to the
end space warfare really every weird
space warfare huh space warfare Call of Duty in space well that's got to be
better than vagina warfare no I'm being completely serious right now there's a
new game out and it's about vagina it's a game called privates it's on the PC
and apparently it's coming to the Xbox 360 I don't know how the hell this is
happening but apparently it's coming to 360 or at least that's what the
developers would tell you it's zombie cow studios it is quote you lead a teeny
tiny gang of condom-hatted Marines as they delve into people's vaginas and
bottoms oh I see it's equal opportunity and blast away at all manner of oozy
shouty monsters so you will be able to shoot the monsters that live inside the
vagina take this yeast infection yeah actually you will be able to blast all
manners of grody infections this looks like it looks like a sperm looks fucking
gross like an evil sperm I'm all for like you know pushing the envelope and
everything of good taste but this is just stupid like really really stupid
but you know I'll have to play it at least once you're shooting sperm you're
shooting evil spur look at that they're evil sperm yes they are they are evil
sperm I should make how the hell is this coming out on Xbox I'm gonna make a
live journal icon out of one of these evil sperm this is not coming out on the
360 I don't know who the hell they think they're kidding but there's no way this
game would not get an M or like a o rating and Microsoft has it in their
thing that a o games will not be released and even if they try to do it
as an indie game it will not get past the review board who the hell do they
think they're kidding it's kind of funny though in a 12 year old sort of way I
mean that's that's the that's the whole point right all right let's open up the
Skype line right now at one eight seven seven game olr or our username on Skype
is orange lounge radio so if you want to give us a call you can right now to give
us your thoughts on tonight's show or anything else maybe you wanted to hear
us talk about that we didn't do how rude you can give us a call and set us
straight at one eight seven seven game olr in the meantime we'll go try to get
some last-minute stories Loki do you have any last-minute stories yeah we're
talking a little bit about a movie coming for a game franchise well this
isn't necessarily a game franchise that's getting in a movie but it has
game stuff in it and that would be that wonderful short film pixels hold on
collar we'll get to you in just a moment pixels which featured Donkey Kong
Frogger space invaders and different stuff from Arkanoid that's being
actually made into a full-length movie now yeah I was reading about that the
other day that's pretty cool yeah happy mess and actually picked it up all right
let me go to the phone call are you there hi hello you're on orange launch
radio who's this this is Rob Rob hey I like your name what's up Rob I am
getting feedback I'm gonna have to hang up oh no okay with that with I have echo
one two three give echo one two three a call and hopefully that will work and
that's a good good reference for anybody who's thinking about calling the show
call echo one two three on skype before you call and hopefully that'll fix
whatever problem you're getting sometimes folks will get a little bit of
echo because just you know a little bit of background as to way we do it here at
orange andreo we have speakers in studio we do not wear headsets because we
there's too many of us to have headsets especially if we have a guest so we do
have in-house speakers so sometimes you will like hear yourself over the speaker
and it's a little crazy so do be aware of that if you call in and kind of hear
yourself all right let's try again hi you're on
orange on its radio who's this hey this is Rob again oh it's Rob above yeah the
right I the Rob above are you still getting feedback no I I was listening to
the show I had to turn off the feed so I could hear you ah yes that's a good
thing just like when you call real radio you have to turn off your speakers so
that will happen well hey I'm glad you're calling in Rob above what's on
your mind okay well first of all I saw you and Bobby playing 3d game heroes to
this afternoon yeah and have you gotten to Ortego town it's the second town is
that the one in the desert yes is that the one with the um foo foo sequence or
whatever it was called poof poof poof poof poof that's it it was the poof poof
sequence is is that what you might have been inquiring about yeah I thought that
was hilarious and also really dirty it was very dirty okay in mine like I don't
know if it was just the way I was playing but when he woke up from poof
poof it was the chicks dad was there and saying doesn't he give really good
massages like I was like this game is filthy absolutely filthy yeah that's what
I thought too and in fact they used massages the same way that incredible
crisis used massages to mean something else mm-hmm exactly well what do you
think of 3d game heroes obviously you've played a little bit if you've made it to
poof poof um I'm enjoying it at a Zelda level but it doesn't seem to to go much
beyond Zelda weren't you a little bit like just slightly disappointed at the
customization features in it like maybe I'm just being a greedy bastard but I
was kind of like you know again we live in an era of little big planet and I was
kind of disappointed that the only thing you get to change is the way the hero
looks like I was kind of thinking like maybe I'm crazy but that there would
have been more customizability to it yeah I was a little disappointed in that
too I knew it wasn't there but I was still disappointed right well at least
it was only $40 you know it was a budget game I still like yeah I think you're
right on a Zelda level though I mean if you want a great Zelda clone this is
definitely I'm one of the best Zelda clones I've ever played Agdeft in our
chat room says death by poof poof well I have one more thing to say and I'm gonna
post a link in the chat yes there was some story on digital times about or
digi times about 10 million iPhones being ordered by Apple of course and
that they they work on the Verizon type network wait a minute way wait a minute
I thought and I could have sworn I read this earlier this week and I'm looking
at I'm looking at your story right now I'm pulling it up but I thought that the
AT&T came out and like laid it on the table and said you know what bitches
we're under contract till 2012 so you needed to stfu when it comes to this
whole Verizon talk yeah but not if they call it an iPad mini that's but anyway
but funny yeah I don't think 10 million I think it's fake because 10 million is
a really bad number to order at startup it would be more like two two to five I
agree didn't the iPad didn't even have that many I mean it was far less like
not even a million iPads did they order right away I just yeah something strikes
me as fishy about this too but I just thought about it because you talked
about it earlier no it's it's you know and and like it or not iPhone is a
gaming platform and needs to be recognized especially we're seeing ports
of so many not just classic but new I mean there's it you can get Street
Fighter 4 on the friggin iPhone it's if you if you don't consider the iPhone a
gaming platform at this point you are behind the times yes sir
all right well Robin but it's nice to hear from you like actual here as
opposed to emails I mean don't get us wrong we love the emails too but always
good I'm here from new callers so uh anything else quickly you want to get
out there for let you go no that's it all right Robin you have a great night
night all right bye-bye did you get it bye-bye but forget it 1a77 game olr
username on skype is orange launch radio we can take a few more calls here
Loki see I gave him a pass on some of the Skype etiquette and so forth cuz a I
know he's listening to the show forever and be you know if it's your first time
calling in I'll give you a pass on some of that stuff so all is forgiven hi
you're on orange launch radio who's this hey what's up guys this is cut judo hey
what's up what's on your mind not much first of all I just want to say that
what was the game you're just talking about the Zelda 3d heroes yeah I call
that basically Lego Zelda it's a confusing game I I mean I I understand
that they it was kind of like a love letter to Zelda and all the other games
from back in the day so I you know I'm not you know I'm not knocking them for
making what everyone's calling the Zelda clone but just the look of it just it
looks really shitty man I mean it looks like our RPG maker for PlayStation 2 you
know any bad looking games and I don't know if you heard my review earlier in
the show but that's kind of one thing you know I do like the game and I do
recommend the game but one of its you know it's not a perfect game and one of
its imperfections is you know it still just kind of looks like a PlayStation 2
game and you know to some extent there's you know when you're doing retro I get
there's probably that the the audience that's sitting there listen to this
right now going well shit Rob if you're doing a retro style game what the hell
do you expect them to do and I don't know one thing might be like a free
roaming camera as opposed to four fixed cameras you get to pick from and yes I
understand you get to do them in screenshots but I don't know it seems
like they did have some optimization problems because again frame skip in a
dungeon that's not okay you know just tone down the water effects they didn't
need to be that awesome you know yeah I mean yeah that that game I'm pretty sure
is giving a lot of people seizures with the water I mean I can't even make out
what I'm looking at half the time you know it's I don't know it's just a
really weird creepy looking game to me I mean I was never into the Zelda games
to begin with so I would never pick it up but um it's just strange I don't
something off with it yeah I mean right on that's part if you weren't into Zelda
there ain't nothing here for you 3d I mean just just walk right on by there
ain't nothing here for you yeah and that and that sword is maybe the worst weapon
I've ever seen in a video game just just the look of it it's just over the time
yeah I mean I can't knock it too much because I haven't played it maybe
playing it you actually get some enjoyment out of it but looking at it I
literally wanted to puke on the television screen the best looking game
the best thing I could compare that sword to is just this more it's just
another low moment you know you did in that game is a lot of lol moments and
this that the ridiculous sword is just another one of them you just kind of
sit there and doesn't the sword doesn't the sword get bigger as you level up or
something like that you can go to a blacksmith and get your sword you can
alter the length and width of your sword and I was just waiting for earth I was
waiting for girth to be an option too but no way you can modify the beam that
it fires but um you can go to a blacksmith and get some of that altered
all right and my last comment is uh are you guys getting uh what is it red
dimension something uh I'm getting I can't remember the name but I'm
definitely getting it I know how sorry it's always yeah I'm absolutely good at
all again you already have it right I already have it yeah my boss is getting
another copy too because I think I've got one free for my work nice look it
must be nice is it like is it GPA in the wild west because that's basically what
I want that's all it needs to be for me um yeah it pretty much I mean it doesn't
play exactly like deep GTA but I mean there's a lot of similarities and I mean
it's not as like intense as GTA I mean there's a lot of me it's more open world
but there's not as much in the open world because obviously it's the Wild
West not like a bustling city but it's awesome and it looks like graphics wise
it's way better than GTA so it's pretty amazing I've ever GTA I was like wow
look at that I can look across the you know the river and see all these
different monuments and stuff like that and it just looks amazing so it'll be
awesome yeah yeah GP I live in New York and I
remember there was playing one multiplayer game and actually ran
through a little section that actually used to hang out when I you know I used
to hang out in that area when I was a kid and actually knew where to sneak
around and avoid people and you know avoid getting shot that's kind of a
creepy like I'm in a good way but that's Wow games are too realistic yeah I've
taken up enough of your time no I love the show we love the call have a good
one have a good night buddy all right all right some good calls tonight one
eight seven seven game olr username on skype orange lounge radio act deaf in
our chat room says I want a free copy of 3d dog game heroes I liked by the way I
like that last caller's comparison to Lego Zelda I think was a great
comparison that was funny and Donovan in chat says actually Lego Zelda sounds
like it could be fun especially with the Lego game sense of humor I that comment
actually kind of I think hits the nail on the head it's it's pretty pretty
accurate let's see Donovan says hmm Lego Wow just as fun of a joke game says the
guy who's all tabbing out of Wow to type in here addict Jamie you make friends
with a lot of Wow addicts I gotta say I know what's up with that more people
playing Star Trek online with me I still have the card I'm gonna use it at some
point but probably after Memorial Day because if I use it now I've got too
many trips coming up I'm going on two weekend trips back to back so I've got
to calm down and actually spend time playing the game and then I got a three
coming up to I got to worry about that I'm gonna be gone a week for that good
times oil are at e3 we don't know what we're doing yet but we'll have the
unfortunately it won't be Loki and Dark Sakura so we won't unfortunately be able
to bring you something collectively unless maybe there's like some type of
I don't know maybe we'll do something over Skype because you know Loki Dark
Sakura will probably be able to follow the news almost better online than I
will be being at the show but we are gonna hopefully bring you some cool
interviews at the show at least that is the idea Loki do you have any other last
minute stories over there that we can get to all we wait for some more calls
this is kind of actually ties in a little bit with the last order talking
about inappropriate games and of course you know leading the market of
inappropriate games would be Japan and developer tea time is bringing new
technology into the adult anime game franchise including they have the face
tracking T cam technology will now they're working on hand tracking as well
so you will be able to use the tall like accuracy to lift skirts and rip off
shirts of anime women and they have some demo videos displaying such
inappropriate but funny funny yes good stuff anything else for us tonight
if escapes come in the ps3 that's kind of neat and this is kind of
disappointing I guess but you know nowadays we have the internet the
Nintendo power line is gonna be disconnected on June 1st fuck that was
still open yeah is that the game counselors I think it is holy shit sorry
to hear though that they'll be out of jobs I mean that kind of sucks but yeah
I actually to be honest I didn't know you still existed sorry it was probably
just one guy with his feet up on the desk not getting cut it's like Loki
eating the sandwich I do that waiting for the call to come in I do that at
work hey if I eat the sandwich at my desk before I go to lunch that's more
time to play grant the thought of that's right anything else for us tonight Loki
or dark Sakura I don't know yeah I'm debating doing something really addict
II as long as it's not reactivating your Wow account no I'm considering finding
a cheap digital download key for Star Trek online so that I can play a joint
drill that is pretty uh but I get another 30 free days all right let's get
to another call hi you're on orange launch radio who's this hey this is
excellent x-link what's on your mind buddy never much I was just talking
about the EA about the charging the extra 10 bucks for the sports games yes
I'm surprised more people didn't want to talk about this what are your thoughts
on this actually I do because I love playing the sports games from EA in fact
I like playing all of them from time to time because it's a good way to calm
down after having a bad day at work especially something like Tiger Woods or
something though I don't condone what Tiger Woods did but whenever I think of
the Tiger Woods game by EA I think of the way South Park portrayed it and I
don't know if you saw that episode where they were like press X to slap him
president actually they have a game out like that where somebody made one that
was put basically Tiger Woods with Grand Theft Auto of course they do of course
it okay obviously shit tons of people and yes that's a metric measure shit
tons of people play these sports games even you know I I may kind of joke I
don't know a lot about them but it's not like I've never played a sports game in
my life I actually rather liked blades of steel thank you very much that was my
jam back in the day double dribble double drip double dribble was badass I
will totally buy NBA Jam when it comes out to well I will too that's gonna be a
great game anyway so so yes so the sports games so what do you think are you
pissed or you know seriously I don't go online that much to play online if I did
I could see maybe paying the ten bucks but personally I could give to you know
two shits about it because I don't really play it online that much if I did
I played it once in a blue moon so I mean I'm more playing it just for like
the season stuff for myself and see how well I can do at the team on on the
teams then I do didn't play in online guess other people that I mostly
probably end up cheating anyway so but um at ten bucks and they've really seen
them much compared to so so like um somebody said earlier about you know so
calm and it'd be in 20 bucks I mean you know it could be a lot worse I mean you
know so I guess my worry is that if this works it's only gonna get worse that's
my well it's gonna get worse no matter what I mean we got to think about a long
run they're gonna nickel-dime us no matter what rather it be downloadable
content where there be online play whether it be flying unicorns you know
it it's going to always be something so but I I look at is it if I give them 10
bucks they better have the servers running they better do it good and they
better have it so I can connect to people without any lag or anything like
that so I mean as long as they can do that kind of stuff I really don't see
any kind of problems so they probably won't I mean they're not gonna change
their service just because they're charging extra 10 bucks they think see
the problem is they have all this download content that was out there in
all these different ways that they were offering extra add-ons whether it be
buying cheats or buying you know extra crap that you probably don't need for
your sports games well that maybe wasn't working so well so now they're making
you buy 10 you know download or I guess multiplayer online if you you know
purchase the game used so that way they're getting you know some money for
that you know used purchase versus no money but I really don't think they
should be getting money for use purchase nowhere else in the industry any
industry do people get money for a used purchase if I buy a used car don't to
pay money to the manufacturer because they didn't sell me a new car too fucking
bad yeah I totally agree on that and that's gonna give other people in our
companies reason to do other stuff too and that could get out of control big
time but you know if I wanted to coach and play online real bad too I might
even look on eBay or something try to find a code on there to somebody's
willing to sell somebody goes you know buy at the game going you know what I'm
not gonna use their online I'm going to sell it I mean I don't see why they
couldn't do that I mean I see that all the time with other downloadable stuff
so that's a good point I mean maybe somebody doesn't really want to play
online or doesn't really have the whole hookup to be able to play online so
there's like hey I'm just gonna sell this code make a quick 10 bucks or 7
bucks recoup some of the money and then between that and selling the game used
in the first place make a little more money hey yeah precisely all right
actually we gotta let you go so we can wrap up the show but thanks so much for
your call anytime and good luck on hitting 80 this week I'm almost at 79
right now as we speak so all right thanks from what I from one addict to
another good luck yeah thank you you're welcome I feel kind of bad I think I
kind of got excellent cooked on that game like I feel like thank God I don't
have to pay like ripper like you know like what pay like alimony or something
like when I I ruin people's lives because of Warcraft I don't know all
right anyhow we're gonna wrap it up and get to the post show and all the fun
stuff so we got to go around though and get everybody's final thoughts before we
close up shop and we'll start with dark Sakura this week dark soccer do you have
any final thoughts boo don't be sad there'll be another all our next week ah
actually I'm kind of thought for you up what brother brother brother brother
brother brother brother brother brother brother brother brother brother I have a
final thought for you
Loki do you have a final thought I have to see what animals or other animals I
can skin in Red Dead Redemption it's too bad that you can't skin a human
apparently human skin does not sell for much that would be Mortal Kombat right
and my final thought is it is getting hot in here and I have to run errands on
my way home tonight from the show here I just should be there I turn on the air
again but Dan's playing something louder sorry we're almost done we're done we're
out of here he can play loud games all right that's it thank you guys so much
for downloading and supporting independent radio whether it be you're
listening live you're listening on the podcast you guys are awesome and we
really appreciate the support because you know what we're not you know the g4
we're not the one we're not the game spots and all this stuff that had these
huge websites able to just you know draw the people in through marketing and all
that stuff we are truly just three people here doing it because it's fun
why else why else play games it's fun so if you like our show and you like what
you've heard just tell somebody else about the show tell two people help
spread the word and then pretty soon the whole planet will be listening mwahaha
world domination although then again it's been eight years and hasn't worked
yet but hey we're getting a step closer every week thank you guys so much and
we'll be back to do it all again next week sound good all right yep we'll see
you next week with more orange lounge radio good night
you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is an orange
lounge production to join us for a live show visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights
at 6 p.m. Pacific time the views and opinions expressed on orange lounge
radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of orange lounge
radio or all games calm but we're probably right anyway see you next week