Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
Dark Sakura, Sky and Lowkey
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends and welcome to episode number 368 of Orange Lounge Radio
The video game talk show where every gamer has a voice
But not tonight apparently, tonight's going to be a little bit different
And I will get to that in just a moment, but my name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours
Maybe hour, I don't know, we'll see how long we go tonight
With my co-host, the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
It better not be hours
Well yeah, it's already a little late, just to put it, well let me introduce everyone and then we'll get into what's going on tonight
Also the one and only tech master, Lowkey
Hello
How you doing Lowkey?
I'm doing good
Alright so here's the deal, we're not live, it's not Sunday, we're cheating a little bit
You know usually we do this little program of ours live and we have a chat room full of people
And you know live callers and all that stuff, but we are not live tonight
We were supposed to be live last Sunday, the 20 something, 22nd, I don't know
But we weren't live because it was kind of my fault
I was out of town and while I was out of town my car was parked at a friend's house
And somehow a nail ended up on my tire while it was parked at a friend's house
So unfortunately instead of coming right home, picking up my car and driving right here to the show
Which was the original plan, I had to go fix a tire
So unfortunately the live show didn't happen
So apologies to you kids and of course Lowkey and Dark Sakura who clear their schedules every Sunday night
And I wasn't even here, I'm a bad person
Damn nail
That's okay, I had more Red Dead Redemption in the play
I was gonna say, you guys probably figured out something to do to kill time
Because I knew pretty early in the day it wasn't gonna happen
I hung out with Becky
Well awesome, you got girl time, ew girl stuff
And we went to Fresh Choice and ate salad
Ew
I can't condone that kind of behavior
I know, gross
Alright I'm glad I wasn't here, I'm glad I was 100 miles away from you
Alright just kidding
Hey
Alright well so here's the deal
We already knew we weren't gonna be here Memorial Day weekend because it's Memorial Day weekend
I know I for one am gonna be in Oregon and just you know the long weekend
I think we wanna all do other stuff
So if Dark Sakura wants to eat Fresh Choice three days in a row, she can go do that
So we wanted to do like a show though at least for the podcastees
So that way we're not going two weeks without a show
So a lot of the podcast folks that don't usually tune in live
This show's kind of actually for you because this way
A lot of the show's been kind of hitting the feed Wednesday, Thursday anyway
So you guys will probably not even notice except for the fact that we don't have a live audience tonight
That we're really missing anything
So just kind of setting the stage there
We're offline tonight, it's Wednesday so we're actually midweek
And you know that's where we're at
We're kind of taping this as a bridge to fill two weeks of no live shows
I do want to point out though, we will be off Memorial Day
Our next live show will be at allgames.com at 6pm Pacific time on Sunday, June 6th
It'll be the next live show and that's right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
At 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
And of course we always have our chatroom at chat.orangelaungeradio.com
So Robby says 6pm specific time
Specific
At a specific time
It's 6! Specifically it's 6!
I'm sorry
I meant to say 6 Pacific but I kind of
Really did that you started, I have to give you a hard time
See right now you've got me in the middle of the week on hump day
When my spirit hasn't quite been broken
You know and I'm not doing the what's tomorrow
So wait we might get good mood Jamie tonight
I'm just teasing
And you're full of salad, you ought to be in a great mood
Actually I'm not full of salad right now, I'm full of taco
Okay, ooh tacos
I had, because we have to do food
Yes
I had refried black beans and brown Spanish rice
On a sprouted green tortilla
Yum
I haven't eaten dinner yet and I'm smelling Loki's chicken so
That's why I ate cause he brings his chicken in and I'm like yum wait I can't eat that
I just didn't want burgers tonight, it's all good
Rob do you want me to make you some dinner?
No no I gotta stop by and get some stuff for the big road trip
Cause I am driving 10 hours to Portland Oregon
And I've never taken a road trip that long
I've never been to Oregon
You should get some raw nuts
For the trip
Raw nuts and dried fruit
Good times
Alright here's the other interesting thing about tonight's show
And what might make this show a little special
We don't have a script tonight, usually we have you know not that the show is scripted
Or even fun but we usually have like an outline, we call it a show roll
And you've probably heard us refer to it before
A little behind the scenes there
We do have like a list of who's gonna cover what topic
That way we're not stepping on each other's toes
And we kinda know who's gonna talk about what
And you know we have a general flow to the show
Not tonight, we're winging it tonight
This is gonna be like the old days
Remember the old days?
Except I don't have the headset on and I won't have a migraine hopefully
So yeah so I
I know I might get high on chicken fumes
We'll see what happens, we don't know
But we do always start off the show with how was your gaming week
And we don't plan to change that
So DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
I gamed Rob, I gamed
I played Portal
Because it was free
And it's really hard to get used to the controls on
You know from going from playing on a controller to playing on
My PC but it's pretty cool
And I of course played a lot of Star Trek online
Because I've got the week off, you know I'm out of school
And it's like I've got all this stuff I have to focus on
But I so haven't been able to
And I played some Babylonian Twins today
For a little bit
And Dan's playing more Grand Theft Horse
He killed his horse by accident
Except he died too so he got his horse back
He keeps complaining about not having his original horse
Because he liked his horse
I was like what was good about the horse?
It was a bay horse and I liked it, it was pretty
Oh whatever
So yeah and he was picking his you know gristled cowboys
Out picking flowers for this old guy
And then Pac-Man, Google Pac-Man
Because Namco had their 25th anniversary
I think it's 30th
30th anniversary
30th anniversary and so the Google splash thing was a playable version of Pac-Man
And if you go to Google.com slash Pac-Man
You can actually go back and play it
What's impressive about that if I recall
I was reading up on it
It's not like Flash
It's not Java
It's using some pretty basic web technology to bring it to you
Which is really impressive
The programming
And actually I was checking out the Twitter earlier
Somebody on Twitter is going to have us talk about that a little more
It looks like it actually resulted in a lot of lost productivity at work
Fascinating
Was it Cnet or one of those news sites posted about how much had been lost
And then it went on saying that that's really nothing compared to the little five minutes at a time
People sneak on reading Wikipedia from their desk
Right
So they're using it as a scapegoat and as an excuse to ban Google
You know what
From work sites
We're free form tonight
Let me jump over to Twitter real quick
I'm going to jump over to Twitter real quick
And read one of the tweets we got earlier
Even though we're not live and we don't have the chatters tonight
We did post on Twitter
Hey give us stories
We'll still try to interact with you the best we can
Because you know we can't just go to all games and say
We want to be live right now
Because I think there's another show on right now
It was from Dr. Noire
Dr. N-O-I-R
Dr. Noire
Here's the fallout from Google's Pac-Man tribute
Sending us a tweet from BBC News
The playable version of the classic video game was put on Google's front page on 21st of May
To celebrate 30 years since the launch of Pac-Man in Japan
Now there were statistics gathered by the software firm Rescue Time
About how much this damn thing was actually played
On a typical day it suggests that most people will do about 22 searches on the Google page
Each one lasts about 11 seconds
But putting Pac-Man on the front page
It boosted that time by an average of about 36 seconds
And that would be based on the browsing habits of 11,000 Rescue Time users
I guess it's the software that companies install on their computers
To know who's being naughty on the internet when they're not supposed to be
And so let's see they did all the math
And they figured that with 504 million unique users
Who visit the main Google page per day
That means 4.8 million hours, 549 years were wasted on Pac-Man
Assuming that people are paid on average $25 an hour
Really?
I know I was like I want to know what that is so I can work there
Or $17.50 if you want to convert it to pounds an hour
This equates to about $120 million in lost productivity
I think that's some fuzzy math there if you ask me but
Well yeah $25 an hour I mean come on
Bottom line people will still waste time on Pac-Man even if it's just 36 seconds
Got Pac-Man fever
Alright so we'll go back to the other tweets later
But I thought that was topical and worth mentioning
So yeah I checked out the Google Pac-Man it was cool
It's topical like hydrocortisone
And it emulated the original Pac-Man pretty well
It was pretty fun except there's this one part where there's the grid a little bit off
Where the last E is because the little place you enter in on the E
Is actually sort of just off center from where the escape door is
Yes and then the G is just weird
Because you have like this dead end tunnel you don't really have on a Pac-Man board usually
I mean it was a great concept
You know what I hope for for the 35th?
Super Pac-Man Google
Lordy
Because Ms. Pac-Man already made a cameo in the other one if you clicked insert coin
Anyway
This is true Rob
Anything else in your gaming week you want to report for us?
I got my Sims 3 working again so I've been playing more Sims
As you can see here I'm back to my hunt for
That's a Sims site?
I thought you were like shopping for like IKEA or something over there
There's people who've actually tried to
Well IKEA and EA had this deal going on for a while
Where they had some of their standard stuff available for Sims 2
Now did your Sims have to actually build it and get frustrated as hell
When they couldn't understand the instructions because they're nothing but pictures?
No
But um there's people who missed the IKEA stuff
And have really gone
Like you know I'm looking at some of the furniture on here
And this is actually some
As a design major Rob
This is actually pretty impressive stuff
If anyone wants to know the sites that I go to for my Sims stuff
I go to The Sims Resource
I actually have a subscription to The Sims Resource
Mod The Sims is good but Stylist Sims
Has got some really
It's got donation stuff and I don't really advocate donation items
You know because you have to pay for them
But at the same time people did put work into this stuff
But there's some absolutely gorgeous design stuff
I would really have in my actual house
Should I be able to afford it ever
I'm surprised Sims doesn't have something like that
I mean in World of Warcraft you can go through certain websites
And you can get an actual figure of your WoW character
From the data it pulls down from the armory
I mean
It's crazy like how interactive some of this stuff is now
I'm surprised you can't buy some of your
Like a fake Sims house that's your actual Sims house
If that makes any sense at all
I know what you mean
You know how like in the fifth grade we used to have to build houses out of balsa wood
For like a school project
I never had to do that
Really? In the fourth grade we had to make missions out of sugar cubes
You were in Alabama
See we had the missions here in California
Did you have to do this in school?
Yeah I had to make a mission
You had to build the missions out of sugar cubes
I think mine had a pasta roof
Cause you know how the roofs of the missions
You know you've seen the California missions on the coast right
They kind of have that very clay wavy look
Well you use like lasagna and you paint it
I made mine out of Legos
Yeah I never had to do that
We would instead
Every so often head down to the museum downtown
Cause keep in mind where I'm from
You just sneeze and you'll hit something that's been around since the 18th century
I was actually showing Loki before you got here some of the old Victorian homes
If you look up Victorian homes, Mobile Alabama
You will see some absolutely gorgeous places
But the museum downtown recreated a lot of these in doll size
Well there's some stuff from the 18th century around here
It's called gold
Did you hear about this big rock
Apparently somebody dug up
Up in Cameron Park or something
Big old gold nugget just hiding in the backyard
My mom keeps telling me that I should go out panning
And I'm like okay you come out to California
In 113 degree weather and you pan
That was another stupid thing we did as kids
We used to go take the bus up to Sutter's Fort or whatever and do gold panning
Sutter's Mill
Or Sutter's Mill sorry Sutter's Fort is the place downtown
We used to actually go out to reservations
Really
I've been to a couple pallets
I go to reservations now but I go gambling
I've actually been to about 5 pallets
We never really had to do anything
I don't want to say stupid but time wasting like that I guess
Because first of all with some of the stupid children
You know parents hated that shit because they had to do half of it
But we did have to do, we had a lot of focus on doing actual full science projects
And experiments and real lab time
The worst was when I got to high school
Because I've talked about this on the show before in my high school
The Whitey McWhite High that I went to that was two thirds Mormon kids
And it was all these rich kids that lived out by the lake
And then like you know I lived in the poor part of town where I came from
So we went to this school I kid you not it was the most undiverse place on the planet
I mean it was tragic
Right from a John Hughes movie
But you know you had all these spoiled ass little rich kids
Like I'm sure they were like hiring people to do their school projects
It was pretty like you know we had to build the houses and stuff
They would be made from like actual stone and all this stuff
And it's just like you spoiled bitch
Mine's made out of popsicle sticks
Where I actually had to eat all the popsicles over the course of like three months
That's the fun part
That's true
Now you can just go to Michael's and get a bag of popsicle sticks
I know
And I'm like god damn ungrateful kids
Who didn't have to realize the value of the popsicles that come with two sticks
Because they're just two popsicles glued together
I don't even remember what they're called
You can get fudgesicles like that
What the hell tangent is this show on right now?
You know what I miss? Pudding pops
They're still around aren't they?
They came back
I miss pudding pop commercials
Those are the best
Dude cause it's all about Bill Cosby
But you know you remember one of my favorite comics ever is Bloom County
And I always liked that um
What was the guy's name?
But his dad Bill Cosby lived in his anxiety closet with pudding pops
Cosby here with a special report from Jello Brand Pudding Pops
Mothers do your kids talk like this?
Chocolate
vanilla
Swirl
Don't worry they're just asking for Jello Pudding Pops Swirls
Good news for your mom and you mom
That wasn't one of the better commercials
Sounds delicious
That was like a fake newscast
I know now you got me fucking hungry
Pudding pops
Rude
Alright um I want to go back a little bit
Something you were mentioning earlier
They even make pudding pops anymore?
I just said they brought them back
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Hello Loki
Hey I'm working on the show
Alright fine
Yeah he wants to do this thing called news
Like we're trying to fucking talk about pudding pops
And Loki's concerned with gaming news
As if we are a video game talk show
When we're done though with the gaming week though
I do need to make a plug
Or do you want me to do it now?
Uh you can do it now but I want to say one other thing about your gaming week
Because you said earlier that Portal is a bitch to control on the computer
Yes
I want to give you a pro tip awesome and a lot of people forget about this
Controller?
Xbox 360 controllers
They're USB you can plug them right in
If you have a wired one
I honestly think the wired 360 controllers are almost a better purchase
Than the wireless ones
At least have one you know
I think I've got one
Yeah I have one I think I have like three controllers and one of them is wired
And it's great because I can go to the computer and use it there
And it's pretty awesome
But I have kind of gotten the hang of doing some of the puzzles
Just I keep forgetting that I look
Well see I've got a thumb track ball on my mouse
So looking around with the track ball is kind of difficult for me
And then remembering that you know
I wish it's just that I could have my action button
Like in Resident Evil back in the day
And hold my action button and turn around and walk
You know but meh
Okay you want to plug something
I think I know what you want to plug
And if it is what I think it is then cool
I was wondering when we could say something about this
Well there is a new website that is currently being worked on
By our dear Tiara as we know on the show
You know as Mar and Marvel
It's geek-life.com
And the site launches on the 1st
And I do an article on there one called Geek Cube
Where it's you know about being a geek working in a cubicle
And you know but we're
Instead of being game specific or you know
Anime specific or something
We're geek total geek
Just nerdy geeky dorky fun
Nerdy geeky dorky fun that's right
I wonder if that domain name is taken
Nerdy geeky dorky fun
No competition please
But we are looking for people to contribute
So if you have something that you want to share
If you want to write an article
We do however ask that you use a spell checker
Someone to proofread it
Because if you don't then we're going to be brutal
I'll try to contribute once in a while
If you lovely ladies will have me
Of course we'll have you for dinner
Or something related because that's what I know
I'll do a wow column
Well I'm going to have other side projects too
Coming up and I know you and I have been talking about one
Hopefully E3 this year will have a press conference of our own
It'll be fun
Good stuff in the future
Well the other thing too is that I'm planning on doing a DIY
Segment you know maybe once a week
On there too about doing little do it yourself projects
You know how to decoupage
Oh god geek decoupage
It's geek decoupage
Dude I've got my bathhouse picture back there
That's pretty cool
That's art geek decoupage
But yeah but I mean that's the general thing so
Alright let's move on with gaming weeks
Also anyone out there looking for designer
Hire me
Low key how was your gaming week
It was good I didn't play a whole lot though
I played basically well two things
But one whatever anyways
Red Dead Redemption playing a lot of that
Grand Theft Tours
Been playing mostly System Link multiplayer
Because we were playing it at work
And it's been pretty fun
You can do little gang missions and stuff
And join a posse and kill people
And you get experience which unlocks more characters you can play as
And more mounts and more weapons
So that's all kind of fun
The first kind of real day that we decided to go play that
We were running around fighting bears with knives
Which is funny because the willing critters seem to team up against you
In fact there was one point where I had a coyote
A boar and a bear chasing after me
Coyote didn't really do much but the boar was really quick
And knocked me over and then left me to get eaten by the bear
So that sucked
And then the cougars are little fuckers
They chase after you really fast and keep killing me
Is Courtney Cox one of the cougars?
Maybe
I didn't name any of them so I guess one of them could be Courtney Cox
Then of course other than that I've played more Grand Theft Auto
And that's been pretty fun
The major part I've been working on stuff with Grand Theft Auto
Like I mentioned before is I'm working on creating another modded game
For us to play at work
And the major achievement that I was able to accomplish this week
Is that I figured out how to edit the map
In Grand Theft Auto on the console
Which as far as I'm aware now has never been done before
So that's been pretty awesome
And I ran into some roadblocks before with stuff being rotated weird
But I actually figured that all out last night
So I'm ready to create all sorts of crazy stuff
Including giant loop-de-loops and stuff like that
Lots of ramps
But yeah, back to Red Dead Redemption though
That game is so glitchy
It's just hilarious
I was playing today, called my horse over
And the horse came galloping at me at full speed
Off a cliff to its death
Bounced in front of me
And then bounced off another cliff
I'm like what the hell
I've seen some angry tweets about
I think I saw a tweet earlier this week that was like
Did anybody QA test this game?
Well there was some other ones
Like there was one of the missions that we were doing
The first posse mission that we did
We were going after this one gang
We had to destroy their ammo caches
And so after you destroy the second one
There's reinforcements that are sent after you
Well for whatever reason they decided to spawn up on the hill
And they jumped to their death
And it was awesome
It has problems with cliffs
It just doesn't understand them sometimes
And so it was just like kept hearing this
Ahhhhhh
See people die
It's like Toons is the driving horse
It's awesome
And then there's been other videos I've seen that have problems
Where different objects are spawning on different characters
So for example
Instead of your mount that's a donkey
You have a woman
So you're riding around on a woman that sounds like a donkey
And has a horse face
I think I saw something like that on the internet once
Yes
And then some other
Crows that are actually people
So they're like flying around
And flapping their arms and stuff
And that's pretty funny
And I think the funniest one I saw
Other than the cougar man
Was the dog
Bounty hunter
Like a real dog
Like a coyote
So it was this coyote running around carrying a rifle
That's pretty funny
Oh and there's a wonderful glitch where you can
Crouch against a wall and get shot up into space
So should I buy it?
There's great reviews and everything
It's a lot of fun
There's tons of people on there to play with
Grand Theft Tourist Rob
And if you don't want to play with those people
You can always start a private game
And just mess around or go on missions
I don't like to play with strangers
I'll play with people on my friends list
And you guys and the listeners
What if the strangers want to play with you?
No
No means no
Alright
Kind of piggybacking on that and going into my gaming week
As part of this whole Oregon thing
You know they don't have sales tax in Oregon
I'm making a list of games
I want to buy while I'm up in Oregon
I'm going to buy that
I think
That's kind of like on the bubble so to speak
But I definitely want to get Blur
I want to get Split Second
Is Split Second cool?
Yeah, Dan loves it
Alan Wake I hear is pretty awesome
Somebody described it as like a Twin Peaks
Type video game
I realized all you all were
All big on, well not you guys specifically
Just the general, if Twitter is any indication
Of where the world's at
Everybody went nucking futs over the Lost finale
This weekend, which ironically was on Sunday night
I think there was actually a tweet out there
That said, you guys cancelled the show
To go watch the Lost finale
I don't watch Lost
I watch good shows
I'm not hating on Lost
Any show that gets people talking as much as that show did
Is doing something right
But I didn't watch the first few episodes
And it's one of those shows where if you don't watch the first few episodes
You're fucked, it's not going to make any sense
So I never watched it
If I can interject, back to Alan Wake
Dan described it as
Oh great, what's that game?
Silent Hill meets Max Payne
Interesting
Sounds good, no, well I was going to say
Before Lost, way back when
In the 90's there was a little show called Twin Peaks
It was awesome
And it was a total like WTF
Mind trip as well, it didn't last very long sadly
They really screwed with it
On the time slots and they answered
The show's biggest question
Who killed Laura Palmer way too soon
And so that kind of killed the show when that happened
But I say that because
I love that show and if there's any video game
Being remotely compared to that show
I'm all about it, so I'll check it out
Yeah, so I'm making this list
And then my goal is to just go hit up a GameStop
Or Fry's or whatever they have up there
And just go to town
What's the big thing they have up there?
Fred Meyer
Those ginormous stores
That they have I guess
Go check out one of those
So that's the plan
As far as my actual gaming week in games I've been playing
Not a whole lot this week, of course more
But I want to say something on that in a minute
Alan hit 80 this week
So I'm very happy and proud for him
But now that he has hit 80
I think I'm going to, believe it or not
Scale back on WoW a little bit
And I am making it my summer goal
Before Labor Day
To actually beat
And this is a big deal for me
I mean actually beat from start to finish
Three games
And I realize that might sound like nothing
But this is me we're talking about
For me to actually complete
A role playing game or an adventure game
Or something like that is a BFD
Because I have the worst gamer ADD
I will start a game and play it for an hour and go somewhere else
No I have not
See!
That's the problem
You know you gotta let me borrow it
So WoW will be
Scaled back
I'll still do the raids with the guild
And play with Alan for at least an hour
Several times a week and so forth
And actually beat three games
And I don't mean like beating
What's something like really easy
That takes like five seconds to beat
You know like
Well no I don't think that would be one of the games anyway
But uh
Like Final Fight
I played in an hour
I beat Final Fight that doesn't count
That takes like an hour
I'm going to beat three adventure RPG
Something games
So I don't know what yet
But I want you guys
As my gamer nerd buddies
Here in studio to hold me to it
And if I'm lagging
I need verbal lashings
Do you think you can do that Dark Sakura?
Verbal lashings?
I'll point at you and laugh
Well I'm down for that
I'm going to try Alan Wake
And if I like it that will probably be one of the three
But I'll let you know
Because I might not like it I don't know
And I might say no I legitimately do not want to play this to completion
But a game like Final Fantasy 13
Really ought to be one of the three
Well beat it and then lend it to me
Get his copy
Whoever beats it first let me borrow it
Sure
I'll tell you right now
I want to play it on PS3
I'm out
Oh I have the PS3 version so I'll have to beat it and then let you borrow it
Alright I'm going to beat it yet
You beat it yet Rob
Fair enough
Someone else needs to get me to Cydia
Other stuff in my gaming week
Game Room I'm still playing the crap out of that
And River Raid came out today
It's rare that we have the show mid-week
Where I can talk about releases as they happen
River Raid was a classic classic Atari 2600 game made by Activision
My Activision room has like six Activision games in it right now
It's crazy
I've literally bought like ten games in Game Room
I've spent
If you say like three to five dollars a game
Most of them I only paid three
Four but there's a few that I also play on the PC
So I bought the upgrade
That means I've spent like thirty five bucks on this game so far
Which you might want to point and laugh at me
Fine ha ha go ahead
But I'm getting my money's worth
I'm playing the games quite a bit
They are cheaper than virtual console games
They are
And I'm having fun with it
You know like Bobby and I have had these friendly little competitions on some games
And you guys know Bradley
Arcadian
Dude did you know he was in the top twenty for Time Pilot earlier this week
Really?
Yeah he's pretty good at that stuff
He wiped my score on Mega Maniac
But I'm still number one
On Pitfall and Crystal Castles
So anyhow
I made it up to rank sixty eight
In Grand Theft Auto
Did you? Well I thought you were sixty seven a couple weeks ago
Yeah I keep losing the game here
It sucks because it takes me like twenty games
To get up a few ranks
And like all I have to do is lose to one person
Not even lose the game
Come in second, buy like a few bucks
And it drops me down a bunch
It's really unfair
But I'm doing pretty good
I haven't lost a game in a while
Alright let's get to housekeeping tonight
Of course our Twitter
Twitter.com slash olr
We're going to get to the Twitter topics in a little bit
And then also our Facebook
Please add us there
Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio
Apparently we have a MySpace still too
But if I haven't added you to MySpace
I check it like maybe once every three months
So don't be sad
Just send us a friend request there
Although I ought to just delete it
But any promotion is good promotion I suppose
Okay
So how about gaming news
We'll get into that a little bit
Okay there's like
I don't know if you have anything you want to talk about Jamie
I know Loki's got a bunch
He was a good guy earlier and went through the show
There's like two things I want to talk about tonight
I'll start with the one that has been big today
And I think yesterday was when the buzz started
Let's talk Rock Band 3
Alright so here's what happened
The Green Day Rock Band demo
Came out on Xbox Live and PlayStation
And you know it's got a couple songs
You can play and check out what Green Day Rock Band's all about
But the biggest splash of this
Was that there is a teaser page
I guess at the very end of the demo
That shows you know how in
Rock Band you have little icons
You have like a little guitar icon
A little bass icon, a little microphone for the singer
And little drums
Well guess what next to all these icons
And the number three
Is a little keyboard
And it looks like at first glance
They are going to add keyboards
To Rock Band 3
And when I first heard this news
I got really excited because
You know Orange Lawns Radio
We started as a music game based show
And we used to play games like
Drummania, Guitar Freaks
And some of the games that inspired
You could say Rock Band in some ways
Well the one I always loved
That I thought was really under appreciated
Because they killed it off way too quick
After only three versions
Which I know sounds like a lot but when you consider
2DX is on
19 or 19 is being tested right now
And then Guitar Freaks
Is on like
16 or 17 I mean there is a crap ton of these games
Keyboard Mania
Which I was actually good at
I could beat the hardest song in the game
I couldn't do it on doubles
I guess that would really be the hardest mode in the game
We have a friend who is really good in doubles
Oh yeah
I would like to think I was one of the better Keyboard Mania players
I could do it
I was good at it
I had to pick it up so I could play with you
And I was pissed when they discontinued it
Because it was like the one Bomani game
I was actually pretty good at
So I heard this news about Rock Band 3
And I was like oh my god
They are actually going to do it
They are going to put out a keyboard
Oh my god I'm like whoa this is going to be great
They are going to be great for this
I'm all excited right
Well today I guess a news story came out that says
Well
It might not actually be a keyboard
It might be a key-tar
Meaning the guitar
And the keyboard mixed together
Meaning like
If you see one of those old ass pictures
Of like I don't know Journey
From the 80's with a big
Hair
Playing a keyboard on a guitar
They really needed to make it just a keyboard
I realize a lot of you think that's cool
This is how you freeze pop the game
Or just any 80's
Band practically had that
And I realize a lot of you think it's cool
But boy did that feel like
A punch in the stomach
Like oh we are going to do this really cool thing
And then we are going to make it so stupid
By making it a key-tar
Whatever I'll play it anyway
It's one of those things where
I could always just like put the key-tar
On the ground and do it that way
And just pretend I don't see the stem
But I don't know if that'll work
I'm thinking it's just screen real estate
How the hell are you going to do keyboards
With three other
How are you going to do a five person band
Or even an eight person band
Well let's see three singers
Guitar
Bass
Drums and a keyboard
So you'd have a band of like
I have a feeling
Call it a gut
But if they do key-tar I think it'll scroll
Sideways
I think that's how they'll do it
They'll have vocals at top and key-tar on the bottom
And then the normal tracks in the middle
I have nothing to base that off of
Obviously this is going to be at E3
Obviously
And we'll know more then
But until then it's all speculation really
Except for the fact that you know what
Putting that little symbol of a keyboard in the game
Is a question accomplished
People are talking rock band and oh what could this be
Most importantly
Something that Guitar Hero is not doing
That was good of them to keep this a secret
For a while because that way
Now it's something to differentiate it from its biggest competitor
Pretty smart
But you know
We shall see when we shall see
Apparently there's something else in this too
About like there's going to be a mode
That's super difficult
But it's just to emulate like actual guitar
In drum playing or something
I'd heard something about that
So that could be interesting
What I would really most like to see
Is them keep, especially for rock band
Is them keep in the harmony
The three part harmony
That they had in Beatles rock band
I think they confirmed that
And one of the dudes slipped up at PAX East
I remember this happening because
My friends were there at that panel
He was there when the guy said
Oh well rock band 3 has harmonies
And then they were all like shut up
It doesn't matter
It's confirmed because also
It's in Green Day rock band
Oh because it's got the mic
And it's got three mics
I really really hope all the songs
Are still backwards compatible
I don't expect them to go back
And add harmonies and keytar
Or whatever they do to all of them
I would still be thrilled if at least
I could just have one massive library
It's gonna be one massive library
Obviously the newer songs
Will support newer things
It'll be interesting to see
What they do with the Green Day rock band
Because those do support three part harmonies
I believe
I think it would be cool if they just went back
And maybe take the top
20 download songs
Cause they know
What 20 songs have sold more
Than any other
Take the top 20 and add support
Or maybe not all of them
Would lend themselves very well to keytar
Or harmony
So take the top 20 songs that would
And just go back and touch those up
That's gonna be enough to get people excited
People were speculating
Because now that you have the three part harmonies
And keyboard
Bohemian Rhapsody
That is hot
Just the fact that Queen could be in the game
At all, well actually I think there's a few songs
But just Bohemian Rhapsody would be amazing
I would really like to see
At least some of the Beatles rock band stuff carry over
Is the Van Halen Guitar Hero thing exclusive
Because you know if there's
Guitar, you know if keyboards are in this
At all in any way shape
Or form
It has to have jump
It has to have
Do do do do do
Like how can you have one of those plastic
Keyboards sitting in your house and not want to play that
It's gonna be awesome
I'm definitely gonna be picking this up
One of the local stores here in Sacramento Guitar Center
I think that's a nationwide store
They actually had a sign up at one of their stores
By the keyboard display
That says, the following songs are
Banned, if you play this song
You will be kicked out of the store
Chopsticks
Fur Elise
And jump
I'm surprised they don't have the axle fully themed
No stairway denied
It's that whole scene exactly
But for real
Anyhow
I'm excited, I'm glad to see they're shaking it up
Beyond just making it prettier
For Rock Band 3, that's gonna be pretty cool
Another piece of plastic crap
To have in my house
I saw my instruments at work
In our game room
I don't have room in my little apartment
I already had to downsize for my house
I have bullshit everywhere
Another plastic instrument is the last fucking thing
I need right now
The thing I love
And it's an awesome investment
Was my drum bag
Cause I can keep my drums and all the other stuff in there
Except for the guitars, the guitars are separate
I have two guitars
Or a guitar and a bass
I do need to get a new guitar though
Cause it's crapping out
Funny enough though
Speaking of quality
The guitar 2 guitar that I still have
Is fucking awesome
It still works great
The guitar 2 guitar I have works
And I did upgrade to a guitar hero 3
Because a while back I was having enough friends
Over where we needed to have a bass
So I just bought a guitar hero 3 guitar
Cause they were really cheap
And now it's wireless, it works awesome
They're fine
Hopefully now with mad cats
Working on the actual instruments
I'm hoping that they'll be a little bit better
It's by mad cats
And I loved it
It's working really well
And please tell me my logic makes sense
That there will be a
Game plus keyboard only pack
They're seeing that there's gonna be all sorts of
Configurations
If you have like one thing then you can get this
And they're gonna do all sorts of different bundles
Which will make it wonderfully confusing
Then I'm happy
Alright
The other big story I wanted to talk about
The armory
For World of Warcraft
Is now available on the iPhone
I'm sorry not just the armory
But the auction house
Oh cause I was gonna say I had the armory when I was playing
Sorry I mean the auction house is now built into the armory
It's a beta test thing going on
That they just opened up to all realms a couple days ago
And you can now
Manage basic auctions
From your iPhone
But it's a beta test because the plan is
This is going to be a pay feature
They're gonna charge I think they were saying
3, 4 bucks a month
I think it was 3 bucks a month
For this feature after the beta
Test period is over which you guess is gonna be
What about 4 to 6 weeks
And I have to
Admit I go back and forth on this
Because when I first downloaded it and played with it
I was like this is clunky
This is kind of stupid
By the way it's not just I should say this
It's not just your iPhone
But you can do it on the web now if you go to the armory
Website and I imagine if there's an armory
App for crack berries and androids
Or whatever other smart phones there are
This feature is going to be built into this too
It's just a matter of time
But when I was playing with this on my iPhone
Of course the day it came out I had to download it check it out
But when I was playing with the feature I have to admit I was like
This is kind of clunky
This is not that great
I can't have auctioneer
The add on I use to be able to undercut
Everybody else this way
It's just not that great and I just kind of
Wrote it off and said I'm not really going to use this
This is stupid whatever
If this is how Blizzard wants to waste their time then so be it
They'll be somebody that wants to use this
But then
Damn it I found myself at work the other day
On lunch thank you very much
And I like to get away from my desk
At lunch because you know the last thing you want to do
During your free time is be at your desk
Staring at your big pile of work to do
So I was in a little break room during lunch
Eating my lunch and you know I'll kind of sit there
And play on my phone maybe look at a game
Sure enough I go on the armory
And I start looking around
I managed to clear out my mailbox
That was full of sold auctions
Relist some of the things that didn't sell
And just kind of manage all that
And clear out my inbox full of crap
On my lunch and I was just like
Oh my god what am I doing
What am I doing
I'm like playing World of Warcraft
Without being at home
This is terrible
That's bad it's bad
Anyhow
It's not something
Extra that I can't already
Get in the game and therefore
I don't see worth paying three dollars
A month is really something I want to
Do I mean I guess there's people
That are more into the economics that want to do
This stuff and if they want to pay for it then so
Be it whatever it's a feature I
Just will not be one of them because I don't think I
Should have that on my phone to be honest
I just don't think I should have that
It's not a good thing to have
Now thankfully
And I say it's kind of a double-edged sword
Because you know it's well
I'm glad
There's not any additional
Game features like something extra
Because then I'd feel a little bit jilted
Because I still held to what I said
A couple weeks ago on this show
The minute Blizzard starts selling
Epics for money I'm out
I quit I'm deleting my account well
Resigning whatever that day
Notice how I can't say I'll delete my account
Because it's too much work but I will resign my
Warcraft membership that day it's done
Um
I just can't justify
That and I really
Hope that's not where they're going I'm a little worried
Did you notice how all this started I mean maybe
It's just me maybe I can I'm a conspiracy
Theorist and what have you call me whatever
Names you want but
Is it just me or did all this nickel and dime stuff
Start happening once Activision bought them
I don't think it's just you Rob
This all kind of like
The sparkle pony
The money for faction transfers
And all these things
And changing your genders and appearance and all this
This all started happening when the
Activision guys came in they swear
Up and down they're not going to sell epics for money
I really really hope
That's the case because it's
It's like starting to push the boundaries a little bit
You know what I mean but whatever
If you want to pay the money and this is a good feature
For you have fun but
I just you know I can't install auctioneer on my phone
So whatever
And that was really it those
Are the two big stories I have some other little things
I can get to but low key I don't
Know what big news stories jumped out at you the past
Few days if there's anything you want to jump in at
Uh yeah one thing I want to
Talk about and it's absolutely
Annoying because I have to deal with this on a daily
Basis now is
The what people are calling
Because I guess EA coined
The phrase for their stuff
Project ten dollar
And project ten dollar is different ways
That EA can make money off of you basically
And the one that's really
I guess the most recent way
They've decided is that they're
Going to have one time
Codes with their um
Sports games starting off
That allow you to play online
If you buy the game used
You have to pay ten dollars
To be able to play
The game we talked about this last week
I understand that but I'm getting into more stuff
Oh dear oh god alright
Okay so I'm sitting here going
Deja vu no no no
There's more stuff we're gonna talk about here
Alright um so
Yeah thankfully they have the seven
Day trial and that's peachy
And stuff for video rentals or game
Rental stores or whatever well that is cool
Um something that's cool
And they're the only ones doing that
Uh THQ on the other hand
Is now they by the way
Weren't gonna mention anything until the day
Of release for UFC
Um but it UFC
Had leaked out so unfortunately
People found out of it or found out about it
They're doing something similar except they're
Charging five dollars there is no trial
So if you buy the game used you ought to play
You know five dollars
In order to be able to play online
Then there was another one
I found out about today
Another company which
I'm just shocked that they're
Jumping on board with this but
Um apparently Microsoft
With Crackdown 2
Will be jumping aboard this um
New trend and they will be having a
One time fee wait wait wait
Wait wait why
Am I paying for Xbox Live?
Why?
If this is if every publisher
Is gonna think because you know
Now this is just the little
Leak in the dam and it's all gonna come crumbling
Down after this why am I paying for
Xbox Live and another story that
You know sorry if you're gonna get to this later but I know this is big
Playstation Network
Is just everybody's waiting for them to say
Something at E3 this year
That there's going to be a Playstation Network Plus
Or what have you
Why am I paying for these services now?
If this is the new way I'm gonna have to pay to play online
Please do not tell me I need both
Xbox Live and the code to play Crackdown
Cause that seems ridiculous
You do um
Oh my god
But it's only gonna affect you if you buy
Used but I still think it's fucked up
That they're double dipping with them
You know this stuff they think that they're entitled
To a part of the used sales I'm sorry
Any other industry you're not
Entitled to used sales if I buy
A used car I don't have to pay a hundred dollars
To like Ford or something for buying
My used car you've already made your fucking
Money and there's like
You know EAs excuses
Oh well we're improving our online
Services and we're able to offer you
More you know download
Content and stuff like that yeah more paid
Download content that I have to buy from you
It's just
It's awful
You know to sit here and say I'm not
Gonna pay for online play would be hypocritical
Because I pay twelve dollars or no fourteen dollars
Whatever it is I don't even know
To play wow you know
That's fine I don't have a problem
Paying to play online I have a
Problem paying twice and I
Have a problem paying like all
These different uncontrolled amounts now
Which okay maybe is a little bit
Hypocritical because of the MMOs
But generally you know an MMO is gonna cost you
And between ten and fifteen
But it's just now there's no
Fucking control anywhere with this
And it really bothers me
I need to hear from Microsoft
At E3 why I should renew my
Xbox Live membership because at this point
I'm not going to
And I've been a member for like six years now
And I'm hoping that there's some sort of misunderstanding
But here's how it came about
We had a head of a company
Might have been Blockbuster Chain
Or something like that
They were asking about Crackdown 2
They were saying well the first Crackdown game was
Online only and you know
I just wanted to make sure there's a single player aspect
To this one and you know of course I was like
Well no the first game actually wasn't online only
And you know
There will be multiplayer and that kind of stuff
I highly doubt that
Microsoft would jump on board with
What they're doing with EA and stuff
Because they're already making money off Live
Our buyer checked with Microsoft
And they're like that's correct
There is going to be
There's a single player and online
And there will be a one time code
Wait is this the internet or are you like
Breaking news here? No I'm breaking news
Oh shit
Huh
So casually too
I know right like
He didn't say secret club or nothing this is just out there
Alright so I mean I'm hoping
That there's a misunderstanding
Ok so yeah take with a grain of salt because
We're not talking about hardcore
Game players with this right
We're talking about business people who might be
Oopsie doopsieing the facts right
Yes and I'm thinking I'm hoping
That the one time code thing is similar
To what we've seen with some of the other games
Like Alan Wake and
You know Gears of War 2
And stuff like that where the one time code is
Download content it's free download content
At launch something like that
I'm retracting my clause
And hoping one of your coworkers is
Fucking up big time
But if it isn't then that's basically
Going to open floodgates because
If Microsoft's doing it then everybody's
Going to do it because they've basically
Been given permission to
So I hope
That's not the case but you know once again
You know I blame a lot of these people
That just don't stand up and
Complain about this stuff you know
They're like oh that's no big deal because you know
I'm getting the game used or whatever
And you know it's just a few extra dollars
Well you know what it's stuff like this
See you feel it's okay
With different things and now they're going to all
Start doing it and pretty soon it's just
Going to be something else what else are they going to take out
Of their game that they're going to charge you five dollars for
You know
It's just it's stupid
And they're not lowering the price of the game by five dollars
Of course not
I don't know
Yeah I worry about
The precedent this might set
I understand why EA's
Doing this ten dollar thing and I think we talked about
This last week and of course other companies
Are going to follow but you know my two biggest
Issues are A
It's not going to stop there
Like Loki's saying and B
I don't want to have to pay for it twice
They need to work it out where
The one source is am I paying Microsoft
Or am I paying the publishers for this
Who's really hosting the servers
And it's absolutely bullshit that they're saying that
You know oh well it's because
We're devl- like THQ's
Wonderful official
Statement about it THQ is delivering
A truly unmatched online gaming
Experience for fans of UFC and across all
Oh shut up
Bullshit uh the main enhancement
Of UFC and disputed 2010's
Premium online content is a new
Fight camp mode in which players can assemble
Ranks up to forty people and train
Together the significant value add
Um value
Add to the game as uh
Players can uh continually
Improve their skills by training
With friends and bringing teams from
MMA specialists together you know what
Though you could have done that and included
That with the game as it is so now you're
Just basically making an excuse because
EA's doing it fuck you EA
You know I you were on a good streak for
A while there Activision was really making
You know themselves look like shit
We're all gonna do it but here
Here you go you know might as well
I'm sure Bobby Kotick's
Eyes are lighting up
Hey we can charge money for that
Uh do you have the story up on PSN Plus
Out of curiosity?
Uh yeah I do
Can you talk about that a little bit?
Yes so people are basically um
Saying that in fact actually the
Sony Computer Entertainment Europe
President has been alluding that they're gonna
Be doing um upcoming paid
Uh Playstation Network subscriptions
And uh
Of course they won't officially comment on it
It says will Playstation Network
Become a paying service
Um Kazrai stated
A few months ago that we were looking at
Premium services sit alongside the current
Free service
And that um objective has not
Changed you'll learn more about it very soon
So yes they are doing that
And uh if I'm hearing it right
They're saying we're not gonna charge you to play
Games online
I'm just trying
To think what could this possibly be
Besides like core you know what I mean
Like I thought core was kind of their
Plus thing with the demos and the
Little things that come with that
Is that just an enhancement of that?
Um from what I remember the rumors
Have been saying that it's supposed to have
Exclusive access to
Cross game voice chat which
You can do for free in Microsoft service
Um it's also
They're gonna say that they're gonna be um
Including I guess some sort of
Cloud based saving system
Um I was reading
That they're also supposed to be I think offering
Uh the ability to
Uh purchase
A full title of a game first
Also they'll be able to play the first hour of download
Games for free Yeah that's interesting
I'd heard that one something about you can download
The whole stinking game and play
Like an like every Blu-ray
Game will basically have a demo for an hour
Like I don't even know how that works
I don't know if that's wishful thinking or what
Am I I think I'd seen something
This is probably another rumor fanboy
Wank or whatever but I'd seen something about
Playstation 1 games are just gonna be
Fucking play whatever you want
They're gonna have a rotating
A rotating list of PSP minis
And Playstation 1 classics, exclusive
In game download content, discounts
To the Playstation store
Um
So stuff like that
Maybe, maybe, I definitely
Want to hear more about it, I mean I
We need to separate the fanboy wank from the reality
But there's some interesting features in there
I can tell you right now when you pay him for this, I don't play on the Playstation
Never good enough But now, well now
I'm paying for Xbox Live
And if this, if, if, if, if, big if
Capital I, capital F, if
It is true that
Crackdown is gonna do the double dip thing
And I don't hear
From Microsoft what the hell I'm paying for anymore
Are you buying Crackdown
Used, that's the thing, if you're buying it
Used, then yeah it's double dipping
If you're buying it new, you get the code
You can play the thing
So, I don't know
Still why am I paying for Xbox Live
You know
It's still, it's really
Kind of a lame thing to be doing because
They're like saying, oh we deserve a portion of
Your used sales, and fuck you GameStop
For being okay with this shit
I mean why, you're the biggest fucking
Company out there as far as retail
You know they're not
They're just, they have no choice
Nah, I'll get into more of that
Why I think they're doing
What they're doing and why they're so gung ho
About it anyway
Please, I want to hear that next, next time
Okay, so fuck them
Freeform tonight, I get what I want
Fuck them for being just okay about this
Wait, wait, wait, surely you have an opinion
What do you think about this whole like
PlayStation Network Plus
And the Crackdown rumor
Do you have any thoughts
Not yet
Would you pay for a service where you could
Just go in and play any PlayStation 1 game
You wanted
Depends
Depends on, I mean, if it was
Any game, any at all
Ever
Maybe
But I don't need to because I have
The vault
Okay
So fuck them for going along with this and basically
Saying, oh yeah, we think it's a great idea
Yeah, you know why you think it's a great idea?
Because you're going to start selling download content soon
And you're cashing in on that
And basically Microsoft is
Saying, hey, you know what
We're going to give you some back end
Rebates from this stuff
I don't know
They may be changing their tune too
When you look at some of these games
That you basically sell them for 30 bucks
They turn around and sell it for 55 dollars
And then they're going to charge me 10 dollars
On top of that to, you know
Say, for example, buy
You know, multiplayer online
You know, I'm paying basically 5 dollars
More than the price of a new game
So I'm going to be buying a new game
Obviously, if I'm really interested in that
Or I just won't play online
Thankfully
A lot of the games, if I were to ever buy them used
I probably wouldn't be playing them online
I don't play a lot of stuff online
I don't know
It's really awful
Alright, get to the other thing
About GameStop
That's why I already went to that
Because they're going to be selling download content
That was it
Sorry, I don't know if that's alright
No, I had heard that
I had heard that rumor a little bit before
I just can't see
Walking into GameStop to get
The download content
Being able to
Sample it in the store or whatever
On their little kiosks
It's just like Amazon
How you can buy stuff off Amazon
And get the codes and stuff like that
But sometimes you want to go to the mall
I get that, but I don't know
It's weird
Alright, what else
How about another story
Then maybe we'll do release dates
Scratch the Ultimate DJ
Coming to iPhone, iPad
And the PC
They're still working on I guess the console versions
As well according to Newmark
But they are going to be out
On those three platforms later this year
It looks kind of weird though
I can't imagine playing this game on an iPad
Or something, very awkward
They have turntables in the
Upper corners and then the five keys
On the bottom and a crossfader
Just above those keys
Little complex
The PC version though will actually have a controller for it
So that will be interesting to see
Um
But apparently
You know, I guess
It kind of sucks that the whole game was held up
Because of the whole lawsuit with
Activision and stuff
Which we never really heard what happened with that
Have they settled or what
Uh, whatever um
Happened to the console release
Is that still tied up in the lawsuit?
It says the console versions
Are still in development
And the PC version will use a special controller
Interesting
Yeah
Alright
Um, how about release dates?
Do you want to do some release dates?
That sounds like fun. Sure. Alright
Do you have Europe ones? I do.
Jamie, why don't we start with you?
We haven't heard your lovely voice in a few minutes
Okay
Yeah, go for it. Why not?
Alright, well then um
It's really just a few things
On the uh
Well, today, the 26th
Doom 2 for Xbox 360
And Sing Star
Kent
Um, on Playstation 3
28th Clash of the Titans and Darkness Within 2
The Dark Lineage for PC
No More Heroes 2 Desperate Struggle
Project Runway
Project One Way, or as I was saying
Pure Football
I thought it was called Project Catwalk over there
Make it work
Critical Blur UFC
Undisputed 2010
Basit
Loki?
Um, well, there's a few things
coming out this week
Witch's Witch from Natsume
That's on the DS
The Sims 3
Ambitions, the new expansion pack
for the PC
Mind Over Matter, another
Bane training
Brain training puzzle game
coming out on DS as well
Backbreaker coming out on
Xbox 360 and Playstation 3
That's one of those independent football games
Alpha Protocol on
Xbox 360
PC and Playstation 3
Pure Football
on Playstation 3
and Xbox 360 this week
America's Next Top Model
on DS and
on the Wii
That's exciting
Hope Crazy Tyra's in it
Diamond Trust
of London
It's a strategy game on the DS
That's nice, I guess
Bass Pro Shops
The Hunt, yet another
deer hunting game
That's on the Wii and Xbox 360
and the Wii, of course, getting a gun bundle
because those people that own Wiis
love guns
And, um
What else do we have here?
Call of Duty The War Collection
is a re-release of three Call of Duty
World War II games on
Xbox 360, I believe two, three in World at War
Uh
Let's see here, Prince of Persia The Forgotten
Sands on PC, I guess it was a few weeks late
And that's
that's basically it
Alright
Oh, Syphon Filter is Logan's
Shadow on Playstation 2
Yes, they're still making Playstation 2 games
Yes, they're still ports of
PSP game, right?
Uh, going to Japan
These releases are for June 3rd, we're not gonna be live again
until June 6th, and I didn't see a lot for May
So let's go to June 3rd releases for Japan, okay?
Some price reductions on Gears of War 2
on the 360, Gundam Musou 2
and Tales of Vesperia
Again, these are June 3rd releases I'm doing today
Uh, going to the
Playstation 3
Also, some more price reductions
Gundam Musou 2 and Katamari Damacy Tribute
which I believe is, uh, Katamari
What do they call it, Forever here?
I don't know that game and I can't remember
Uh, nothing really notable on the Wii
This is kind of a dry period over there
I don't know if there's, you know, just not the season
but it's mostly price reductions going on in Japan right now
Uh, same thing when you look at the PS2
Gundam Musou 2, Mobile Suit Gundam
games going on sale
Uh, Nintendo DS
another Pachinko game comes out
Kaiden Restaurant Ura menu, 100-sen
I don't know if that's like 100 different things
on the menu or what, but that is coming out on the DS
and then on the PSP
100-sen
Is that the 100 classic books thing or?
From Nintendo?
No, because it's Kaiden Restaurant
I don't think that's it
No, there's like a little happy ghost on the cover
It's a horror buffet
with chilling blood curdling
and creepy stories as dishes
Maybe it is, 100 tales for you to order
Choose the one that suits your mood
Vampires, ghosts, psychopath killers
These characters fill the cartridge and all you have to do
is order them to come out
That sounds creepy
It's like Silent Hill, but you read it
Uh, and then lastly
on the PSP
Bleach, Heat the Soul 6
gets a price reduction
and probably the only new game I'm seeing on this whole list
Fairy Tale, Portable Guild
is coming out this week from Konami
on June 3rd, next week
There you go, Japanese releases, there you have it
Uh, let's do a
couple stories and then we'll get into
other topics
and we'll do the mailbag and all that other fun stuff too
Um, let me
I'll tackle a couple things here
that I wanted to touch on
that rolled over from what we were going to do on Sunday
Uh, Facebook and Zynga
Kiss... Zynga? Zynga?
Farmville, people
They kissed and made up
They had make-up sex
and everything's better. Remember how they were threatened
Remember how Zynga, Zynga, Zynga
was threatening to leave and like, we're going to take Farmville
to their own damn website and I said, it'll never work
It'll never work
Well, they came to their senses and they kissed and made up
and they have committed to their
long-term relationship
and, um, meaning that I guess
for years and years, they're going to
basically, Zynga got a deal on that
Facebook credit thing, you know that's how it works out
Did you hear something else about them too?
What's that? They're teaming up with Yahoo
and they're going to have all their games on Yahoo as well
Um, they're going to be integrated into
all their different web pages and stuff
It's not the same. Yahoo already has
a gaming portal
A lot of the PopCap stuff and all that's on
What were the games?
I actually used to play some games on there
There's like a Scrabble-type game on there
and the freaking whiteboard game
It was like Pictionary
and everybody drew dirty fucking pictures in that game
I can't remember the name of it
Yeah, I even played some of those games before
Whatever
It's not Facebook
If you can't collect the things and post
them to your wall so you can prove
that you have the biggest E-peen farm
that you're farming all the E-peen in the land
then
The part where I
banged my head against the wall
was when I saw the Farmville cards for sale
at like 7-11
There was like little $10 Farmville cards, I was like
Oh my god. Did you see the Farmville ice cream?
Oh god, yeah, I heard something
about that, like there's Farmville ice cream
and Farmville...
Slurpees or something? Oh god
No, do not want
It's all fattening anyway
Ice cream is bad for you
It makes you fat
This is why you're fat
Alright, the website
I wasn't saying that to you, Loki
I thought this was an interesting story too
that had to do with Epic
and a comment they made this
week, or this past week
about piracy
And they basically said that
6 years ago, Epic was a PC
company, but because
of piracy, they went to
consoles. We did one
PS2 launch title and everything else was PC
and now people are saying, why do you
hate the PC? You're a console only company
It's because the money's on
consoles. That's from President
Mike Capps
We still do PC, we still love
the PC, but we already saw the impact of
piracy. It killed a lot of great
independent developers and completely
changed our business model
And then it goes on to talk a little bit about Steam
and how Steam is essentially single-handedly
really helping
breathe life into PC gaming
because piracy is just driving it bankrupt
Any thoughts on that, Loki?
Not that I'm insinuating that you're a pirate or anything
but I know you usually have strong feelings about
these types of topics
There's piracy on any
platform, regardless of PC
Xbox 360
handhelds
other consoles
It's easier to do on PC
so I guess that's
true, but
they're facing piracy everywhere
Is that really an excuse?
I think it's because they can charge more for their
games, but
whatever
Good for you
You're a console developer
now
Do you want me to pat you on the back or something?
Really?
Alright, one other story and then I'll let Loki take over
for a little bit. BlizzCon tickets
on sale
June 2nd and June 5th
$150 if you want to go
and the con is in October
October 22nd and 23rd
You know what, DarkSakura? I think you and I
should go down to Anaheim on October 22nd
and 23rd and go to Disneyland
Fuck BlizzCon
$150?
No thank you. The 22nd and 23rd
October
Except I'll be going to Alabama right after
No, I'll be going to Alabama in November
I haven't done Disney with Jamie in a while
I've done Disney with other people, not Jamie
It's been a little while
Here's my thing
You might be thinking, what the hell, Rob?
You're like the biggest wow addict on that show
and why are you all hating on BlizzCon?
A, they want
$150
What am I getting?
Cataclysm ought to be out by then
I mean, and if it's not
Damn, they're moving slow
When is it again? October 22nd and 23rd
Well, they did release the last expansion
I want to say, or there was one of expansions
that was released in November, so
Yeah, but Burning Crusade
was out in like January
Well, then that's both after October
Look, it's World of Warcraft
Blizzard can release it
whenever the fuck they want
They could release it on Christmas Eve
and nerds would be out in force to get there
and be the first
It doesn't matter, it's Blizzard
They can do what they want
Look, I understand
They got to recoup their costs
They do some big stuff for this
Whatever, it's a pretty big effing deal
Am I going to get to be the first to play
their new MMO?
Which is the rumor that they have a type of
action-ish MMO that's in the works
I think the last rumor I heard
was like a spy, espionage-y type of game
might be their next MMO
So, the agency?
I don't know, I don't know
Rumor, huge fan wank rumor, don't quote me
And I imagine Diablo 3
is going to be playable
but $150?
I'd rather ride Space Mountain
three times in a row, what?
Dude, I'd just rather ride Space Mountain
period, instead of like
almost anything
Yep, so maybe
we'll walk out front of the convention center
like when we
when we get bored
we'll go walk over to the convention center
I don't know how we're going to get bored at Disneyland
but let's just hypothesize that every ride we want to go on
is broken
We'll go walk outside the convention center
and look at the people and go
So, how's it going?
Be like, hey y'all
we're going to go on
on the Matterhorn
have fun waiting in line
You might be able to get in as a press
maybe
Is it bad to say
that again, I would just
the convention center
let me put this in perspective, if you've never been to Anaheim
the convention center is literally
two blocks from Disneyland
You can walk there, it's not that bad
I mean, with all the walking you do at Disneyland in a day
I don't get why you drive anyway
You can
especially California Adventure is like right there
it's the first park you hit moving that direction
I know that
You could
literally walk to Disneyland
and if I'm going to be that close, I've got to go
Maybe I should be doing a Disney podcast
I don't know
I might feel a little more
excited if I knew
what games I was going to get to see
but Starcraft 2 is out in July
so maybe one of the future expansions
but I'm not a Starcraft person anyway
I'm assuming it's all about Diablo 3
and I guess
Cataclysm if it's still not out
but it's got to be in beta by that point
so people are already playing it
maybe they'll announce another
Warcraft expansion
I mean, I don't know
I could go off on a tangent about this
maybe this isn't the right forum
but I kind of think Cataclysm
is less of an expansion
I mean, don't get me wrong, I'm very excited for Cataclysm
it sounds like an exciting expansion
but I think this is the
closest you're going to get
to WoW 2.0
like, they're literally going back
and upgrading the old game
and they're using the Cataclysm as the retcon to do it
so it's kind of like
you're getting a little less of an upgrade
with all this new stuff
as you're just getting your old stuff enhanced
to be competitive with newer releases
does that make sense?
so I wouldn't be surprised at all if another expansion
comes pretty quickly afterwards
the actual expansion
where you go out to a new area
and all this stuff
and the additional five levels you didn't see in this first expansion
but that's just
you know, again
fanboy wank
are they raising it in level cap again?
to 85, but not to 90
which is, you know, fine, whatever
but it just kind of makes me think
that they already have another expansion
planned that will take it to 90
I ultimately think WoW will stop at 100
level 100 seems to be a nice
even round number, but we'll see
again
fanboy wank, nothing more
Loki, what do you got for us?
apparently
Edge is reporting
that Project Natal
will
be out for
$150
and October 26
give or take a few weeks
didn't they say 100 bucks?
oh no, that was a Playstation move
I
I don't think
I would hope that they're smart enough
not to put it out for that price
that's how much a week costs, isn't it?
yeah, and they're also
basically
the Xbox, well we know that
a slim Xbox is coming out
so perhaps
they're going to be bundling with that
and they're saying that they're going to be bundling
with the new Xbox 360
for $300
I don't know
it seems awfully high
I know the technology is probably great
and all, but
they've got to have learned
something from Sony, if you put it out
at that kind of price point
no one's going to pick it up
you've got a few people picking it up, but no one's
going to really jump on board with it because
I can get a Wii for that price
but, if there's some
kick my ass amazing, blow
my hair back game
I might pay it
a system is only as good as the games that are on it
and the advantage of this
over the Playstation Move
is that you have to buy this
and you're done
there's no additional controllers you have to buy
because you're basically the controller
so it works up to
do you think maybe that's their leverage?
they're going to come out and say yes, it's $150
but maybe they're going to do a price comparison
and they'll say, if you want to buy
the Wii for the whole family to play
that actually costs you
$150 plus what?
$40 plus $40 plus $40, right?
it's $40 plus
actually because you're going to need nunchucks probably
so $40 plus $20
so $60, so a lot
another $180 on top of that
alright, so a lot, but they're going to say
that's going to be their leverage, they're going to come out and say
to buy the Xbox 360
Natal for the whole family
$300 and it plays DVDs
and it does Netflix out of the box
and...
all this stuff
I can see it
again, if they have
the game to justify it
then
they'll get away with it
I think it needs to be sub $100
but that's just me
I would say they should
put it out for $99.99
you know what they should do?
here's how they would sell a million copies
you ready?
no joke, you guys are going to hate me
for this, all the people listening
are going to cringe, but I'll tell you what
they would sell a million copies of this
you ready?
the biggest loser video game
the whole family can play
Project Natal
so it's like
a competitor to Wii Fit based off that
TV show
it would sell like crazy
number one
they put it out on the Wii
pretty successful, because it came out last October
and it sold pretty well
it's already out
and it was okay
but it's not a system seller
and yeah, I understand there's going to be
all those kind of party games
and fitness games and stuff like that
and it's going to suck
because there's going to be a ton of these crappy games
coming up, but that doesn't really affect me
too much because you don't have to buy them, obviously
it's just really how much is the hardware going to cost
that's really the thing I'm interested to find out
but
I will find out in a few weeks
I'm sure they're going to say a price point
they better say a price point
E3 is kind of the time you lay it all out on the table
for the holidays
I would expect
you may not get specific dates
but you're going to get
I think you'll get prices and you're going to get a pretty good
understanding of what that blow your hair back game is
that they're putting behind
whether it be Fable 3, the Milo thing
and I said that
a long time ago, it's going to be Gears 3
I did, remember?
I said, because they were hiding
that game for the longest time
Gears is a pretty successful franchise
and they just recently announced Gears 3
and I think it's gotten a top support
Here's the other thing I'm thinking
though, is that
one of the
I guess conspiracy theories about it was
that they were saying that they originally
were remembering that it was going to be like 50 bucks
for the game, for the actual thing
and that now they're
putting out this rumor that it's going to be $150
so they can come back and put it out
for $99, so those people are hoping
that it was $50 aren't as
disappointed, you know, whereas the people
that thought it was going to be $150 are like, hey!
Now it's only $99, that's awesome!
I don't know
If they do come out with Natal support for Gears of War 3
at E3, I want to be called
from here on out, games analyst
Rob Roberts, games analyst
If I'm wrong
then I'm just some dickhead with a podcast
which is what I've always been, nothing new
You could be Robert Patrick, stupid Michael Patrick
I want to go on record saying
Michael Patrick's a fucking douchebag
and the reason why, because he just throws out guesses
and yet people come
That's what we do!
I understand that, but people fucking run
It's like if he comes out on his balcony
to the game of press
He's like the pope
Pretty much, he walks out
writes his declaration
and then goes back to
I think this holiday season
game consoles will do well
and everybody reports it like
Oh my god, he said something!
Game consoles do well! Michael Patrick says so!
Oh my god!
Women fainting
I just don't understand
why people have
This is why, other than complaining about him
I will never mention any analyst
I don't give a shit what an analyst
thinks
Who cares? If that's your job, great
I don't go asking meteorologists
what the weather is going to be like
Because they're not always right
Would it be wrong for us to put
in the description of our podcast
three games analysts
conquer the video game news
every week
You don't really have to have a degree to call yourself an analyst
You just have to analyze the market
We've been doing that for eight years
That's on the job
experience, right?
Dark Soccer, you know this
legal stuff better than I do
Can I call myself a games analyst?
You can call yourself whatever you want
There you go
Orange Lounge Radio brought to you by three expert
games analysts
every week
We've been analyzing the industry for eight years
I will go as far as saying I'm the most
expert analyst of them all
That's my opinion
I am the most expert analyst ever
We are the most smartest
games analysts out there
The most expertest
I'm the smartest of them all
Another news story
please, before our egos
inflate anymore
Michael Patrick's coming out on the balcony again
Oh my god!
What's he saying?
Madden 11 will sell a lot
Oh my god!
It's the holy word
God's awful
I just don't understand
I hate me because it's true
I hate you because it's true
Mama, what have you done now?
That's right
Babysitting mama
including your very own plush baby
which you shove a remote down its throat
in order to play
I kid you not
Really?
Yes, really, that's right
It uses a plush baby in which you have
tucked a Wii remote inside
also using the nunchuck that is somehow hanging out
of the plush baby somehow
You play 40 mini games
and the usual cookie mama style
and representing feeding
changing the baby, rocking it to sleep
and six different
virtual babies, each with their unique personalities
So if the baby shits
everywhere, then don't worry, mama will
fix it
I don't know
Oh, you wanted a girl? Don't worry, mama
will fix it
Don't worry, Dr. 90210
will fix it I don't know
It's weird, they did have a game
come out like this
I think it's called
My Baby There was a story
It was on an Australian blog
It was a Twitter topic one week
I remember that Yes
The character of the baby doll
Oh my gosh
And it's also like that Wiiwa thing, remember the doll?
Yeah, I remember Wiiwa, did the Wiiwa ever come out?
Not yet
Oh, it's interesting
But that's going to be weird that you have to have a baby doll
Not a damn person
listening to this show is ever going to play that game
It is cooking mama
Dark Sakura is the biggest
fan of cooking mama, I know
Dark Sakura, babysitting mama, yes or no?
I have a great idea No
No, no, no, I have the greatest idea
She's lip the baby, high heat
She's a games analyst
Loki, and she says
it's just not interesting
We should have a contest with this game
I'm telling you
The contest is, and this is great, you're going to love this
The contest is
to photograph your best
baby mama
not baby mama, yeah
Baby mama? They should have done it
Is that the babysitting mama? Baby mama
Anyways, um
No, the best babysitting mama
baby analog you could create
So, I mean, because basically
the Wii remote has to go into something
It doesn't necessarily have to be this
doll, unless the doll is actually going to have
a cord or something that's coming out of it
that you can plug into your Wii remote
and actually going to be its own controller
but assuming that it's not, it's just going to be some stuff thing
We should have people, like, take
other stuff things or
take your own baby out of whatever you have lying around your house
and that might be funny
and take pictures
playing the game with it
That's, that's
the game that we need to have
instead of, uh, uh
Cookie Mama or whatever, we need to have
this one
Not who that is
Not who she is
Why is it always the same old thing?
Y'all knew that
joke was coming, come on
You knew it, you knew it, don't sigh
Don't sigh at me
It's grown, Rob, it's grown because I knew
I got a quickie story of something you might hear
at E3, or you might not, I don't know
but apparently there are rumors going around
rumors abounding that Final Fantasy 13
versus may actually
release on the Xbox 360
Apparently that's something Squeenix is looking
into
Yeah, because Final Fantasy 13 did pretty well
so where the money is, they will follow
The answer will be at E3
Just dropping that little tidbit out there
Also one other little tidbit I wanted to drop
just because I thought this was cool
Top Gun apparently is coming to Playstation Network
There's, not, not the movie
It's an actual Playstation 3
game, and it'll be out on Mac and PC
as well. It's gonna be an air combat game
My hope is it's
pretty much the 8-bit game, but with
better graphics and new stuff, right?
That's what we want, right? I had Top Gun on the NES
That was a badass game
Good times
Loki, maybe one or two other stories, then we'll get
to the, like, we need to do the tweets and the mailbag
and all that other fun stuff
GameStop, remember they were talking about
throwing around the idea of some sort of
new rewards program
Well, now it's being
launched, I guess, their Power Up Rewards
program, and there's
two different things. You can get a card for free
Wait, first off, is this something that they
will try to force on me with every purchase?
It's basically the same thing
You'll see it's not very different
than what they're offering right now
So they have a card that you
can get for free, that, you know
you don't really do anything for
Or a card that's the
Platinum card, I guess, for
$14.99
Now, here's what you get
with the different cards
The standard black card
for each dollar that you spend
on new games and consoles
you get 10 points
Points that you earn on pre-owned games
you earn 20 points
For your trades
you get 20 points
per dollar
There's different birthday bonuses
exclusive member offers
and you get entered in
each time you buy something
to the Epic Rewards Giveaway
and then online activation
I guess
250 points
and if you establish a game library
with them you get 250 points
Now, with the Platinum card
you get basically all that
plus
in the Epic Rewards Giveaway thing
you get two entries
If you upgrade
to the Pro tier you get
an extra 250 points
you get a
one time buy two get one free
offer for pre-owned games
you get 10% off
10% bonuses on points
for your purchases
10% on pre-owned purchase
discount, I guess
and 10% trade bonus
and of course 12 issues of
Game Informer. So basically
you get the same shit that you
get now, except there's this point system
that you can trade in for different things
including
like, I guess you can
get
gift cards
free
controllers, but the prices on them
are just absolutely
ridiculous
like you have to basically spend
$4,000 to get it
My God, well the way
and the sad thing is the extra $5
I have to pay online to play it online
now, it will not count towards this
Yeah, basically it says the rewards range from
coupons for $5 to $10 off
purchases, and that ranges from
$4,000 to $8,000 points
You can even get a free
Xbox 360 controller or eternal beach
X11 headset for
40,000 points
of course would equal about
$4,000 spent on new games
The eternal beach headset, it's like $100
I think, and the controllers are like
$40, but
$4,000, really?
I mean, is that
what you're expecting? Oh, you're gonna give me something for
$40 after I spend $4,000?
Yeah, no
Yeah, no thanks. Do not want
But hey, I mean if you're really dead
set on spending your money at GameStop
anyways, you might as well get the card because at least you're earning
some points towards something, but I
mean, I don't know
Just like I have this thing at Petco where I
like buy cat food and stuff
I'm supposed to like buy ten bags of cat food
and I get one free, but it's within a certain
time limit, and that never happens
You might as well, because you're buying cat food
No, it never happens
It never happens, because I don't go through that much cat food
You don't have enough cat food, you need more cats
You need more cats
Alright, how about a quick story, then we'll go to Twitter
Alright
UFC Undisputed
2010 just was released
yesterday, and
unlockable is
Shaq
That's right, you can play a little Shaq-Fu
with Shaquille O'Neal
And there's actually an easy code to
do that
On the Xbox 360, at the main menu
you would hit down, up, left
down, down, left, up, down, down
left, X
Y, Y, X
And then start
On Playstation 3, it would be
down, up, left, down, down
left, up, down, down
left, square, triangle, triangle, square
start
So, there you go
There's your pro tip for the day
Right
Because I know everybody's just
running out to put that code in
right now
Let's do some Twitter topics, huh?
We may not have a chat room tonight
but we still have all you kids on Twitter
The nice thing about doing this mid-week is
we kind of get some different people, we catch different people
because a lot of folks that don't listen to us live
don't because they have other things going on
Sunday night, but we, looks like we got a little bit of a
different crowd tonight
Uh, let's see
Rockman Rock
sent us a tweet that says
You thought the movie, The Human Centipede
was a bad idea, just wait until
you play the game
That's right, there's a Human Centipede
game that I got
linked to here at Newgrounds
that I could play, but
I don't know if I want to
because the Human Centipede
is fucking gross
Yeah, but it's just Centipede
Let me just do this
You are doctor, wait let me make this full screen here
Wait, let me turn off the Twitter music, we already heard the Twitter music tonight
Shut up, Santa
Alright, let's see, you are Dr. Heider, a brilliant German
surgeon who's gone mad and surgically attached people
ass to mouth to create the Human Centipede
Your parents are not pleased
You must take your trusty rifle
and put down these Human Centipedes
with the bad dogs they are, whatever
Oh look, there's some
little people with their mouths on their butts
and there were ten points
Oh, that's not very gross, it's just digital
It's like little, let's see, we can do mouse
controls, mouse to move and left click
to fire, oh this is just
Centipede
Ha, but the Centipede
I get it, it's
the Human Centipede
The sounds are right
This is totally a hacked version
Oh, there's a police officer
Oh, and I just shot him to bits, woohoo
Yay, I beat the first stage
They change colors really stupidly
Yeah, that's a little dumb
Thanks anyway
A little dumb
Uh, let's see
Blade 3, or Blade III
How about
It says Blade E!
Blade E!
How about new Facebook privacy
Finally fixes games, annoying achievements
being posted everywhere, did you hear about this?
Facebook's been in the news a lot and I guess they
came out today, well they came out a couple days ago
and I love
the Facebook CEO because he's such
a bro, like you know
he's just, he looks like that total
douchebag frat guy
and like he's running this multi
like what, billion dollar company
and like he came out a couple days
ago and literally said the corporate
equivalent of, oh yeah my bad
My bad on that one
guys, sorry guys, my bad
I forgot
the keg, my bad
That's pretty much what happened a couple days ago
Well they came out today and talked about the base
so they're going to have to dumb down the privacy because
too many people are
you know, getting information used
that they don't want to be used, the biggest problem
is that
Facebook sets a lot of things to public by
default without really giving you enough warning
that's the biggest problem I always had
with it, but it sounds like they're getting rid of that
they're going to make it really easy to block applications
which includes games
so if you want to just block
all the fucking Facebook apps
and all the games, one click, done
how about that Dark Soccer, you won't have to read any of that
crap ever again, sweet
at least that's what it's
sounding like, we'll see, I guess we won't
really know until later tonight when it's implemented
maybe it's on there now, I don't know
Let's see, Sponge Twang wants to tell us
that he is going to a medium sized
Anime Con, not a big one, not as small
it's a medium sized
Anime Con in Boise, Idaho
Anime Oasis
Are there Oases in
Boise? I don't know
Oasis? Oasis
Are they in Boise?
Boise Oasis?
Anyway, saying
check out the game room, Sponge Twang is going to check out
the game room at Anime Oasis 2010
Yes, please, let us know
We like the Anime Cons, but we like the gaming room
reports, especially
Popo
and Jer
I know this guy, this is my buddy
Jer, not on Facebook, he's probably
on Facebook too, but LiveJournal
Popo and Jer says, or it's Pop
on Jer, I like Popo and Jer better
although it might be Pop on Jer
says Rob's Giggle sounds like
the Riddler from the old Batman series
just saying
Woo hoo hoo hoo!
I don't know
This is like Winnie the Pooh
That's what he did, the old Riddler guy
had this hoo hoo hoo thing he did
Yeah, it does sound like the Doughboy, shut up
I hate you, stop judging me
But I love the old Batman series
That's, that's Batman
Screw this
Batman, that's right, that was
Batman was awesome
GGBeat wants us to talk about
how Jet Set Radio should go to
Xbox Live Arcade, it would be awesome
I agree, it should go to Xbox Live
Arcade, it would be awesome, there should just be
a new Jet Set game, period
I thought it was coming to Xbox Live Arcade
Was that something that was
spoiled on the partner net or whatever?
I think it was one of the ones spoiled on the partner net
I can't remember, there is a lot
of Dreamcast stuff coming to Xbox Live
Arcade at some point
GGBeat, you need to cross your fingers, cross your toes
hold your breath and hope for a miracle at E3
I wonder if it'll be, yeah, it'll probably show it at E3
Maybe that'll be the game, you know how sometimes
at E3 there's like a game that they go
and it's out right now
Like I think, wasn't that Doom a couple years ago?
They came out and said Doom will be available tonight
Right?
Ironically Doom 2, maybe, maybe
GGBeat
Do it, do it, say a prayer
Light a candle
A satanic chant, whatever it is you want to do
I would guess Sonic Adventure over
that, cause that's actually
leaked out already
MNZeba
wants us to talk about
this game Ryzom
that is going open source
pretty interesting when an MMO goes open source
Ooh, this is cute
I've never seen this, is this
I don't know if that's the same game or if that's the
website, but there's this
cute little background with like a little raccoon
with a hard hat on and it's a cute little character
Well, whatever, anyhow Winchgate
who is developing and publishing Ryzom
they have announced that the Science Fantasy
MMO Ryzom, it's open source
That's kind of neat, an MMO going open source
And you install Linux on
the MMO
Probably, you can now use the
Ryzom core toolkit to make mods
or enhancements to the existing code
and even develop your own virtual world
Wow, that's pretty crazy
Who knows what might come of that, well thanks for the
heads up, if we have any programmers
that want to make the OLR MMO, go for it
The SEG
wants us to mention, how about the
Supreme Court hearings in October about the
California video games law
Oh yeah, that's going to be a big deal
Whatever happens because of that, I mean it will be
you know, the Supreme Court is
supposed to be the end of the line, the highest court in the land
Hopefully it will be the last we hear on it
I just feel like
I just don't know enough about the law
I might be a games analyst
But I don't really know enough to really
say what's going to happen with this
Of course I want it to be struck down, of course
I think the whole thing is a little silly
But I have no legal
basis to say it will or it won't
Do you guys have any thoughts?
The California video games law that
will, the California law will
make it illegal to sell the game, right?
I don't remember
I don't remember the specifics
about it, I have to look that
up real quick, hold on
What's the problem with doing a free form show?
You haven't really researched your topics
I think we're going to see
I really
I really don't see that it would
fly
I mean
Haven't they tried before?
Let's see, the California
law imposes restrictions on and a
labeling requirement with respect to
the sale or rental of violent video
games to minors. Several other states
have passed similar laws and others may well be
watching the case, the stakes
extend beyond California. I remember
this now because the verbiage
in the law was very vague
I remember this, it didn't really state
how a game was
It was a very
gray area
type of thing on what constituted a violent
game and hopefully that's going to be the same thing
that does the law in
But we'll see
I don't know
We'll see what happens
Butch Kawa says
Might be a late one, no you got in just under the wire
But the topic of heavy rain rights might
go to a movie deal, trivializing
the game or just trying to cash in
Heavy Rain movie, also
I'll piggyback on this, I wanted to say I read
this week a Mass Effect movie
was sold to Legendary Pictures too
What do you think? These games are pretty epic
to begin with, I mean they're a little different
than what we've seen before
Mass Effect would be kind of hard to condense down in the movie
Heavy Rain I could see it because it pretty much played out like a movie
so why not?
As long as the Jason scenes in it
Jason! Jason! Jason!
Jason!
Did you see the Press X
Jason music video today? I did actually
That was awesome
Good stuff
As long as they have the Jason scene in it, Bochi Kawa
I'm cool
But of course it's kind of
I don't necessarily think it's trivializing
the game, it's trying to cash in
They realize that the game is done pretty
well and will have a built in audience
to go see it and they can probably make
the movie relatively cheap
Speaking of which, I'm kind of curious to see how Prince of Persia
does because we might actually have a
mainstream video game movie
that does well With no Persians in it
Imagine that I know
It's so whitewashed
I think I saw something on Yahoo where the headline
was Prince of Persia called
Offensive
They're talking the movie, not the game
But it had to do, it was a story about that
and the movie
they can't call Avatar
The Last Airbender because they're all whitewashed
Well if they can't find
Persian actors that are
good enough for those parts
I think that's a little silly
Jake Gyllenhaal of course
is an A-list actor
There's going to be lots of people
Maybe myself included
who will want to see the movie
Don't mind me while I sound really racist here
Who would they get to play
these Persian roles?
Would they have Kal Penn or something?
Playing the major lead in this?
Well I think
you only need
one or two A-list actors
To take a step back
I think that
says something about our society in general
where you've only got one or two guys
to pick from
Was Aladdin Persian? I don't remember him being very
Persian in the cartoon
He was pretty white
I think that says something about society
A much larger
problem of society
What? The Disney one?
He looked
Middle Eastern?
Let me say this
There's an Aladdin stage show at California
Now you are making me do a Disney podcast
Adventure
The last time I saw it
the Jafar they had playing it
was a black guy
He's the best one I've ever seen
He was great
He was just enough camp
that the little kids want to boo him
but he was still really campy
He was by far the best Jafar
He happened to be a black guy
I didn't get offended that he wasn't
actually looked like the Sultan in the movie
or was Persian
He played the part well
The problem is people complain about everything
and that's really what it comes down to
If you don't like it
If that really gets your butt hurt
don't go see the movie
Also
Can I just say this real quick
They had a girl in the ensemble
in a wheelchair
A power wheelchair in the ensemble
She was actually pretty fierce
I got to say
They were kind of smart with how they integrated her into all the dance numbers
and everything
During a whole new world where the ensemble will come out
and they're carrying famous buildings
I shit you not
She had pyramids tied to the back of her wheelchair
and she'd ride along with everybody else
She's singing
It was great to see
You know why I like to see that?
Because there's a lot of handicapped kids that go to Disneyland
and for them to be able to see that
that if they want to do that, they can
I think that's great, personally
Boy, we're getting into too...
These topics are too deep
We need dick and fart jokes, help
We're done with Twitter, twitter.com
I burped, did I help?
Well, there's a game coming out
called Warriors of Alaysia
and it's basically
bikini-clad women fighting each other
Mortal Kombat style
And they have a lot of bikini-clad women that are
promoting it as well
So that's kind of interesting
Boobs!
Exactly. Speaking of boobs
If we have any listeners that are
going to Phantom this weekend
There's actually one of my friends
from high school
She's an amazing artist, worked for EA
Did a lot of the artwork for My Sims
That franchise
And draws chicks with big boobs
Very, very big boobs
She does, and she has
a comic that she works on
Her name is Genevieve, by the way
She works on, and I believe
her
I'm trying to remember who
her other artist is that she works with
I want to say his name is Robert
Forgive me if I got that wrong
Anyways, they have a comic that they work on
Called Islands in the Sky
And it's basically this big boob chick
That goes around stealing people's food
In these different islands in the sky
And putting them in her boobs, apparently
Pretty much, but
As kind of an exclusive thing at Phantom
They're going to be selling
And I don't know how the hell they got these made
But it's just awesome
They're going to be selling boob
Mouse pads
And they have one that's semi-tame
But still, she's got big boobs
But you can actually purchase those
She'll be on Artist Row
I believe booth 300 and 301
They're going to be doing
So, unrealistically proportioned women
Is your thing, then Islands in the Sky
Exactly, so say hi to Genevieve
She's awesome
Tell them OLR sent you!
And recommended the boobies
That's right
Not much has changed
No, but she's cool
These boobs were endorsed by Loki
Yes
How about, um, I don't know
Do we want to do, like, Mailbag?
Do we have Mailbag ready to go? Do we have some emails we can read tonight?
I didn't pull up Mailbag
Can we, well, let's
On a quick story, if you want to pull up Mailbag
Yeah, pull up Mailbag while we do another quick story
So, that game, Super Mario Crossover
Was pretty awesome, the Flash game where you can play
Super Mario Brothers with a bunch of different characters
Well, one of the characters that they talked about
Adding in there that they never really
Got a chance to do that was
Hayabasa, or Hayabusa
And, um, they have now
Added him in there, or at least they're going to very soon
They have a video teasing it
And he has, of course, his
Wall climb moves and he throws ninja stars
And whatnot, so, that's awesome
Can't wait to play that
Version of it
And that's that game you really love to play that has, like, the Contra characters
Oh yeah
Sweet
Alright, Dark Sakura is prepared to dive into the Mailbag
Headfirst, our Mailbag, of course
Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
And she's going to dive in headfirst
And pick out an email to read
Or two, or three, or fifteen, depending on how many people
Three, email us this week
Dark Sakura, go to it, Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
If you would like to participate, please do
Hey guys, Sturlock here
I've tried calling about this a couple of times
That I've been unable to get through
I was surprised that Loki actually brought the closure
Of Nintendo Powerline up as
As I've known this for a while
Excuse me, I wanted to clarify
What the Powerline actually is
It's a line you can call to get walkthroughs and tips for games
Instead of talking to live individuals
The walkthroughs are automated with a menu interface
Which makes it quite easy to find the specific information
You're looking for on a particular game
I have very fond memories of running up
My parents' phone bill back in the day
Although this is only a regular
Long distance call, not even a 900 number
The thing I always liked about the Powerline
Is that they will frequently have music from the games in question
In the background over the person giving the information
That's cute
By the way, I do want to point out
That may be how it is around these days
When I was in high school
You talked to a person
Yeah, go watch The Wizard
There's actually a scene where they call
The game counselor, it's pretty epic
Yeah, I just sat in, you know
And jawed with some guy one day about like
Weird Zelda stuff and
Prototype games one time
Because I was bored, I ran up the phone bill
I get what he's saying though, he's telling us that it's different
Because I think we were reminiscing about that on last week's show
Trying to tell us it's a little bit different now than it was then
Since I have a lot of memories of this line
I've actually been working to record every last game
From it I can
I know I'm probably the only person on the faceless planet
Who actually gives a fuck about this
But it's something I'm passionate about
I see it as part of my childhood in a way
And I don't want to see it go away entirely
It's a neat little artifact of the 90s
And if nothing else, I'm sorry, if nothing else
Sorry for the rambling nature of this message
But this is something I feel quite strongly about
You might actually be able to petition Nintendo
To actually put out DVDs of their
Ivor or something
If you feel strongly about it, go for it
I think that's actually kind of cool
If he's recording stuff
I don't even know if you have this ability at all
But if you've been recording it and you can make MP3s of it
Send us one, I'll play one on the show
I think it'll be kind of fun to listen to
Send us one that you think is really cool
This one is from Doug
Or Dragonboy
Hi Doug Dragonboy
I was wondering if any of you were playing any PS1 games
On the PSPs
I have 23 PS1 games now on my
He wrote no, it's supposed to be now
On my PSP Go
And I love playing them
As many PS1 games are far better than PSP games
That are available
Keep up the great work on the podcast
I'm a loyal listener and your podcast is without a doubt
My favorite Dragonboy
Aw, thank you
PS1 games on the PSP?
Did they ever do Jumping Flash?
Yes they did
What about Jumping Flash if you don't have it?
Um Jammalammy is a great music game
A lot of fun
And of course that's one I play personally
Suikoden, I have the original
And I've played that on the PSP before, that's fun
And Final Fantasy 7
You might as well go, you know what
All the fanboy wank is there for a reason
Final Fantasy 7 is pretty good
Not the best Final Fantasy game they ever made
But pretty darn good
Okay, this last one
From Rababa
Oh, never mind
I think it's sort of a continuation from an old email
The subject line is iPad mini
Maybe iPad nano
I only suggested that on the last OLR episode
Because the leaked iPhone images
Are designed to match the iPad
If it played iPad apps
It would be a way around the contract
With AT&T, the iPad itself
Seems like it would qualify
As a non-phone since it has
No phone capability
Well isn't that what the iPod touches for?
I'm pretty sure the AT&T network
Is used for the iPad for access to the app store
By the way, I have an iPad
And a netbook and the iPad is just better
Let's keep an eye out for an Apple branded
Phone for Verizon
I still want an iPad
I love my netbook though
Now the rumor is Apple is going to team up with Sprint
Let's hope not
Well that's done
Alright, if you really want to do that
Alright
Well thanks for the emails guys
You can go to our website
If you want to send us some more
Couple more news stories
Do we have any more? We done?
We still have the classic game of the week
We'll get to that in a minute
Any more news stories for us, Loki?
Not really, don't have anything
I got one
I'll do a couple quick ones
I have a couple here that I can do
Classic game of the week
Dragon Quest 9, Sentinels of the Starry Skies
July 11th, finally
Ready for US consumption
4.2 million sold in Japan
And it's finally making its way over here
Dragon Quest 9, Sentinels of the Starry Skies
And the Nintendo DS
That's too bad I knew about that weeks ago
I should have mentioned something
I always see this stuff and I'm like
Damn you, Loki
It's like not news for me
The crackdown thing is really interesting
But again, I hope they're wrong
I really do hope they're wrong
Other one, I think this is really interesting
The NPD report
The top selling accessory
On the Microsoft Xbox 360
You know what the best selling accessory is for the 360?
The 1600 point Microsoft
Xbox Live card
Even though you can buy them with the touch of a button
The 1600 point card was the best selling accessory
I'm surprised live subscriptions aren't
And you know why?
Because if you've ever tried to buy a live subscription
With a credit card on
Their service
You're stuck in the stupid auto
Renewing shit
And it sucks
Getting out of it is near impossible
So I tell you
Man, if you
Really are limited on money
Spend the time to go out and buy
One of those memberships
It's a lot better to buy it at the store
And have it dumped down
To silver again
Than having it auto renew all the time
And you can't get rid of it
It's awful
Alright, let's go to the
Classic game of the week
You ready for this Dark Sakura?
May as well be
Alright, every week on the program
Oh my gosh, you know it's free form tonight
Because everything's broken, I don't have the
I don't have the song, where's the song?
There it is
Classic game of the week, every week Dark Sakura
Goes into the vault and picks out a classic game
She says, hey, you kids
Get off my lawn
And go play this game
A classic game that we all
Grew up on
I don't know, what constitutes a classic game?
Um, it's old
What is this week's classic game of the week Dark Sakura?
Keyboard Mania
How appropriate
I know a lot of listeners of the show will be big on this one
Keyboard Mania is your classic game of the week
Want to hear someone butcher a song on Keyboard Mania?
Yeah, let's do that first
This is a song called Pink Rose
That originated in Keyboard Mania
I'm gonna butcher it here a little bit
It's not terrible
It's a B-
And it's not
It's not an easy song to play
No
This person's doing doubles
Let's go to the real song here
Which, by the way, this is one of my favorite songs
Totally in this game
Um
But actually I really like it better in pop music
But, anyway
So, um, Keyboard Mania
Is one of the Bimani games
It has two, um, 24 key keyboards
And, um
The different notes that come down
Correspond
To a different key on the keyboard
Um
And, um
Also there's a- you know how BeatMania
Had, uh, the BM-98 simulator?
Um, there's one called
Doremi
For a Keyboard Mania simulator for me
I get it, doe, a deer, a female deer
Yeah
Anyway, um, so we got out Keyboard Mania
Then, uh, Keyboard Heaven
Which is the Korean version
Of Keyboard Mania
And then Keyboard Mania 2nd Mix
Um, 3rd Mix
Uh, actually, uh, linked
To Drum Mania 4th, Guitar Freaks 5th
Um, and
Drum Mania 5th, Guitar Freaks
6th for certain songs
Cause we used to have- Those were epic days
At Roseville Golf Land. One of the few arcades
Anywhere that had that. There's pictures of all of us
Amazing. Playing
Like, Jamie would do drums, I would do
Keyboard, and, you know, like
Bradley would do guitar
I don't know if Loki was playing with us then, but
I was playing guitar with the other side of the keyboard
Good times. You'd always pick keyboard
Can I play one of my favorite songs in Keyboard Mania?
This kinda sounds like a song
This is not Henry Henry
No, it's not. This is like a song that would be like an act-raiser or something
This is Kyu No Tame No Sonata
This-
This sounds like the overworld music
An act-raiser to me
I think it is
Like, remember when you were managing your people?
This is one of my favorite songs
In Keyboard Mania
We'll play a little bit of this, then I'll do the
Castle Baby song
Yeah, the Akumajou
Uh, medley
Okay, but anyway, um, well
There's actually, um
Three songs, though, that were big
Carryover songs into other Bimani
Games. Um, that was
Frozen Ray
Pink Rose, which we played earlier, and the least
Hundred Seconds, which we should actually
Play that too, Rob
I love Frozen Ray, though
Um, but, uh
Keyboard Mania, um, had two home versions
There was Keyboard Mania, and then
Keyboard Mania 2, which was the second and third
Mix
Um, and it had, uh
You know, basically the arcade-style
Controller. I don't see
Any other way that you could've
Had, like, the full arcade-style
Controller, like, you know, they brought out for
2DX and
DDR and all that
But the other way is that if you had, um
The Windows PC version
You get a Yamaha EZ250i
Keyboard, um, to play it
Which one you've got there?
Oh, yeah
Someone's butchering it a little bit
They're doing pretty good. This is about as good as
I would do, probably
And I love how, on the interface
When it has the little
Background music up, you know, screen up there
From the arcade
The wheel thing always weirded me out, though
Like, what the hell was that? It's your scratch!
Yeah, but it was a little dumb
It was a little dumb
I'm kinda glad that, hopefully, uh
If we get this keyboard thing in, um
Rock Bandit probably won't have that
But, I mean, really, there's not much else to say
About it other than what I've said, you know
It was fairly short-lived
For the Bimani series, and, you know
It's sad
That it didn't do better, you know
It was really difficult, though
This is one of the few songs
Cause, like, when you did that multi-session
There was probably, like, six songs you could play
This is one of them, at least 100 seconds
I love this game
This was my favorite Bimani game
Oh, okay
Because you could also do, um
I think there was also a version of Ride on Time
I'm pretty sure there was
Good stuff
Yeah, but
The other big song, though, of course, was Frozen Ray
Which we got for other versions, too
Um, but yeah
This
I don't remember, though
And I want to say
It didn't have it
Cause keep in mind, I've got
Drum Mania IV, Guitar Freaks V
For home
And Keyboard Mania
And I don't think it had Super Session mode
For the three
No, not on the home version
So, which made me very sad
Because I was all like
Yeah, Super Session, and no
The 2-3 mix came out
Way later, too
And people were pretty convinced
The others were never coming out
I think I had the first time, and then I borrowed yours
For the longest time
We basically, I think for a while, had Communal Bimani
Yeah, pretty much
Because one of us would make sure that we bought a version that no one else had
And then we would play the hell out of it
And then switch it out with somebody else
So we had our Communal Bimani
Going on, and we always made sure we knew
Who we had our damn game
Good times
A good Bimani classic
Find me a Frozen Ray, Rob
You want Frozen Ray?
We'll close out with a little bit of Frozen Ray here
For the Classic Game of the Week
And, uh, let's see
Here we go
Here's from the PS2
Somebody's selecting on the mini list
There we go
Intruder, good job
Jinx
That part's really easy to mess up on
What I really liked about this game
Is that if you, like, could memorize
The note patterns
You could play the song on a real piano
It was the one Bimani game
It was closest to a real simulator
Was the closest thing to the actual
Instrument than anything else
It really was, you know
I'll tell you one thing that had to help me
When learning how to play it
Is that, um, it was easier to play it in the arcade
Than it was at home
Because your keyboard lined up
With the keys and didn't move
Um, but
I would always have to find something
To hold my, um, controller stationary
And put it right the hell in front of my
Of the TV for me to be able to really get it
You know, cause otherwise
It was, it was
Way, it was way too much coordination
I think, I mean, 2DX is definitely
Easier in terms of building your
Hand-eye coordination, and I was never a keyboard player
So
See, when I was like 5 years old
I started taking organ lessons
Yeah, the double decker
Church organ, you know
Completely off topic
I found an accordion at the thrift store today
Good stuff, did you buy it?
I wanted to, it's 85 bucks
I bought a Fendi purse for 6 bucks though
Anyway, um, that's my thing lately
Y'all, by the way, is going to thrift stores
And buying designer stuff
You get good stuff there, no lie, no joke
Anyway, um, so the game of the week
Is keyboard mania
If none of you have played it, you poor deprived people
Go check it out
If you can, good luck
I'm sure the keytar thing will be pretty cool
But it's never going to be as cool as keyboard mania
Keytar freaks?
Uh, keyboard mania, still I think at Milpitas Golfland
At least, I think, last time I was there
Might still be there, I don't know
It's been a little while
Ours has been gone, for ages
Alright, uh, one more segment
That we have to do on this show every week
It's just mandatory for no other reason
And sometimes we have to vent a little bit
GRRR, FUs of the week, Darcy
GRRR, FU to, um, the place which shall not be named
Loki?
Um, FU to the fact that, uh, this weather changing
That's like rain, sun, rain, sun, rain, sun
Is really fucking with my allergies
Is this really giving you a headache?
Uh, yeah, I've been getting headaches the last few days
I just took some time a little bit before I came over here
My throat now is really dry and scratchy
But I think that's from yelling a lot during the show
You know, imitating Michael Patrick really
Takes a toll on you
Oh, the holy name, ah
Alright, uh, my FU goes to myself
Actually, most things in life are pretty good right now
I can't complain
Uh, FU to myself, though, because, like, every time I start
Like a pattern of good eating habits
Like, I guess you could say a diet, if you will
I break it within, like, a week and a half
There's always something that breaks me
And this time it was vacation
You should go off
Oh god, no
Like, I know my limits
Props to you for having that sort of discipline
For a fact, I could do it
By the way, I'm not 100% raw, you know
And I had a beer the other day, and it totally
Oh my god
And it totally made my face break out
So, I have no more beer
I've lost 16 pounds, Rob
For you? Good for you, that's great
Wish I could lose 16 pounds, bitch
Alright
Hey!
You were on your, uh, involuntary toast diet
Yeah, that was bad
That was bad
That was bad. You know things are bad
When you kinda almost wish you would get sick again
So you could be that thin again
Remember when I had pneumonia?
I really don't want that, I really don't
I do not recommend anybody lose weight by pneumonia
It's not fun
Well, no, I got, I lost
Actually, I shouldn't joke, like, that can't kill people
I lost 35 pounds when I had pneumonia
I was sick for three months, they thought I had whooping cough
But it turned out that they were just
Not paying attention
Yay, unnamed healthcare company that Jamie has
I called it the plague
Alright, let's wrap up
We're done, we don't have any other game stories
Right, Loki, you burned through them all, we're good
Yeah, we're done. Dark Sakura, alright
Loki's ready to go
It's hot in here
I thought we'd only be going an hour, we gave you two
What the hell are you thinking, Rob?
Hey, you were here too, lady
It's my house
You're gonna fuck out
Then I am, goodnight
Bye, goodbye
You've been listening
No, we have to do final thoughts, we can't do that yet
Final thoughts, Dark Sakura
Hey, my final thought list, this is my house
If you don't like it, you get the fuck out
Loki, your final thought
Uh, I can't wait to edit some more
Granted, I thought it was gonna be awesome
Hire me
My final thought is I'm stopping getting fast food on the way home
And ruining my diet some more, yay
I did that today because I bought
the wrong kind of bread, you know, I buy this like
you know, whole wheat bread or whatever
And I bought the wrong brand, so it was really
it just had the wrong texture and just
tasted weird, so I'm like
McDonald's
But I've been pretty good, I haven't been going to fast food
except for today
My other final thought, my mom's gonna be
pissed when she finds out who won American Idol
Who did?
Dweiss, or whatever
He sucked last night
I don't want shit any of this season
I know, I barely do, I did like that Crystal Bowers socks
I thought she was good because somebody showed me her
And apparently Alanis came out to duet with her tonight
Okay, I have to see
That I have to see
Doesn't go with the dreads, right?
He sucked last night
That was the chick with the dreads, right?
She's cool
No, she lost, just like Adam and I lost last year
You know what, I did actually
My mom's gonna be pissed, you know what?
You wanna call my mom and tell her?
About the week, Rob
I have to tell you, I did
actually buy
some of the stuff off of Alison Irajeda's album
Okay, clearly the game
part of the show is over
So, if you were here for the video games
then goodnight
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio
is an Orange Lounge
production
To join us for a live show, visit
www.allgames.com
No, I talked over to this gamer
Blah, blah, blah
All games, listen to them, they rule
Yes, they do
Shh, no they don't
But they do have my competitor
No, we won't
We'll see you in two weeks
Let's go on
She's watching it right now, too
Your mom's so funny
Oh, don't ruin it for her
Oh, then we're calling right now
Hello
Hi mom
Who is this?
It's Rob, your kid
I already know who won
Damn it
I was calling
Why are you laughing?
We're on the radio right now
and I was calling because I read it on the internet
and I wanted to spoil it for you
I got on the internet at
7 o'clock, I'm not stupid
She was Rob
This is weird, my mother
Now admit it, mom
a year ago, you made me
go online and look it up
You didn't know how to do this
Yeah, but I don't need your help anymore
Is this why you decided to
Did you hear that?
You got served
I'm not on the radio, am I?
Yeah, you are, it's okay
You don't mind, do you?
My mom said that I had to text her
and warn her before we call
Mom, this is the part after the credits
so no one's listening, it's cool
Are you watching the finale anyway?
I didn't watch the first half
I said I'm not gonna watch it
because I'm too mad
I couldn't stand it, so I turned it on
Now, did you or did you not tell me last year
First off, who should have won last year?
Adam
I know, right?
And why should Adam have won last year?
Because he was by far the best
And what made him the best?
He just was, he was more of a showman
He was the best
That's why that Chris guy is selling
his stuff on QVC
and Adam's touring
I did like Alison
Explain why you...
Yes, I like Alison too
and she's doing okay because I saw her on
I bought her album
It's actually really good
Hold on, you guys are talking last year's news
I wanna talk this year again
I'm still reeling over David Cook, pardon me
Well, okay, last night
Lee stunk
His first single's gonna be a beautiful day
and it was awful
It was terrible
The one that she did was really good
and I was hoping that would come out on
a CD because I'd like to buy it
I think maybe she's gonna be more
Don't you think the runner-ups
often fare better unless you're the beatboxing guy?
In the last few years
they have, and the reason they have
is because, and I've told you this before
it becomes a popularity contest
in the end and the little girls
all vote for the cute guys
Except for David Cook because I thought
David Cook did not have nearly the talent
that David Cook had
Well, I
And David Cook is
I think it wasn't so much that he didn't have
the talent that he was really young
That was my mother respectfully disagreeing with you
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
I know the tone
I honestly, personally
I think that David Cook had better stage presence
but that's me
Well, he probably did, but he was older
and more mature
same way as this year with Aaron
cause I thought Aaron was really a good singer
but he was only 17
and he didn't have the
you know, he didn't have the charisma and stuff
I had him in my third place spot
I was picking, well originally when we had
cause we had a work pool for this
I had Crystal, Casey, and Aaron
cause Lee, at the time, I mean
it was like a good, you know
before, I think it was at the top ten
Well he didn't start out to be one of the better ones
he started out, really
he just sounded like
a bunch of mainstream artists now
Okay, I have to
I like Big Mike too
I have to ask you this, because I just
you know, you said last year, when Adam lost last year
you said, and I quote,
I am never watching that show again
because the person that should win never does
and yet, you watched this year
No, they used to, but
lately it hasn't been that way
Well, did Reuben deserve to beat Clay?
No, Clay deserved it by far
Okay, actually if
you don't mind me asking, because
I'm of two minds about this too
Did you prefer Carrie Underwood
or Bo Bice?
Oh, I preferred Carrie Underwood
Most of the time I've been for the person that's won
there's been a few times
so that I thought the second place one should've won
See, I'm from Alabama
so Bo Bice automatically got my vote
And you're biased, that's fine
And he sang with Lynyrd Skynyrd, how could you go wrong with that?
Okay, I have to ask my mother though
Are you gonna make the threat that you're not watching next year?
I don't think
with Simon gone, I don't think it's gonna be
nearly as popular
Are divas leaving?
Who do you think should replace Simon?
I don't think there's anybody
that can replace him
It's just like when they
took Paula off, the show lost something
What are the names they're throwing around?
Elton John, could Elton John replace Simon?
No
You know who I want to replace Simon?
Graham Norton
Who?
Graham Norton, he's a talk show host
He's funny
What about Perez Hilton?
Well some people have suggested
Howard Stern too
He wants to do it
Howard Stern
it's like a big joke gone out of control
and Perez Hilton is just a bitch
And it would turn into a
dirty show if Howard Stern got on
What else
was I gonna say?
The X Factor, Simon's new
show that Paula is rumored to be a judge
Suddenly it's the reality TV podcast
No, no, she got a dance show
She's gonna do a dance show
Where have you been? Are you into rock or something?
Sorry, I'm doing a show on video games
It makes sense for me
I'm a games analyst, did you hear?
No
How'd you get to be a games analyst?
I told Robbie I was
Yeah, Jamie told me I was
In other words
you're a games analyst
in your own mind
That's not what my business card says
but sure
I'm an authority on Idol in my
own mind too
Well then she's the official
Rob's mom, the official
American Idol
analyst for Orange Lounge Radio
I just used my
female powers of always being right to make
Rob an analyst
Alright, X Factor
Yes or no? Are you gonna watch it?
Probably because I think it will be a much better show
because it won't be
relying on the public
to pick the winner
Ok, one more then I promise I'm wrapping this up
That little 11 year old kid that Ellen DeGeneres
I know you watch her show everyday, right?
Absolutely great
He's got that Bieber kid beat to it
He's so much better
This is why I love my mother
His name is
Chance
His first name is Grayson
Grayson Chance
He's absolutely great
Did you watch Glee last night?
They did Gaga
Where were you?
I have to ask my mother
this
About this whole thing
Rob I adore your mom
I know, she's pretty cool
Now I forgot what I was gonna ask
Glee
Grayson Chance and the
Bieber
Since you're hooked up to the internet now
You know how to use Google?
Yeah, absolutely
I want you to Google this website
Lesbians that look like Justin Bieber
There's
probably a lot of them with that haircut he's got
There is
There's a whole blog dedicated
to lesbians that look like Justin Bieber
You should see Rob right now, he's all red in the face
This is my mother
My mom likes Lady Gaga
Do you like Lady Gaga?
Yeah
She didn't use to
She thought Lady Gaga was disgusting
But then when I said Lady Gaga is cool
My mom came around
I'm still not coming around
I never said she was disgusting, I never really paid that much attention
You said when she did that performance
When she set the piano on fire
Whiskey bottles and stuff
You were like, oh no
You were mad because Adam Lambert
Got in trouble over kissing a guy
And everybody else
had grabbed their crotch
And everything, right?
And worse things were done by other people
And they didn't pay attention to it, that's what made me mad
That's what he said himself
He's like, well if all these other people can get away with it
Why shouldn't I be able to?
Exactly, on the same show
I can't remember, was it Janet Jackson?
I don't remember, somebody
Did something worse
Alright
They didn't even say anything
But I think he's getting past that now
And I'm glad
Because I don't think people
Um
You know, they're not being that judgemental
About him anymore
We have to wrap up this extremely random
Epilogue that's had nothing to do with
Video games whatsoever, is there any video games you're excited
There's an American Idol video game
Are there any video games you're excited about, mom?
I don't do video games
Are you going to play Farmville?
I absolutely know nothing about video games
You don't know Farmville?
Is that the one that
My friend was playing on the internet
Where you own a farm and you try to make money
She knows Farmville
There you go, see, she's a bigger gamer
Well she was playing that on the internet, she got hooked on it
Alright
You officially know more about the internet
Than my grandmother does
Congratulations
I don't know, I don't know a lot
She's come a long way in a year
No, I remember
I don't want to give out my mom's email on the show
But it's really funny
Absolutely not
I'm not, but it's really funny
Like if you know her email, it's really funny
But I actually remember a couple years ago
Actually we gave you a call a few years ago
And tried to ask you about something and you didn't
Know because it was online
My mom's on the internet
My grandmother's on the internet now
My dad is on Facebook
I think that the apocalypse is happening
Well I won't do Facebook
Why do you not want to go on Facebook?
Because I don't want to put my face on
There for a day, see
Alright
Mom, we gotta wrap up and put the nail in the coffin
At the show, but thanks for being a good sport
It was good talking to you again
Okay, I hope the right person runs next year
Alright, bye
I love you
Oh, she's hung up on me
I love you too
She's hung up on me
Wicked woman
Okay, so Rob, next show that we do, we're calling my mother
We have to call her early though
Alright, text her and get her to her age
Alright, we really are wrapping up and it really is a night
Goodnight everybody, thanks for tuning in
Thank you for supporting our show
If you like the show, I forgot to say this earlier
Please post a nice review about us on iTunes and all that stuff
Tell a friend or two about the show
Help us spread the word, blah blah blah
The end, here's the ending theme, one more time to take us out
Goodnight
Thanks for listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production
To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com
Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific Time
The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio
Do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio
Or allgames.com
But we're probably right anyway
See you next week!