[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, August 5th, 2012, another MMO is set to go free to play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone decides to take Zynga to court over an allegedly copied game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And has the Wii U detailed launch lineup been revealed?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is Orange Lounge Radio with this episode number 468 for August the 5th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_14]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you with my co-hosts over the next few hours to talk about video games and gaming culture and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here they are.
[SPEAKER_14]: Say hello to the one and only Dark Sakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_14]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of in pain.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's Bank of America, but I'm not going to say anything else.
[SPEAKER_14]: But maybe a silver lining to it all, at least I hope.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're all pulling for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Something will come up.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you listen to Bobby Blackwolf's show, let me just plug real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I could work for Zynga and get sued.
[SPEAKER_14]: Listen to us live at the Voice of Geeks Network and participate at live.vognetwork.com where we do tape Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_14]: And as we learned on Bobby Blackwolf tonight, you never know who might recruit you.
[SPEAKER_14]: So tune into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think I could work for evil.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to evil tech master Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could if they pay well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care what they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: We slaughter kittens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do I hear $100 for your soul?
$100, $100, $200.
[SPEAKER_14]: How you doing, TechmasterLoki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they'd be virtual kittens, but it's not real kittens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's new?
[SPEAKER_02]: Doing fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_14]: What was this project thingy?
[SPEAKER_14]: You were showing me pictures of a project thingy you've been working on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it was just brief.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to make something for Josh's birthday party because he had a Mario-themed birthday party, but...
[SPEAKER_14]: Is this to match his Mario-themed bedroom and so forth?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's just this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because last year was pork-themed, so... We decided that... I love that you threw a baby a pork-themed wedding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wedding?
[SPEAKER_14]: Birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gee, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: One step at a time, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe later on down the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be down.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, he had a Mario birthday party.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you made like a little paper mache, or no, that was more like a paper craft.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a paper craft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paper craft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Koopa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like origami or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's pretty much full size.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's over two feet tall.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the thing is I didn't finish it because I neglected to look at the paper craft model that closely.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently the way they have things connect together are impossible in reality because they just kind of phase through each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that might work in a computer game, but it's not going to work when you have to glue stuff to other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, okay, I have to cut a hole here, I guess, in order to get this to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I managed to get two of the pieces together before the show, like his leg in the shoe.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to take a long time.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're the one that wanted to start arts and crafts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, but it's pretty much done.
[SPEAKER_14]: The pictures look good.
[SPEAKER_14]: We should try to get those up at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: But anyhow, let's also introduce, we have a special guest tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, it's a big night at the Voice of Geeks Network, and I'll explain why in just a little bit, but a big night made bigger by the return of a favorite guest to OLR.
[SPEAKER_14]: He hasn't been here in some time.
[SPEAKER_14]: The last time I remember you being here was the Marathon show, maybe one show after that, but you definitely haven't been here since the VOG switchover and all that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Say hello to Arcadian42 is back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's favorite?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, probably last year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So welcome back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it's earlier this year, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it was in the old place.
[SPEAKER_14]: So welcome to the smaller condensed studio at Casa de Rob and Alan.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you fit a little bit better here with the open environment rather than a little room.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Sometimes it works pretty good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like last week when we had the whole PlayStation Home thing going on, you know, it was going on on the TV over there.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's like, you know, we got we got a nice open space.
[SPEAKER_14]: And once in a while, a cat might come through and try to lick your feet.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not likely.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Marco might walk by, stick his tail in the air and then run off.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not bloody likely.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, if folks haven't heard you on the show before, let's try to tell the listeners a little bit about what you're all about.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're a huge Sega fan.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember that about you, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played a lot of Sega games when I was growing up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had Genesis and Saturn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, I have a bunch of Japanese Saturn games, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you also do a lot of traveling, like following you on Facebook and everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: You love to go on the, or at least it seems like, reading your Facebook, you love to go on these kind of like just adventures.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, I'm going to get in the car and drive to Yellowstone.
[SPEAKER_14]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've done a big road trip the last two or three years.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't done too many small road trips other than going to Yosemite a bunch just for hiking.
[SPEAKER_14]: You climbed Half Dome this year, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did that four years ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you didn't get killed, which is a thing that unfortunately has a bit of a reputation for these days.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you only get killed if you're stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Allegedly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe they should change it to Half Darwin.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there's only been one person who's died on a dry day.
[SPEAKER_10]: They might have had a little bit to drink.
[SPEAKER_10]: Most everything at the time was when it was stormy or wet or there was a thunderstorm or something around.
[SPEAKER_10]: Someone got close like two months ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: We almost fell off the side.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know you like to kind of sometimes go to expos and conventions and things too because you're kind of like the norm of these things.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, you know, remember Cheers?
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's kind of like, you know, I'll be at California Extreme and then all of a sudden, oh, Bradley's through the door.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bradley is here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you go to California Extreme this year?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just knew you did.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I was so...
[SPEAKER_14]: I was irritated I couldn't go.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, granted, you know, I have to pick my priorities.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do I want to do screening movie thingies or do I want to do California Extreme?
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you run into Dan?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I ran into him once.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was playing Kung Fu Master and he stopped by and said hi.
[SPEAKER_14]: So how was it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Since we couldn't review it, none of us went.
[SPEAKER_14]: How was California Extreme this year?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much similar as usual.
[SPEAKER_10]: A bunch of games here and there and everywhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can't remember if there's anything super special there.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a bunch of new pinballs, but I didn't get to play them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if they're new, but at least newer ones.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did they have the Tron pinball?
[SPEAKER_14]: I have yet to play that still.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan's friend owns one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to visit Dan's friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the special editions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can't remember if I saw one or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: It might have been there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just didn't get a chance to play it.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's just, yeah, it's just all these arcade owners, private owners mostly that own old arcade games and they just convene on a convention center or a hotel ballroom and it's just all these games you pay 40, 50 bucks and it's just free to play the whole weekend, all these old games.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's really an emphasis on classic games.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I've got to play so much stuff that you just don't get to play anywhere anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like I played Journey the last time I was there and some pinball games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Once in a while they have a couple new things here and there, but it's mostly about classic.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I've got to say, Neil, a friend of mine, he sent me a video from California Extreme.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess, like, I don't know what it was.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was one of those, like, animatronic bands they had.
[SPEAKER_14]: He sent me a very scary video of the animatronic band singing Total Eclipse of the Heart or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was like, what is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I went by there just, like, once.
[SPEAKER_10]: I kind of just passed by and went, saw it for, like, 10 seconds and went on to something else.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: As awesome as what it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: of course you guys are here too the always present fourth guest on our show or I guess fifth tonight because we do have Arcadian 42 here tonight join us live participate with the show live at VOG Network the Voice Geeks Network live.vognetwork.com is where you can join our chat room and occasionally
[SPEAKER_14]: We read comments from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yeah, DDRDollarBill is like, what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Robotron?
[SPEAKER_14]: What's Robotron?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, Robotron.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they do have it on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was one of the first Xbox Live Arcade titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Robotron was a rejected 2DX character, just saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: Little inside joke there for the music game fans.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played it in band.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you really?
[SPEAKER_05]: London 2012!
[SPEAKER_05]: That one in the, was it 92 theme?
[SPEAKER_05]: Play that too.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Olympic event on a 12-hour tape delay, live from London.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just change the AM to PM.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyhow, I don't actually really want to talk about the Olympics itself, but I want to talk about, because you know, you can probably go to any other website on the internet and read something about Michael Phelps.
[SPEAKER_14]: But what I really want to talk about is I want to talk about a story that's circulating the internet.
[SPEAKER_14]: And when I'm talking circulating the internet, I don't mean just like on the video game blogs.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean this is on CNN.com in their tech section right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: So on CNN, they're running a story right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Should pro gamers be considered athletes?
[SPEAKER_14]: And I think that's a good question I want to ask you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, you're starting off with a bang.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, why not?
[SPEAKER_14]: Why should pro gamers not be considered athletes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's a video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't really require any physical prowess to be good at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe some good hand-eye coordination, but the Olympics are traditionally a test of physical skill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe DDR?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but it should be something purely physical.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, let me read some of the quotes from this article before I get too much more feedback.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I definitely want your feedback in our chat room as well, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the article talks about StarCraft II and one of the big players in South Korea, Marine King.
[SPEAKER_14]: And he got kind of a bit of a reputation because he practiced 20 hours a day sometimes.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that got him called a gaming addict.
[SPEAKER_14]: but according to and CNN basically compiled some comments and according to one commenter on the CNN website one person said would you claim that Phelps is addicted to swimming so why did they want to say this guy was addicted to gaming because he trained 20 hours a week would you say that Michael Phelps is addicted to swimming no he's addicted to pot
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyone who can smoke weed and then win 21 gold medals, you win.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not saying that's bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Didn't slow him down any.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not that I personally endorse it, but it is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: It does set that whole argument back a little bit, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_14]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some folks say Marine King represents dedication, skill, perseverance.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's one of the best in the world.
[SPEAKER_14]: The skill required to be a pro gamer.
[SPEAKER_14]: The original article that the folks had commented on, it didn't distinguish the difference between game addiction and professional gaming or even gaming as a hobby.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do not believe the article shows the amount of skill needed to be one of the best in the world or how truly big professional gaming has become.
[SPEAKER_14]: on physicality being an important part of athletics.
[SPEAKER_14]: Again, these comments from CNN.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wouldn't call them athletes.
[SPEAKER_14]: The one common denominator with all Olympians is the physicality involved.
[SPEAKER_14]: Even the word athlete refers to physical activity.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have no issues with video gaming, but the Olympics just seems to be the wrong venue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what venue that the Olympics needs?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck this video game playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about fucking laser tag.
[SPEAKER_02]: Laser tag!
[SPEAKER_02]: That is physical.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is what we need.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then they could just do paintball.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be fine with paintball.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd settle for paintball.
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as they have to be active.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I want some crazy Hunger Games-ish thing where if they don't move, then they explode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that I'm not working, I think I should be a professional paintballer.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about that for a career change, Rob?
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Now's the time to try new things.
[SPEAKER_14]: Find what you really love.
[SPEAKER_14]: I sure do love shooting people.
[SPEAKER_14]: You could design guns.
[SPEAKER_14]: You like design and you like guns.
[SPEAKER_14]: You should design guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to design a new gun.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_14]: Should video games, StarCraft II be an Olympic sport?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they don't do anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, not saying they don't physically do anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving a mouse is not exercise or is not athletic in any way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That does not belong.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody in chat just said a comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cyber Olympics or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we're going to create something that sort of way, then yeah, sure, why not.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody in chat just said a comment.
[SPEAKER_14]: I agree with 100%.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bradley, I'll check in with you.
[SPEAKER_14]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_14]: Do video games deserve to be in the Olympics or no?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not only athletic or anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: They could do a spectator.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not a spectator, but what do you call that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: Exhibition.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exhibition sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because they did something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can do exhibitions.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not that type of exhibition.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they did like, I know they were talking about the last time that London had Olympics, they had like an Olympic poetry competition.
[SPEAKER_14]: Olympic poetry?
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is pole dancing an Olympic sport?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because that's physical.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm liking this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, you know what used to be an Olympic sport?
[SPEAKER_05]: Solo synchronized swimming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because strippers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, should pole dancing be an elite sport?
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely, and you know why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's not necessarily for strippers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I understand that that is what they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, it's basically like the gymnastics routines and stuff that they do, but just on a pole.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll include it in gymnastics.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it does require physical strength, and there's a bit of... The ability to spread your legs.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: As someone who took a pole dancing class, it is not just about spreading your legs, all right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I think it should be included under gymnastics.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should be under there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because if you can have this stupid gymnastics event where you're prancing around with giant ribbons, then I should be able to, you know... They should have somebody that's, you know, prancing around on a pole.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, if... Look...
[SPEAKER_14]: There's like a ball dance or something where the chicks come out and play with balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ribbons.
[SPEAKER_14]: Balls and ribbons.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have one at the ball too.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like a rhythm ball.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like Zumba.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bradley, pole dancing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes or no in the Olympics?
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder how they're going to go judging on that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: The lady from Russia had the most erect nipples.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, to get it out of the gutter here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free running would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of the X Games stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you put a motorcycle in there and you can't really go wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we just combine the Olympics and the X Games together, maybe that would be kind of like a gymnastics event for the X Games would be like strippers.
[SPEAKER_14]: The problem is pole dancing has that stigma attached to it and it's not classy enough for the Olympics.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why it would not, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure pole dancing can be done very classily.
[SPEAKER_05]: Classily.
[SPEAKER_05]: Classic.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's a good word?
[SPEAKER_05]: It can be done with class.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not trashy.
[SPEAKER_05]: With class.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of it class.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not a stripper, I'm a dancer If you're dancing at Cheetah, that is not dancing TigerClaw in the chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says Would love to see games like Super Street Fighter 4 or Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom at the Olympics Those fighting games are super competitive So some disagree with what we're saying Now here's what I agree with This was the statement I agree with 110% which is why the video games aren't going to be in the Olympics Fifth dream
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they can do chess boxing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the way I play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bitch table!
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to be on the chess team.
[SPEAKER_15]: Table flipping emoticon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it could be chess boxing.
[SPEAKER_10]: That actually is something that people actually do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, is that like beatboxing?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's something they like to play some chess and then they box and then go back and do some more chess.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's battle chess.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like that biathlon or...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the biathlon for... I don't even know what that would be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chess and boxing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sophisticated and not sophisticated gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Blackwolf says full contact chess.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actdeft says extreme chess.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm gonna take that time clock and shove it up your ass.
[SPEAKER_14]: What about, what about, um... There was an old Saturday Night Live sketch from, like, the 70s with the guy coaching the chess team, and it was all, Ponderick 4!
[SPEAKER_14]: Ponderick 4!
[SPEAKER_14]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, like, really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about, like, uh... I don't know, um... Some sort of, like, CGing or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, let's just start taking stuff from, like, American Gladiators or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, where we have, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot of, you know, they have, you know Fucking Siren and Zap and, you know, Nitro Those were my Olympians back in the day Okay Here we go Here we go The Olympics, I think, should stay to mostly traditional sports Curling should not be an Olympic sport, sorry
[SPEAKER_05]: However... Get out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Curling is like the only thing I'll watch.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like professional cleaning as an Olympic sport.
[SPEAKER_14]: My mother would love curling.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is exactly what she does.
[SPEAKER_14]: The puck travels down and you follow in front of it with a broom.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like air hockey on the large scale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't we have Olympic air hockey?
[SPEAKER_05]: That I would vote for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Olympic air hockey.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have ping pong
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, but I think that, you know, going back to stuff like the X Games and all the alternative sport things, I think they need to stay in their own kind of venue for the people who are more willing to watch that sort of activity and make pole dancing part of the gymnastic section.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about water skiing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't they have like water skiing or something like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't know what you could do with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have like rowing.
[SPEAKER_14]: There are events on the water.
[SPEAKER_05]: There used to be, I think, water ski jumps back in... Are you saying water sports is an Olympic competition?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think back in the day, but like I said, tug-of-war used to be an Olympic sport.
[SPEAKER_05]: Solo synchronized swimming, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Solo synchronized swimming was an Olympic sport.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you going to synchronize to?
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's synchronizing to the music, but you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree with Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything goes rhythm gymnastics.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, you have all the diving competitions, but they dive into a ball bin, you know, like a giant ball bin.
[SPEAKER_14]: You just want to put on the pomp and circumstance gown and get up there in front of everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: May the odds be ever in your favor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not even.
[SPEAKER_14]: You want to be the Queen of England of these games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to be the goddamn queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: She looks like she has diarrhea the whole time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the goddamn chairman of the Iron Chef in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck this American Iron Chef.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone needs to give old Liz a suppository.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, look.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's her heart for that James Bond thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what else used to be a sport?
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Distance diving.
[SPEAKER_05]: As in who could dive the longest distance before having to come up for Eric's...
[SPEAKER_14]: I like Stan in chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: 100 meter streaking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody in London participated in that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Takashi's Castle and Ninja Warrior.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are two perfectly acceptable events in my guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Look, look.
[SPEAKER_14]: We got to move on from this topic and actually get to video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do want to say, I love the comment, and I'm sorry I forgot who said it because it scrolled on by long ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: What about a separate competition for video games?
[SPEAKER_14]: Where is the true video game Olympics?
[SPEAKER_14]: Could we ever see a video game Olympics in our day?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or, I mean, is it kind of already here with eSports?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the MLG garbage.
[SPEAKER_14]: The views and opinions expressed on this program do not necessarily reflect those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I just don't like the whole MLG as like a
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm cool with MLG.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't have a beef with them.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want something with the pomp and circumstance of the Olympics.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do want Queen Elizabeth out there going, you know, scowling at everything and judging other countries.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want that for video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've decided that this country is the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck all of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck off.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, even if she won't show up, get...
[SPEAKER_14]: Who are the two that just got married?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm such an ignorant American right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: What, Kate and... Kate and William.
[SPEAKER_14]: Get Kate and William out there, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, because video games are a younger generation.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how I always remember them?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the little boy and witches, his mice were Kate and William.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or were they William and Mary?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they were Kate and... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're talking about disc wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't we have disc wars?
[SPEAKER_05]: Disc golf should be an official sport.
[SPEAKER_14]: You smoke a lot of pot and then try to hit the ball.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tigerclaw in our chatroom says they have the world cyber games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I have to quote Actdeft here because I have to do the voice from the queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bunch of wankers!
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_14]: We gotta move on.
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't even done announcements.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have a huge show coming up after Orange Monterey.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should do the whole show in a rotten accent.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, you shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's my queen voice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somewhere, Peker Uno and Syl and other British listeners of this program are like crying at our accents.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because I sound like What's-His-Face from Monty Python when I do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Every time you talk in a British accent, God throws a crumpet at a kitten.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it was my cat, she wouldn't move.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: She'd be like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_14]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's talk about our gaming weeks and the video games we've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll start with you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: What have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing lots of Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played a crap ton of Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: And being laid off, I had Pity Day, where I did nothing but look at Garrus fan art, read bad fan fiction, read some good fan fiction, played more Mass Effect, and we did a raid in WoW.
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually raided.
[SPEAKER_05]: It happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I had to go to bed early because of work that I don't have anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it, I could have finished the raid.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the thing that sucks most in retrospect.
[SPEAKER_14]: I could have finished that damn raid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could have stayed for the whole damn thing, but no.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Dan and I decided to watch some gameplay throughs on some stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we've got the CDX hooked up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so tempted to play through...
[SPEAKER_05]: and put in Robo Alust and play through that again because it's one of my favorite shooters.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We did watch several playthroughs of full motion video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: We watched Dragon's Lair and Space Ace all the way through.
[SPEAKER_14]: Space Ace, Did You Know, Star Fox, R-Wing
[SPEAKER_05]: Pizza
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's go to Bradley.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll let our guests go next.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bradley, what kind of stuff have you been playing in the past week or so?
[SPEAKER_10]: The main thing I've been playing is Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been sitting up on my shelf for a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I said, I want to go play that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's one of two series I get the most emails about, why aren't you playing this series?
[SPEAKER_14]: And the other is Borderlands, which I finally did start playing.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I've got to get into that at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some people kind of get bored with it, at least the first one, just because there's a lot of things you have to do several times, like you have to climb all these towers to get to the top.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of things are kind of repetitive, but I'm fine with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of the big stuff, the acting is pretty good, and actually getting up above the city and looking down is kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like your Batman?
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Usually there's like a bunch of people there and you have to wait for them to get to a secluded area but I killed all the guards that were there and then just once you activate that thing you just beat them up right where you started so it makes that little thing a little bit easier to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now are you playing these games to kind of set up for the third one that's coming out that's getting a lot of hype?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not really worried about that at the moment just because I don't have loads of time to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might probably get to two sometime, but just something I wanted to clear for my backlog because I have hundreds of games on the backlog.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another game played was
[SPEAKER_10]: Tetris Axis, which is more Tetris, and various different Tetris modes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just the bad thing about it is that they don't let you use the circle pad to control.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also played Mole Mania, just the first level of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a classic sort of game that's on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a classic hard puzzle game sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just played the first part of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: and also the other game I got to play was Rhythm Thief, which is a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So far I've gone through the first two chapters and all the rhythm games so far have been distinct.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played the demo of that on 3DS and I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Everything seemed to be kind of different.
[SPEAKER_14]: I liked that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It kind of was a throwback a little bit to me to Space Channel 5.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kind of like that zaniness off the wall uniqueness, but kind of like a different play style, which was cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been good so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: The one silly thing about it is that the dog that follows them around is called Fondue.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they have all these opportunities to make cheese jokes, and they do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's definitely an old school Sega title right there, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also I've played a little bit of Spelunky.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been playing that the past few weeks and still haven't beaten the game and I've died about 800 times.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's one of those games that I get really frustrated at at certain times.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just dying left and right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, fuck you, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I heard the soundtrack's really good to that because I saw something about the soundtrack is out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a pay what you want thing, but as long as you pay at least $7.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I've heard that the XBLA version is different from the original, like the PC version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think people might like the PC version.
[SPEAKER_10]: That might be from the PC version.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think people like the PC version better.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I haven't heard the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't tried that one yet, though, on the PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, if that's it, before I go to Loki, because Loki I know has a big week we got to get into, I'm going to go next because mine's actually really quick.
[SPEAKER_14]: As far as new games go, there's really only one new game I got to try this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Played a lot of the same old stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I played World of Warcraft, played some Mass Effect multiplayer and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: One new game I tried over the weekend because it's having a free weekend is a new MMO called The Secret World.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's an MMO, obviously, and it's set a little more in the modern-day world.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's more of a modern-day MMO with the whole zombie element to it and cyberpunk kind of a twist on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's one of the first MMOs I've played in a very long time where I didn't sit there going, oh, this is a lot like WoW, or oh, I'm looking for the WoW influence, or oh, I see that they took this from WoW.
[SPEAKER_14]: And keep in mind, I usually kind of have that eye because I have been playing World of Warcraft for so long and, you know, have the podcast and everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's how I approach a lot of games, or MMOs.
[SPEAKER_14]: But Secret World really didn't remind me of WoW at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: The combat was really fast-paced, which, you know, another friend of mine was playing it and it kind of irritated him, but I kind of liked the combat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I also liked that there was no leveling.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I mean, that was kind of fun to play, and the different environment leads way to a different set of quests and all that, and a different type of story, and yeah, I gotta say, I was feeling it, but I'm gonna tell you what I'm not feeling.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the price.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because if I wanna play Beyond this weekend, I'm gonna have to pay $50 for the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Which I understand, yes, World of Warcraft sells those mounts and those pets I've never bought one that wasn't for charity But those things also don't give you an edge in the game And I was a little put off by that And honestly, I think it's happening to every other MMO As we're going to get into later this week I think it's just a matter of time before Secret World goes free to play Or gets a price reduction So you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just going to wait until then
[SPEAKER_14]: I did enjoy what I played of it, but if it's going to go the way of every other MMO, sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know that that might give me some stink eye from developers and things like that, but I didn't love it enough to just jump on board and support it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's where I was with it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And SSJ100Matt in chat says, yeah, but Rob, didn't Blizzard sell useless mounts?
[SPEAKER_14]: Correct, they do.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I gotta admit, I don't like that they do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't buy those mounts.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think $25 or whatever they charge for a mount, I think it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, once in a while Blizzard will put out a $10 pet where it all goes to charity or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a lot different.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those I have bought, but I've never bought a mount for the $25 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just think that's a little silly.
[SPEAKER_14]: and I also think they charge way too much for the server transfers and WoW has other pricing issues too.
[SPEAKER_14]: The cost to enter the game right now between buying the Battle Chest, Wrath of the Lich King, Cataclysm and soon Pandaria, it's ridiculous and that's why WoW is losing subscribers but I'll get into that a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: for now that's it for my gaming week Loki, Loki, Loki, Loki alright, so I read Twitter and I listen to this show so I know you took the day off work on Wednesday, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: so you could stay up Tuesday night
[SPEAKER_14]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: So immediately I was greeted with, you know, the next page and they're talking about how, you know, how, you know, the third gate contest and basically, you know, here it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Ready Player One Easter Egg Hunt, the third gate.
[SPEAKER_02]: To complete the third challenge in the RP1 Easter Egg Contest, you must, and this is where I was like, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You must set a new world record high score on one of the following classic video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Robotron 2084, Joust, Black Tiger, and Tempest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, since then, they've added Joust on the Atari 2600 and Pac-Man, but all the rest are arcade versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and then of course it goes into a little bit detail what you need to do basically this is tied in with Twin Galaxies you have to follow their submission rules and stuff and I haven't really played around with Twin Galaxies that much because I kind of roll my eyes every time I hear about Twin Galaxies but their submissions are ridiculous basically you have to so here's the challenge number one
[SPEAKER_02]: Pick a game that you're going to somehow get the world record to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, even before that, find an arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, find an arcade that has classic games because classic games don't bring in money to arcades anymore so they don't have them anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number three, find an arcade with a classic game that happens to be nearby because there's not a lot of them that's also willing to allow you to stay there for long hours and open up their arcade machine and film the inside of their arcade machine as well as you playing the game without any sort of interruptions from little kids or something jumping in the way, knocking over your camera equipment and all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's even before...
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just... Here's my disappointment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that, you know, he's basically saying, okay, well, this is the type of competition stuff that was in Ready Player One The Vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, let's back up for a second.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, the first gate was an Atari 2600 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: An original Atari 2600 game they made specifically for this gate.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was cool, because it tied in with the game, and it was challenging, but it wasn't like, oh, my God, this is impossible to beat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, and granted, these are all supposed to be increasing in challenge each time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two was not a challenge at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a Facebook game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only challenge was my patience in playing a Facebook game that was basically pay to win.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to point something out, though, between that first and second gate.
[SPEAKER_14]: That first gate, you have the classic.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have the old.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have the history of video games right there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, granted, it's not like Space War or something like that, but for all practical purposes, Atari 2600 is about as far back as most our gaming memories go.
[SPEAKER_14]: and then for the second gate you had the most modern thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, love it or hate it, Facebook is gaming right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only reason that it was tied in with it because it was Richard Garriott, the guy that was behind Ultima, a pretty classic series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, I would have thought the Ultima MMO that they're beta testing or something like that would have been better fit for this, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook game where you collect vintage stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine, but it was annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't difficult though.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was absolutely no skill involved in it at all other than click, click, click.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, crap, I ran out of energy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotta wait for more energy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click, click, click.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I don't want to wait anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to pay for more energy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's really the only skill that was involved there.
[SPEAKER_02]: To, oh, hey, by the way, you got to set a fucking world record.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's a little like, woof.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, what the hell kind of a difficulty curve is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, to be fair, you know, like I said, this sort of kind of ties in with, you know, the book and, you know, how, well, you know, the main character in the book, he played a perfect game of Pac-Man and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, oh, cool, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: but you have to understand in the book these people were this guy leaves his fortune of billions of dollars billions of dollars and these people have to find these Easter eggs to get this vast amount of fortune so they become experts in everything 80s including playing arcade games
[SPEAKER_02]: All of their free time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're talking people just playing games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the reason that that main character goes in the first place to an arcade museum and plays that Pac-Man machine is because he likes playing Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not because, oh shit, I gotta play this Pac-Man machine perfectly so I can get this whatever to open another gate.
[SPEAKER_02]: It didn't even have anything to do with the other gate.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's just because he enjoys playing these games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, forcing people to play these arcade games and get world record, you're not targeting your audience of people that enjoy 80s stuff and read your book and like the book.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're targeting people that play arcade games hardcore, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let me... Since it's only a three-hour show, Loki, let me throw some tough questions at you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bobby Blackwolf in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: The guy apparently doesn't want to make it easy for someone to get his car.
[SPEAKER_14]: You knew it wasn't going to be easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't think it was going to be easy, but I thought it was going to be a little bit more original.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like,
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, let's get the guy that created, you know, fucking, I want to be the guy to create some new custom game that ties in with the series and it's fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't mind that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would have been fair because it would have been something unique that, oh, this is challenging, but I just have to be skilled enough to do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: The thing that, you know, and I got to say it,
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: is not something everybody can accomplish.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's kind of an uneven playing field.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not even talking about gaming skill.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just talking about access to these games because, yeah, to find an original machine, there's only so many arcades in the nation that even have something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And if you're like, you might be the most hardcore gaming fan in the world and you live in Montana.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're fucked.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I don't know of any big classic gaming arcades in Montana.
[SPEAKER_14]: Excuse me if I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_14]: but you're going to have to find an independent game collector.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're going to have to be like John Jacobson from Video Game Outsiders who has the arcade in his basement.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got to know somebody like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any of those places will rent out classic games to pizza parlors, to mom and pop places, to restaurants in general, skating rinks.
[SPEAKER_05]: The skating rink I went to in Dothan, Alabama since I was a little kid had the same damn frogger there
[SPEAKER_05]: Even when I went as an adult, the same Frogger I played since it was brand fucking new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying, you can find them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm not saying it's impossible, but it's not like, you know, hey, any of these challenges where it's, okay, here's the ROM or here's the game that you can play in a flash, you know, in the browser, and everybody has access to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like, okay, find arcade game and play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: He keeps adding more stuff to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's supposed to be adding more games each week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's the thing too that I also don't like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because these rules keep getting fucking tweaked every time.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's what shows me it wasn't thought out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because they're having to consistently tweak the rules because they're realizing, oh fuck, we did make this impossible.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's my other question for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: It seems like there's some good sportsmanship and camaraderie amongst all the people who have gone far in this competition, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, you guys are all talking to each other and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sort of?
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, what's been the reaction overall?
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, is everybody pissed like you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or are there some people that are like, alright, now this is a contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some people that are kind of like kiss asses like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my opinion at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: That are like, well, I think this is a perfect contest, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But like, I'll read some examples.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like one of the posts or whatever on Planet Lotus, which is one of the websites that's kind of dedicated to all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: and I laughed when I saw it because it was is basically the thread topic was you've got to be kidding me and then you know the post seriously and then you know the next ones well nobody's gonna beat it tonight haha man I live in it I live in the country it's gonna be tough finding an actual working arcade I bet collector has these um arcades are gonna be bombarded and um what was it uh
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, what's to say they're not going to go, oh hey, I'm just going to play these really fucking easy games and cool, I got a DeLorean now too.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to see Billy Mitchell with a DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_05]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's exactly what's going to end up happening.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think one of the existing record holders is going to get wind of this if they haven't already and it's just going to motivate them to break their existing record and it's over.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope it's that guy that plays with his feet though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, see, that's fucking lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's the other thing, too, is they've also, like I said, they keep adding and changing the rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: They put in a thing now, well, if the third gate's not completed by October 1st, you know, check back to this page.
[SPEAKER_02]: We may have a fourth gate, or we may just end the contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you're going to do this crap?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the problem, though, and I'm trying to make this short, but here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm torn because I don't want to quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to quit now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, I don't want to invest in the stuff that I need to in order to complete it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, for example, I have an arcade machine at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a main cabinet, but it's an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I pop that computer out of there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a JAMMA cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can pop any JAMMA game in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to play Black Tiger there was a whole bunch of drama behind that too because there's a conspiracy that the Black Tiger machine that the guy used to complete the world record was somehow not necessarily modified maybe he didn't know it was modified but that it was a hybrid machine meaning it had some of the chips from Black Tiger and it had some of the chips from Black Dragon which is the Japanese version of the game and the Japanese version scores differently than the US version
[SPEAKER_02]: which may have caused that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, Twin Galaxies approved it and said, no, it's legit, but they're doing it off of video.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's not legit, are they really going to go back and go, oh, we made a mistake?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that they're going to at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool, that you're into arcade games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Where does he live?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no fucking clue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go play at his house.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I'm actually thinking about buying a Black Tiger arcade board.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: See, the thing is, though, is I don't want to... Black Tiger, though, like I said, the high score on it is millions... You are being such a boy right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are being such a boy right now where you do not want to give up on this.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are just... I know I'm not going to stop and ask for directions.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to beat this, damn it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then you're going to get cut off at the knees by one of these guys that already holds the world record and you're going to be three times as pissed as you are tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've known you for ten plus years.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's exactly what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, and then, of course, the Pac-Man world record.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to beat the time.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're already 50 minutes in.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've got to bring this to a close, but I have to ask this, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: And we have a show following us tonight, so we can't have a marathon show tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I've got to ask this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Twitter drama.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I've got to say, Loki, you were a little bit ranny pants on Twitter, and you went so far to say, fuck you, Ernie Klein, which did strike me as a little bit angry 12-year-old.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, okay, you're mad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's going on on Twitter?
[SPEAKER_14]: You get angry and he follows you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've tweeted him before because he did a video talking about his DeLorean that he's given up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he misquoted himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, oh yeah, it's got 249,000 miles.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, you've put fucking 6,000 miles on it in like a few months.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Bobby and Chad are saying, is the Black Tiger arcade board cheaper than a tricked out DeLorean?
[SPEAKER_14]: You guys don't understand, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't matter at this point because now it's a thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's become a thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And now it doesn't matter anymore, folks.
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't matter if the value of that board is greater.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Am I right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to win.
[SPEAKER_14]: See?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Personally, I would want to try Robotron, but finding a Williams machine is like near impossible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so... Other things, I played Minecraft, I played Call of Duty, and... Oh, I did play Black Tiger a little bit, because that's what I did that night when I got pissed off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to boot up my cabinet and play Black Tiger a little bit, because I haven't really played that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're going to grade this world record, I think a lot of these people will do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't just say, I just want to hold the world record.
[SPEAKER_02]: They enjoy playing that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't enjoy playing Black Tiger.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see what they add.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not really... I don't think... All of them are going to be breaking world records, so I don't think anyone's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to be honest, he said so far, he has four... Because one of the first things you have to do is you take a picture of the machine that you're going to attempt the thing on, and you send them also your pictures that you took for the first two gates.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's had... There's almost 1,200 people that passed the first gate, 725 that passed the second gate, five that have emailed him a picture for the third gate so far that even say they're attempting...
[SPEAKER_14]: GameGuru says just buy the damn DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry, buddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what you're missing.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not about the DeLorean anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a manual DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a manual car that sucks gas.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't even drive a manual.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't drive a manual.
[SPEAKER_02]: God damn you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucks gas, and it can only be repaired in Southern California.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you still want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's gotta be the dumbest thing I've ever heard in my life.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is him.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are... Buy one!
[SPEAKER_14]: You'll spend less money.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I won't.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, how long have you known this man?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's not gonna get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not the answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one's gonna win it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to give away my DeLorean anyway, man.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, we're talking in circles.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anything else for your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_14]: I just want to win so I can punch him in the face.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are so mature.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for exuding the maturity that hosts of this show should have all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fuck you, Ernie Klein.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, you're following me?
[SPEAKER_14]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actdeft is right, it's time for an intervention
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like I'm walking on sunshine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just frustrating, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like I've put this much effort into it so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to quit right now, even though it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, playing a 2600 game, playing a Facebook game, world record!
[SPEAKER_05]: We got passed by something cooler than a DeLorean last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Fencer because it has fucking swords in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to really narrow down your fan base.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to bring the one ring.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Loki will be the chick from South Korea that's sitting on the platform crying.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how this ends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am almost considering... Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not putting much effort into this right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not buying a Black Tiger arcade board right now, but I'm just saying I will play it casually, and if I see that, okay, look, I figured out something that no one else has figured out on it, and I can get a high score that can beat the world record, then sure, yes, I will do all that and film all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't, I just don't have the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have the time to do this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, you just played 67 hours of joust in an attempt to win a used car.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: 67 hours!
[SPEAKER_14]: Who the fuck's gonna do that?
[SPEAKER_14]: You just played 67 hours of joust in an attempt to win a used car.
[SPEAKER_14]: How do you feel?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm walking on sunshine.
[SPEAKER_02]: 67 hours?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's how long it takes for Joust.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, it's a historical night here at VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_14]: www.vognetwork.com The Voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twin Galaxies wanted to remind everybody that if you do break the world record before September 5th, you get to be in the Guinness Book this year of gaming.
[SPEAKER_14]: Speaking of Twin Galaxies, let's talk about space.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can I talk about space?
[SPEAKER_14]: Talking about space.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, space.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm in space.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you the best at space?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, Travis Donovan tonight at VOG Network is the best at space.
[SPEAKER_14]: He is going to be hosting live after our program tonight, the Mars Curiosity Landing Special.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, for those that don't know, the thing they shot in space, like how long ago was that?
[SPEAKER_14]: It was probably almost like seven years ago at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nine, nine, nine, nine, nine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, it was that day?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Portal reference.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have issues.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: So they shot this guy into space, and it's landing on Mars tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's happening late at night, like 1.30 a.m.
[SPEAKER_14]: in the morning Eastern Coast time.
[SPEAKER_14]: But Travis Donovan, he loves his NASA.
[SPEAKER_14]: He loves his space program.
[SPEAKER_14]: And God bless him.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's going to stay up late tonight to talk about what this all means and go over the live landing with all of you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: And kind of, I mean, for some people...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what he plans to do as far as archive and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm hoping.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just stay tuned to VOGnetwork.com if you can't listen live tonight and there will be something later on.
[SPEAKER_14]: But if you do participate live tonight, there's special loot in it for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Mars Curiosity starts at 10 p.m.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pacific, 1 a.m.
[SPEAKER_14]: Eastern thereabouts.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's probably just going to take over when we go off air tonight, which at the rate we're going will be around 1 a.m.
[SPEAKER_14]: Eastern time.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about we just continue?
[SPEAKER_14]: How about we get into some gaming news?
[SPEAKER_14]: Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio, Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Congratulations, Critical Myth, on your 200th episode.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is also something that's going on at VOG Network this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll make you a logo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't go with the papyrus thing right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Monday, Wednesday, Friday, 4 p.m.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pacific, 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_14]: Eastern.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dark Sakura will make you a new logo as a present.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will make you a new logo for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Papyrus is the devil.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_14]: Be respectful of everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm respectful, but Papyrus... You're being generous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm being generous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm saving you from yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to understand, this is 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: Papyrus is the new Comic Sans.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's about the in-depth, and I mean in-depth, television critiques that they do every week.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're very mindful about spoilers.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're very good about all of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't even know what they have planned.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently there's a special guest coming on for the 200th episode.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: That starts tomorrow night at VOG Network, Monday, 4 o'clock Pacific, 7 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_14]: Congrats, you guys, on your 200th episode, even if Jamie would like to question your font choices.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, Papyrus is like crack cocaine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it may look pretty, but it's really bad for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm gonna make an Orange Lounge radio logo in Comic Sans and see how that goes over.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do that, and I will judge you forever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, gaming news!
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeez!
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Star Wars The Elder Republic's going free-to-play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, well...
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll transition to a hybrid free-to-play, is what they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, they're going to allow a major portion of the game to be free, including the first 50 levels in all eight classes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, there's going to be restrictions and microtransactions to go with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you do subscribe to the game, you will be given currency each month called cartel coins.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can buy customized gear and other items.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, you'll get other special rewards if you're a different subscriber.
[SPEAKER_02]: They basically said that they want to give people flexibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to do a subscription, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, you can not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, apparently, the numbers have been dipping a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: The people who actually subscribe to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've sold 2 million copies.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, right now, there's only less than a million people actually playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's not very good.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's tons of people playing for it who aren't paying for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or are they doing that whole free... Isn't it already free to play?
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you say playing for it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Free to play to level 15 or 20?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's below 20.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's either 10 or 15.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think free-to-play will definitely help their numbers, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I just think that a lot of people maybe didn't like the game, and so they just stopped playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not necessarily that they're so painful.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it's a really good single player game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think there was enough cutting edge content for the multiplayer was the problem.
[SPEAKER_14]: And for me, PvP ran really sluggish and I have a pretty high end computer so it made it a lot less fun to play.
[SPEAKER_14]: I liked a lot of ideas in the game and the storytelling was done really well.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I just think it was a game that had about three months worth of content.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's about how long it lasted, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a tough, highly competitive marketplace right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think people give too much credit to the fact that it's Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_14]: it doesn't matter folks that's what gets that's what will draw people in for that first taste that and the fact that it's Bioware and that Knights of the Old Republic has a good history behind it that's what draws people in but it ain't gonna make people stay and I think people put way too much stock into this just because it's Star Wars it's not like everything Star Wars related has always been golden cough cough Christmas special cough cough prequels right true
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, yeah, Star Wars is a great movie.
[SPEAKER_14]: The original Disney trilogy.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just want to piggyback on this real quick before I go into the next story.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you hear about World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it's not like things are all roses over there either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard that their numbers are dropping too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Their numbers dropped to 9.1 million as reported at the...
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Expectations this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, for a game that had 12 million subscribers, that is supposedly at the pinnacle shining MMO, a 25% loss, which is what that essentially equates to gradually over the past year, that is something that makes investors go, oh, really?
[SPEAKER_14]: The game is kind of expensive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait till Pandaria, then.
[SPEAKER_14]: the biggest problem with World of Warcraft and I've said this until I am blue in the face on a horde house and Blizzard Activision pulled your head out of your ass on this I swear to god this is what's holding the game back and I don't know why they can't see it the cost to enter the game is too big
[SPEAKER_14]: every other game consolidates the expansions into the original game at some point Warcraft has done it once with what's going on a fifth expansion that's unacceptable it's not working I realize they put the expansions on sale once in a great while I'm sorry if that sale is not sitting on the target shelf you're not going to draw in new players it is time for them to consolidate Wrath of the Lich King and Cataclysm into the original battle chest sell it for $19.99 or you will never
[SPEAKER_14]: Get more subscribers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what happens if you don't have those expansions?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you just not get the play?
[SPEAKER_14]: You play to level 65.
[SPEAKER_14]: You play to level 70.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because Burning Crusade is included now.
[SPEAKER_14]: They finally did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, when I started Burning Crusade wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, when I went back, Burning Crusade wasn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, that was more of a recent change.
[SPEAKER_14]: I bought them all.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, I mean, it sucks that you had to do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, you know, it takes a special kind of crazy to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, I've found places that sold everything for less than retail.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not much less than retail, but less than retail.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love you fries.
[SPEAKER_14]: But still, I mean, you know, if they really want to attract new subscribers, $19.99 for the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: But for some reason, sell $19.99 for the base game and then charge for the Mists of Pandaria expansion or whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, you know, the reason why it's not working is people want to play with their friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they have this whole recruit a friend program that will get you to level 80 real quick.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can't get to level 80 without buying at least the first expansion.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_14]: there's a total logic fail going on here and they need to fix it so Ragenator in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says well 9 million plus subscribers is still respectable it is that's why this isn't quite the doom and gloom I mean show me another MMO that's anywhere close to that that's not called lineage let me rephrase show me one in the states that's anywhere near close to that level of hysteria that World of Warcraft is
[SPEAKER_14]: Panaxium in our chatroom says, I was going to play with a friend.
[SPEAKER_14]: He saw all he had to buy.
[SPEAKER_14]: We played something else.
[SPEAKER_14]: My point exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's what I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, and you know this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had already had Burning Crusade like early on because I did play it back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I played all the way up until I hit level 70 and then that night I went out and got Wrath of the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_14]: and all you were doing with these expansions was paying to level you don't even I mean that's what Blizzard doesn't get nobody is running the old raids anymore hello except us well because we're doing them because they're fun it's a little different and you're doing them with over leveled characters which is really fun because I like you know overkill
[SPEAKER_05]: but I mean you know I did my I actually got 1 to 85 pretty much by myself except for saying hey Rob help me kill this guy well it's nice that you can solo so much of the content you know yeah there is a lot of it that you can solo and you can go in and go back and do other quests low level quests and get more of the story which is what I was doing for the longest time alright I don't want to turn this into the Warcraft podcast but I will close with this comment from our chat room live.vognetwork.com I wouldn't want to compete with Horde House
[SPEAKER_14]: SSJ100 Matt says, Blizzard needs a rude awakening.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think Diablo 3 was the start, but they won't change their tactics without getting hit in the pocketbooks.
[SPEAKER_14]: I agree with you with 90% of that statement that I would change the word Blizzard to Activision.
[SPEAKER_14]: And now I agree with that statement.
[SPEAKER_14]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Everything started going downhill when?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, moving on with other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hopefully this won't be downhill for Nintendo because that could be bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendo needs the Wii U to be successful this holiday season and we may have some of the details thanks to an apparent GameStop leak.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm reporting this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't write the news.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm reporting this, bringing it up for discussion because it's circulating all the blogs out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I kind of don't think this is news, personally.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I want to get your thought.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_14]: GameStop apparently got marketing materials for the Wii U that talk about what games are going to come out when.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it outlines all of the different publishers and when the games are coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And for example, the first party stuff from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lego City Undercover, holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: U, holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ninja Gaiden 3 Razor's Edge, holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendo Land, holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sing, holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wii U, Panorama View, I didn't even know about that one, Holiday, Game and Wario, Launch Window, Pikmin 3, Launch Window, Project P100, Launch Window, and Wii Fit U, Launch Window.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's that tell us?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a lot.
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't tell us dates.
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't tell us which of those games will be available on the actual day and which ones are closer to December 25th.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I mean, it's not like there's going to be that much time between the time this system releases and Christmas anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: So
[SPEAKER_14]: And I kind of was like, I thought we already knew if you listen to the way they delivered that keynote.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought we already knew Pikmin 3 will be out the same day as the Wii U. We know that.
[SPEAKER_14]: WeFitU, I think we had a good feeling was going to hit that same day too.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we kind of knew Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: U. WeFitU where?
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: WeFitU where?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_14]: And New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: U was coming out after that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I believe Reggie said all that.
[SPEAKER_14]: The only surprise of this whole thing, Nintendo Land is marked Holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the only thing that surprised me because I think Nintendo Land, I thought, was going to be like a pack-in game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to hear something funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That list was released on June 6th during E3 by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_14]: So these things have changed.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that list is exactly what they released.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is no news here.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are all the announced titles.
[SPEAKER_14]: but yet everybody's GameStop just leaked the entire Wii U lineup.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they didn't because Nintendo already leaked their fucking lineup a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can link everybody to the wonderful, you know, because I knew I recognized that list and yep, it's exact.
[SPEAKER_14]: August 2nd, all over the interwebs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_14]: Only, only I shouldn't say only in this industry because this shit happens all the time but only in this industry can two month old news be made news all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let me go back and tell you about things that aren't on the list because, you know, that's always fun since, you know, we, we, you know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's get you while you're in a mood tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying, you know, we talked about this a few weeks and here's the other thing too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, there's some publishers that aren't on here like Disney Interactive because there's certain titles they...
[SPEAKER_02]: haven't announced yet that our Wii U titles that are coming, but they haven't officially announced it yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Was that because they're 2013 at this point?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how we know when we, that's how I think I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Wreck-It Ralph's going to be Wii U, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: EpicMinky2 is oh yeah I remember that and then of course you know also this list is not accurate too because they you know they just talked about Madden 13 and also FIFA 13 are going to be launch titles that are going to be on the Wii U so like this is all this right here I can tell you right now just looking at it
[SPEAKER_02]: If I were to guess, I would say that this is a merchandising manual from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people that may be privy to kind of stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that would be my guess where this leak came from because I think that they deliver this stuff to these stores that kind of informs them of the lineup and what kind of stuff that they can look forward to.
[SPEAKER_02]: and they also give them bullet points to talk to with their customers about that stuff it's basically to inform the people that work there about the titles that are coming out and stuff all things Nintendo because if you look at this they have Nintendo DSi product information Nintendo DS product information Nintendo 3DS product information connectivity and policies warnings and disclaimers so it's from Nintendo but it's just the stuff that was all the announced titles from E3
[SPEAKER_14]: Actdeft in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says the internet has really low memory spans.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ain't that the truth?
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, it's cool that certain websites can run with it because GameStop posted it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It must be legit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I have some news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about stuff we already know about, but I'm going to talk about it because it's fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA is suing Zynga.
[SPEAKER_05]: They filed a lawsuit against Zynga saying that The Ville is a blatant ripoff of The Sims Social.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it was filed on August 3rd, 2012 saying that they willfully and intentionally quote, copied and misappropriated the original and distinctive expressive elements of the SimSocial in the violation of U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: copyright laws.
[SPEAKER_05]: And basically it's like, you know, I'm going to paraphrase as I understand it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zynga's gotten away with a lot of shit against a bunch of people who really can't pay to go against them.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is the plaintiff.
[SPEAKER_14]: EA claims that the defendant willfully and rootfully copied all of the assets from their popular game, The Sims Social.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna add this.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're suing for $4,000.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a quote that's by the EA Maxis label manager, Lucy Bradshaw.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a case of principle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maxis isn't the first studio to claim that Zynga copied its creative product, but we are the studio that has the financial and corporate resources to stand up and do something about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Infringing on a developer's copyright is not an acceptable practice in game development.
[SPEAKER_05]: By calling Zynga out on this illegal practice, in other words, calling them on their shit,
[SPEAKER_05]: We hope to have a secondary effect of protecting the rights of other creative studios who don't have the resources to protect themselves.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that even if there is an offer of a settlement, I don't think that EA should take it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they should nail their asses to the fucking wall.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is so fucking weird what's happening with this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, for real.
[SPEAKER_14]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Suddenly we're all Team EA.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which, weren't they just named the most evil company in America thanks to the internet not that long ago?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yet suddenly here we are.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're all Team EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just trying to redeem themselves, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: And like...
[SPEAKER_14]: EA, hold on, hold on, this is where it gets better.
[SPEAKER_14]: EA is championing for the little guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're sticking up for Nimblebit and all these other, the Bingo Blitz creators and all this.
[SPEAKER_14]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's my thing on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: First of all, I mean, at least they're not Chick-fil-A.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, they're not serving up Mass Effect with a side of hate.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I was hoping we could go all night without that coming up, but if it had to come up, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, back to the original point.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've done things that we disagree with, but overall, they've put out quality products, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you're nodding, so if everyone can hear the rattling in Rob's head, then you'll know he's nodding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, you're kind of bobblehead-y tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway, you can... I'm not saying that we're completely team EA.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I honestly do look at part of this as a PR stunt.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, here's our perfect opportunity.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zynga's been taking all this money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's our opportunity to put them down and get some good PR out of the deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you know what if I was running a company I'd do the same shit I'd be like hey opportunity let's knock on the door but this is something that honestly a lot of good will come from as long as they stay pretty you know steady in their pursuit and nails didn't get to the wall I think they have to keep going until it's completely just until they're torn apart and then maybe nimble bit will get some money
[SPEAKER_05]: The end.
[SPEAKER_15]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to go back real quick to talk about that last story we were talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I completely forgot about Activision.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was another thing that's on this list.
[SPEAKER_02]: None of the Activision titles are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Skylanders Giants, Call of Duty Black Ops 2, Transformers Prime, there's a Cabela's Expedition.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, right.
[SPEAKER_14]: We get it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was full of crap.
[SPEAKER_14]: That story on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just wanted to add that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Nintendo news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, going back to the current story, if you look at the comparisons, it really is side-by-side.
[SPEAKER_05]: They took a lot of the material from SimSocial.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, the hilarious part was the one that flip-flopped where the lawyer got the damn screen wrong.
[SPEAKER_14]: but I mean when they're I mean there's some pretty damning evidence in there I mean I know this is all allegedly and we're not supposed to talk about it like it's already a done deal but let's be real we're all gamers we've saw through this shit a long time ago yeah and I gotta hand it to the lawyers they're breaking it down the fucking number of pixels in the doorway is the same between the two games when you look at that you're like I the smacketh down has been broughten
[SPEAKER_02]: If you rearrange the furniture in this room to look like the other room, you overlap the fridge, and they're the same fridge!
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sitting there with my big tub of popcorn.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want this to play out in the people's court.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want this to be televised.
[SPEAKER_14]: We will Wapner on them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Get Wapner out of retirement to preside over this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know that this shit is pretty much...
[SPEAKER_02]: We want you to take this game and change it enough so we don't get sued.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the groove.
[SPEAKER_14]: Look, Zynga is really going to need a moment of how are we going to survive as a company?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because they're being kicked in the balls left and right right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: People are selling their stock.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I mean, we've all talked about we know good people that work for Zynga and I don't want people to think just because we think Zynga is evil means all the people that work there are evil.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's not the case.
[SPEAKER_14]: People just do whatever job they have to do to get by.
[SPEAKER_14]: But clearly management needs to go another direction and some higher ups need to get sacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's not to say that they can't pull themselves out of this because let's look at another company that was kind of and it's still kind of famous of ripping off other companies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gameloft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gameloft does a lot of like
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, that looks awfully close to Halo, or hey, that looks just like Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: They aren't literally... I mean, it's ripping off of a genre, I guess, or like a type of game, but they're actually good games.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the weird thing, although they aren't... One might argue that Dungeon Master Online is actually better than Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: At least one of those games can be played offline.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they can focus on making good games, because they are capable of making games, it's just come up with your own fucking ideas for once.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of independent guys out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You bought some of them because maybe you couldn't figure out how to copy their game without it going.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're running long tonight, so let's pick up the pace a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's talk a little bit about the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've adopted the Peggy rating system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray for uniformity.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were already duplicating it, weren't they?
[SPEAKER_05]: Doing double ratings?
[SPEAKER_02]: They were doing something.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then also now UK retailer workers can face prosecution for selling games with a PEGI rating of higher than the customer, obviously 12, 16 or 18 to underage customers with a maximum sentence of six years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's pretty ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Six years for selling a game to a minor?
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially like a teen game, that just seems a little harsh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I think it's more just trying to... Well, see, you know what my problem is with the rating systems is that it's discouraging parents from doing their damn job.
[SPEAKER_05]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I think that the ratings should be there to inform the parent, and then the parent should do their damn job.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_14]: This is kind of like that California law come to life, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't this the whole thing that the Supreme Court overturned not that long ago is now happening?
[SPEAKER_14]: Am I reading this right, or am I misunderstanding something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yes and no, but see, their thing was, it wasn't tied to, I don't know if it was tied to the M-rated stuff, but I don't know if that law, I don't know the UK laws too well, if they do something similar to the movies, the movies that are rated by the BBFC.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's mature or something and you sell it to a minor, if they get the same type of infraction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if they're going to put that in place on games, I think it should be uniform across all platforms of media if you're going to do something that drastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's still kind of drastic, but if that's the route they're going to go, as long as it's equal across all the different media platforms, then okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'll be interesting to see how this pans out and what possible future legal challenges await, yes?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because that's what always inevitably ends up happening is legal challenges.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know anybody who will sue over this unless they somehow get roped into playing this without agreeing to be a willing participant in this.
[SPEAKER_14]: And this is a case of some kids with a lot of free time on their hands.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not that that's bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just the interesting things that are created.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a Sega Genesis modification.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's called Genesap.
[SPEAKER_14]: It has a motto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe it would be Genesap.
[SPEAKER_14]: Genesap?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's G-E-N-E.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gene.
[SPEAKER_14]: Genesap would be Gene.
[SPEAKER_14]: Genesap?
[SPEAKER_14]: Like Genesis?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, look.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, Genesap.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, I'll go with that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Genesap.
[SPEAKER_14]: No pity for bad players.
[SPEAKER_14]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a dog shock collar.
[SPEAKER_14]: That will zap you, whoever's wearing it, when they screw up or take damage in certain Genesis games that have been modded.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I guess they do say it's Genesis, so it's Genazap.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not GeneZap, my bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Looked like GeneCo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their genes may be zapped by...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Where, let's see, it says go to 4 minutes 10 seconds in where Sonic falls into a spike pit and there will be a stream of bleeped out French cursing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, that sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's fast forward to that part in the video.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go to 4 minutes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's in French, but you can hear Sonic in the background.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad to see that the kids in other countries are just as dumb as the ones here.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's really what it boils down to, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Clover Nikon says, sounds like an add-on for Jackass the Game.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, it's really weird that I kept getting shocked when I was playing Bomberman Act Zero, but for some reason... It felt like I was getting kicked in the balls repeatedly, but it was just when I thought about the $60 I spent on Bomberman Act Zero.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, one more story from DarkSakura and then the release dates.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, how about some good news for E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: They've confirmed they're staying in Los Angeles until 2015.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, they're like, bitches, this is our town.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not building shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because the city was going to tear down, what was it, the South Hall?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think West.
[SPEAKER_05]: West Hall.
[SPEAKER_05]: And build like a coliseum or some shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: But instead they're like... They're going to build a stadium for a football team they don't have yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, like I said.
[SPEAKER_14]: Weren't they building it on the roof or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I said, some shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, basically they're saying that they've generated $40 million for Los Angeles in three days when they do the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're basically bringing in enough revenue that the city can't really afford to fuck with them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's going to be there for another three years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Three more years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I have a comment.
[SPEAKER_14]: Three more years.
[SPEAKER_14]: I ran to the kitchen, but I have a comment.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm stealing a chip.
[SPEAKER_14]: I seem to remember something else about this story about how they've also worked out that the nearby vendors will no longer jack up their prices during the week of E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: And here's my big question.
[SPEAKER_14]: Does that include parking?
[SPEAKER_14]: It should.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many blocks away did we have to park the last time?
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Because the year that E4ALL happened and, you know, LA lost that money, it was a little kick in the butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they learned.
[SPEAKER_14]: And one could argue they may be building that new stadium to bid for, I've heard rumors LA is supposed to be bidding for another Olympic Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a mistake.
[SPEAKER_05]: That ends up putting such an economic cripple on the town that hosts it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you look historically, when LA did it, it actually didn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know how, I'm sure Bobby could answer how it worked for Atlanta, but I think when LA did it, it was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seoul was plunged into debt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beijing was plunged into debt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Almost anywhere that's hosted it has been plunged into debt afterwards with just the fallout from what's going on afterwards.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's the Olympics.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not to mention that they have to kick out residents to build whatever facilities are there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The one in Greece still wasn't finished while the games were going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: What you saying?
[SPEAKER_14]: Bobby clarifies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Atlanta didn't lose money at all in the games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, but it was commercialized all to hell.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: When I went to Vancouver in 2006, the Olympic Games were being shoved down my throat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not that it's a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Olympics are fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: I prefer the Winter Olympics, personally.
[SPEAKER_14]: But anyway, let's not talk about things that are going to be happening in the year 2020.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's talk about next week and video games that are coming out to your nearby stores.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll start with the U.S., Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I hope you like games that feature Persona characters fighting each other because that's all that's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Persona 4 Arena on Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, it's not region-free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not region-free.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sniper Elite V2 Sniper Elite V2 Sniper Elite V2
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, there's nothing on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: That kind of surprises me.
[SPEAKER_14]: There ain't anything listed until the 23rd on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: What a slow period.
[SPEAKER_05]: What holiday is going on?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me look at the Vita real quick, see if there's anything big there.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a couple games there.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's Ginsei Shogi, Kayutendo Tofu Rajin comes out this week, as well as...
[SPEAKER_14]: Orga Rhythm comes out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wonder if that's the same thing as the Sound Shapes game that's coming out here on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't that this week, by the way?
[SPEAKER_14]: You might have missed that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think Sound Shapes is out this week on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a digital only release.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh, that could be.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, this title actually looks a little different.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's actually not a rhythm game, even though it's in the... Or maybe it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sound Shapes is.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks like Pikmin to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, this game, this Orga Rhythm looks like a... It's an action game, they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, hit a button when the queue falls.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it is kind of a music game, but it looks like music infused with Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kind of looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, AkumaJP in the chat room, next week is Obon Holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope I said that right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_14]: Obon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought there was a holiday coming up around this time of year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it could just be for the holiday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, in the UK, there's a few releases.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 7th is Unmechanical.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 8th is Hero Academy and Hybrid.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: A few.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just a few.
[SPEAKER_05]: A bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: A few more stories and then the classic game of the week is coming at you.
[SPEAKER_14]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some interesting things with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, starting off, 1.31's update has come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what you can get with that, of course, now they've merged single players and multiplayer so they have a unified mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then also they've added a few things including a chest for or the ender chest as well as writable books and you can trade now they've added tripwires which sounds awesome large biomes world type also some cocoa beans to the jungles emeralds and emerald blocks and emerald ore and
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess a bonus chest option, which allows people to have some stuff starting off.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you spawn with a chest with a few basic tools nearby, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, let's see...
[SPEAKER_02]: just some other bug fixes like mobs being able to clip through walls stuff like that so that's kind of cool and then to go along with that Minecon 2012 has been announced and it's going to be going to Disneyland Paris in November I want to go to Minecon Disneyland Paris November 24th and 25th I found something for you in Japantown by the way
[SPEAKER_05]: A Minecraft mask.
[SPEAKER_05]: A big foam mask of the dude.
[SPEAKER_14]: Steve.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Creeper.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had Creeper masks too and the pickaxe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I doubt you found any memorabilia for this game because it's several years old, but it's coming back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you remember?
[SPEAKER_14]: Imagine 1994.
[SPEAKER_14]: And remember Wolfenstein 3D?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there was a game that came out not long after Wolfenstein 3D called Rise of the Triad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rise of the Triad is coming back, y'all.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's coming on Unreal Engine 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apogee Software announced this at QuakeCon over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_14]: This was in rumor status earlier in the week, but literally earlier today it was confirmed and a trailer is out right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: The developer is Interceptor Software and the original Rise of the Triad level designer, Joe Siegler, is one of the members.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Single player, of course, online multiplayer and a level editor.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Via Steamworks you'll be able to share stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: So all of the crazy weapons and dog mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: So this is definitely for the fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: The gameplay and it looked pretty awesome because I wasn't really a fan of Rise of the Triad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I played it a few times, the shareware game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it looks pretty cool because it's kind of like a hybrid between like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a Wolfenstein or Duke Nukem, but fast like the Unreal games, Unreal Tournament stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it looked kind of cool, like a lot of the fast gameplay and just with that kind of setting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could dig that.
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot of folks in our chat room are getting excited.
[SPEAKER_14]: DDR Dollar Bill, yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: I am a bit disappointed that there's not a console version.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only PC right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Eh, if they're doing all the Steamworks and all that, I can see it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I realized PlayStation was supposed to do the Steam integration, but only one game has done it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, hmm.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, let's go back to a time maybe perhaps even before 1994.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, I have no idea when this week's game came out.
[SPEAKER_14]: But DarkSakura will clarify that for us right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little older than that.
[SPEAKER_14]: A little older than that.
[SPEAKER_14]: A little newer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry, a little newer.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Every week, DarkSakura likes to jump into the classic gaming vault and find a classic video game that she thinks, hey, you little brats, play this game or suffer my wrath.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Donpachi, which is awesome and very hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Donpachi is one of the... Actually, play the screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play the opening screen, because I can never say it quite right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the way the guy says it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then after that, you can fast forward.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Presented by Kate.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that helps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Little voiceovers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I can never say it like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't punch!
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, it's made by Cave and published by Atlas in 1995.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, for anyone who knows the term Cave Shooter, this pretty much started it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the first game that was developed by Cave and the second on their first generation arcade hardware.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first was Power Instinct 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: The title means Leader B. But it's also an onomatopoeia as in the sound of firing guns.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it is, like I said, one of the first bullet hell games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, you play as a pilot whose mission is to just survive an eight years long training mission so that you can become one of the Dompachi Squadron.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, you're progressing through their training period.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you have two modes of fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a shot fire one, but holding it down, you have a concentrated vertical beam, but it slows down your ship like a whole freaking lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have three different kinds of aircraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have Type A, which is the red one that has a narrow stream of shots.
[SPEAKER_05]: Type B, which is green.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a helicopter that has main guns forward and then side guns that rotate 90 degrees from forward when you're moving horizontally.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Type C, which is the blue or black one that has a wide three-way spread shot, which honestly, Type C is my favorite.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: So you've got five different areas, and you can loop them if you complete them.
[SPEAKER_05]: The second loop has the same areas, the same patterns, but it's a denser bullet, so basically it really does turn into the bullet hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you get the final boss in the second loop, you have a secret area where you meet the big boss of the game, the Hachi, which is a bee.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, other than that though, it's pretty much a shooter.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can get your power increases, you can get your bomb increases, and MP, you can pick it up after you've continued so it returns all of your powers to full strength.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, your leftovers.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, this was the game that started the whole bullet hell series of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it did have a sequel, Dodonpach, which is out on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can play it on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it probably sucks, let's be real.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Espagabaluda, which I can never say right, did perform very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually planned on buying the Domepachi Revolution, wasn't it called?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Resurrection or whatever the crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game Domepachi is out on Saturn and it is a game that's on my list to buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome freaking game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Domepachi!
[SPEAKER_05]: Domepachi!
[SPEAKER_05]: Bullet Hell, Vertical Love See, you're not even getting into the Bullet Hell part of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is still like the first fucking level.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, this looks easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I can make it through the first two levels of Donpachi, no problem.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me forward later in the video here, see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there you're getting a little bit more into the Bullet Hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the second playthrough, uh-uh, no, I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I ended up getting kind of dizzy playing Bullet Hell games.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, that's where you get into it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am not good at bullet hell games I'm just going to go ahead and say this But I love them She doesn't dodge bullets, she shoots them
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's kind of why I like Ikaruga, because you can absorb the ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes it a little bit easier to get through the mass.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I freaking played the crap out of Espaluda on my phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, just saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to take a break, kids.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't go anywhere when we come back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rapid Fire News, the Fugle Question of the Week, your calls, your emails, and some more news, including a Steam decision that may prove to be not too popular, but seems to be popular with a lot of game makers and game publishers right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back after a quick break with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio, episode 468 in progress, August the 5th of 2012, live at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, Loki, what was this you were bringing up during the break?
[SPEAKER_14]: You were going to tell it on air anyway, so go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to send Ernest Cline a message on Twitter because...
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, the world record for Black Tiger is only possible on this machine at... What do they call it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Fun Spot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the one that the world record was accomplished on.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the huge classic game arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the one that's in the movies and all that shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a huge arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their people have already beat it on the actual machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that they haven't been verified by Twin Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: And though for sure it's all in English, I just figured I'd push it higher at this fun spot.
[SPEAKER_02]: This morning, I think I scored 2.7 million.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my highest.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, it's impossible to hit that score unless you go to fun spot.
[SPEAKER_02]: So fuck that shit, is what I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_02]: and just because Twin Galaxies doesn't want to cop up to the fact that oh hey, we didn't really investigate this board and just because the guy that refed that shit fucking doesn't know anything about Black Tiger and maybe isn't aware of the fact that you can grind your score up by running through the game really fast and at the end you're basically taking out zombies that keep respawning and that's how you get your score up.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is well known in the community that plays Black Tiger even for me who doesn't know anything about Black Tiger but oh, just all of a sudden got into the community about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that needs to be pointed out so that they can fix this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I would like to legitimately have a high score in that game, but I can't if the game is fucking modded.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is the plaintiff.
[SPEAKER_14]: He goes by Loki on a podcast that nobody listens to.
[SPEAKER_14]: He claims that the defendants, a bunch of fucking fucktards who don't know how to run a contest...
[SPEAKER_14]: We're negligent.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's suing for a 12-pack of Diet Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy that beat the score is familiar with Black Tiger, and that's how he said it scored.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't understand why Twin Galaxies can go and claim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go investigate it then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go have someone play that game because obviously someone's very easily able to beat that high score.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have them play the game and watch how it scores or have them verify.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am so over this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just like, we don't check the machine, but they did it to Steve Wiebe's machine on film.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that you guys are over this, but you're not over the fucking Chick-fil-A shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean Chick-fil-A show?
[SPEAKER_14]: Please, please don't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I am over it, so let's not go there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, I need to filet this episode over to Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did see the best ever take on that for marketing purpose.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chick on chick filet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a double chicken breast.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're gonna get into rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey Bradley, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Our special guest here in the studio on this historic night.
[SPEAKER_14]: How you hanging in there?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: I apologize for Loki's behavior tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the constant barrage of references on things we come to Sunday nights at Orange Launch Radio to escape from.
[SPEAKER_14]: What are you playing on your 3DS over there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Playing Mole Mania right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mole Mania?
[SPEAKER_14]: Mole Mania.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I thought you said Mall Mania at first.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, what the hell game is that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Why are you playing it?
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: How is it?
[SPEAKER_14]: How's the game?
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that an old school Game Boy game or like a new 3DS game?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's an old school Game Boy game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on a virtual console.
[SPEAKER_14]: What other virtual console games you own on that thing over there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the only thing I have is Dragon Crystal, which is a Game Gear game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course the other like Ambassador games, stuff like that, but.
[SPEAKER_14]: As quickly as possible!
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll wait for the mic there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyways, let's talk a little bit about NBA 2K13.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently now, I don't even know why this is a thing, but apparently Jay-Z is going to be executive producing the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that changes your opinion on whether you should buy that game or not, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so he's going to have, I guess he's doing some of the, picking up the soundtrack maybe?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got a bunch of his songs in there, and looks like a lot of other hip-hop artists in there as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, actually, I think it's kind of a clever move.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, I know some of y'all might be skeptical about it, but it's star power, and it's a big star with a lot of power, and I think for those two worlds to kind of collide, the music world and the gaming world, I think there's definitely a lot of people that are going to
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to turn their head a little closer at NBA 2K13 because of Jay-Z's involvement.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, it's stories like this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Would we talk about this otherwise?
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's that whole thing that's probably good for him being on board.
[SPEAKER_02]: Props to them for including Daft Punk around the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's a Justice song in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm pretty sure Jay-Z's married to Beyonce, for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I'm pretty sure he's pretty diverse with his music likes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess they were a little disappointed about all the characters being leaked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chan Park of Superbot Entertainment said that was unexpected and unintended.
[SPEAKER_02]: No shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, apparently they're going to make some more official character announcements.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll probably include it in those ones that they've already leaked out August 15th during Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_02]: And last but not least...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: The religion, I guess, is called Kiflam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, EpsilonProgram.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can go check it out, and they've got some stuff there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you getting excited?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you getting hyped?
[SPEAKER_02]: All this Grand Theft Auto V stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's not really much Grand Theft Auto V stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, they had the whole financial conference thing that they were talking about all the different games and how they were doing and everything, and Grand Theft Auto V wasn't even really mentioned too much, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of neat that they're going to have some stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hoping that we get some out of Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to see something, but I'm guessing that this game is probably not coming until at least April of next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stan in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com says, if anyone gets a beta code for All-Stars Battle Royale and you don't want it, I'd be happy to take it off your hands.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ratchet Tag speculating on the JZ NBA 2K13.
[SPEAKER_14]: Blue Ivy will be in it.
[SPEAKER_14]: No way, Jose.
[SPEAKER_14]: That baby's going to be like Michael Jackson's kids back when they were young.
[SPEAKER_14]: They had to go out and wear the face coverings so that the media couldn't get pictures.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what will happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, moving on to some other rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Doom 3 is getting a re-release as we've already talked about before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Doom 3 BFG edition.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some news coming out of QuakeCon.
[SPEAKER_14]: There is going to be an extra Lost mission that will be in the HD remaster.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't know what the Lost mission entails, but not too surprising.
[SPEAKER_14]: Usually these types of remasters and remakes get some type of extra bonus thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: So something that was originally on the cutting room floor makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it comes out this October if you missed Doom 3 the first time around or you'll want to play it again.
[SPEAKER_14]: One game I can't understand why people play again and again, but it's like torture.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is the type of game that I would have expected Loki would have to beat to win a DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_14]: You ever played QWOP?
[SPEAKER_14]: I've played QWOP.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been dying to download this because I really want to shoot some pigeons.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, actually, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not QWOP.
[SPEAKER_14]: I call it QWOP.
[SPEAKER_14]: QWOP.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, what, how, god, how the hell do you describe it?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like a running simulation, but, like, remember, like, Track and Field by Konami back in the 80s in the arcade?
[SPEAKER_14]: Running was simulated by hitting the buttons as fast as you can, like, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: And on the old school NES games and the power pad, run as fast as you can.
[SPEAKER_14]: Q-Op is actually about, like...
[SPEAKER_14]: Ben the Knee, Ben the Ankle, and it's four buttons to control it, but it's all like super physics and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: So now there is Klopp, and it is by the maker of Klopp and Gurp and whatever other games they've come out with.
[SPEAKER_14]: Klopp is a four-legged unicorn that you use H, J, K, and L to control the unicorn, and in this one, good luck getting up hills.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the game Loki should have had to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried playing Klopp and I kept laughing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You haven't played Klopp?
[SPEAKER_14]: God, I'm worried where this is going.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've never played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Klopp, you control each foot of the horse.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you happen to use the front feet, you unlock lame horse mode where the back feet get broken and you have to crawl with the front feet.
[SPEAKER_15]: This sounds ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's like this weird Justin Bieber looking character that keeps making fun of you when you die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or not even necessarily die, but you like... That's just rude.
[SPEAKER_02]: You slowly tip over backwards.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just rude.
[SPEAKER_14]: Justin Bieber comes out and makes fun of you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it looks like Zac Efron or Justin Bieber.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ratchet Tag in our chatroom says, Unicorns make everything better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's exactly what this game is all about.
[SPEAKER_14]: Does it fart rainbows?
[SPEAKER_14]: It might.
[SPEAKER_05]: I only want a unicorn that farts rainbows.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, maybe you can find the rainbow farting special item in the World of Warcraft arcade cabinet that is apparently on its way out in China.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a China Digital Entertainment Expo going on right now, and apparently there is a World of Warcraft arcade machine on its way.
[SPEAKER_14]: League of Legends, Starcraft 2, and some other stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yeah, they show pictures of people playing it in an arcade-style machine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now don't think, like, I'm not talking like it's a special arcade release of the game, but you gotta remember the arcades in Asia, still very much a thriving community.
[SPEAKER_14]: Things like cyber cafes and things that never took off here do much better in these other countries.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's really about the kind of the community and getting together.
[SPEAKER_14]: So the fact that they're putting these games in arcade style cabinets, really not a surprise at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: Especially if you look at Counter-Strike Neo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a very pretty machine.
[SPEAKER_14]: All these little sit-down cabinets, people playing Counter-Strike.
[SPEAKER_14]: So...
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting, but not something you're going to see over here anytime soon, I'm sure of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, are we able to get those stories going?
[SPEAKER_14]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, how about first off, Sonic and All-Stars Racing Transformed has bonus edition with an Outrun track and Metal Sonic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, and it has an in-game emoticon sticker pack.
[SPEAKER_14]: But will it have Magical Sound Shower?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care because it has the Opa Opa.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, Rocksmith.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's getting a base mode on August 14th, looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it will have bassists that can improve their skills with two-finger plucking, slapping, and popping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds very dirty.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it also has bass technique challenges, tutorial videos, and minigames.
[SPEAKER_05]: So lots of bass stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because bass is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am partial to the base and then how about this for QuakeCon Steam's having a sale Bethesda games are cheap it's the QuakeCon bundle that's going to have 20 games and again I'm reading this off of a British site so 300 pounds worth for 70 pounds for the lot of it
[SPEAKER_05]: And today is Elder Scrolls Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is, of course, as of Sunday, where you can get the Elder Scrolls collection for 47% off, Morrowind for 66% off, and Oblivion for 66% off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Skyrim will be 50% off, so this is your chance to get it on the cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also going to be a QuakeCon sale happening in the App Store.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_14]: And every week we do a segment here called the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take Facebook, take Google, put it together, you get Fugle.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we ask a question of our Facebook and Google Plus communities every week and read some of the answers here on the show and to poll our folks in studios as well as to their thoughts on this question.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll start with Google Plus tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's the question.
[SPEAKER_14]: An article on VOG earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope you all are reading the articles at VOG.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know we haven't been publishing a lot, but we've been trying to get some stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: And there was a good one this week from Alan.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm not just saying that because he lives here.
[SPEAKER_14]: But he wrote a good article about Minecraft and kind of what made him really like the game the third try.
[SPEAKER_14]: The first time he played Minecraft, he was like, what the hell is this shit?
[SPEAKER_14]: But, you know, the second time a little more, third time finally fell in love with it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So our question to the Fugles this week is, has there ever been a game that you really didn't like the first time you played it, only to come back a second or third or fourth time and fall in love with it?
[SPEAKER_14]: What do you think caused the change in your opinion?
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm sure some of us here in studio can think of games like this, but what is the game?
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll get around here in a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's start with Panaxiom on Google+.
[SPEAKER_14]: For me, it was the Civilization franchise.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just couldn't get into it, but then I started downloading all the awesome mods for Civ 4, and that changed everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fantasy World, yes please.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sci-fi colonization, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, mods.
[SPEAKER_14]: Redertainment says, yes, in fact I'll be playing it when this show airs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dragon Age Origins.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I saw a movie in the theater and it's one of my favorite movies.
[SPEAKER_14]: This was a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stardust.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you ever see that movie?
[SPEAKER_14]: I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have it on HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's based on a Neil Gaiman novel.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I thought the movie turned out great.
[SPEAKER_14]: Michelle Pfeiffer is great and all that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But when I came home from watching the movie, I suddenly wanted to play Elder Scrolls Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: But that's the same type of thing that Red Entertainment's talking about.
[SPEAKER_14]: Watching Game of Thrones made them want to play Dragon Age Origins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chair of Swords.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's this weird kind of... For the record, reading Tolkien is torture.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to take patience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good stories as long as you get past the descriptions of the countryside.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about that whole Hobbit going into three movies?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I read The Hobbit when I was a kid and I freaking love that book.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess they have enough to fill it with.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's three movies I don't have to see.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like the original Lord of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's go to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I love the whole original 20 ending.
[SPEAKER_02]: Princess Bride.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_14]: This might surprise you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Again, games you didn't fall in love with until second or third time you played it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shane.
[SPEAKER_14]: Y'all know Shane.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should be in chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think he's rating or something tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: This answer might surprise you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_14]: No joke.
[SPEAKER_14]: Way back when the first game was on Xbox 360, I gave it a go because of all the things people were saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't make it past Eden Prime before I decided it was dumb.
[SPEAKER_14]: Years later, I got a free copy of 2 on PC for buying Dragon Age 2, so I gave it a go and thought it was pretty eh.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't even get much farther than the opening escape from the Cerberus base before I just quit caring.
[SPEAKER_14]: A short time later, I picked up the first game because I figured I should have the collection on PC for some reason.
[SPEAKER_14]: I made it past Eden Prime this time, but again, didn't care.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then the trailers for Mass Effect 3 came out and I thought it looked so cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I forced myself to get in the first game and something just clicked.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was amazing and I couldn't stop playing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then things made much more sense in 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's how I came to love the greatest game series ever.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Osfer replied and said...
[SPEAKER_14]: Going to Mary.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay for second chances and wow
[SPEAKER_14]: Cody T replies it would probably have to be the Call of Duty games I tried to play them a long time ago and never really understood why people thought they were so fun until I had a child and didn't get as much time to play video games and those games multiplayer wise are easy to pick up and play for 5 or 10 minutes and another is Borderlands for the same reason I'm not that good at FPS games lol
[SPEAKER_14]: Ragenator says,
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Degenerate Johnny says,
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Easy for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, moving off of WoW, because honestly it was really until they tweaked the gameplay to where I liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually going to add Mass Effect on the list because I'd watched Dan play through it at first.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, oh, this is kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: First person shooters make me sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: and honestly, I had a hard time getting into it on Xbox until I started playing on PC and then, boom, all the way through the game, all the way through the second one, all the way through the third one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I beat all three games in the span of a month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm still playing Mass Effect 3 again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Call of Duty Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't like it the first time I played it.
[SPEAKER_14]: What clicked for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: something uh for me most of mine have already been said believe it or not World of Warcraft the first time I played it I left for a while didn't end up coming back till Burning Crusade and then that's when I fell in love with it um Mass Effect is a big one because I played that and you know passed off my review of it sometime excuse me some time ago and then just came back and loved it and I don't even know what clicked I think I just I played from the beginning instead of in the middle and that made a huge difference yeah
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, you know what I have to say?
[SPEAKER_14]: Geras.
[SPEAKER_14]: Minecraft is another big one.
[SPEAKER_14]: If I have to name one that hasn't been named yet, maybe you'll come sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've tried Minecraft and I really do not care for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would say Halo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Halo I didn't like the first time I played it because like first person shooter controller but it was the first time I did an LAN local area network because remember the first Halo wasn't on Xbox Live it wasn't around yet when I played that first Halo in a local area network oh it was awesome so awesome Bradley anything that comes to mind for you
[SPEAKER_10]: There's nothing I can say that's all the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hated it to have loved it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there was one game I played.
[SPEAKER_10]: I started the game Adam Zombie Smasher.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played a demo of it at PAX last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there was a guy there that kind of threw you in, and I didn't know how to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so I said, I don't feel like playing this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it came up in one of the Humble bundles, and I tried to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it starts you off from just doing one thing rather than several things.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I basically...
[SPEAKER_10]: Got into it for a little while when I played it there and went through and beat the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was one that came with I don't care to actually like the game pretty well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, thank you guys again for answering on Facebook and Google, and of course, those of y'all here in studio.
[SPEAKER_14]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio on vognetwork.com, use the passphrase SUGAR.
[SPEAKER_14]: We will continue on with some news.
[SPEAKER_14]: We do have the Mailbag, FUs of the Week, and Twitter topics, Skype line, all those ways to interact coming right up.
[SPEAKER_14]: But first, more news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so let's talk a little bit about Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know I purchased a few things on the Steam sale during the summer here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did also happen to see the update to the...
[SPEAKER_02]: The terms of service that they have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now they have you agree to a Steam subscriber agreement that basically bars you from filing a class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of similar to what we saw with Sony and Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: and of course you know they said we've considered this change very carefully it's clear to us in some situations class actions have the real benefit to the consumer in far too many cases however class actions don't provide any real benefit to users and instead impose unnecessary expense and delay and are often designed to benefit the class action lawyers who craft and litigate these claims
[SPEAKER_14]: you know I gotta say at least it was a very honest as far as corporate can be a very honest letter which you know we kind of Valve's been pretty good about communicating with their community they really have you know especially through some of the other you know like when they were hacked and all that they were pretty transparent with all that and that it's happening here too I don't know how I feel about this I mean obviously this is the trend in the gaming industry I gotta admit there's still a part of me that wonders if that can really hold up in court
[SPEAKER_14]: I understand they're doing it to cover their butts but can it really hold up in court?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think it's been tested yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can still file a lawsuit against them but you just can't do it as a group.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right, but I'm just saying, does that necessarily stop it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, do they have the power to put that in agreement and force you to agree to that?
[SPEAKER_14]: You're waiving your right to sue us a group?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm surprised that hasn't been tested yet, and I think it will be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would think it's going to be a little bit difficult with them, too, because you bought all these games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They give you no warning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I guess it would be in the end-user license agreement that, oh, you can change this at any time.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of a sudden, no, I can't use these games unless I agree to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would think that a judge would see that as unreasonable.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't expect to just all of a sudden cut off the service that this user has paid for because you just put this clause in place that they don't want to agree to all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess there's that part of me that says, why do we let corporations dictate what rights we do and don't have?
[SPEAKER_14]: And I totally understand the viewpoint of, well, then don't agree to it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, didn't somebody say  maybe I saw it on Reddit or something or saw it somewhere where somebody was like, well, what happens if I don't agree to it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Do I get to access my games anymore?
[SPEAKER_14]: And the answer was essentially no.
[SPEAKER_14]: So would that hold up in court?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not so sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess maybe I'm just
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, trying to root for the little guy or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: So that I don't really understand if that's the case, but like something that they force you to read every time you play the game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really know how it works.
[SPEAKER_14]: GameGuru in chat, good point from GameGuru at live.vognetwork.com, says it has been tested.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Supreme Court ruled for them, hence why everyone's added no class action lawsuits clauses.
[SPEAKER_14]: that's right I think it was an AT&T thing if I remember right I totally understand that but I just think if something bad enough happens it's really going to put this to the test and maybe that particular scenario wasn't the right scenario I totally understand why they want to block all this frivolous lawsuit crap and there are a lot of very frivolous class action lawsuits I get that but if something really bad happens I don't know maybe there's that tinfoil hat part of me that wonders why does Valve feel the need to do this
[SPEAKER_14]: What news is about to come out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's the whole lawsuit that was in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole, you know, use games thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they're just trying to prevent something like that happening over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did you make me buy so many cheap games during the summer sale?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to sue you because I'm irresponsible.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, we'll see what develops with this as we move on.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, most people are pretty forgiving of Steam, but certainly there's going to be a few people like that guy who tried to get around it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Was there a postcard clause or any of that?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think there was.
[SPEAKER_14]: EASports Season Ticket Free DLC
[SPEAKER_14]: You get free packs of cards for Madden, FIFA, and NHL Ultimate Team Modes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do the sports games work like Mass Effect 3?
[SPEAKER_14]: Where you open up the boxes and get cards and they are like... Like in Mass Effect 3, it's weapons and team members and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because that's another EA game.
[SPEAKER_14]: No?
[SPEAKER_14]: I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't play these games.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what is this card thing in Madden?
[SPEAKER_02]: The card thing in Madden is for... Remember how there was the whole FIFA hacks?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have that, the ultimate team thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the Madden version of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: What do those cards get you?
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few days before they would come out, you would get a digital version that you would play, and then you'd go purchase the real game on the release day, and then that digital version would stop working.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other things the season ticket had done in the past, early access to full titles that got deleted when the games were actually released.
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it used to be discounts on premium content, but now it's...
[SPEAKER_14]: A little different.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're saying, though, that the only way you'd actually be able to pay for it is if you bought all of the DLC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which I'm sure they'd love to have you do.
[SPEAKER_14]: SJ100Matt says, Rob, yep, you are correct.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the same thing in the NHL games now.
[SPEAKER_14]: BlackWolf says, you can use real money to buy new cards, but there was an in-game auction house that uses the point system that you get for playing Ultimate Team.
[SPEAKER_14]: Live.VogNetwork.com And Monty Boggs, great comment, hard to call it free if it costs $30. $30.
[SPEAKER_14]: that is true it's like PlayStation Plus but I see I like PlayStation Plus I think PlayStation Plus that whole thing's really come a long way and it's got a lot of value I gotta say it's interesting interesting we'll see how many people sign up for it I'm sure there's enough if they're continuing into a second year from the first year meanwhile some more news stories for you guys DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: In other news, we actually have some Mass Effect goodies about the Wii U, which is kind of eye-rolly every time I think of the Wii U, but I'll go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to basically have touchscreen controls so that you can see a map of your immediate areas where your squad mates are and where the enemies are highlighted.
[SPEAKER_05]: you have four powers and abilities that are on each side of the gamepad screen so you can just select one without having to go to your quick menu although honestly my quick menu is my friend I'm like pause hold this pause basically it was also at the EA Summer Showcase where they had the first viewing of Mass Effect 3 on Wii U but the graphics are pretty much going to be the same as how they were on the PS3 and Xbox 360 version
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: That's good to know, because we wanted to know how that was going to work.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, how are they going to catch the Nintendo fans up?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then this is the thing that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mass Effect 3 Leviathan.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's Reaper DLC that's going to come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get to shoot Reapers in the face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm looking forward to shooting a Reaper in the face.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's about time for some single-player DLC, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, I realize the whole extended cut set everything back, but I've been foaming at the mouth for DLC.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's almost been six months since the game came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they were saying that it's supposed to also affect the ending.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like maybe an extra little cutaway or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think it's going to be like a five second cutaway or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think it'll be anything major.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just trying to see when the release date for that one was.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had seen it before and completely missed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But in fact, I'm double checking.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's what I really want to know about the Reaper ending or this Leviathan based ending without spoiling too much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Will you still cry when Edie dot dot dot
[SPEAKER_05]: I cried so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I more cried over Garrus, because keep in mind... Keep in mind, I started with the extended cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the whole little goodbye part on the Normandy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just, like, I'm not going to spoil anything.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's not, I will say this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not talking about dies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, I know a lot of people are like, oh, great, Rob.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's dies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope, that's not it.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you've beaten the game, you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of the particular endings, there's a moment when Edie and dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's like, oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a little bit of a klempt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they said on here also that they actually said there were some things leaked in the script that actually link it to the extended cut.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Patents Connect Patents
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of weird, too, because this patent basically allows taking Kinect, I guess, into mobile cameras.
[SPEAKER_02]: So allowing you to use your phone or something like that to basically scan people into...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: and they said the visual mapping isn't enough the camera relies on motion sensor like an accelerometer to better judge its position as it's moved around and that's interesting does this mean the next Windows phone is going to have Kinect built in for no particular reason but maybe to take like a 3D picture of my face
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also filed another patent that basically uses the Kinect for, I guess, directing movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use your hands to gesture to do different movie editing stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I guess, the depth camera both generates the model environment and also creates 3D props out of real objects, so augmented reality stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Motion capture and, I guess...
[SPEAKER_02]: Doing other augmented reality stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, a lot of people have been trying to do video stuff with a lot of augmented reality stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that would kind of tie in with the supposedly leaked plan or their timeline or whatever that they were planning on doing in the next system with all that crazy Kinect stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Morpheus in our chatroom says, I would love to have the ability to have my in-game character look like me via image capture.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't they have that on the 3DS, and doesn't it not work very well?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the 3DS, remember, it has that front camera, but the front's not 3D, only the back.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, there's three cameras in the 3DS, if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: One in the front, two in the back for 3D images.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a little, you know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyhow, speaking of Nintendo and patents, I don't know if you guys remember this, but Copper Innovations Group filed a lawsuit against Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a patent lawsuit back in 2008.
[SPEAKER_14]: and it's just now over.
[SPEAKER_14]: To remind you, because you probably forgot, Copper Innovations Group claimed that the Wiimote and the Wii console infringed on a 1996 patent for quote, handheld computer input apparatus and method.
[SPEAKER_14]: This looks like a mouse.
[SPEAKER_14]: You look at the little figures, whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, Pittsburgh U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: District Court basically found it in Nintendo's favor, halting the need for a jury trial.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendo, of course, is pleased with the decision and thanks their legal team and so forth.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think most of us saw this as a patent troll type of thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a lot of these type of lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_14]: That took four years to resolve and it hadn't even gone to jury yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: It actually got cut off before it went to jury.
[SPEAKER_14]: The judge basically said, nah, nah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: The legal system in this country is so interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know I'm not a lawyer, but that doesn't stop everybody on the internet from pretending to be one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, joy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see what homemade lawyers we have.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what is wrong with my talking ability lately.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are speaking English good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Clearly.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Slow down, Rob.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to go to the mailbag and see what homemade lawyers we have in the email bag this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to email the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just going to start with one from Steven W. Home does get a bad rep from how it used to be back in the day to what it is currently going down with its updates.
[SPEAKER_05]: With the recent updates and fixes, they have pushed out some really good content and finally fixed the glitch that allowed users freezing others.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does Home still have its issues?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why, yes it does, but it does what comes when software is still in beta.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, this is very run-on sentency.
[SPEAKER_05]: Home is constantly evolving, and with evolution comes bugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you look past those bugs and look at the community, the atmosphere surrounding it, and all of the events slash games within Home, you see how epic it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yes, Home gets a bad rep, but it has a lot of good inside of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who does it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it like a pinata?
[SPEAKER_05]: So everyone should hop on and check it out, even if it's for a few moments.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I beat it with a stick, will candy come out?
No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody won a $20 gift card last week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, that had nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was not Sony sanction.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was a generous fan helping another generous fan out.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I'm glad to see... Good.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm glad some people followed through because I don't know if you remember, but during... Hey, it's not time for the FUs yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Be quiet.
[SPEAKER_14]: During last week's show, I actually asked all those guys in PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_14]: I said, does your network get a bad rap?
[SPEAKER_14]: Does home get a bad rap?
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm glad somebody followed through with that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for replying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is from Nasty Canesta.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, OLR.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of my favorite nicknames, by the way, that emails the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I think about the card game Canasta.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think of old people.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like strip Canasta or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's time to get nasty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if you covered this before, but you might be interested in a teaser for an upcoming PC first-person horror game called Among the Sleep.
[SPEAKER_05]: The protagonist for Among the Sleep is a two-year-old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aside from the utter helplessness you have to deal with playing as this poor toddler, imagine if you also had to struggle with the baby's current developmental stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: How could the game screw with you if this kid didn't grasp the concept of object permanence yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: Scary!
[SPEAKER_05]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: Garris?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I think a two-year-old understands object permanence better.
[SPEAKER_14]: says the parent of a two-year-old.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually peeked in the mailbag earlier and I watched the little trailer for this thing and it looks creepy as hell.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's a weird concept for a game to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: When you do things about children, that's always a little creepy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'd like to stay away from that.
[SPEAKER_14]: At least the child doesn't get eaten by a grue or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just, you know, it was a scary looking game, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like amnesia level scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Armadillo which I don't think came out in the US and then Panic Restaurant which actually that is the US release and I went to find because I only remembered like half of the name because it was something Gourmet World it was One Paku Koku no Gourmet World and it came out in 1992 and was published by Taito where you play as a guy named Cookie who looks like Chef Boyardee
[SPEAKER_14]: Not to be confused with the announcer from You Don't Know Jack.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is one of those games that had one of those classic things of mistranslation of a name because the bad guy in the game was called O'Durf.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was French to Japanese.
[SPEAKER_05]: So when it came to translating it from Japanese to English, they called him O'Duff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: it was a neat little game and it was by Sakura and then Armadillo was sort of like Super Mario 3 where you had like a map that you could move from world to world I know of all three of those games so yeah good job dude you can send me your copy of Armadillo if you want I'll play the fuck out of it
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, so, uh, this is let me know your opinion and happy podcasting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, Banana Prince is pretty, pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, Armadillo is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually did not play Panic Restaurant, but I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen, I know someone who had Panic Restaurant when I was younger.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just saying, I didn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, moving forward, shall I?
[SPEAKER_05]: This comes from Clover Nikon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi guys and gal, just writing in to say that I am loving the show and loving the VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have not been on the VOG site as much as I would like to due to my two jobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, today, August 6th, is my one year wedding anniversary and unfortunately my beautiful wife Lisa has to work so I'm spending my morning here with my friends at the VOG Network while I do CG renders.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, Lisa is playing Fable 2 Star Wars Connect and will soon play Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hope everyone has a great evening and keep up the great radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sent from my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, happy anniversary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, anniversaries are great.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry to hear that, you know, somebody's having to work during it, but, you know, you've got to make the money.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's how it works.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have two more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was trying to find something for that last email here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Better not be Happy Wedding.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: We already did Happy Wedding a couple weeks ago for Tiara and Dan.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is the other song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Remember Parapara Paradise?
[SPEAKER_14]: Paradise?
[SPEAKER_14]: Dave, Domino, and Virginelle anniversary.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy anniversary.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've just started my tour in the Mass Effect universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say that I have owned both 1 and 2 on Steam for at least 2 years now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am hooked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Played through the first one in about 22 hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am absolutely in love.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game is epic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly had chills from the first 2 minutes when 5 year later, spoiler alert, Shepard crawled out from the wreckage.
[SPEAKER_05]: some things happen in my game that make me sit in my office during the day and question my decisions when one of my favorite characters was shot and killed I wanted so badly to reload my game and make different choices yet I didn't you totally could have
[SPEAKER_05]: yeah I continued on letting the decisions I had made played out for the rest of the story my question is which choice based games such as KOTOR, Mass Effect, Heavy Rain, Fable do you go with your gut feeling and let the story play out as it will or try to change it in the way that you want it
[SPEAKER_05]: Mass Effect I played I've actually played the second one the exact damn same way I played the last one my last playthrough on Mass Effect 3 the only thing that I changed was I killed Caden and played with Ashley using my save file editor just so I could see what Ashley was like in Mass Effect 3
[SPEAKER_14]: I have to admit, Mass Effect was really the first game where I didn't feel this need to do everything perfect.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because usually when I play RPGs, I'm kind of that anal retentive, search every corner, talk to every person in the town, explore every story, do every side quest.
[SPEAKER_14]: And there comes a point when you're playing these Bioware games where you just have to realize you can't do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: You cannot do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is not possible without playing the game 500 times.
[SPEAKER_14]: so Mass Effect was really one of the first games to kind of like get and I realize this is very recent but it's it's a different way of thinking for me so and it's not been easy so that's my long-winded answer
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I also did play Dragon Age 2, and I really liked it, but it was like, when I started romancing What's-Her-Name that was voiced by Eve Miles, I was like, oh my god, she's annoying, oh my god, she's annoying, so I started going after Fenris.
[SPEAKER_05]: because I was like, ooh, he's kind of broody.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd go for Fenris.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really play the Fable games because I really didn't like them that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan played the crap out of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I started on Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: I liked Fable, but I never finished any of them, which is weird because I own them all.
[SPEAKER_05]: um my favorite choice ever was how to bitch slap the bitch slap fight in Final Fantasy 7 just saying and those you know choose your the the little mud games or choosing who you would date in Final Fantasy 7 yeah trying to get the Barrett date fuck no it was always Tifa and I did not use that bitch Aerith more than I had to because she was a hoebag fuck her and now she's tell us how you really feel
[SPEAKER_05]: I still have my save file.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where I can kill her as much as I want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the Jenova fight, which is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like the most fun fight in the damn game is that Jenova fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm so giddy from her being dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you just like the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really love the freaking... No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the Jenova music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate the Earth music because I hate everything about the bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, also completely off topic, but I've ordered Sound Shapes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any of you guys played demos or have any thoughts about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I really needed something fresh on my Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got an inch of dust and shame on it at the moment.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dust and shame.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep up the great work, Travis.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dust and shame.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have not personally played Sound Shapes, but Shane, who's a friend of mine, will not shut up about how great it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, is he in chat?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe he'll call in later because apparently it's great.
[SPEAKER_14]: And he says he's getting it launch day.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know much about it, but Shane sure talks it up.
[SPEAKER_14]: It makes me kind of want it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope there's a demo.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's Shane in chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, Sound Shapes.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last email?
[SPEAKER_14]: One more, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is labeled bad rep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not all, but some clubs and especially fans slash mafias are a bad rep on home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than that, home is a great place to have fun and to get away.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, even though this has nothing to do with this, who's the porn star?
[SPEAKER_05]: It could have been me.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's from Skull King.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just want to say Marissa's in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Marissa, can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell me if I can say.
[SPEAKER_05]: It starts with a G. All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why you get a letter.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a G. It starts with a G. Like OG.
[SPEAKER_14]: G would have wasted time I spent on Google.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that it for emails?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send us an email for next week.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was two home emails.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you, kind emailers.
[SPEAKER_14]: all of you that emailed from Mass Effect to Sound Shapes to PlayStation Home appreciate it let's get to the FUs of the week the part of the show where we get ranty why?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know
[SPEAKER_05]: FU.
[SPEAKER_05]: So losing my job.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really fucking liked that place.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked everyone I worked with.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved my cubicle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked my Mass Effect wallpaper on my dual monitors.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm really going to miss the people I worked with and I'm going to miss all the reps I worked with.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were some awesome people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I have to tell you what my FU is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's this whole debacle with this stupid Black Tiger score and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, there was literally a forum thread on Twin Galaxies from the people that beat the fucking high score that actually set the goddamn world record that said, hey, the machine doesn't score right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yet they're not willing to do anything about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So fuck that shit, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Way to go, Twin Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some integrity you got there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Honestly, I don't have a lot to complain about.
[SPEAKER_14]: Things are going pretty well for me.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to the lack of motivation I have to exercise, because I really need to get that done.
[SPEAKER_14]: I need to join a gym or something, but I just know my lack of motivation too well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, fuck you to my bee-hurting.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least I'm done with my hiking season for the most part.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except for since I'm on later, just hopefully I won't hurt more later then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, and also fuck you to getting tired in the middle of the day after your lunch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, uh, get all the work done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Work.
[SPEAKER_10]: Work's not that exciting.
[SPEAKER_10]: That makes arguing harder.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, there it is, EFU's The Week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's do a couple more news stories.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then we're going to get into Twitter topics, if we have any.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really make a lot of calls for them, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then the Mars Curiosity Landing special.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_14]: What are you pointing at?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, what is this?
[SPEAKER_14]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's discuss.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's discuss this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a bag of stuff from Swag's kind of stuff from the last packs that I have sitting around on my table and I'm not going to do anything with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I thought I'd bring it over here so you could give it away.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: A mouse pad for EVE Online, ShatteredCrystal.com, Combat Arms, World of Tanks Alright, so like a little mouse pad Let me look Take it all out, Rob They actually had a tank there at the opening Yeah, whip it out, Rob There's a lot of postcards and brochures and things
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe some codes in here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why not just dump the bag out?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I don't want to do that because then I have to put it all back in the bag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lazy?
[SPEAKER_14]: Some stickers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that a tattoo?
[SPEAKER_14]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Air Mac.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, it's like a business card.
[SPEAKER_14]: A little QR code.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's like one thing that I got at the harmonics panel.
[SPEAKER_10]: Grab that thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a chain sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Holy crap, this thing's heavy.
[SPEAKER_14]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a weird Dance Central chain thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, that's like... You can wear the chain like they wear in Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, so how do... Yeah, unfortunately, I can only stay there, pan off like 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_14]: How are we going to give away this bag of crap this week?
[SPEAKER_14]: I need to think of something.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about we make a forum post and...
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll make a forum post after the show because I want something the podcasties can participate in too I want the live listeners and the podcasties to have a chance at it so we'll say we're going to do a forum post and we'll do something about if you're not going to PAX this year
[SPEAKER_14]: What are you going to do instead or something?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll come up with something and we'll have a question and we'll pick one random answer on the forums and give away Bradley's bag of crap from PAX and you won't even have to pay shipping.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shipping will be covered by OLR because we're generous and kind.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm looking in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com DJ Morpheus says, F you to not hearing Bradley.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's just a quiet guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's just soft-spoken.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's not as loud and obnoxious as the other rest of us.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me?
[SPEAKER_03]: You did not.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, girl.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Morpheus says, is it a bag of shit?
[SPEAKER_14]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, dude, Dance Central chain.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Monty Boggs says, I didn't even know VOG had a forum.
[SPEAKER_14]: I fail.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the point of the contest.
[SPEAKER_14]: See what I'm doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm driving traffic to the forums.
[SPEAKER_14]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe we'll throw in another prize or two.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: So win Bradley's bag of shit from PAX featuring Dance Central Chains and Whoopie Cushions.
[SPEAKER_14]: Enter on the forums after the podcast goes up tonight, live listeners.
[SPEAKER_14]: Keep an eye out on the forums at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let us move on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some folks in chat talking about E3 swag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: E3 swag, that was E3 circa like 2003.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now it's all go on our website.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's a business card with a link to our website.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's a QR code to scan to get on our mailing list.
[SPEAKER_14]: They don't really give away stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: When the economy got tight, those are the first things to go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, Loki, news stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it's been a show where we haven't mentioned the Ouya yet, so let's mention the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_14]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, there's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Ouya, they've got a few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, they're kicking starters running through, I believe, this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it ends this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've added a few things, including you can get a special edition console if you pledge $140.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's slightly darker metal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of like it, but I'm not going to pledge any extra money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Shadowrun Online has been confirmed to be getting Ouya support.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm assuming that's, of course, if they hit their Kickstarter goal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy 3 is going to be one of the launch titles for the Ouya, which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, that was just recently released on Android, but they will be doing a version for the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_02]: um kind of neat and then um also iHeartRadio has been confirmed as one of the apps on there and then there's a game called Offensive Combat that's getting a port to um oh yeah as well that's um kind of like a Call of Duty type of game first person shooter so neat
[SPEAKER_14]: Neat indeed, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm still waiting for the OUYA to hit the shelves, that's all.
[SPEAKER_14]: But their Kickstarter's doing very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and they've got some of the people backing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Square Enix is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now it's all about, will it come out on time?
[SPEAKER_14]: The countdown is beginning.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because now aren't they offering limited edition colors and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's more expensive because it's going to be a limited run, and so because they're producing less units, it's going to cost a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_14]: all right one more news story for you guys tonight and then the skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on skype orange lounge radio opening right after this story and this is one of those wow i uh i'm not sure i believe this is happening but it's happening a new game coming out for the wii note that's not wii u it's the wii and it's happening on september 14th
[SPEAKER_14]: Andrew Lloyd Webber's musicals Sing and Dance coming out on the Wii I think I know who's putting this out too September 14th who?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's oh god now I'm gonna forget it's not City Interactive O Games Oxygen Games is the one putting this out because they had well they had a game called Everyone's Sing and Dance and I believe that they picked up licensing now for this if I already guessed
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because in kind of a similar story, you know how they have that Marvel Avengers game that's coming out that kind of looks a little similar to that Ubisoft fighting game that they have, like another superhero game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's actually the sequel to that because it was just going to be Power Up Heroes 2, but then they got the Marvel licensing, so they skinned it.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, I want to talk about Andrew Lloyd Webber, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: This game is coming out September 14th.
[SPEAKER_14]: 32 classic hits from 13 musicals.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can sing and dance to Don't Cry For Me, Argentina from Evita, Superstar from Jesus Christ Superstar, and All I Ask of You from The Phantom of the Opera.
Man.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sure that's in there too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_14]: The game is called sing and dance.
[SPEAKER_14]: How the fuck do you dance to any of those songs?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen Cats and all she does is shuffle across the stage and pose a lot.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or I think of Madonna in Don't Cry For Me Argentina.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did she do?
[SPEAKER_14]: She was in the balcony with her hands.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or you take the Wiimote with your hands and point to the subjects.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't cry for me Argentina.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, good lord.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still kind of want to buy it and have Loki play it on the show it would be interesting to do a whole segment of drunk people performing the musicals
[SPEAKER_14]: Poor Andrew Lloyd Webber because he doesn't know about how bastardized his musical songs are about to become.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the Phantom of the Opera.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great musical.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen it a few times.
[SPEAKER_14]: The sensitive side of Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have you seen the movie that came out a couple years ago?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I did see the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to the theaters to see that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It wasn't bad, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great opera.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen Wicked was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I even got dragged to A Light in the Piazza which is
[SPEAKER_02]: Spamalot Tim Curry King Arthur
[SPEAKER_14]: Tim Korean, anything, awesome I was given very bad news Oh, Black Wolf's got a good point, Book of Mormon I'm sure is one you might enjoy Avenue Q is great too But one bit of sad news I got this week, thanks to SSJ100 Matt, you jerk Sister Act is closing on Broadway at the end of this month Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: You're surprised?
[SPEAKER_14]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Didn't it win Tony's?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to tour, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to tour.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm going to say a little prayer that Sister Act will end up in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_14]: How can it not?
[SPEAKER_14]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_14]: It might.
[SPEAKER_14]: We got the Lion King.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now we have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only do we have that now, but they have the kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: Off, Off, Off, Off, Off Broadway stuff now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they have, like, you know, the three stages, which is in our, like, Folsom.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got Davis and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, like Music Circus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but they do, I mean, they do, like, Wicked and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: A Family Friend.
[SPEAKER_14]: A family friend, their little girl was in Little Orphan Annie, and I think that was the last musical I went to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they did The Lion King.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't know, you know, is that the same Lion King, or are we seeing, like, high school production of The Lion King?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, Tigerclaw in chat says, but the costumes for The Lion King musical are crappy, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, you and I clearly didn't see the same production.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, you must have seen community theater Lion King, because the costumes and the puppetry and all, that's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, if you don't have good costumes...
[SPEAKER_14]: The Lion King is screwed.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about Evil Dead the musical?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That exists.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why I did it in San Jose.
[SPEAKER_14]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Launch Radio if you want to give us a call right now or Loki and I can just sit here and talk about musicals.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, do you have any other last minute stories before we...
[SPEAKER_02]: There was some stuff about... There was another Kickstarter project that's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's for the heads-up display.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a virtual reality display that's being backed by id Software and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that might be something cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hold up.
[SPEAKER_14]: I never realized your picture was on the ErnestKlein.com website.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: But somebody linked it in chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: And my favorite is that your face...
[SPEAKER_14]: You're so fucking mad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I was so pissed off at that fucking thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I purposefully looked angry at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Texas, for linking that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another one on there that I looked tired because I was playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's one for the Atari 2600 game from Gate 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was number 159, so you can look up the picture for that, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, we've got a million calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_14]: I need to get some calls.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, hi, it's Panaxium.
[SPEAKER_14]: Panaxium, what's up?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, hey, I actually finally got through.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Long-time listener, first-time caller?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, actually.
[SPEAKER_14]: My favorite.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I love your little Skype icon.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is the best squirrel in the universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that like the epic Iron Man squirrel?
[SPEAKER_14]: I wish it was a video show sometime so you all could see that because that's cracking my shit up.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, Panaxian, to what do we owe this phone call tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, actually, I just got done playing a game recently that I think is awesome, and I don't know if you guys have covered it before.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is Insanely Twisted Shadow Planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've wanted to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought it, and I don't think I've played it yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I bought it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't finished it yet, but it was one of the closest, like, Super Metroid-esque games I've played in a very long time that actually kind of, like, took me back to how good, like, outside of, like, Castlevania, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, took me back to how freaking good Super Metroid was.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, it really kind of took me back to that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But then I got to admit, I don't know if you know this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Where are you from, Panaxium?
[SPEAKER_14]: Colorado.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, Colorado.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you have Del Taco in Colorado?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Del Taco did an insanely twisted Shadow Planet promotion.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I was like, what?
[SPEAKER_14]: No way, really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was like, buy a taco, get an insanely twisted Shadow Planet cup.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I was like...
[SPEAKER_14]: I have never heard of this.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Call of Duty was unavailable, huh?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not there anymore, but it was like six months after the game had come out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was so fucking random.
[SPEAKER_14]: Google it or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's really weird.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, I was just calling because I thought that game was just amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I loved the art style of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: and uh just the gameplay just kind of like you said it took me back and I was like wow they just don't make games like this anymore well I guess they do because it's out so did they ever do the DLC for that I heard there was supposed to be DLC coming out but I don't remember reading about it uh I don't know actually huh yeah Loki yeah DLC came out for it oh did it yeah oh good
[SPEAKER_13]: I know it has some multiplayer stuff, but I actually got a chance to try it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's on Steam too, maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or they have a PC version.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, there's like a PC version now.
[SPEAKER_14]: The original one was on Xbox Live Arcade, but that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: So yes, yes, I am familiar with Insanely Twisted Shadow Planet, and it's a good pick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything else on your mind tonight, buddy?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, just wanted to pop in and say hi, because I've been meaning to call in to you guys for quite a while, and I just never get around to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a wonderful voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should do radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_14]: You just made him blush a little bit, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: She hasn't talked to the callers often.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's a little stuck up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am not.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm judging you a lot right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Y'all can't see it on the radio, but I'm giving Rob the look of judgment.
[SPEAKER_14]: Should I get the people's court theme up again?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Panaxium, thanks so much for the call, and glad we can make you blush.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I'm honored.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: You gonna flirt with all the callers tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm not flirting with the callers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, I compliment people on things that deserve complimenting and he's got a very nice voice, just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not Garrus level.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, well thank you for bringing us back down.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you're not Garrus, but you're alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, that's an amazing voice actor.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's Travis, guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: How y'all doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, Travis.
[SPEAKER_14]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, you're not Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm Travis that just emailed about Mass Effect and all my other... I like you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you what, DarkSakura... That's not flirting!
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you just say?
[SPEAKER_04]: You said, I like you.
[SPEAKER_08]: That game is absolutely phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I started it probably twice or three times on my Xbox 360, and I never wanted to play it because I just could not get into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And y'all were just talking about games that you play once and you're just like, I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I just played it on my PC and I absolutely love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, unbelievable.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have you gotten it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I got chills right now talking about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you cheat like I do?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Godmode.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm playing on the PC right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, so am I. And I am fully cheating.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can do this hacks thing where you can like hack the game for Godmode and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kind of like the, you know, the old school shooters where you could be invincible.
[SPEAKER_14]: IDDQD and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not doing anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just played it through and like I said, I was just going with my gut feeling on everything that I said and I was actually a complete asshole in the game and the whole like
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, what do you want to do with the council at the end?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like, yeah, screw them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kill them!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just after Sovereign.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got two other things about it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys were just talking about musicals.
[SPEAKER_08]: Has anybody or have any of y'all seen Video Games Live?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm in Florida.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's coming to St.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pete.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm so excited to see it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe Dark Tetsuya, who is like the OLR historian, will know the episode number.
[SPEAKER_14]: But we actually had Tommy Tallarico on the show for like an Uber interview, like 45 minutes long.
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: other than camp well I need another 45 minutes to get into that but let's just say in our adult lives yes so this is funny anyway sorry no that's really cool because I mean I've been wanting to see it for years and I've got a Spotify account and I listen to like the albums on there and I'm just so stoked that it's coming back to Florida again I can't wait to see it but my other question was
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you guys heard about the game, or it's a mod for Arma 2, it's called DayZ?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Has anybody gotten into that, or what is it all about?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm a huge Walking Dead fan, and it reminds me so much of Walking Dead, it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't really gotten a chance to play it yet because I'm still trying to figure out how Arma controls to my Xbox 360 controller I've gotten close but it gets complicated but apparently it's very just it drops you down you have you know you have to go find resources and you know there's random groups of people walking around doing weird things like kidnapping people and you know of course you fight zombies but it's more about the crazies that are out there too which are all real people
[SPEAKER_14]: and that's what I've heard and I'm trying to like I guess wrap my head around the point of the game because it seems like the point is just to keep your character alive as long as possible which seems kind of creative pretty much yeah and by the way according to Misty the other OLR historian how dare I how dare I give that crown to only one person because Misty just came in and snatched that crown by saying episode 285 was the Tommy Tallarico interview thank you Misty
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have to try to look it up then.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but right now I'm playing through Rage, which everybody has told me to play through, and it's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess it's kind of like a Lanier fallout in a sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now's a good time for that with QuakeCon in the air and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was just on Steam this weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a Steam nut, so I picked it up on Steam for like $10 the other day.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was like, yeah, why not?
[SPEAKER_14]: Quickly, before I let you go, because I do have to get more calls, but quickly, since you said you're a steam nut, how do you feel about the new end-user license agreement and the waiving your right to a class action lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, they've been so good to me over the years, and I've had an account forever, so it's just like I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send me a message in chat, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not a too happy type person, so I mean, it's just like, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cool with me.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, DarkSakura, what's this all about?
[SPEAKER_14]: You want a private message from the caller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I was going to show him my femship.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is why I like playing on PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura wants to take this conversation offline.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Freaking Sound Shapes is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tell me more!
[SPEAKER_14]: Why is it fantastic?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a music game that is like a cross between a crappy, boring platformer and LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I do like those creation games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you know yet?
[SPEAKER_14]: Is it easy to share the stages?
[SPEAKER_14]: Is it easy like LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_12]: That I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would hope so.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I want to make a million levels.
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Morpheus in our chatroom says, It shapes with sounds!
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_12]: It's got a charm to it, though, that makes me feel like I'm playing one of those really retro-style games, kind of like VVVVV or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're naming all these games I love.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're doing that on purpose to try and get me to be a fan.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not hard.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've played it...
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's download only, so good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: or isn't Sound Shapes on the PlayStation 3 too?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was also PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you can get a discount apparently if you're a PSN and you pre-order it.
[SPEAKER_12]: A PSN Plus member.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am a PSN Plus member.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, so am I. Holy shit!
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a $20 PlayStation Network card that I got today so I'm going to pre-order it tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: How did you get a $20 PlayStation card today?
[SPEAKER_14]: You ended work a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: Those, I didn't get discounts on those.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, no, I cancelled a pre-order and put that towards Guild Wars and this.
[SPEAKER_12]: I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, no, no, I'm sorry, I'm searching Amazon right now to see if it is something that's retail or if it's download only, but it looks like nothing's coming up on Amazon, so.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, Best Buy's website had it and it said it came out May 31st, 2012.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, that's not right.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not right.
[SPEAKER_12]: but I'm excited for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You need to watch that video though.
[SPEAKER_12]: So now there's going to be Luminous and Sound Shapes and then DJ Max is coming out which had new videos out this week too and it's like I can't handle all the amazing music games on my Vita.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's too good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything else before I let you go?
[SPEAKER_12]: More people need to call in about Mass Effect because it's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, we'll try our luck with one more call.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously, how much did you smile or laugh when that last guy called in just to talk about how now we've passed it on.
[SPEAKER_14]: We got him hooked on Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_12]: That needs to happen more often.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't listen to the show earlier because I was playing other stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: But...
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw that I wasn't the only person on your question of the week that said Mass Effect, so I was kind of proud.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's try to get a couple more calls.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're getting slammed tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, X-Link.
[SPEAKER_00]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, doing good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wicked and Rent for musicals for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Those were my two favorite to have soundtracks to, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: But no, the reason I was calling it tonight was because I've been playing the last few days and of course some of our other friends have too was the Kingdom Hearts 3D Dream Drop Distance or 3DDDD as I like to shorten it to call it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been a really great game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been a lot, a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really short but it's really fun though.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really taking a lot of the old stuff and tying it back in and making it so when 3 comes out at least it'll
[SPEAKER_00]: Bring the storyline up to Data Part 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you get to Tron World?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_00]: That was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's very unique in its own way, so I really did enjoy a lot of it and how they're splitting the storyline up between Riku and Sora, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: Mm-hmm
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's because of the different ways it branched out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, you had, of course, you had Kingdom Heart 1, you had Kingdom Heart 2, you had the, you had Recoded, you had Chain of Memory, which Chain of Memory was practically between 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then they branched out, like, these little storylines.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then finally, with this one, at least, they're starting to take all the games and saying, okay...
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's the story line between the games in case you didn't see like Burp by Sleep was a prequel to everything and of course so it's pretty much was all over the place but like I said before I like it how they sat down with the game so far and they're pretty much going through and tying everything together going okay this is the reason why this has happened and
[SPEAKER_00]: This is the reason why that one happened the way it did, and this is the reason why this one happened the way it did.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's kind of, they're taking all the pieces, tying it all together, and getting ready for that big finale at the end, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I hope to hell it is Kingdom Hearts 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got my fingers and toes crossed for Tokyo Game Show announcement, but then again, we still have to get through 13 versus... Well, they did say they are making 3, which is really good, and it's just as to when, who only knows.
[SPEAKER_00]: And like I told you before, I really hope when they do, they take their time, they make sure they end it, you know, they...
[SPEAKER_00]: They tie everything together and they end it in a way so we can go, okay, that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of like with the whole Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is there one of them secret endings that gives you the extra scene that maybe it's too soon to know, but that kind of gives the big kingdom?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, there is.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just don't know what it is exactly yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I hear it does tie in.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's supposed to tie into that three.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, before I let you go, I just got to let you know, Rent, I wasn't such a fan of Rent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know a lot of people are into it, but not me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some people are, some people aren't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Everybody has their own, you know.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll get hate mail for that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, man.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of my friends growing up was turned into a total rent head.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then when I told her later, you know, I saw rent and I wasn't such a fan.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's like, Shun.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Opinions.
[SPEAKER_14]: People have them.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: One more call.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, hey, hey, from the Brooklyn studios, it's DJ Ranma S. How you doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm doing good, how about you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Disappointed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sister Act was going to be my reason to come back to New York City, and now it's gone at the end of the month, and there's no way I can afford to get there this month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, well, well, stop.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sister Act is your reason to come to New York when there's a bunch of us here that love you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought you, I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought, I thought, oh, you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rama, Rama, Rama, Raven Simone.
[SPEAKER_14]: scene better sorry anyway actually and I will say this too DragonCon was the other thing I was really trying to get to happen but unfortunately it's not going to happen I can't do DragonCon I was hoping with the Southwest sale I could make it work but there's other priorities that's okay PAX East 2013 we got to get the Club VOG suite going
[SPEAKER_14]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Gabe Newell is talking out of his ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is the whole Windows 8 thing, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I have been running Windows 8 on one of my machines here and at work.
[SPEAKER_11]: All you have to do is turn off the new Metro user interface and you have the desktop back.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You mean to tell me...
[SPEAKER_11]: This portly man couldn't figure out how to push a button to flip it over to that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: And he's also complaining about Microsoft is having their own Windows Store.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, look, Apple has the App Store.
[SPEAKER_11]: Linux distros have their own different stores.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's open competition.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's fair gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, everybody has a choice.
[SPEAKER_11]: He just needs to roll with the punches.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you're saying deal with it, sunglasses falling.
[SPEAKER_14]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're damn right.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, Ranma, I got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: We got to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all I need to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: You want to plug your show?
[SPEAKER_11]: Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_11]: This week will be our Otakon 2012 Con Report, and it's going to be quite a good one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tuesday's on VOG.
[SPEAKER_14]: When are you guys going live?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that still happening?
[SPEAKER_11]: I gotta do some upgrades on my machines and I gotta do a run of tests then we'll go live.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm hoping by the end of September because there's a lot of stuff I'm working on coming down the pipe and you know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Make it happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: Crack whip.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm hustling.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: You too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stay fabulous.
[SPEAKER_14]: Always.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Super sorry if you didn't get through, but you can always leave us a voicemail or you can send us an email, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com or join us in chat, get your thoughts out there or send us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to try and read some tweets right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: What do I do with my iPad?
[SPEAKER_14]: While I get my iPad, let me check in with Loki and see if there's any last minute stories from Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: This whole lawsuit between Guitar Hero or I should say Activision and Gwen Stefani is still going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, what's the latest on that?
[SPEAKER_02]: They still want to sue them.
[SPEAKER_14]: The latest is No Doubt has a new single out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so apparently they are, I guess...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're still wanting to file a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, ideally they would like Activision to apologize and promise to never mistreat artists in the manner that they have been mistreated, no doubt, and countless others.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like I don't care anymore because Guitar Hero, it's not coming out anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: And I do remember reading about this.
[SPEAKER_14]: The World of Warcraft movie, apparently it's still happening.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sam Raimi's not involved anymore, but there is a new scribe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Charles Leavitt is the new scribe of the World of Warcraft movie.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is the dude who wrote The Seventh Son.
[SPEAKER_14]: What else did he do?
[SPEAKER_14]: Blood Diamond... Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_14]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, yeah, he did do the latest script.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, so The Seventh Son is the latest movie that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry, I read these live.
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't read this article in advance before it was tweeted to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Warner Brothers is putting out that Seventh Son pick on October 18, 2013.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other movies he's written, Blood Diamond, The Mighty, and K-Pax.
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't seen any of those movies, but Blood Diamond was Oscar nominated, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it was Oscar nominated for performance, not for script.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't K-Pax the one with Kevin Spacey?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I did see that one.
[SPEAKER_14]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was it well written?
[SPEAKER_14]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I think it was well written.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we don't know any details outside of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, they do say Legendary also has the Mass Effect film in development.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is still a thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that has been kind of reaffirmed.
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: The Mass Effect film.
[SPEAKER_14]: No way!
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, they're doing a Mass Effect film.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was just talking about this earlier.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's supposed to be based off the first game, but I'm... It needs to be Chick Shepard.
[SPEAKER_14]: you know what everybody's saying it's going to be Dude Shepard and I don't know if they made that announcement officially but I play a Dude Shepard in Mass Effect but for real I actually totally agree with you I think the only way they're going to make the fans all of them happy is to do Fem Shep in the movie and I think it would be totally acceptable but at that point it's all about the casting if they don't cast the right person as Fem Shep and I don't know who it could be
[SPEAKER_14]: Kim Kardashian No, no, and more no
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, I got to pull this one up on the computer because Tigerclaw sent us another link, but it's to a video.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it did kind of crack me up.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually saw this earlier.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think he or somebody else posted it on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's a guy getting a question wrong on who wants to be a millionaire that you think everybody would know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, apologies.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is somebody shooting at their TV.
[SPEAKER_14]: So he's going for the $7,000 question.
[SPEAKER_09]: So everybody here knows that one, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the Konami code.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the Capcom code?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's one of the answers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, let me see if she reads them here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bandai Code, Capcom Code, Konami Code Seriously, if you're going to do a YouTube shooting at your television, stop doing the dishes in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: It gets in the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they literally do A, B, C?
[SPEAKER_14]: And you can't figure out which... A was Atari Code, B was Bandai Code, C was Capcom Code, D was Konami Code.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gee, which one stands out?
[SPEAKER_14]: Derp Derp Code, well...
[SPEAKER_09]: so he used his lifeline called jump the question which essentially allows him to skip it
[SPEAKER_14]: There it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, Konami Code on TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the Jump the Question lifeline now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Man, I haven't watched that in a long time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, they got rid of the hot seat.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's standing now.
[SPEAKER_14]: The game's all played standing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, who wants to be a millionaire?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like a totally different show.
[SPEAKER_14]: But Meredith Vieira's still there.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the only thing she hosts now.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: one more tweet from Osfer sent us a tweet hi guys I'd listen live but I'm going on Space Mountain instead he's at Disney World right now you butt so Osfer you know you're a great guy I like you but fuck you love OLR that's gonna do it for tweets that's gonna do it for phone calls that does it for last minute stories
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, and that does it for the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: But not before we get around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_14]: Before I do that, I do want to say one more time, thank you all for listening to Orange Lounge Radio and spending your Sunday evening with us or your work day or whenever you're listening to this podcast, your commute or what have you.
[SPEAKER_14]: We really appreciate you supporting the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do remember...
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we hope you enjoyed the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: And come listen live sometime Sunday night at VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bradley, I want to thank you very much for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope you enjoyed your first show back in a while.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't be a stranger, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have any final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anything you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you think about that, and next time you come back with something to plug...
[SPEAKER_02]: and have a good road trip whatever you go on next time all right um Loki we'll go to you next your final thought tonight I really don't like Jason Steele what he's done with the film cow channel I mean just do another Charlie the Unicorn not stop trying to like kick start these new like series like hit it with a car or you know the horseman or something it's just not funny
[SPEAKER_14]: My final thought tonight is I smell dinner and it smells good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you, Alan.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got a yay.
[SPEAKER_14]: And naming your WoW characters after Mass Effect characters, it's the hip thing to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means that I need to make Shakarian.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, and DarkSakura, is that your final thought or do you have another one for us?
[SPEAKER_14]: Garrus.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you guys once again for tuning in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: We will be back next week to do it all again.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hear we have a special guest again next week.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think I can say Jason's gonna be back next week.
[SPEAKER_14]: He hasn't been here in a couple months so we're gonna have him back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_14]: More news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really curious to see what develops on Twitter with Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: and Ernest Cline.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm very excited to see what becomes of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe this whole nightmare will be over in a week's time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody will break that score.
[SPEAKER_02]: All they have to do is just drop that game off the list of eligible games and we'll be all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be just ridiculously hard challenge instead of ridiculously unfair hard challenge.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, if you're listening live at the VOG Network, please stay tuned for the Mars Curiosity Landing Special.
[SPEAKER_14]: Get a little bit of science fiction real life in your evening.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's science reality.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, science reality.
[SPEAKER_05]: You said science fiction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Science non-fiction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Science stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bill and I would be proud.
[SPEAKER_14]: Be blinded with science by Travis Donovan up next.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: We will see you next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!