Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loku
Tonight, August 26th, 2012
More unfortunate layoffs hit the industry
A company requests its game be pulled from store shelves
And are 90% of PC game installs pirated copies?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
And welcome back to another week of the show
Where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio
Live as we are every Sunday night
At the Voice of Geeks Network
vognetwork.com
Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
That's where you can participate with our show
In the chat room
And if you are listening live at VOG Network tonight
Check out our chat room
Live.vognetwork.com
This is episode number 471
For this August 26th, 2012
My name is Rob Roberts
And I'll be joining you over the next few hours
To talk about what is going on with the game industry
With my friends
Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you?
I feel vaguely fit
You feel fit?
Vaguely
You feel pretty and witty and...
Hey
Well I don't know, everyone a little gay
That's good, it's good to feel healthy
Cause I've had days where I feel healthy
And I've had days where I feel fat
You know, and sometimes a fat day is good too
Once in a while, but healthy is a good feeling too
Well it was just like
My intention is to walk a few days each week
And I decided to go walking
But I don't know if I've said it on the show before
But I wear Vibram Five Fingers
Which are like the toe shoes
You wear the glove shoes
They're awesome
You make your feet look like hands
They're creepy
Well but it makes your feet walk how you're supposed to walk
It makes you look like Spiderman
Well it's how people are supposed to walk is the thing
Is that our, not to go too deep into it
But our modern tennis shoes
Have changed the way people walk for the worse
You know, that's where a lot of injuries come about
And I'm really getting back to the barefoot walking thing
Like hands, they're...
Sorry, sorry for the echo
And I really love them
But it makes me think more and more that
Humanity is not meant to walk on concrete
Concrete is terrible, terrible, terrible stuff
And so my feet did not hurt until I walked on concrete
When I walked on the grass, no more hurt
But it was a good walk
It was a good walk
I got outside
Outside
Going outside is good
Everybody should put down the controller or the keyboard
And go outside once in a while
However
What?
I was listening to the Mass Effect soundtrack
That's how you can make your worlds collide
There you go
Alright, by the way, I apologize
One of the perks about listening live to Orange Launch Radio
Is that you can check into the show live
The check-ins are now up
I forgot to do that because I was sidetracked
During the pre-show
And I literally sat down seconds before
I picked up the microphone and went live
So the check-ins are now up
There you go
For those of you listening on the podcast
You can also check in
Just listen for a little noise
The little victory sound
And then it'll tell you the passphrase
It is somewhere in the show
We have to make sure you're listening to it
So it's somewhere different in the show every week
Anyhow, also say hello to
What?
Damn it, that song is in my head now
The song from An American Tail
That's somewhere out there
Is that what the check-in noise sounds like?
No, when you said somewhere
I was like
That song is stuck in my head
I haven't thought of that song in years
Damn it, Rob
I'm sorry
I don't know what to tell you
I was gonna play this really quick here
If I can find it here
I don't know if you've heard this, Darkstalker
I know you don't listen really back to the podcast
Because you're on it
So you don't have to
But this is a little noise
Now, this is not the actual noise
But this is it
Isn't that kind of catchy, right?
Yeah
Now that's gonna get stuck in your head right there
That's a little Bobby Black Wolf original right there
Um, it's like, I have an idea
Okay
Let's introduce Loki
Techmaster Loki is here tonight too
Hi
How are you doing, Loki?
I'm full now
You're full?
Yeah, because I
Full of rage
I know
I bought one of the Memphis barbecue burgers over at Carl's Jr. Hardee's
That is drenched in barbecue sauce
I normally get the single
And the single is normally enough
I haven't eaten really today
So I was like, okay, I'll go with the $6 burger
I really should have just stuck with the single
The single is enough
But it's delicious
And what makes it delicious is the fact that it combines
Not only a cheeseburger, but pulled pork
So you've got barbecued pulled pork
And a cheeseburger with more barbecue sauce on it
And onion rings
It's fantastic
Delicious
I like their Western burger
Western bacon or whatever
Yeah, that's not really what I get
But remember we just had this discussion about healthy days
And fat days
If I have one of those, I'm definitely having a fat day
Because they are not good for you
That's how I discovered it
Because I normally don't go to Carl's Jr. that much
Because it's further away from my work than normal
The other fast food places
So I was like, I'm tired of eating McDonald's or Burger King
I'm just going to go to Carl's Jr. today
And so I went there to get the Double Western
And I saw that they had this burger
I'm like, hey, I like pulled pork
I'm going to get a single
Because I'm not that hungry
And it was delicious
You know, I swear I don't have delusions or anything
That our show is that big in the scope of things
We don't have a whole ton of ton of listeners
Though we do love the family we have
That comes participates with us live in the podcast
But it would be great if somebody deemed our audience
Large enough to get a food sponsorship
With as much as we talk up the different foods
We need to start censoring all the food titles
We're going to go get yogurt after the show at
No, instead what you do is
Instead of doing the beep
You add like a sound file that says nom
So every time you talk about
Yeah, I totally had that burger at nom nom nom nom
Get the little kitty nom nom nom
Yeah, but then you're talking about editing
That's why I like to do live radio
Because it doesn't involve editing
If you haven't noticed
I also like to do live radio
Because we have the chat room
At live.vognetwork.com
And Bobby, in reference to me playing the theme
A little bit before said
Now people are going to think that the check-ins
Are happening that early
Well, gotcha
I just want to make sure everybody was paying attention
So like the people that just
The people that are kind of just doing data entry
In the background and zoning out and all that
Now that I have your attention
Watermelons
Anyway, let's see, also
What are the other comments in chat
Oh, Tigerclaw said you can use that sound
When there's breaking news
But then we can't jack the NBC breaking news theme
Which is so epic
It is epic
You know, as much as people hate NBC
After the Olympics and all that crap
You have to admit
NBC gets some epic fucking music
For their presentations
Like, you know, the Olympic theme
That shit is epic
And I realize John Williams did that
Not some NBC dude
I played that in high school band
And didn't you feel epic?
We can start stealing
Especially since I played saxophone
And got the little
You know
We can start stealing the Game of Thrones theme
I mean, that's pretty epic too
Or like, you know
No chair of swords allowed
But the theme's awesome, okay
Separate from the whole
If you want awesome
We should just use the Xena theme
Yeah
No, that's if we want the show to have lesbian undertones
I have no problem with this
Maybe in a future week
How do you have lesbian undertones
When there's two men and a woman?
I'm not sure how that works
She's double lesbian
I like boobs too
You'll have to like your own boobs though
Unless we get some lady callers later
Which is always a distinct possibility
When we take live calls from our
Should I ask everyone about their boobs?
Do you want to have booby chat tonight with the callers?
No, thank you
I don't know if any of our women
Would call in to do booby chat
Well, Sil would totally do it
But the show's on too late for her
Because she's on the other side of the pond
And they're eight hours ahead of us
If you have to stay up anywhere in the UK
Really, no matter where you're at
Britain, Scotland, Ireland
I know we have listeners in all those places
And what time is the show live here?
I miss our Swede
2 AM
I miss our Swedes
Yeah, we had a couple folks in Sweden
I did see, I don't know if you've looked at email
But we do have an email from Belgium tonight
I love Belgium!
Me too
I love waffles
Such an ignorant statement
There is so much more to Belgium than just waffles
There is not, that is not an ignorant statement
I love waffles, okay?
It just reminded me
There's nothing, alright
Belgium also has wonderful chocolate
Alright, usually we do a kickoff topic at the start
Beer
Usually we do a kickoff topic at the start of the show
I actually don't have a whole lot tonight
Beer
What?
It should be beer
I want to ask this question
We have a long weekend next weekend
And it's very likely we probably won't end up doing OLR next weekend
We'll have to talk about that during the break tonight
But Bobby's not going to be here
DragonCon's going on next weekend
Because a lot of the cool kids at VOG Network
Like Travis and Brad from Pod Culture
And some of the dudes from Critical Myth and all them
They're all going to DragonCon
In Atlanta
That is going on
Penny Arcade Expo is also going on at the same time
And it's Labor Day weekend
So I don't know, we may take the weekend off to
You know, just chill
And sit around and play video games
And Pinkberry
And I'm wondering
I'm wondering if there's any video games
You really need to catch up on
That if we have a three day weekend
To just sit in your underwear on the couch
With a giant
What is that, how did Grandpa describe it on Horde House
The other show
I'm sitting there in my boxers in my big thing of Pinkberry
Just playing video games or whatever
What video games do you need to be catching up on right now
Because we're about to enter the holiday season
And a shit ton of new games
What games do you want to spend your Labor Day weekend
Catching up on
I propose to my husband of marathoning
Super Mario World
However, I also just proposed to Becky
Of marathoning Mass Effect 2 on Saturday
You do that anyway
No, I play Mass Effect 3 for me
Which means I have to finish it
Before we finish Mass Effect 2 for her
So that I can play through Mass Effect 3 while she watches
You know what would be fun, actually you should try this
Jamie is
Marathoning ROM hacks for Mario Brothers
That would be awesome
I would scream so much
Well not necessarily the ones that are insanely hard
But just the new ones
They have some really good ROM hacks
That and Link to the Past has some really good ROM hacks
I'm like
I kind of want to play those because it's different
It's like going into Link to the Past
For the first time again
And it's kind of cool, that sounds really cool to me
Except the whole thing is actually breaking out the systems
And playing
The other thing that we had, we actually just watched a whole
Dan and I watched a whole play through of Vampire Killer on MSX
Which came out after the Castlevania that we got on the NES
But it sort of inspired me to want to actually play through Dracula X again
It sort of sounded like a classic gaming weekend
Sounds like fun
Plus Mass Effect
Maybe it would also be a fun weekend to go out to the flea markets around
And try to find some more classic games
Let's do it
And then
If it's not 105
No and then
And then
Farmers Market
No and then
Mexican Candy
Loki got it
Dude, where's my car?
Loki
What do you need to catch up on over the long weekend?
Honestly, what I've been trying to do is stop doing modding stuff
Because I have people that ask me for Grand Theft Auto mod stuff
They're like, I can't port my map mods over, can you do it for me?
I'm like, so waste a whole fucking week doing that shit
And it just gets so tiring
Because I'm like, I don't want to do this
But yet for some stupid reason they keep saying yes, I'll do it for you
So I'd like to just not do that and actually play games
But at the same time, I don't really know what games I'd want to play
I want to play Minecraft on 360 with other people
But there's no one on
There's a way to burn an entire weekend
Seriously, but there's nobody to play with
That's the thing
Although I do have one of the people that's on my friends list
He keeps wanting to play, but it's always when I'm on break at work
I'm like, dude, I can't play with you right now
Because I'm going to have like five minutes and that's it
Because I'll be on my 360 during break
But there's no one to play with
I really wish that Minecraft on the 360
Had an option to randomly connect you to a server
That has, okay, allow strangers to connect
Or something like that
Or have that option where I can allow strangers to connect to my server
Granted, you run the risk of someone going through and griefing and stuff
But you can always ban them
And I would just kind of like that
So I'd be able to play with random people
And actually get a multiplayer game going
It's kind of boring with just one or two people
Because we've been playing, we actually started yet another world
And we actually picked the tutorial world this time
Which is kind of fun
Because it made it a little more interesting
Because there's actual things built in, little hidden things to find
And you can, you know, you didn't have to worry about right away
Okay, I need to find stuff to make sticky pistons
Oh, I'll just steal some out of the stuff that's already built
Which is kind of cool
Or hey, you know, I need to go find some diamonds
So they can make some diamond armor and stuff
Oh wait, I know where the hidden thing is
Where there's some diamond stuff
So that's kind of cool
Or I'm gonna need some wood
So I'm gonna just tear down this house instead of those already built
And so that was kind of fun
For a little bit
And then it got boring again
And that's the problem
It's just, it's so far behind
The PC version that it's kind of boring
Whereas like I'm reading about like the cool PC stuff that they're adding now
And like the kind of snapshots for each week
And it sounds pretty awesome
Like they're adding all this new stuff
Like new monsters that look really fucking hard to kill
I mean that would be really cool in the 360 version
But it's just not there
So I guess I have to start playing the PC version since I bought it
That would be kind of fun
Maybe I should do that
But once again, I need people to play with
And, you know, I don't want to play with random strangers
Are you upset that I haven't been signing onto Xbox lately?
Is that what this is all about?
Well just everybody
No one is
I mean like seriously, I can't
I launch Minecraft almost every single day
There's no one on, ever
So
That reminds me of WoW
But yeah, I mean like that
That's going to start picking up real soon though with the expansion
I mean if I want to go
I'm not really trying to get into any games right now
Like any, start anything new
Because Borderlands 2 is coming out
And I know that's going to be, you know, big time drain right there
That'll probably be the one game I play
Until Call of Duty Black Ops 2 I think
Let's go to some comments from our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
SSJ100Matt says
I know what Loki can do during the break
Update the OLR PSP site
That's not going to happen
But much like, so much like
It's time to start on the PSV
OLRPSV.com that doesn't exist yet
But
I don't want to do that
I know
No one cares anymore
OLR3DS.com not happening
No
OLRWEU.com
See the problem is
I mean now all these things have web browsers
And hopefully they all support HTML5
And so that's not even an issue anymore
You can just go to our site
At vognetwork.com and
Just listen
Without having to, you know
One thing we do need to look into doing
Though at some point is
Remaking the OLR.com site
Because now we kind of have
A lot of our forum resources
And community resources are pouring in
Trying to pool together with the other shows
To make vognetwork.com bigger
OLR.com was probably more about us
And our history and our shows and so forth
So it would be fun to have something for that
You know
It would, to me, I mean
I think it would be kind of cool like how we
Had on the all games
While back where it was just
A section of the website, it's like okay
Here's the Orange Launch Radio section, like there's a section
For each show and just have it linked to that
And just, you know, make something cool there
On our own site, on VoG
So we don't have to like, because we have
Forums already, you know, the forums
And the Orange Launch site are kind of dead
I mean we can just
They're technically supposed to be closed by now
Because we're going to fold them into the VoG network
So that's what I'm saying, it's like
Just kind of erase the site
And just, because we were already kind of
Doing everything that we were doing on that site
Anyways, on VoG
So just kind of move it over
If you have ideas, we'd love to hear a mailbag
At orangelaungeradio.com
And some of the folks in chat room were talking about apps
And so forth
I have to learn how to program
As soon as I learn how to make apps, I know somebody
That makes apps, but they have other priorities
I almost
Signed up for
Another Kickstarter that had
A thing on how to make apps
And it looked really cool, but I'm like
Am I really going to sit here and do this?
You're addicted to Kickstarter
Alright, let me get some other answers here
That one took us on a tangent
How about Locopoco, which I love that name
Because it's like Locoroco's cousin
Locopoco says, I need to catch up on
Folklore, Resonance of Fate
And Valkyria Chronicles, those are all excellent choices
Valkyria Chronicles is one of my
Personal ones too, we've had that on PS3
I don't know how long, and I've yet to make a lot of progress
In that game, but it's really fun
Tigerclaw says, in reality
Sky just wants to go to Disneyland again
LOL, in regards to the week off
A, if I was going to Disneyland, I would not
Do it on Labor Day weekend, because that would be a mad house
B, I was actually
Supposed to be there tonight, I was originally
Planning a trip that would have had
Alan and I there, well we would have been driving
Tonight, I would have not been at the show
Tonight, been there Monday, Tuesday, but
We had to cancel that
Rob, not and I, and me
It's an object
No one Kern, alright
Moving on
Let's see, oh, and lastly
In reference to the mental image
I put in all your heads earlier
VxjasonxV in our chat room says
Oh, and now that underwear is involved
Video live stream
Y'all are perverts
I would love to do a live stream
Not of that, of the games
It's technology
Well, I do want to do
Live streaming stuff, I have
About two or three
Capture cards, capture devices
Set that crap up over here, we can do that
It's just, it's a little bit
More complicated, like I always watch
The playthroughs like
Freddy Wong, they've been doing
They've been doing a land game
On PC, Minecraft, and it looks so much
Fun, playing with other people
It's just like, okay, everybody gets one life
And we're just gonna work together
And we're gonna do this stuff and then they just kind of
Film it and edit it together and it looks fun
I'm like, I just want to do that
I want to play with those people
I did not, you got me sidetracked
Though, because in reference to the
Comment that Jason made, now that underwear
Is involved, video live stream, I
Had the chance to play my favorite Tyra Banks
Clip that I haven't played on the show in years
You know, that's gonna be my Labor Day
Weekend right there, panty party
You know, my wife, ever since
The passing of Whitney Houston has kind of
Latched on to Tyra Banks instead
I've noticed
Kind of like
Kind of observing the
Train wreck that's happening, cause you know
Whitney Houston, well she used to like
Watching Whitney Houston's Facebook page
Because there's a lot of stupid people that comment on there
But Tyra's page
Tyra comments on
Post a lot of really stupid things
And it's funny
I mean, this has absolutely nothing to do with
Video games, but this is kind of a game
In itself, and it has to do with Facebook
Which is, you know, big for gaming, right?
This is hilarious
Go to various fast food
And chain restaurants
And just go to the thing that lets you see
What everybody's posting on there
And I'm not even talking like the controversial shit
Like Chick-fil-A, like go on
Facebook and look up like the Olive Gardens
Page, Red Lobster
Applebee's
You will see some amazing
Shit that people post on those
Pages, everywhere from
Complaints about a particular restaurant
To, you know, somebody
Making a post like
So-and-so just took me here to Applebee's
For my anniversary, I'm so excited
There's a picture of them smiling like
Cause people don't understand privacy
Controls
That just makes me think of a line from one of my favorite
Comics, Henry Cho, who's not related
To Margaret Cho, although he is Korean
Born in Tennessee
Saying, talking about his
Brother-in-law from Arab
Alabama
Good times
We just got a new Italian restaurant
It ain't no Olive Garden
I can't help but be reminded
Of that 86 year old
Lady or whatever that reviewed restaurants
For the local paper and she wrote that huge review
About the Olive Garden
I don't know where that, she was like in Montana
Or maybe Wisconsin, one of those northern states
And was writing about the local Olive Garden
That shit was hilarious
With the buttery breadsticks
Alright, alright, quickly
My weekend, my plans
For the weekend, I think it would be really fun
To do an epic Civ 5
Match that goes all weekend
Long, but I don't know if I can find
Any other suckers that would buy into that
And there's someone who plays on Xbox, but I don't think he plays online
Yeah, but that's
The Xbox one is different, cause that's the Civ
Revolution and those games can go a lot faster
You can do one of those in a night, but I'm talking like
Civilization 5 epic mode
Although that would, that game would take
Like months to finish, but you could even
Do just even a normal game
Takes forever in Civilization 5
That would be fun
DayZ would be fun too, once, like
I guess that's going back to games
That would be fun to do like a live stream of
Actually, live streaming PC games might
Well, that might be, it's still difficult
But yeah, DayZ would be fun
Hey, oh my god, zombies
Here we go
Crazy person
The other game I really need to catch up on is
Borderlands
But let's be real
There's so much happening on Tuesday between
The official launch of Guild Wars 2
The patch in Warcraft
Rock Band Blitz
Mass Effect 3 DLC
There's no way I'm playing catch up over the weekend
Cause I have to play everything that came out on Tuesday
That's the problem
You don't really need to play through Borderlands 1 anyways
Because they just kinda, all they have
The characters have cameos
And that's about it, but
I just wanna play it cause I was having fun with it
And I just stopped because of my MMOs
And other games I was playing
Oh yeah, Alan has it too
There you go
Bobby's the one to play too
There we go, the foursome
Alright, let's talk about our actual gaming weeks
The stuff we have been playing this week
More current stuff, yeah
Can I say one more thing about the week in general
Of course
I did a good deed this weekend
We rescued a kitten from the dumpster
Outside my synagogue
Now, before people start crying
You found out nobody left the cat in the dumpster
He was feral
Little faith in humanity restored
Yeah, he was feral
He fell in looking for food
I sat him in my lap, he clawed the crap out of me
And then calmed down
Got him some water, got him some food
A nice lady downtown
He was taken care of by a lady downtown
And he's going to Animal Outreach
On Monday
Where they're gonna get him shot
Tested for leukemia
Fixed and adopted out
So I just wanted to say for anyone who's asked
The kitty's story has a happy ending
Yay, meow meow
His official name is Donut
They've called him Donut
Instead of Batcat
That's a good name, I like Donut
I'm just glad I don't have those cats in our backyard anymore
11 cats at one time
All I know is I got a text message from Dark Soccer
On Friday night, do you want a kitten?
And I'm like, um
We have a tiny ass apartment and two cats already
I would love
to, but no
Yeah, Shermy would be too old for me to have a little feral kitten in the house
To tame
He's only six weeks old, so he's tammable
Alright, before we get into our regular gaming weeks
And what we have been playing
I do want to talk to the chatters
WhatupG leaves a comment about Tuesday
Saying Sky forgot the biggest
game release, Madden 13
Although certainly I will acknowledge
That will be a huge game release
And lots of people are going to be playing that over the Labor Day weekend
My household won't be one of them
Cause we just, that's not really a series
We've ever gotten into
I'm not a big football person
And if you're not a fan of that, and for whatever reason you just
Don't download games off the Playstation
There's a Journey collector's edition coming out this week
On disc
It's got the soundtrack, you get Journey
Flower of Flow
And also two
Little quick games that they made
And a month of Playstation Plus
That's a great deal if
You don't have any of those games
Cause all three of those games are great
Well, I don't even know if you could call
Flow a game, but whatever
It's alright
They're neat, but Journey is
Amazing
Contender for game of the year to be honest
Alright, not that Journey
It's a Journey 2012 Journey
That might make it a little bit better if it had Journey music in there
But their music was pretty good
Little mishmash, I'm sure somebody's done that on YouTube
Journey set to Journey? I've seen it
But the music in Journey 2012
Is legitimately really good
Like, as much as I love Journey
1980's
You can't do that
To Journey 2012
The music in Journey 2012 is so flippin' good
Can we get a Journey 2012
2 where it's basically
The premise of Revolution X
But with Journey
Instead, you know
Wouldn't that be kinda cool?
Dude on the toilet at the beginning of the game
If Steve Perry was talking to any of the others
Whatsoever, maybe
Although, well, the guy they have now
The guy they have now, number one, is hot
Number two, has really nice hair
And number three, can sing
Don't get me wrong, he's really good
And he can sing, and yes, I have seen Journey live recently
When he was the front man, they were really good
I know, but
I mean, I don't know
There's something about, you can't put a Journey
80's sequel in arcades
And not have Steve Perry involved
I don't know, it just would feel weird
Maybe it's Steve Perry being like
The bad guy
He's the super villain trying to get revenge on the band
It's like new Journey albums
Quick, name a Journey single after
The 1980's
Yep, yeah
That's what I thought, alright
Anyhow, your gaming week
What have you been playing this week, Dark Soccer?
Uh, WoW
Mass Effect 2, Mass Effect 3
Um, the Mass Effect thingy
On my phone, since I'm trying to get my rating back up
Um, and
Uh, yeah
That's really good
Same old stuff for you
That's not bad, I mean, it's not like you're playing bad games
And watching a lot of playthroughs
Okay
Like, Dan and I had our big Castlevania fit
The other day
But you guys like to do that, you like to go on YouTube
And watch all the playthroughs, like that's something you guys do
Dan likes to do that
Every so often I'll just get invested and watch
Do you ever do the live stuff?
Do you guys ever go onto one of those sites like Ustream
Or Twitch.tv or whatever other sites
There are and watch the live stream?
Nah
But that's because you and the hubby are more classic gamers
More than anything, yeah
I mean, I wouldn't mind doing like a
Episodic playthrough of something
But, you know
I like watching other people do it
Except it kind of bugs me because, I mean, it is
Truly what an almost perfect playthrough
Looks like because they're usually, um
Machine assisted, you know
Tigerclaw wants to know if you're going to get the Mass Effect 3
Leviathan DLC
Fuck yes
As if that should surprise anybody whatsoever
I am so excited, you guys
That's why I kind of don't want to beat my game yet
You finally set foot in multiplayer
Not that long ago
And I couldn't find anybody else on
Because no one would let me know when they were playing
We need to make that happen again
Well, for me, I have to change out my EXE
Because I have a hacked EXE so I can play in god mode
But I saved my original file
So that I can switch out for multiplayer
Tigerclaw, I just want to give a plug
There's a lot of classic games played on Twitch.tv
There are people doing speedruns on old Mario games
That's cool
I just don't like to watch it live, I guess
Unless it's for charity
Okay, like Mario Marathon you're down with
That's understandable
And even then I'm like, dude, you're still playing Sunshine, why?
I like Sunshine
Wait a minute, didn't you say Sunshine was a good game on last week's show?
I like Sunshine, but it's kind of boring to watch it
Like
Even as much as I love Mario 64
It's kind of boring to watch it
Understandable
Alright, Loki, how about you?
How was your gaming week?
This week I played lots of Minecraft
Mainly
Little bit of Grand Theft Auto because I was
Working on mods
And stuff
But yeah
Going back to Minecraft though
We started a new map
That's a tutorial level, which is kind of fun
I had to start off on that
And then played through a little bit of that
And I actually went back last night
To my VoG map
And was working a little bit more in peaceful mode too
I was finishing up some minecart stations
They make the little
Bell
Intro thing when they
Stop and then it waits like
Five seconds or so and then it makes that noise
Again and then goes automatically
Have you figured out what worlds you should be playing on
To get the awesome
Stuff? Like, I'm sure people out there
Post on forums like
Oh, use this seed, it's the best or something like that
There's all sorts of seeds
For different things, but it
Doesn't really matter
The only kind of unique thing there on some of the seeds
There are like
Landscape I guess
And then there's a few that have like the golden apples
Hidden in there and chests and stuff
But it's just
That's pretty much it
If you restart your levels
Or start new seeds now, there's clay
Which I never used anyway
So it's not a big deal
And then
You know, slimes, I guess slime farms
Are kind of important now that they're sticky
Pistons and that kind of thing
But I don't know
I haven't really bothered to
You know, find those
Usually I just try to find some interesting
Looking
Landscape and stuff
But even now it's just kind of
It's kind of boring going back to that stuff
Just waiting for the next update
The adventure update I think is going to make it a lot more fun
But we'll have to see
So anyways, Minecraft stuff
And then I actually played
A little bit of new stuff
I played more Sleeping Dogs again
For some reason my save
Like I had done a bunch of missions
And my save just didn't save or something
I must have forgotten the save
Or it didn't auto save or whatever
And so I'm having to redo a bunch of missions
So I did that
Today and then
One new game I actually picked up
I picked up
What was it? Scott Pilgrim vs. The World
I don't know why they picked that up at launch
It was fucking amazing
Yeah, I thought you had bought that at launch
So I finally got around to playing it
My only gripe about it
And this is just kind of a weird thing
Is that the stages are too long
Like I'm trying to fit in
Playing a stage with my friend at work
And we tried our 15 minute breaks
There's just no way to beat the first stage in 15 minutes
So we tried during lunch
Where we had an hour
And it actually
Got to the boss and that was about it
But we didn't get to beat it because we ran out of time
So the stages are a little long
In my game, since it's more like an arcade game
But
It's really awesome
The animation is amazing
I love the way it looks and sounds
It's just a really fantastic game
Really cool, recommend checking it out
Kind of disappointed the stages are so long
Because it does make it hard to play on break
And then beyond that
I think that's all I've played this week
Yeah
Alrighty
Oh, how's your little con...
I know this will be over by the time
The podcast hits, but for the live folks
That contest thing you're doing, how's that going?
As of right now I'm in the first place
And what that means is
Assuming I win, which I'm probably going to
Unless this one chick gets
A couple more retweets
I'm going to have them
Draw me a picture
Of myself dressed as Tingle
That is going to be the closest you'll get
That's still pretty awesome
And she's a pretty awesome artist
So expect that
An OLR in-joke will finally
Come to an end, although we all know
It's not going to come to an end whatsoever
However, it will finally reach the next step
Some resolution, yes
If you can get
Because you don't want to just win
You want to win big
And we want Footy's Kickstarter to do well
It's really
I guess it's really
About that
That's really it
They're doing okay
But I'm kind of worried that they may not
Hit their goal
They're just under $6,000
Of $10,000
They've got 11 days left
Sometimes those last few days are the biggest
I think they can do it
It looks like a pretty cool game
They're not asking for too much
If you want to check it out
It's Evilot
It's E-V-I-L-O-T
The game looks a little similar to
Zombies with
What was that?
I'm trying to remember the original name of the game
It was like, Hey Bad Man
Why?
It was a game on PSP
It was like where you play the villain basically
So it looks cool
It should be neat
Alright, Mike Gaming Week
Kind of like Dark Soccer
I played a lot of the same stuff that you're used to hearing me talk about
Like World of Warcraft
And was continuing to play
Sound Shapes
I don't know why the name escaped me for a minute
I was playing more Sound Shapes
I was playing Mario 2 still
However, there is one new game I spent
A pretty good chunk of time playing
It technically started on Friday
It's Guild Wars 2
I have spent some time playing
I didn't get to play a lot a lot
Because I was in San Francisco this weekend
Hanging out with Grandpa from Horde House
But on Friday night
And a little bit today
I'm at Guild Wars 2
I'm up to about level 10
So I'm not sure I've really had
A full amount of time to really flesh out
What I think about this game
A lot of the things that were bugging me about it
At first, I'm easing up on a little bit
And it all has to do with
You know, the Guild Wars 2 model
Because you know the pricing model is a lot different
For Guild Wars 2
You pay the one fee to get the game
And then you never have to pay
Like a monthly fee or anything again
Like no monthly fee
But now they're adding a little more of the free to play
Elements in it
Like you can go into the online shop
And buy like sunglasses for your character
You know, dumb little things
But there are some
Like basically steroids
Performance enhancing things you can get
Like you know, short time XP bonuses
And things like that you can kind of get in the shop
With real money
One of the things that started to irritate me
Is that I got a chest that dropped
And the key I needed to open it
Was something to buy in the store
And I was like, oh that's bullshit
That's such bullshit that you
You know, I was going to rage because that's a Facebook game
But then finally, I don't know if I got it as a quest reward
I think I got it as a quest reward around level 10
I did get one of those keys
So it doesn't bug me nearly as much
If you can get it in the game by doing a lot of grinding
You know, either you're going to be free to play
Or you're going to be
You know, not free to play
I still think Guild Wars 2
Despite that bitch
Is relatively minor bitch
I'm really impressed with a lot of what I've seen so far
Graphically, it's
It's really nice
It's a wonderfully presented game
You know, there's always
That temptation to compare MMOs
To World of Warcraft, but this game
Doesn't really feel like World of Warcraft
And I think one big reason
For that is they've managed
To figure out a new way to do quests
There are no yellow exclamation marks
Over people's heads
And it's not like the Final Fantasy XI style
Questing either
Basically what happens is that
You have this giant map
And I gotta say
There's a little thing I love about this game
And that is when you go to the map
The way the map appears is your camera
Actually pans down
And does like
It does a subtle transition to the actual map
But it makes it look like
You're on Google Maps
And then it zooms back in to show your character
The way it does that transition
It's one of those little things
That really makes you go
That's so cool
And then Shane found out you could draw on the map
Like it's a Madden thing
You could draw the plays on the map
Anyhow, questing
So you go on the map and you'll find these little scouts
And the scouts will tell you these things
So and so is in trouble and needs help
This person is having to deal with this conflict
Going on right now and could use some help
This person is near the cave and da da da
So the scouts will tell you where these people are
And then they draw the little hearts on your map
And you go over to the hearts
And then when you're in that general area
The game will tell you either kill these things
Collect these things
You know, kind of the general MMO stuff
But you get to pick what you want to do
Do you want to kill? Do you want to collect? What do you want to do?
And as you do those, you start to gain
It's like mini reputation grinds
Little mini reputation grinds
They don't take you any more than like 30 minutes
And then the person, the heart fills in
And that person will start selling you gear and stuff
And you've basically completed the quest
And you get like gold and XP
And the typical things
Now generally in these areas as well
Somebody could start an event quest
And the event quest is like the public questing
Which a lot of MMOs besides WoW have in them
And even WoW is getting it to some extent
With the scenarios in Pandaria
But like Warhammer
Was a game that did this very well
Was the whole public questing
And I gotta say with the Guild Wars launch going on
I mean it was crazy, like in the starter area
It would be like so and so needs help
Eradicating the mosquitoes from the village
Because you know it's like a level 2 quest or whatever
And then suddenly like a big orange circle appears on your map
And all these mosquitoes are everywhere
There's like 75 people everywhere
Killing mosquitoes and you just watch the bar go
And it like fills right up
And then you get a medal based on your contribution
And the medal gives you experience, gold, and karma points
And karma points you turn around and use to buy gear
So I gotta say
I love that they've really challenged themselves to think outside the box
And not make a clone of the successful formula
But as MMO fans
What do we think MMOs ought to offer?
And it really does feel like in that regard
Guild Wars 2 is taking MMOs to the next level
I really think that
I think it's giving a lot of
I don't want to turn into a Guild Wars 2 vs. WoW thing
I love WoW, I can't say
Oh Guild Wars 2 is going to kick its ass, whatever
And I totally disagree with people that are like
Oh WoW is dead
Oh WoW is so dead
The panda people is stupid
It's a little kid and Guild Wars is going to kill it
I've been saying every game is going to kill WoW
WoW will continue to exist
But I gotta say Guild Wars 2
Really brings something else to the table with that
And one other little thing about Guild Wars 2
That I love
They brought vista points into the game
Which I remember from a racing game called Fuel
From a couple years ago
You remember that game Fuel?
You remember how there would be places on the map
You would drive to that it's just a really gorgeous view
And you got points for that
And I think Assassin's Creed does something like this too
At least somebody was joking with me
And I haven't played that series a lot
But basically you go to these points on the map
And you might have to interact with the environment a little
Like you'll have to find the little mushrooms
You have to jump up to get to the top of the building
And then once you get up there they'll be a little book
And you press the button
And all of a sudden you'll go to a cutscene
Where the camera will do this gorgeous pan
And show you everything around you
And then 60 XP for finding the vista point
And it's marked on your map
I thought that was so awesome
Like it's something else to do that's not
Grinding a dungeon or whatever
It's just neat
There's a lot about Guild Wars 2 that's just different
It sounds like they could have it
Like you know there's people that kind of
Challenge themselves to play like a pacifist
That you could probably level up
You don't get enough XP
However, yeah the passive
Because you could go to these areas where they're like
Because to help all the people
You can
Collect kumquats or whatever
And turn them in or you can collect things
And turn them in usually
I think a pacifist, and you get XP from gathering too
So I think a pacifist could do very well
In Guild Wars 2
To be honest
Although I honestly haven't played the game enough
I haven't played it past level 10
So I can't give you like a full full review
But I, despite some of my minor bitches
About what the free to play
Traditional free to play mechanic is doing
To the game
Despite my minor bitches there
I really love some of the stuff they are trying to do
A couple other quick things
I want to say about Guild Wars 2
We will move on with the show
But this is the new game
A lot of people are going to be talking about this game
PvP
If you elect to do PvP
Which you don't have to do
But you go into your character and you hit the PvP button
And you basically get transported
To a whole new PvP world
Where your character is suddenly max level
And you're automatically a template
And you can pick whatever skills
And your PvP gear is separate
You separated the PvP game
From the PvE game
But you get to have your same character
And when you design your character
You get to pick your favorite colors on the garb
And all that stuff
So it's like you still have a sense of character
But it's like a completely separate copy
Of that character in PvP
And if you never want to touch PvP ever ever
You don't have to, it's like a separate little thing
And character design is great
Because they kind of do a little bit of the mass effect
Thing with it
Where you pick like
Did your character in their vision
See a snow leopard, a stag
And you make those types of decisions
That ultimately affect your story
I think my character saw a white stag
And that has been a big part of the story
I've been playing so far
So they have definitely taken some Bioware
The people designing this game
Clearly love
All these different types of video games
And have now made the video game they want to be playing
And for the most part it's like 98% successful
From what I've seen so far
I'd play if I had the 60 bucks to afford it
That's the problem is dropping the money up front
You know it's an investment
I mean whereas you know
I've already got wow I'm already in the blood pact
Sure sure
But that's the other thing I like about Guild Wars is that once you buy it
You know if I don't go back to it ever
It'll be there 6 months now
12 months from now
One other thing I'll say about this
The guild system is pretty awesome
Oh and then I'm going to give you one more negative
So the guild system is pretty awesome
Once you form your little guild
Every little thing that you do during the day
Kind of contributes points to the guild's total
And you can use those points to buy perks
So it's kind of like what they were
Going to do with World of Warcraft's
Guild leveling system
But they actually did it where the guild master can elect
What guild perks you're going to build
You know do you want the guild to have an XP bonus
Or a money bonus
Or what is it that you want
And you can like use the resources to build those
Which is pretty cool
Now the place I'm going to knock it a little bit is that
This is actually a big one
I'm glad I thought of this because I got to knock the game for this
It's an issue
They did this whole 3 day launch thing right
So there's a lot of people that aren't really going to be in the game until Tuesday
And some of the servers are already full
And you don't get to pick
One server for each character
You pick one server
For all of your characters
Now there's a system in the game
Where I guess you can have
People from other servers
Kind of like in a real ID
Kind of way they can guest in your game
And you can still kind of party
Cross server and there is a lot
You can do cross server
But the one thing you can't do cross server is guild
The server I'm on
Filled up in like a day
So if people want to try to get on that server
It's full
So what if I have friends like Jamie say
Who haven't bought the game yet
And then they're going to try and get on my server
It's going to be too bad, it's full
I kind of think that's bullshit
That she can't join my guild because that filled up
Because all the early people have the space
They need to have a system
Where she can still get into that server
Now
To be fair
I understand that they are doing some type of
Open transfer for 7 days
They're going to allow you to switch worlds
However much you want for 7 days
So that people can kind of settle down
Find a home and get off the populated servers
And all that stuff
However they're going to charge for that later on
And I still think it's kind of bullshit
Like there needs to be a way
If I have a friend on the server
Remember how Final Fantasy 11 did the world passes
I thought that was a good way to do it
If the server is populated make it expensive
To bring somebody on the server
But still make it possible
So that part
Sucks and needs to be rethought
A little bit
But otherwise
I'm really cool with Guild Wars 2
So I've talked 20 minutes about Guild Wars 2
But it's a big game
So there you go that's my gaming week
Finally
So let's talk about housekeeping
Twitter.com slash olr
Facebook.com slash orange lounge radio
And I didn't really clear this with Loki
Before the show but I don't think he's going to care
We're not doing a show next week
For Labor Day
And it's because
PAX you're all on vacation
You know what just enjoy
The long weekend we will try to have something
Special that does play live on the feed
Like a best of or an oldie moldy
Classic episode or something for those
Few of you that will still be there on Sunday night
But if you know what
If you have an opportunity to go out and get a
Rest and vacation a little bit enjoy
It I guess that would also be
We have to remember not every country is
Getting a three day weekend that's mostly an America
Holiday not really celebrated
Other places however please understand
We do want to take the rare opportunity
To go have a three day weekend and you know
Take a road trip if we want or what have you
I'm toying with the idea of taking a little
Quick road trip for the weekend
We'll see I think it will be fun
Of course sitting on my big butt and playing video games
All day long will be great too
Civ 5 uber match yeah
I just think it's kind of weird that like school
Is starting this week
And then there's Labor Day
So like two days of magazine class
No day of magazine class
School year has been like that for forever
So alright
Alright let's get into some gaming news
And talk about what is going on
In the gaming world and unfortunately
I better cue the Debbie Downer horns
Cause it doesn't start off pretty
Does it Loki? No layoffs
It's more and more layoffs
So PopCap they were hit
With layoffs internationally
And at least so they kind of
The way they did it
At least they were talking about
What happens in the industry
And they try to like kind of make it
You know
They didn't kind of hide it
From the public I guess
And so basically
They have
Shrunk down I guess
Shanghai's studio
Also in Seattle they let
50 people go
And Dublin was shut down
So you know
Quite a bit of layoffs
They said that you know
I guess
They made a statement
And I
Just think it's kind of interesting the way they did it
You know basically you know
You know 12 years ago
We founded PopCap we never imagined the games
We'd made the vast number of people
You know who'd play those games
Or the success that followed and so on and so forth
And then you know
This morning we informed our employees
Of a reorganization in our studios
That will include a reduction in force
In North America operations
Mostly our headquarters here in Seattle
And an exploratory
Consultation to evaluate
The future of our PopCap office
In Dublin
Ireland
And now in English reduction in force
Means that some people are losing their jobs
Exploratory consultation means
We're taking our Dublin team
About the future of that
Or talking to our Dublin team about the future of that office
And whether we can find a path to improve
Our profitability in Europe without having to
Close operations. Today's news is something
You expect periodically from companies
In a fast changing industry but it sucks
If you're one of those people losing his or her jobs
These people are our friends
And we don't like doing this
So at least they're being very personable about it
And just like you know
I think that's the way you do it right there
However I think
There's another pink elephant in the room
And allow me to echo the
Pink elephant? Yeah
Pink elephant that stands out
Isn't that when you just drink a lot?
You see pink elephants?
No I've always heard the pink elephant in the room
Is the obvious thing or whatever
Anyway you're derailing me
The pink elephant in the room in this
And allow me to echo the rest of the internet
In this is
I don't understand
Why PopCap?
Is PopCap struggling?
I thought out of all the
Gaming companies out there
PopCap was doing a lot of things right
And granted your whole memo
And everything you're talking about there is
An example of some of the things they do right
A lot of us had a great fear
When EA bought them
Something like this would happen
They go into why
And basically
A little context on why we're making cuts
In some areas and why we're investing and expanding
In others, in past years
We've seen dramatic change in the way people play
And pay for games
Free to play, social and mobile games have
Exploded in popularity, that happened fast
Surprisingly so
The change in consumer taste requires
Us to reorganize our business and
Invest in new types of games on new
Platforms, it's a completely different world
From where we started, that's why
I still
Does not make sense
And granted PopCap
Wasn't putting out a lot of games
Maybe unfortunately there was
Just too much that was in development
That was costing them too much money
Too much in development, not enough out on the table
But still, how fucking huge
Was Plants vs. Zombies
But Jeweled
But Jeweled changed
The industry in some ways
But Jeweled was one of the first Facebook
Games, period
Everybody knows what kind of
Jackpagle is
I don't understand
I get it when game companies
As much as this pained me
When Bizarre Creations closed
I understood that Blur
Was not very well received
And that the Geometry Wars games were kind of
Losing steam and all that
And that they weren't doing the PGR games anymore
I kind of saw the economics in that
I don't get it here
Despite everything that they're saying there
I can't help as a fan
That this company was doing very well
Before EA bought them
I can't help but think
Despite what they're saying
Something's up
Well maybe
Because they are bought by EA
The investors thought
Hey, there's too much overhead on this company
And so we need to cut back
In order to make it more profitable
So EA just jacked all the franchise
EA just snatched Jeweled
Snatched Plants vs. Zombies
Worked for Zynga
Of course they're seeing though that that's not the case
They said if we didn't have EA behind us
The cuts would have been worse
So, I don't know
I'd have to
I wouldn't really know what to do until I saw a financial report
Honestly
It's just weird
Maybe because everything is free to play
Like for example in Jeweled Blitz
And stuff like that on Facebook
That no one's actually buying the games anymore
Maybe that's why
You think of not enough people buying
Those power ups and the things that
Maybe
Substantiate the free to play model
Maybe not
Maybe because of PopCap's style
They've always been pretty good about not shoving that shit
Down your throat like Zynga Games do
That maybe
Unfortunately being nice isn't profitable
Maybe
I don't think that it was a lack of that
I thought that they had very innovative ways of getting
The games out there
I've got a
Special version of PEGL that teamed with Valve
That came out
When they were doing
It was like a special PEGL
That had Portal stuff in there
And Team Fortress and everything
And it was free
It's like if you liked this, here's the full game
Here's the whole thing
The Plants vs. Zombies stuff in WoW
The PEGL add-on
Which I played a lot of the PEGL add-on
And really wish it was still available
They really did look into
Getting it out there in different ways
And I think that
If they had been able to keep that up
Then maybe this wouldn't happen
But I'm not sure
I really don't know what to say
Until I see a financial report
Tigerclaw in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says
Could it be that people are finally
Getting tired of playing
Casual games?
Nah
No
Here's the thing
If you mean casual games to mean Facebook games
Maybe
I think what's going to happen to Facebook games
Is what happened in the video game crash of 84
Which is there's just so much shit
In the market
And a lot of commercialized shit
And money grabbing shit that isn't worth it
There's just so much shit out there
It's going to crack
And people aren't feeling all that great about Facebook
These days anyway
I feel like
The other shoe is going to drop on Facebook
Any day now
If there could actually be a competitor that could come in
I realize Google Plus is out there
But Google
Kind of just couldn't do it for whatever reason
If there's somebody
That really gave the public what they wanted
It could all come tumbling down for Facebook
Pretty soon
I'm on a social networking thing that doesn't have the stupid games on it
Well I always liked the way Google Plus did it
It was just another tab somewhere else
I mean to be perfectly honest I'm actually thinking about
Going back to using Google Plus
Because of just how ridiculous Facebook has gotten
But I don't play the games
There's a lot of people that are worried about
System security
So they, like I have done, have blocked
Every single game request that's come through
Well this is the thing that pisses me off about Facebook
Literally pisses me off
I don't know how many times
I have turned off
Location statuses on my post
I don't want all my posts posting
Where my location is
I use an app called Foursquare
When I specifically want to disclose that
I hate being tagged
I don't check into my house
And all that stuff
I don't do that
So I don't want my post to be tagged
With my work address or my home
Or whatever it is
Yet that shit keeps turning itself back on
I just had to do it on a Facebook post
I made an hour before the show
And that shit is driving me bonkers
The site's broken, remember I've talked about this a few weeks ago
And it's still broken
It's been broken for over a month now
Where you can unsubscribe
From somebody's
Comments and likes
Basically you just don't want to see one
Okay I like this picture
I don't care if you like that picture
And it keeps popping back
No it keeps popping back up
I want to unsubscribe from it
And it will hide that post
But it will still be there
I have to stop
For people that keep having that stuff pop up
And I'm just tired of seeing their post
I actually have to unsubscribe from them
Why do we keep using Facebook?
I'm sitting here bitching
Yet I'll still use it to make some stupid posts this evening
Why? Because I need instant gratification
Not that people are on Google
It's not even that
Why do we need that right now in our society?
Why do we need it?
The only reason I keep up with Facebook
Is just to piss off my mother
To keep up with my friends and family
In Alabama
To keep up with my friends
In other countries
To keep up with my friends across America
Because only three people
Anymore still use AIM
Which I still use to keep up with people
I've found old friends
That I used to chat with
Back when I had AOL for real
Back in the day
One of my friends just found me through DeviantArt
And we're on Facebook now
I mean, I use it to keep up with people
But other than that
I mean, like
I get so irritated that
People just use it for a
Sympathy grab, you know what I mean?
Or, hi, look where I am and you're not
I don't care where you are
I don't need to know when you go to bed
I think it's just this whole
I think it really is a modern phenomenon
That everyone wants a little bit of
I hate to use it
In this respect, but everyone wants their own little
Piece of celebrity, you know what I mean?
Where they want people to care about what they're doing
It's that whole Andy Warhol thing
The 15 minutes of fame, it's all of that coming to light
Andy Warhol predicted things better than the Mayans
Well, he was a fairly
Interesting person
Yes he was He was an OCD collector
Yeah, yeah Anyway
My teacher got to meet him Why did he do a painting of soup cans?
One of my teachers got to meet him
Oh yeah? Yeah, back then
Anyhow, how did we get from PopCap to this?
You're the one who changed it to Andy Warhol
I do find this topic fascinating
Let me read some chat comments real quick
Those participating with the show at live.vognetwork.com
Locopoco says
I use it, talking about Facebook
Cause all my family and friends use it
And that's all I can use to keep up with them
Why?
And I'm not saying that at you
Because I bet everybody would answer the question the same way
And I'm even asking myself this
Why not just pick up the phone and call somebody?
I'd
I'd pretty much
I'd call my mother
I have nothing to talk to them about
That's why I post
Things on there
Not like, hey I did this today
It's like, hey look at this cool movie trailer
Frisbee in our chat room
Why does Facebook have to be the only way
To keep in touch with people?
And lately all I do now is just for
Reblogging political shit
It helped me with the kitten
You know?
You gotta love
DJ Morpheus from Understation Live
Just made a Facebook post
I was told to reload Facebook, so that's why I did it
No, I hate being tagged in a location
Where you were tagged. Jamie hates to be tagged
So I'm tagging her. I don't mind being tagged
In a picture, I hate location tags
Actually I don't like being tagged
In a picture sometimes, like the ones
Not necessarily pictures, but like the ones that are like
Here's a calendar of all these birthdays
I'm gonna tag everybody
For the record, I can't hide that
Travis, just saying
I hate the picture tagging too, but
At the same time, like earlier today
Clover Nykon, one of our listeners
Made this awesome 3D vog art rendering
And he tagged me in that
And I was okay with that
At least that's relevant to my interest
I may not be in that picture, but it's a vog picture
And I want to see it, so that's alright
I don't give a crap about that
I hate location posts
I am going to
resolution
We've been talking a lot about Labor Day
And what we want to do over the Labor Day weekend
And I am going to resolve
To not touch social networking
Labor Day weekend
No Facebook, no Google Plus, no Twitter
You know where I live these days?
Tumblr
None of that either, none of that for me
Have fun, I'm gonna be on Tumblr
Why won't you do it?
Because I love Tumblr, I can give up Facebook
I don't give a crap, but I love Tumblr because
I actually get news articles
On Tumblr, I use Tumblr as my
Blog for my
Fitness thing, and actually if anyone wants to follow
My fitness blog, it's called Dieting Can
Bite Me, all one word
At Tumblr
But I mean, I use that for
I use it for art blogging
I actually use that for real
Blogging stuff, and for getting my thoughts
Out there, it's sort of my
Live general replacement for right now
Alan Alchemy in our chat room says, well the issue of Facebook
Is that it managed to get everyone's like
55 year old aunts and shit on it
Which really is unprecedented
And that audience does not give a shit about moving
On to the next great thing like the rest of it
It's kind of a good point
Is that that's one reason why Facebook took off
Is that it got everybody on it
And now it's ads, ads, ads, ads
Alan Alchemy continues
So the problem is that if you're in the same situation
Of keeping track of your family, re-Facebook
There is no reason to ever believe they'll move on
To something else, so even if you move on
To the next thing, you'll have to keep your Facebook
So it's always going to be a little bit relevant
Then let's move off
Let's go back to Live Journal
Here's some selected likes that they want me to like
Wreck-It Ralph, Cuddling,
Five Finger Death Punch, and Act of Valor
What?
All that liking stuff is, is marketing
Exactly, I've had to go back
And unlike things because
I realize it's ironic, we tell you to go like
Orange Lounge Radio and Vogue Network
But guys, that's
I mean, and that's the double-edged sword about Facebook
Is that it's still a great way to promote
My shit, when I don't have the million dollars
To spend on magazine ads and
You know, TV ads and the other stuff
The big boys get to do
So yes, I do realize it's ironic
Here I am bitching about Facebook, yet
I say, go like Orange Lounge Radio on Facebook
Because it still is a good way to remind you guys
The show is here, and to listen
And all that stuff
Well, I'm going to stick to it
I'm going to put
Make my actions match my words
I am stepping off Facebook
For one weekend, it's not even
That big of a deal, one weekend
Is anybody out there going to try it too?
Is it just going to be me?
Are you really all that attached?
I guess we'll find out
Where were we? We were talking about PopCap
I'm sure the PopCap employees don't
Really appreciate that it became a Facebook rant
But whatever
Travis tagged you with
Your location
Yeah, but he did it for my fan page
So keep pouring that out
That's fine
In Sacramento, well that's fine
I just don't like it when he gives my address
Alright, moving on
More bad news
Sometimes I don't want people to know
When I'm having lunch at Wiener Works
Only when I'm having dessert
That's why I got rid of Foursquare
I really don't give a shit anymore
I don't care if people know where I am
I don't necessarily want people to know where I am
And I don't care where you are
I actually, okay
I swear this is the last thing on social networking
The reason why I like Foursquare
Is I actually like the search function
To see what restaurants my friends have been to
And if they left tips, if they enjoyed it or not
I have found it to be way more useful
Than Yelp and that
I usually just ask people
Yelp reviews are a lot of
Well, but like, okay
Literally one night, Alan and I were out shopping
We were at Bed Bath and Beyond or something
Getting the coffee stuff
Because they sell a lot of the coffee cups there
And we were like, alright let's go somewhere for dinner
Where should we go? I don't know
Let's go somewhere new
And I pulled up Foursquare and I'm like
Alright, let me see what restaurants are coming up
That my friends have been to recently
Oh, Tex Wasabi's
That's that one guy
From Food Network's restaurant
Yeah, thank you
That guy with the horrible hair
It's his restaurant and I've never been there
And I loved it actually
I thought it was really expensive
Yeah, it's a little bit
It's not like Ruth Chris expensive
It's like Red Lobster prices
That's not so bad
It's sushi and barbecue
And I
You think it's the weirdest thing in the world
I shit you not, it's fucking amazing
Not to endorse
Johnny Garlic's
But there's none around here I don't think
No, there's one in Roseville
What are you talking about?
Alright
Let's move on
This is more bad news
This just sucks
I don't know what else to say about this
Sony Liverpool has been closed
You know them because they brought you
Wipeout 2048
If you're like me you remember this studio
When they were called Psygnosis
You remember Psygnosis?
Lemmings
I mean that game
Was like PC gaming
Golden Child
For years and years
They became Sony Liverpool
Shadow of the Beast was another game they made
And of course the Wipeout games
What happened?
I guess Wipeout on the Vita didn't live up to expectations
I don't think that's Wipeout's fault
That was probably one of the better games
To get on the Vita
This is another one I'm looking at
Going
Is it just because Wipeout
Isn't making waves
The way that LittleBigPlanet
Is? I mean I don't know
But I mean Psygnosis has put out some good shit
Over the years
It's just weird
What else can I say?
That sucks
A little known fact about Psygnosis
They received top billing for creating
The faceoff games
Featured in Nickelodeon's 1992 television show
Nick Arcade
That's right they created the faceoff games in Nick Arcade
Get the fuck out that was them?
Yeah Posthaste, Jet Jocks
And Battle of the Bands
A little piece of
The 12 year old boy in me
Who is playing Lemmings on his
486 PC is having a cry
Right now
I don't get it
Poor Rob
Poor me, poor all of us
We all lose with this news
This week, the only thing we can hope
These guys form new stuff
You know see this would have been another game
That would have been good from them
That they could have remade and it would have been really sweet
Colony Wars was another game that they worked on
When they were Sony
I swear all this is just putting me in a bad mood
I'm sorry
Well I hope they can
Rise up and start
Something new, I mean I remember PopCap had
That iOS studio
No one's gonna do anything new
There's no money in anything new
People want the same recycled
Crap and companies don't like to
Take risks, end of story
Do you find it a bit ironic that they're
One of the launch games for you know
This whole Sony mobile thing or whatever
Their platform is Lemmings
That's just salt in the wound right there
But I mean well
That's just because what's new hasn't been thought of yet
Facebook at one time didn't exist
It was new
But it was still based off of a pre-existing concept
Social networking is not new
Well video games aren't new
But there's still lots of ideas that haven't been discovered yet
You know we had pen pals back in the day
This is updated pen palling pretty much
You know
Concepts can evolve
But I really don't think that there's
Much new to be had anymore
Everyone copies everybody
I think that's with all due respect
I think that's just a jaded perspective
On where our industry is at
We feel that way because that's all we're getting
We're getting sequels, we're getting all this same old shit
The people that are doing new things are being ignored
And I agree
That sucks
We need to pay attention to the good ideas
And I've told a couple people this
I'm actually gonna be writing a book and I'm gonna self publish
Because
You notice that all the books
And I hate to use these as examples
Because they really are just awful fan fiction
But like that 50 Shades of Shit
There's some pretty bad writing that gets published
And people eat it up
But the thing is
That that's someone who
You know some of these other books that came out
That have been rejected
By major publishers
They've self published and have since turned into
Pretty big money making schemes
There's a girl that writes episodic
Vampire stories on Facebook
For 99 cents a copy
And she's a millionaire now
A million bucks isn't that much anymore
Relatively
I wouldn't mind having that
But a college student putting up
Her own little stories on Amazon
Selling them
I think she'd get like a
10% profit off of it
Or some really small margin of profit
What's the trick? How do you make people pay for it?
If we charge 99 cents an episode
Of Orange Lounge Radio
Let's not kid ourselves
The thing that I'm saying is
That I think that's why the Kickstarter thing is actually
Really taking off
It has to do back with that self publishing
Self actualizing
They're going to the people instead of using
Some formula
That companies think works
They're putting
Say hey, show me you're interested with your money
I mean
Except 5% of it won't actually go to the idea
At all
But the Kickstarter idea is new
Relatively new
And they made a business off of it
So that's something there
It's basically I think a lot of people
Taking their own ideas
Into their own hands
Not letting someone else corrupt their idea
And seeing how far they can make it go
Based on the will of the people
Alright
I'm sorry I didn't mean to go off on that
That's alright
That's funny news though
It's been an hour and we've done two downer stories
Fuck this game
Final Fantasy XIV
It's being pulled off the shelves
Aw no more Final Fantasy XIV
Squeenix said take it off your shelves
You know why?
Because they don't want it to get in the way of a
Realm Reborn
They're basically saying
That those who are registering
Their copy of Final Fantasy XIV
Will have full access to a 30 day
Free trial period prior to the servers shutting
Down in preparation for the
Alpha and Beta test of a Realm Reborn
So they're wanting to just
Not have those old copies go out there anymore
They want people to focus
On the new
What happens if they don't
Use those free, like if I bought
The game and I knew that they're gonna
Shut the servers down
The servers aren't shutting down
Don't be confused
They're just pulling it off shelves
They're shutting down the servers
What? I had not heard that
Exactly what I read off here
From their own thing
Prior to the servers shutting down
To prepare for the Alpha and Beta tests
Oh shit
So like why would I want to
Wow
If I had 30 days
Wouldn't I want to save that for when it starts
When I originally saw this, that update wasn't there
That's why
Basically the update
Is a confirmation that
The original story came out from
People posting about, hey we got this
Note in our store, we have to take it down
I'll read the
Actual statement, okay
In anticipation of the upcoming Alpha and Beta test
For Final Fantasy XIV, a Realm Reborn
Square Enix, in coordination
With our retail partners, has decided
To discontinue sales of the current version of Final Fantasy XIV
This move was done
To help ensure that new customers who register
Their copy of Final Fantasy XIV
Will have full access to the 30 day
Free trial period prior to the
Servers shutting down to prepare for the Alpha
And Beta tests of Final Fantasy XIV
A Realm Reborn
Wow
See, in my mind I was like
Oh, they'll do kind of like what World of Warcraft does
You have your test servers that run one
Copy of the game
That's archaic and dumb
Not that anybody's really gonna
There'll be hundreds of people that weep over
Final Fantasy XIV servers being shut down
But, I mean
When it vanishes to that though, it is a clean break from the old
Yeah, that's
That's unprecedented
I think it's gonna kick it
I think it's gonna
Kick him in the ass
Square is literally trying to erase your memory
Of that game
So that when Realm Reborn comes out
It's treated like a brand new game
A brand new launch
Like the old one didn't ever happen
That's crazy
I think
That it's gonna come back to kick him though
I think it's gonna come back
And I think it's really gonna hurt him
I'd
It's a, you know what, I'm gonna give it this
Final Fantasy XIV
Sucked
I tried it two or three times
I really tried to like it
It was not a good MMO
Harry Monkey Balls is what it sucked
I'm just, having played WoW
Having played Guild Wars
Night's the Old Republic
Having played just about everything that's come to the
Table
Final Fantasy XIV sucked
XI was still a better experience
For the month I went back to XI
I just
Yeah
And XI made me cry with frustration
And everything I saw made me like it better
Oh, but I don't think it's necessarily
Going to, you know
I applaud them for taking risks
I don't know if it will necessarily
Be a failure
But I think if you're hedging your bets on sales of the
Console version of the game, that's dangerous
Because console MMOs
Haven't been super super well done
So
With the exception of Final Fantasy XI
So I hope they also
Consider the relaunch on the PC as well
I'm
Fascinating
You know what, it's like the more crap they do
With this, the less I'm interested in it
It's not worth it, there's bigger and better out there
Alright, let's move on with some more news
So EA is hoping
To avoid a whole
It's kind of funny that they're actually
Acknowledging it now, but they're trying
To put a lot
Of resources in preventing another
FIFA hack going on
With FIFA 13
And basically
They made a lot of money off the Ultimate Team DLC
A 69%
Increase from the same period last year
And of course people suspect
Hmm, that might be because people were hacking
Accounts to steal
People's live information
And buy
FIFA stuff so they could resell those characters
They said
We've learned a lot from the experience
A lot of companies are suffering from this right now
There's a lot of sophisticated hacking
Or hacking happening in the gaming industry
And it's a continuous battle
And we've
We take it very seriously
And we put a lot of resources on it
We're learning from the FIFA example last year
And it's been incorporated into this year
And there's some incremental and additional
Things, I don't want to get too detailed
Because I want to tip our hand
But rest assured we'll take it very seriously
I'm sorry
I still don't see how that's going to happen
Considering that you're selling the same stuff
On Madden now
And you're still doing the FIFA thing
So as long as you keep making
It profitable for people to steal those
Accounts and actually be able to sell
Stuff for real money
Then people are going to keep hacking those accounts
To try to make money off of them
This whole thing gets a nice hearty kiss my ass
From EA because
I mean, granted, okay
It's nice that you're like acknowledging something's
Going on now
Now that you're trying to sell the new copy
Of your game
You know, like, screw you for not
Having said that this was a problem
Before
Now you're just casually
Saying, oh yes, well we've learned from the past
And da da da da da
But the new one's going to be bigger and better
You are using
People who had their money stolen
As an excuse to plug
Your new game, that's what it feels like to me
Honestly, as somebody who was FIFA hacked
For all this
Some people frown on the use of the term
Hacking, whatever the fuck it was
Money was stolen and
Social engineering is still
A form of hacking, I guess
So they're going to add
More stuff to their marketplace so that
There's more things for people to buy
Is that what they've learned?
Hey, we've learned that we can get a lot of money
From people getting their accounts stolen
So we're just going to
Add more things that they can buy
Maybe some stuff for $500 instead
I don't know
How about putting some restrictions down
Like Blizzard does on some of the digital
Purchases when they're suspect
They don't go through for a few days
So that people have an easier time getting the money back
Or doing the back charges and all this stuff
For the suspect things
How about a little more about the security side
Of things and all that
Well
The reality is
Where we're at in this industry now
I just don't think that's possible
Anymore
I think it's stupid though that they have a $60 game
That they're doing all these microtransactions on
I think it's ridiculous too
But unfortunately people are buying them
So
It's working
We need to hunt these people out
If people
We shouldn't tell people what to spend their money on
Legitimately are doing this
The other problem I have is that
Probably 80% of that was all from stolen money
But
Besides that
People can spend their money however they want
If they want to buy $60
For the game and then pay all this money
For the expansions
Let them spend their money on it if that's what makes them happy
Vote with your wallet
If you don't like it
Don't buy it
But the problem is
My wallet was stolen and then used to vote
That's a problem
Oh it's not our problem
It's not our issue
A year later
Oh we've taken steps to try and make sure that won't happen again
It's never our issue in the first place
Why would you need to take steps if there was not an issue with your
If it was all Microsoft
So I'd love to know
Moving on
Boy
Dark Soccer you're right
The news tonight just makes us
There's so much to get angry about this week
Let's close the show and go get Pinkberry
I thought you were having a healthy day
It's yogurt
Trust me
You'd want to get that delicious new chocolate
Hazelnut which isn't the best yogurt for you
Anyway
Ubisoft made an interesting statement this week
The CEO of Ubisoft
And I can't even say this name
Yves
Guillemot
Isn't the T usually silent
Came out and said
That PC retail games
Have a
Gigantic rate of piracy
And this was
Talking to games industry
At gamescom
He said that
Only about 5-7%
Of freemium players buy content
Because
Like the retail PC product
They have a quote
93-95% piracy rate
So he's basically saying retail PC games
Some other comments quote
We also take content which we've
Developed in the past graphics etc
And we can make cheaper games and improve them over time
What's very important is that we
Change the content and make it a better fit
To the customer as time goes on
But still throwing that statistic out there
93-95%
Piracy rate
That sounds really high
To a lot of people
Well
I'm not so sure
I think there might actually be some truth to that number
You know why I think there's truth to that number?
I think if you're looking at
Just the US
And Britain and Japan
And the rest of the UK
Where Ubisoft or wherever in the world
They have a presence where they sell games
Maybe that number seems high
But I mean
Piracy is fucking rampant in other parts
Of the world
I'm sure there's copies of these games
Easily available in the most populous
Country in the world
China! I'm sure there's tons of free copies
Of these games roaming around in China
But when you throw in the worldwide
Perspective into the mix
I could actually believe
The 93-95% piracy rate
But
Some people are still
Successful off that model
I'm not excusing it
I'm not saying it's okay
I'm just saying
Numbers can lie, you have to manipulate them
It's not like piracy is anything new
Or like it's never happened before
We've never had successful PC games
But before I believe any of those numbers
I'd have to see where the polls are
I mean where
I wouldn't trust
Anything
Numbers based on markets that wasn't made for
You're having a very I want to see the receipts
Kind of night
I am, well you know I'm like that anyway
I'm like that anyway
Loki what do you think of that number
93-95% piracy rate
Seems a little high
I don't know
Frisbee in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
Says 85% of statistics
Are made up on the spot
Especially in this industry brother
Alright one other note
About Ubisoft which is interesting
Because Ubisoft previously
Came out and said the game I Am Alive was never
Going to come out on the PC basically
Because there was no
Other version
Creative director Stanislaw Metra
Came out and said about I Am Alive
Quote we've heard loud and clear
That PC gamers are bitching about
There being no version for them
Wow
But are these people
Just making noise because there's no version
Or because it's a game they actually want to play
Would they buy it if we made it
It's hard because there's so much piracy
And so few people are paying for PC games
That we have to precisely weigh it up
Against the cost of making it
Perhaps it will only take 12 guys 3 months
To port the game to PC
It's a massive cost but it's still a cost
If only 50,000 people buy the game
Then it's not worth it
Only 50,000?
Well to
I have to say to his credit
He does make a point
If it takes 12 guys
3 months to port the game
Then using fractions
That would also be 3 guys 12 months
Or 3 annual salaries
And let's say these guys make
I don't know 75k a year
So to just pay those 3 guys
Is going to cost
225,000 dollars
And that's not even counting the cost to print the game
To market the game
To sell and all that stuff
Make it all download content you don't have to pay for materials
I don't know
But there's some people
That would be like
Viral marketing
I don't download games
Because I have to have the tangible copy
Then they lose out
You're a collector and all this shit
Why?
Hold on
I collect old shit Rob
I collect old things
I don't know it just doesn't make sense
This doesn't make sense coming from you
It really doesn't
My first 2 copies of Mass Effect were all download
The only reason I paid for a fiscal copy for 3
Was because I got them to price match
And I would have
I would have done the download copy if it had been the same
So
Let's make believe
I use Steam Rob
Let's make believe la la la
That the next Xbox and the next Playstation
And just making
Pulling shit out of my ass
The Wii U all go digital only
Digital download only
That's not a problem?
Not really
Honestly I'm going to say this is going into a little bit of my home stuff
We're thinking about downsizing
We have
Shelves that are taken up with DVDs
And with you know
Our current game collection
We have buckets of the old stuff
And the old stuff that's fine
But anything new
I really wouldn't mind having it
As a digital copy
I mean as long as I've got the software
The hardware to play it on then I wouldn't mind
You know it
It's less waste
Less um
It's green Rob it's green
It's green
I'm a hippie
One more news story and then the release dates
So how about some
Some persona
There is going to be
Persona 4 the solid gold
Premium edition
And it's going to be only
10,000 copies produced
But it will have a
Hori hard cover pouch
A face cover
Stickers and Vita skins
And 8 matching wallpapers
And it's going to be 70 bucks
And the first run copies
Just to let people know
Had just the skins and wallpapers and it was 40 bucks
So
For people who are persona fans
Also just to let you know
Only in Japan
Of which there are a few
That won't stop many people I know
The bonus stuff that came out
With the solid gold edition
Are the same ones that came out in Japan
No
No Europe
Is intended
AlphaCananagram in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com
Says they are sold out on Amazon
For this persona for the golden kit
Well yeah it's only 10,000 being made
That shows you how rabid the fans are
They've already sold it out
I know people that are really
Really really into this game
There's no Europe that it's not coming out though
Sorry guys
Alright let's travel around the world
And check out release dates
Games that are coming to a store near you
This week
So this week we've got
Damage Inc Pacific Squadron World War 2
Coming out from Mad Cats
It's the first game that they're publishing
On Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
It's a World War 2 flight sim game
Guild Wars 2 coming out on PC
Both in limited edition and regular edition
Madden NFL 13
On Playstation 3
Xbox 360
And Vita
Couple collections
For you on the PS3
Infamous Collection which features
Infamous 1 and 2 in the DLC
That's coming out as well
God of War Saga with all five
God of War games including the HD
Remasters of 1 and 2
And the PSP games
Also
Let's see here
We've got Ratchet and Clank
Collection which is the HD
Mix of the first
I think the first three Ratchet and Clank games
Journey Collector's Edition
As I mentioned earlier that's on PS3 this week
As well
And
That's it
Alright let's travel to Japan
And check out what's coming out over there
On the Xbox 360 Dirt Showdown
On August 30th
That's not like a dirt fighting thing
Dirt of course is the racing series
So Codemasters is putting that out in Japan on the 30th
It pops the line from 2K games
Those are both on the Xbox 360 in Japan
On the PlayStation 3
On the 30th quite a bit more
To pick from there's also Dirt Showdown
But you also can get
Aqua Pazza Aqua Plus Dream
Match in regular and limited edition
Kamejigen Gamae
Neptune 5 in limited and regular
Edition from Idea Factory
From Capcom Sengoku
Basara HD Collection comes out
Over there
What game is that? What's Sengoku Basara?
It's Samurai Warriors
No it's not Samurai Warriors
It's their Dynasty Warriors clone
Looks like it
No Sengoku Basara it's over here
It's a Capcom game
Somebody in the chat will shout it out in a minute
I can't remember
It's on the tip of my tongue
Devil
Not Devil Kings
Is that Devil Kings? No it's not Devil Kings
Well look it up
Well I read the rest of these
Shadows of the Damned gets a price reduction from EA
This week as well
Moving on
To the 3DS
The 3DS this week
It's Devil Summoner Soul Hackers
From Atlus
I think some people will be excited about that
And also
Senran Kagura Burst
Gurren no Shodutachi
Comes out as well
Devil Kings says hitstun
Dynasty Warriors clone says AkumaJP
That's basically what it is
Thank you
That's why I love having a live chat room
Lastly
On the Playstation Vita
Hatsune Miku
Project Diva F
I teased that last week
You can get a whole damn Vita
There's a bundle coming out for Hatsune Miku
I'm poor
So you can check that out if you want
And that's the big release on the Playstation Vita
The game that will save the Playstation Vita
Is out this week
Let's go to the
United Kingdom
On the 28th we have
Damage Inc Pacific Squadron World War 2
Guild Wars 2
Journey Collector's Edition for PS3
On the 29th we have Anomaly
Wars on Earth
Joe Danger 2 the movie
And Rock Band Blitz
On the 31st we have Final Fantasy Dimensions
For the Android, iPad and iPhone
And Tales of Graces F
On PS3
Alright just a couple more
news stories for you guys and then the classic
game of the week
But first, Loki
Well we were talking about Facebook and how they
want to shove advertisements down our throat
Well Sony has patented something to shove
advertisements down our throat
It's called a TV, no actually it's called
Interactive TV Ads
Which basically allow you
And I've actually kind of seen this
On some other websites, for example
One of the
interactive bits about it
Like a McDonald's ad or something like that
You have to say McDonald's to end commercial
And if you say McDonald's
Then the commercial ends, that type of thing
There's a website, as I talked
About a lot of Freddie Long
They do videos and stuff like that
They have a YouTube channel, but they have their own website
Called RocketJump and their video player that they have
On there has ads, but to skip
The ads, you have to type a word in
So you can
Watch the ad or you can type
Ford Focus
And it'll stop the ad
So it's kind of like
Okay, this way the
Advertiser knows this person saw
The ad and it's not just like clicking on skip
They know what the product is
And they're aware of
What you're trying to do
That's kind of cool
I mean
I just don't know what sort of
Things and games
Are going to require advertisements
Or commercials where I actually have to
Say something in order to
Have them go away, but
At least they have a way
For them to go away, I mean because if I could do that
On TV, it's like
You know, tampon commercial!
It's like, go
Go away!
No!
Um
Yeah, I wish I could do the same thing
With male enhancement
Commercials
Big penis!
They have a pill to give a guy a boner, but no cure for breast cancer
Just saying
Well
I don't want to get into it, to be fair
The Viagra was not
Made to do that
It was made for heart problems
But it just happened to have this side effect
Oh, how's your heart?
Boner!
That happens in the pharmaceutical industry
A lot of times
Well, the medication I was taking for
My chronic fatigue syndrome
Is actually what they all
Prescribe for narcolepsy
Isn't it kind of ironic though that they tell you that you shouldn't use Viagra
If you have heart problems?
You know, it's like
Well, because it was for a certain type of heart condition
I'm not a doctor, I'm not going to try to explain it
Anyhow
Some folks in chat says
Hitstun says adblock plus is made for
Invasive ads like this
D Singe says thank god for ad and flash blockers
That's true in browsers
But when you're talking about being built in the
Consoles, and you're assuming
This is going to be like streaming stuff
Like I'm watching ad supported things
Which, I mean, it's ad supported
It's like if I'm watching TV
And it's free, if you're on Hulu
If Sony's about to do something like the Kinect
Where they're putting a microphone in your living room
You know, because think about it
Microsoft's going to incorporate this into the Kinect right now
Can you imagine if the Kinect would
Interrupt you, for example, like you're talking about
Man, I wish I
Where do you want to eat tonight?
Hey guys, were you talking
About eating somewhere?
Oh my god, that's terrible, can you imagine
We're sitting here doing the show and Jamie's like
Rob, let's just end the show and go to Pinkberry
And then suddenly up on the TV and all
Did you know Pinkberry's latest flavor is chocolate
Hazelnut
We laugh about that now, but that is the future
No, no, no
No, we have to put our foot
Down, there's like
The whole big brother is watching you
Here's the thing though
But that's targeted advertising
That's targeted advertising
You want to know about Pinkberry versus like
You want to know about natural male enhancement
Or you want to know about
I don't need natural male enhancement
I have natural male enhancement
What's not natural about
You know, naked boobies
That's natural male enhancement
Her turns you on
Although I like boobies, but you know
They should have a strip club
Named natural male enhancement
That would be pretty awesome
Alright
R.D.G. Singe in chat says
I did that trick to block MS ad servers
From pushing ads on my Xbox system
But every now and then they get through
Would be nice to know what to update
You know
We have ads on vognetwork.com
And you know
It isn't free to produce this stuff
We pay for a lot of this shit out of pocket
Because it's our hobby
And it's what we like to do
But I just would really appreciate it
If you like the shows at vognetwork.com
Just put it on the whitelist
For fuck's sake
We really tried to design things
To not be invasive
Because we know like you guys
We don't want to be invasive
You're blocking the little guys too
Click an ad every once in a while
Visit the site
Help us out
You can click the ad and then close the page
Alright
Moving on
Technically I think encouraging people to do that
Is like a violation of the whatever
Don't be suspicious when you do it
They know that's what's going on
Moving on
One more thing
Maybe this is a little more exciting
This is a ranty and depressing
And sad segment of
Orange Lounge Radio
Well we're about to be off for a week
With something a little better
That is that Harmonix is apparently looking for
A combat designer
What?
Harmonix of course makes rock band
Dance central
Yes apparently they've put up a job listing
And you can find it on Gamasutra
That is looking for a quote real time single player
Combat experience for a brand new
IP on next generation hardware
Bummer it's a brand new IP
Because I was thinking the next Dance Central might
Have like, you got served
I was thinking everybody's kung fu fighting
Or you know
When you're a jet you know you're a jet
You know what it's capoeira game
Who knows
Anything's possible
In addition to finishing development
On rock band Blitz and Dance Central 3
Harmonix is actively developing multiple new IPs
On next generation hardware
And looking for the best and most experienced devs
Out there to join us
So obviously speculate away
What the hell could this be
You know a lot of people making up their own ideas
But I guess it's exciting at least they confirm
We're working on a brand new IP
Is at least something I pull out of that
So yay new ideas right Dark Sakura
Possibly it's Harmonix
But it's real time
Single player combat
It's gonna be another fucking strategy game
But it's I don't
Harmonix down as a company that would do
Quote another fucking strategy game
You know what I mean
Like Harmonix has a pretty good record of being innovative
I'll believe it when I see it
I am the queen of jade today
I wanna see the receipts
I just think it's ironic that a music game company
Is working on an action game
That could be cool Tigerclaw in chat says
Maybe Harmonix is working on a battle of the bands game
You're in a band and you actually have to battle each other
By hitting each other with musical instruments
That's been done on the Wii
It's terrible and it was called battle of the bands
And they literally had it where
Your band equipment would turn into a mini gun
Tigerclaw is gonna get taken to court
Sued for 1.2 billion dollars
It's terrible
Battle of the bands on the Wii
If you wanna have battles right away
Yakuza 5 will have dance battles
Cause you know
Don't we just love minigame dancing
In every fucking game
So Yakuza 5
Will have
Well granted Yakuza has a lot of shit going on
So
Maybe this isn't completely out of character
For the Yakuza series
But whatever they are doing
Dance battles
And Yakuza 5
One of the subplots is about the adopted daughter
Of Kazuma Kiryu
It's Haruka
She's trying to become an idol
So you'll do these dance battles
It's a little rhythm game
I could explain more about it
Let's hope that Harmonics isn't working on
A step up revolution
Game cause
She wants to be a pop idol so that her song will be featured
In the newest anime put out by Gainax
Not really
Can't wait
They have karaoke
And sleeping dogs
Let's travel to a time when we didn't get so fucking mad
About everything
Except this game, he got really mad at one of the bosses
I got mad when
Nintendo Power arrived late
Which by the way
More on that in part B
But first up
The classic game of the week
Where Dark Sakura is going to
Go into the gaming vault
Find a game that she thinks
Hey
If you're super depressed about all these studios closing
Why not play some of the greats from the past
Yeah if you're depressed
Pretend you're a ninja
And slice shit to death
And blow shit up with ninja bombs
Go into denial
Yeah go into denial
The game of the week is called Shadow of the Ninja
Or as it was known in Japan
Yami no Shigo
Okay I'm going to mispronounce this
It's Yami no Shigotonin Kage
Which is
Dark Professional Shadow
That's actually a cooler name
So basically it's a futuristic
Ninja themed side scroll
Arcade action type game
And I am trying to get the
Audio up but um
Remember when Natsume didn't do Harvest Moon?
No actually I don't
This was a game by Natsume
Um
It came out in Japan in 1990
And came out in North America in 1991
The PAL version was published by Taito
Under the name Blue Shadow
Which is actually a pretty cool name
Oh cause he's blue
Well yeah but also there was this big thing
In the 80's and early 90's in
England where you couldn't
Have Ninja in the title
Like for example Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
Was Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles
Rob did you know that?
I did know that
Well Natsume also did a Game Boy version
Of this however
It actually got picked up by
Tecmo and they tried to make it into
A Ninja Gaiden game called Ninja Gaiden
Shadow which is sort of half Shadow
Of the Ninja and half Ninja Gaiden
And 100% kind of crap
Maybe about 85% crap
So
Basically the story of the game is that
In 2029
The evil dictator
Emperor Garuda
Which means eagle by the way did you know that?
What?
Well it actually
In Hindi it means eagle
I learned that from doing yoga
Has taken over the USA
And made a
A big
Stronghold in the middle of the nations
Largest city
So these two Ninja Hayate and Kaede
Have to go
Infiltrate the Stronghold and kill him
To death
So it is
Up to two players simultaneous
Or you can pick one or the other
Like I said Hayate or Kaede
And
You can
There's actually no difference
Between who you play really
But they just look differently
Um
And uh
You uh
Basically you can run
You can crouch, you can climb ladders
You can actually hang from
Certain areas overhead
Including a lot of the moving platforms you can do that too
Um
And you actually can get
You can build up your weapon over time too
They have special attacks
One of them is a thunderstorm
That will just damage all the on screen enemies
But it takes half your life to do it
It actually is quite possible to play this whole game
Without using any of that
Um your default weapon is katana
Um however you can also get um
Kusarigama
It has a longer range but the um
Katana will actually get a full screen range
Once it's fully powered up and
Everyone really likes it better
You also can get some limited use items
You get shuriken or um
What my husband calls the ninja bomb
Which is
Just some sort of hand grenade
Um
And then once you use up your
You know number of those
You actually go back to either using the um
Katana or the Kusarigama
For anyone who doesn't know what that is
It's a hook on a rope
Um it has five levels
Um totaling 16 stages
The first four are in three stages
The final one is in two
And uh you have your bosses
You have your mini bosses
And uh
You um when you beat a boss
It explodes but the explosion heals you
And you can
That way you can carry over life into the next level
If your um
Your game uh
Your game will actually be over if you lose
All of your energy and you only have
Five continues um
If you have two players in the game your continues are shared
So I hope you play with someone who doesn't suck
But I mean the game was
Really awesome when it came out
And I mean just
Sit and watch a play through of this
Or play it yourself if you've got it
It's got neat effects
Great animation for a NES game
The music, Bob Trump's the music if you don't mind
The music is really good
And it's totally
Worth everyone's attention
It has an old Mega Man feel to it a little bit
A little bit
In fact there are actually these little enemies
That you know slide across the floor
Slowly but when you're on the floor they move faster
You know it totally made me think of some Mega Man 2 enemies
Let me um go to part
One here of the little series here
Just to um
Get like the first level music
I guess they're waiting for
Here's one two
It's pretty cool
It's a really neat game
And on top of that you can find it really inexpensive
In a used game store
It's a game that I think everyone should have in their collection
Yeah the American box art
Is stupendously hokey looking
It's like ooh action game
With a couple of
Ninja who look you know uh
Amazingly white
So but it really is a very
Very good game and I totally recommend
Everyone you know shell out the
Five to ten bucks it is at your
Local used video game store
Shadow of the Ninja get it
There it is a classic
Game of the week Shadow of the Ninja
On the NES
To register participation
For this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
On vognetwork.com
Use the pass phrase element
Alright we're going to take a break
But don't go anywhere guys we'll be back with more of
Orange Lounge Radio after a quick break
Where yes we'll talk a little bit about that
Nintendo power thing I'm sure you've all heard about
We'll talk a little bit about that
And we're going to talk about some changes to
Diablo 3 we'll talk all about
That and more including your emails
Your tweets at twitter.com slash
O-L-R and your phone calls coming up
A little later including one phone call
From someone who has something to say about Wii U
Who actually has touched
One and played one I've got something to say
I've got something to say
I miss that show By the way that
If you want to know my favorite TV show of all time
Of all time ever and it's on
Netflix It's on Netflix?
Oh yeah Strangers with Candy
The most amazing
30 episodes 30
30 minute episodes what when it's
Cut out the commercials like 23 minutes
So put it together most amazing
600 minutes of your life
That's what you should do Labor Day weekend make it a point
To watch every episode of Strangers with Candy
Because it's the greatest sitcom
I've ever seen in my life it's not even really a
Sitcom but it's
Look Steven Colbert's in it before he had
That Colbert rapport and he's
He is my absolute inspiration as an
Educator
Where's your permission slip Mr.
Noblet? Shut your dirty little
Mouth!
Fucking amazing
Now I'm going to be thinking
About that as we go to break we'll be back
With more of Orange Lounge Radio right
After this
Welcome back everybody to Orange
Lounge Radio live
On this last
Episode for the month of August
And again we won't be here next
Week have a great Labor Day those of you in the states
Those of you not in the states have a great weekend
Whatever it is you do but sadly we
Won't be here live next weekend as we enjoy
The three day weekend and catch up
On some games that we've been needing to
Catch up on or Marathon Strangers
With Candy one of the two
Alright let's get into some rapid
Fire news some quick
News stories for you guys before we get to
The Facebook and Google question of the week
Or the FUGL question of the week
First off Loki Microsoft wants to let you know
That the Kinect has dropped in price to
$109.99 that's $40
Cheaper than it was
When it first came out
The games being better though
Maybe not so much
But hey
That's pretty inexpensive
So check it out
If you want to connect I guess
The Humble Bundle for
Android they've added some new stuff to it
If you pledge over the average
Price which
Right now I have no idea what the price is
Because I did not look
But it's probably under $10
6.71 you can't beat that
If you pledge $6.71
Not only will you get the games
That they were offering which were Field Runners
Bit.Trip Beat
Space Chem and Uplink
And you would have previously unlocked
Spirits but you also will now
Unlock World of Goo, Osmose
Anomaly and Edge
So all those games available
For Android and for PC
They're multi platform so you get the
Steam codes as well as the
DRM free downloads
For all that stuff
Actually I should
Correct myself
To get the Steam codes you have to pay another
You have to pay over $1 so
Obviously if you're paying over the average
You would get the Steam codes
Check them out! Sounds awesome
And then
Last but not least
That wonderful Scott Pilgrim online
Multiplayer DLC that was also
Gonna unlock an additional character
And what not
Yeah it got delayed to the fall
Womp womp
I don't know why but
That's unfortunate
And I guess the Playstation Network version
Will also release during that time frame as well
Alright moving on with some other
Stories
I wish I could
But my internet is slowing down
And I don't have to slow down
Something's up with our web
We suddenly just lost our web
Mine just plain hasn't worked today
I don't know what's going on
But um
Awkward pause
I wonder if we just had a stream
Hiccup because of that
Let me look
No we're still connected
The joys and pains
Of doing live radio that's alright I have a few things
Here for you guys
Mashihiro Sakurai you know that name because he's the
Director of Super Smash Brothers
He mentioned at the CEDEC
Developer conference in this past week
That the Smash Brothers game on Wii U
And 3DS will have new and exciting
Moves for existing characters
He also mentioned there will be
Of course a bunch of new characters
Now will come the epically
Long tease of which characters
Will be there and which characters
Won't be there and so on and so on
But uh sounds like they are gonna
Expand the move set a little bit I'm wondering if that
Means there's gonna be more than two buttons from here
On out for Smash Brothers that could be interesting
Speculate away
Because lots of people already
Are still button Mash Brothers
I bet um this
Is gonna piss some people off
This is coming from
A former 3D modeler that worked
At Rare on games like Donkey Kong 64
Jet Force Gemini
And so forth apparently
Rare did want to do a new Killer
Instinct game but Microsoft
Was more interested in broadening the Xbox
User base quote the same
Game every Rare fan wants to see and that's
Killer Instinct 3 we all wanted to
Make Killer Instinct 3 but Microsoft
Was more interested in broadening their demographic
Than making another fighting game
So it never got made I doubt
It never will
Microsoft F you
Alright this last story isn't loading
For me but I remember it pretty well
Anyway cause this is another story that made a lot of people
Say F you
That is that they are making
Remember that whole countdown they were doing
For The World Ends With You
And a lot of people were like oh yay it's gonna be a
Sequel yay
Nope no sir it's an
IOS port of the game is coming out
Next week and I believe the
Price on it is $20
Square Enix likes to
Charge more money for their games than 99 cents
To be fair they don't shove
The free to play model down
Your throat make you buy power ups and all that
So at least for your 20 bucks
You're getting a well rounded game and I gotta say
Some of their iPad
Games and such look great like their
Final Fantasy and Final Fantasy 2 ports
That they did on the original iPhone kind of before there was
iPad looked great on the iPhone
So you know
I'm sure the game will look really good
But I don't know
Again the lack of tactile controls
I think is what frustrates a lot of people
Like we don't really want to see
Games like The World Ends With You get ported
To IOS because touch
Controls kind of suck on a lot of these games
At least I know that's what frustrates me
Yeah and then um
20 bucks is still pretty expensive
For anything that's on
You know IOS
I think for that reason because it's you know
You're kind of
Gimping the game a little bit
Not everything is 99 cents I was just looking at iPad
Apps today and some of the better selling
iPad apps are the official Apple
You know versions of
What is it Keynote is like their PowerPoint
Type thing is one of their top sellers
It's $9.99
GarageBand does very well, it's a $5 app
So there's you know
$5 and $9.99 versus $20
Is still a bit much
Well
But how much did it cost on the DS?
Probably closer to
$35
Technically it was free
Well it's been out for a while now
I mean you can buy on the DS for
Probably less than 20 bucks
Now that I'd agree with yes
So that's my issue
With that is if you know it's been
Out for a while I mean they can put it at 20 bucks
But it doesn't mean everyone's gonna buy it for that
Well look I'm gonna admit and this might like
Ruffle some feathers or whatever but
I actually didn't play this game on DS
I just didn't get around to it you know
We don't have time to play every single game
So um
I don't know if I would necessarily go out of my way
To check it out on IOS
But I know there are some fans of this game
And are really hoping it will result in a sequel
It does make me think oh I need to go back
And try the one on DS so
We'll see and um
Shima panic in our chat room
Says the world ends with you DS
Was $40 at launch
Thank you
$40 so I think mine's actually
Still in my DS makes 20 not seem so bad
Alright uh let's move on
Dark Sakura
Well um XSeed put out an announcement
That Ragnarok Odyssey is gonna have two
Editions to choose from
The first one is a standard that's only the game
And then the mercenary edition that comes with the soundtrack
A mercenary guide that's sort of
An art book and strategy guide
And monster cards um
10 random ones the standard edition is
$40 and the mercenary edition is
$50 so depends on how much money
You wanna spend for stuff that'll collect dust later
Don't know
And for fans of DS
There is a song list out for
Dance Central 3
Nine new songs actually are coming out
There's um
Afrojack featuring Eva Simmons
Takeover Control
Alexandra Stan, Mr. Saxo Beat
Half the shit I haven't heard of
I know that song
It's a total gay bar
song I don't know how else to phrase it
Sierra featuring Missy Elliott
One Two Step, Cupid with Cupid Shuffle
Daft Punk, Around the World, I love Daft Punk
Dev featuring the, what band
Is gonna call themselves the Cataracts
Hi, I'm an eye disease
Based down low
Inna featuring Natasha
I guess is how it's supposed to be
Calabria 2008
Martin Solvig featuring
Dragonette, Hello
That song's cute, I like that song
The Tramps, Disco Inferno
I fucking love Disco Inferno
Cause I was a little kid
With my Saturday Night Fever soundtracks
Freaking dancing on my bed to Disco Inferno
Any song that has
Burn Baby Burn in the lyrics
Totally down for it
Around the World
is gonna be awesome
Oh and last but
never least
There is a survival game coming up by
Can I read a comment from Stan
in our chat room? What band would call themselves
Anthrax?
Well no one ever accused
metal bands of having much in the way of intelligence
They're probably
on heroin
True statement
Allegedly
I like Anthrax actually
Who doesn't like Anthrax
But you have to be in a certain mood
for Anthrax
Anthrax is just fun, anyway
Anyway
The developer
Clay Entertainment that did Shank
Is doing a survival game called Don't
Starve that has a closed beta
available to those who pre-order the game
for a whopping $7
I hear the closed beta
is in Africa
Africa?
Because that's a game that they play all the time
Don't Starve
Anyway
It's gonna be $15 when it comes
to Steam so you're pretty much getting it for
77% off if you
order it ahead of time
The demo is on the official
site so you can give it a try
for free. It's about a
gentleman scientist who has to go to the
wilderness world of a demon
and he just doesn't starve
So it's like Tokyo Jungle with
Minecraft
I guess
I'm gonna buy it $7 why not
I can afford that
Sounds cool
Is that it?
Indeed. You don't have to break things
It's done
Alright
Let's travel to the
FUGL question of the week
What is the FUGL question of the week?
Facebook and Google Plus
Slam them together and you get FUGL
Which I know is ironic considering the first
half of our show but look
We've never been one to turn away
ways to participate with our listeners
and this is just one other way to participate with listeners
But I'm gonna start with Google Plus
Here's the question
Actually we got more
answers on Google Plus than we usually do
I know look I had to scroll
to see them all
Here it is on
FUGL question of the week
This is about the world ends with you
getting announced for iOS to extremely missed reaction
What game would you actually
like to see ported to mobile
phones, iOS, Android, whatever
your choice is or would you
be perfectly happy if we never had another
port of a classic game again
And of course we expect the listeners
to give us a little bit of why
Canaxium said anything
puzzle strategy or turn based
The controls wouldn't suffer much which is important
for the smartphone transition
Those kinds of games would also be a lot easier
to set aside with little notice
Revenge of the Titans would be a blast
Redertainment
has a very get off my
lawn approach. What happened to the good
old days when phones were phones
music players were music players and gas
cost under $2
That being said, Portal
I would like to see the classic game Portal
ported to mobiles just to see
the spectacular ways that game would crash
my phone and drain my battery like a
vampire. Classic? Well, yes
it is now a classic
No
Ok, 10 years from now
In 10 years, yeah, it'll be a classic
Alright, maybe I shouldn't have said classic
game in the question because I think Portal
is a fine answer. But anyway, also
Tetris, not the version available
now that required swiping. A version
of Tetris with button based controls that I can
play on the go seems like a great idea to me
Yes, I remember the Tetris DS exists
but I want to play competitively and my
Wi-Fi at home sucks
Jim replied saying
I would love to see a port of Deja Vu
utilizing the touch controls of course
Remember those old ass PC
games like Shadow, was it
Shadowrun? No, Shadowrun is the other game
Shadowkeep
I'm the one that likes Loom, so
No, I remember, but Deja Vu
and then there was another one, The Uninvited or something like that
there was a whole trilogy of them that was on
the NES and they were originally Mac games
if I remember right. Shadowgate
Shadowgate was freaking hard
God
Shadowgate had an amazing
soundtrack though, oh my god
I seriously, have you ever done Shadowgate as the classic game of the week
if not, you really need to think about it. I never really was
a fan of Shadowgate to be honest
I'm doing it a week you're gone then
I'll do it, I mean
I know a lot of people like it
Can I play some epic music from Shadowgate real quick? Sure
I just love the music of Shadowgate
I like this music
But then like, the death music
was really freaky
Like, shit
I died
Harpsichord furnace
Anyhow
Moving on
to Rababababa
Says Donkey Kong for iCade
It was the original April Fools joke
and it sold me on the iCade
If Nintendo ever released on
iOS phones, it should start with their
80s arcade games
Let's see
ActDeft replied, despite me hating
on the iOS port of The World Ends With You
I would really like to see Viva Pinata
on mobile. The game is great to play
for short amounts and it will keep you really occupied
playing it. Interesting, he takes an approach
that's not about controls, but about the way
we play games
And maybe a game like Viva Pinata in short
bursts is better suited for
mobile phones
How would you feel about Animal Crossing on mobile phones?
Monitoring my village
That would be crack
It would be, wouldn't it?
So
Alright, let's see
Oh, I'm just looking at our chat room
Dungeon Buster agrees, Shadowgate rocked
Chigurh said, we have a copy of Shadowgate
It was awesome
Hitstun says, it's a sad
thing that your frugal questions have come to
an end here
That's a death joke
Alright, moving on
Tiara, hi Tiara
Geek-Life.com, wonderful site
Please visit it. Tiara from Geek-Life
replies and says
This is Facebook now, by the way
They're already on every other
type of console ever, so I'd love an
iOS port of Final Fantasy 4 and Final
Fantasy 6. I have the original
Final Fantasy and Final Fantasy Tactics on
my iPhone, and I love being able to play
them when I'm on the subway or looking for something
quiet to do while my hubby is working on law school
stuff. It's great having old classics
that I love at my fingertips without
having to carry around anything larger than my phone
You know, Tiara, they did, you might
already know this, but they did a really good port of Final
Fantasy 3, the DS version
that's on the iPhone
I've been playing that. It's a pretty decent port
all things considered
So they did a DS
Final Fantasy 4
So a lot of us are actually kind of waiting
like, when would that come over
Final Fantasy 3 style to the iPhone
That would be kind of neat to see. I thought they already did that
Well, they did that for the DS4
They did 4 for the DS, but they didn't port that
to the iOS yet, you know
Which I'm sure some people, not everybody's a fan of
And plus, I don't know, like
There was a lot I liked about the DS
remake, and there was a lot I just
I didn't, just, it was just
weird seeing the sprite
based game I used to love in the 3D
environment was so weird
But then again, I would love
to see that opera scene from 6 redone
You know, there's
things I'd like
Zethurb says, Time Crisis
Touch controls for a light gun game
just sound right. That actually
does sound like a really good idea
I've already done that
Did they do Time Crisis? I believe they did
Oh, well, maybe Zethurb needs to go check the store
How about Point Blank then?
How about Point Blank? I was gonna say Point Blank would be awesome
Great fucking suggestion
Nick M. replies and says
I would love a port of the original
Worms Armageddon, not a sequel because
Team 7 has screwed up every Worms game since
I chose this game because the gameplay
and fun factor would not be affected by
touch controls. I could see that
I'm sure there's Worms clones, there's gotta be
Worms all over the marketplace already
Um
Allen replied and said
Troll answer. Steel battalion
Serious answer
I think the Panzer Dragoon
games would clean up nice and make great
use of tilt controls. Res would be great
too. Steer with tilt and drag
finger for linking targets. That's
surprisingly not a bad idea
Good job, Allen
Matt replied, Matt J. replied on Facebook
with a no. We're finally seeing some no's
I personally feel we should
not port various titles to mobile platforms
These platforms are not designed
with these games in mind. Virtual
controls simply do not work
most of the time. My favorite iOS
titles have been built from the ground up for mobile
platforms. Games which were designed
with physical controls in mind, which
specific hardware in mind just don't translate
well to the ever changing mobile platforms
I agree with what some have said
The World Ends With You is worth $20
It's worth $20 on the DS
It's not worth $2 on iOS
It will not be as good of an experience
A good example is
Grand Theft Auto 3. I got it from my
iPad. I've yet to beat the very first mission
for the horrible car controls just drive
me nuts. I beat the same game
years back on the PC. Loved it
I'm just glad I only paid a buck for
Grand Theft Auto 3 iOS
Did they ever do Dragon's Lair?
Yes. I'm sure they did
I was just thinking that one would be perfect
I'm gonna quickly go through some of these other ones
I'll just read kind of the game
or whatever
Haseo Sumurogaro replied and said
no
in a nutshell because IOS will fuck it up
like they fuck up most games
Locopoco replied saying
a mobile version of the adventure game
The Neverhood point and click adventure games
would be great ported and he's not
happy about the Square Enix
World Ends With You remake
Stan replied a new chapter to the Space Channel
5 series
for IOS or for anything
Hitstun said
Missile Command and Crystal Castles
work great on multi-touch phones
You know they do have that in the Atari
thing. I think he said
I think he knows that because he says they work great
on multi-touch phones. What about Marble Madness?
That's a good idea too
He does say more faithful ports
of classic trackball games
Marble Madness. There he is
Marble Madness he says. An arcade perfect port
Capcom Bowling would be a
natural too. Maybe we could get
a port for the Japanese only
Sega Sonic the Hedgehog
There's a game called Manic Marble
Lastly I'm not sure what Clover Nikon means by
this comment. LucasArts Outlaws
first person shooter. Was that a game? LucasArts
I don't know the game Outlaws. Is that a
LucasArts game that I'm just not ringing a bell?
Because I think LucasArts I think of the
old strategy games
like Loom
and Indiana Jones and shit
and Maniac Mansion and all that
I'm looking right now
Of course I'm sure the chatters at live.vognetwork.com
will be happy
to correct me in a minute
I'm looking right now
Let's see
Outlaws yeah shooter game for the Commodore 64
I'll be damned
1985 and 1997 there were different releases
That's not the one
The 1997 release must be the one he's talking about
Yes it was LucasArts and the Jedi Engine
I didn't know this game at all
Now I want to look it up
Was it Jedi Outlaws?
No it was done in that Jedi Engine
Let me look
The first person shooter one that was from 1997
or whatever
I'm looking it up right now
except YouTube won't work
so I'll have to look later
Alright
anything quickly you guys would like to
see on iOS or not
Second point blank
Yeah
A real Marble Madness I guess
I'd like a Marble Madness sequel
type of thing
Maybe a better version of Silent Hill
and Metal Gear Solid those shooters
On iOS though
I can't see Silent Hill on iOS
They had a Silent Hill
iPhone game and it was terrible
It was like the old Sega shooter games
Any of the Sega shooters would be pretty cool
Like um
Uh
I'm trying to think of what I was thinking here
Gunblade
Gunblade would be fucking awesome
Also
Yeah it was any of the shooters
Any of their
arcade stuff
Alright I knew the chatters wouldn't let me down
VxJsonXV says Outlaws was quite fun indeed
I think I bought it at some point
and sucked at it a lot for some reason
Dungeon Buster says
Outlaws cutscenes had the same animated look
that Full Throttles did only stylized
for a western adventure
Um
Tykey in our chat reminds us there was Marble Madness
too it was called Marble Man
Marble Man I don't think that ever actually came out
though it's like a prototype thing one of those like
legendary games right
Alright S2 under Matt says this sounds like a listless
topic alright maybe
Maybe next time maybe next time
Alright let's get some more news out of the way Loki
Alright so um
It's unfortunate but
Nintendo Power is coming to an end
their last issue will be running in December
and unfortunately
they just have no plans
on continuing it any further than that
and you know before you know they were
you know running it
through in house stuff
but then it was
forwarded to future publishing in
2007 and
that's that
just I guess
not print media is just not
as popular anymore as it used to be
um and then of course Nintendo is
going to be getting their news out slightly
differently can I just say this real quick
about Nintendo Power though because like I saw a lot
of the people on Twitter and Facebook were saying like
oh this makes me really sad
I used to love this magazine as a kid
and oh I remember when I had
Nintendo Power and it's just kind of funny like I
you know and while it is sad in a way
I think you're really sad that you're getting older
because nobody said
oh I'm really sad it's going away because
I'm currently subscribed
nobody said that
like I think a lot of people are just sad
because it's a relic from their childhood
it's no longer there but
hello they went bankrupt because nobody was still
subscribed anybody in here subscribed to
Nintendo Power currently? Nope
and let's be real it's changed
hands over the years and so forth and there is no
more Howard and Nestor
it's just it's tough for a
print magazine to survive right now
it's tough I would have loved for an ebook
that makes me so sad
because that's like what I went to school
for
got to evolve into the digital format
wouldn't it have been great on the Wii U tablet
you could have flipped through pages or something
it would have been awesome
so to get the word out about the Wii U
release date and pricing September
13th they're going to be doing another
press event
they're going to be talking about it it's going to be held in
New York City and
at least that's assumed what they're going to be talking about
is Wii U pricing and release
date
$249 for $349
and November 18th
we'll see
that's just a guess
allegedly
the titles that were released on the 20th
now move to the 13th
alright we'll see
alright moving on
you remember Adventure on the Atari 2600
I mean back in the days
of the Atari 2600 where we had games like
baseball
basketball
video pinball
we had Adventure and a lot of people remember
Adventure because it was the very first game to have an Easter egg
or at least a prominent Easter egg
which had the hidden designer's name
in it because if you want to go way back
go back to a time where designers
would not get credit for games and sometimes it would leave
them a little frustrated so you could find
that in Adventure well also
Adventure was just kind of a neat little game that
a lot of games like you see things in
Adventure that influence the Legend of Zelda
for real like a lot of what comes
Legend of Zelda was in Adventure on the
Atari 2600 and therefore it has
its fans and
more than 30 years later we're looking at
yet another sequel to Adventure
now I believe there was a prototype some time
ago of Adventure 2 but that's not
part of the canon that we have
now what we do have is
that in 2009 there was Evil Magician
Returns which was
programmed by Bite Knight from the
Atari Age forums and he did this in
2009 and this is in reference to
the unseen antagonist who
stole and hid the chalice in the original game
he didn't have the rights to call it
Adventure 2 but he could call it Evil Magician
hooray generic bad guy
well now Evil Magician
Returns 2
ahhhh
he's back bitch
you have to overcome both
him and his apprentice
they are personally guarding the chalice
keys, mages
mazes, flickering
grottos and bats
and it has
come out yes it is an adventure
game there has to be an easter egg in there
somewhere so be on the lookout for that
you know I gotta say this
for an Atari 2600
game the graphics are pretty sweet
I know you're looking at this
picture of the game and laughing at me but
hello remember what the original
adventure looked like like this is a step up
I love that people are still
programming for the Atari 2600
of course
ROMs allow them to make the
games however big they want
I don't think this is actually getting printed on
a cartridge no but
it's just neat that there's still all that
love for the Atari 2600
so there you go
Dark Sakura?
well for those who are still
playing Diablo 3 and I know that there are
da da da
there is
going to be new upgrade levels
for all of those who have reached your level cap
it's called the
Paragon system which has nothing to do
with Mass Effect
has 100 additional levels
for you to push through once you meet
the current level max
it's coming in update 1.0.4
and basically all of your
experience that you get after 60
will be put into your Paragon levels
so it gives you a boost in your core stats
and
an extra 3% boost
in magic and gold find
also
there is this
trying to find
where exactly it was
the Nephilim Valor bonuses
will also give a 15% boost
in experience towards the Paragon levels per stack
so fun
I love that they
made the end game more exciting by basically
adding 100 levels
pretty much
apparently there is some game balance things and other things
they did too, like we talked about this on
Horde House a little bit
and Extifer has been playing a lot of Diablo
lately because he's not really playing WoW right now
but him and his partner play a lot
of Diablo and he says
it's great that the game balancing and everything is great
me, I haven't touched Diablo since like the first
month it came out but maybe
I need to take a second look after
WoW and Guild Wars
and all that other stuff
free with blood packed
which you can't sign up for anymore
just a couple more news stories for you guys
in the mailbag
mailbag at orangesloungeradio.com is where the emails
go but first some more stories
alright
now this is kind of interesting
you remember that whole
Peter Molyneaux thing that they were doing
on the iOS platform where it was
basically this
curiosity is what the game is called
and it was kind of controversial
because you can buy
in-game things to help you
chip away at this cube faster including
one piece that's $50,000
or $5,000
so anyways that game's been delayed
to September and
also because it's been delayed
I'm not sure if this is the reason but
they had to change their title because
you may remember there was a certain
program from NASA that landed
a rover on Mars named
Curiosity and
yeah that was kind of
bad so now it's
that wasn't bad
no it was bad for Curiosity because
they couldn't use the name
bad for Peter Molyneaux but fuck him
so now it's not just Curiosity
it's Curiosity what's in the
cube or what's inside the cube
is what it's called
WHAT'S IN THE BOX
TELL ME WHAT'S IN THE BOX
anyone?
pretty much yeah
you don't get seven
so they have that going on right now
I gotta wonder though
when is the next Apple announcement
for iOS 6 isn't that supposed to be
in September sometime?
the iPhone 5 announcement is heavily rumored
for September 12 which is just
a few weeks away really
and I'm assuming that's probably when we're gonna see iOS 6
oh absolutely yeah
iOS 6 was the one that had that patch in it
or they're supposed to be patching that loophole right now
where you can get free DLC
probably they wouldn't want to
release that game that has
$5,000 or $50,000 DLC
when there's a loophole to get that for free
wouldn't you think?
that might kind of skew the way the game's played
just the thought
I thought they were able to
fix that I thought they patched it
somewhere on the back end
Chiggers in our chat says
dick in a box
that would be fucking hilarious
actually Peter Molyneaux
would gain my ultimate
respect if what's in the box
my dick
that would
make headlines
I mean you'd have
to have a real egotistical person
to pull a stunt like that
you could do it
how would you feel Dark
Sakura if you opened the box
because you were curious and
it's his dick
I'm just getting blinked at
I feel short changed
alright moving on
Konami is set to shake the industry
god damn it
what is wrong with our web tonight?
alright I remember this story from earlier though
Konami is
I forget who said it in an event
I want to say it was Kojima
somebody involved with Kojima Productions
because there's an announcement coming up
from Metal Gear's 25th anniversary
and they were quoted in saying
Ken Mandaza
with Kojima Productions
that was quoted in saying
that the industry
is going to get shaken up
yeah they have a lot of things to look forward to
next week not just for fans
but I think the industry is going to be shook
they're going to be able to present here
at least it's not a Frogger game
that's all I know
oh I finally got it here
I was going to say my internet is working just fine
I don't know
it's because I streamed the show and all that off this computer too
but anyway we will find out what the shakedown is
August 30th
when this event
is placed there at Tokyo Midtown
alright whatever
moving on
let's get to the mailbag
every week you guys send us emails
mailbag at orangelaungerator.com
DarkSakura dives into the mailbag head first
hope she doesn't find any anthrax
sticky!
unless they're 80s metal bands
dude anthrax on public enemy just saying
alright read the emails dammit
hey sexies
this labor day me and sally's girl
this is from gem sally by the way
me and sally's girl are going to catch up on portal 2
we bought that game day 1
and neither of us has beat it yet
I'm hoping we can tap out those
portals all day then tap out
her portal all night oh yeah
if you were stuck on a desert island
with your sexy partner and could bring only
one game to play what's the sexiest
game you can think of to bring
sexually yours gem sally
sent from the sexy wifi cafe
on the sally train choo choo motherfuckers
um you wouldn't have
any um electricity
on a deserted island
let's make believe there's a bike
that will power it
fuck that well you know if the professor
from Gilligan's Island could get it would be
something on the internet so I would have
um net gaming
and GPS it would be
something on my phone so I could turn on my where is my
phone feature and people could find me that way
you're so not fun
low key
well if it's with a bicycle then it's gotta be
a prop cycle I added
a bicycle go back to the original question
sexiest game to take to the desert
island sexiest game
desert island
guy game
damn he took my answer
um
I would say I don't know
some of the some of the scenes in mass effect
you know if you're into uh
you know whatever it is you're into if it's uh
you know shepard and garris or
in my case shepard and alinko you know some of those
uh can be pretty
well guess what I don't
get you either so
step off
next email
don't make me smite you
actually I thought of another
answer too late
power pad games
dance aerobics
humps master
um no it'd be custer's revenge
ok greetings orange
knowledge radio this is a message from
hasseo sumi ragawa
regarding final fantasy and their rampant cases
of disappearing acts yeah we oh this is
what we covered ok so six years
ago square enix announced final fantasy
versus 13 as part of the fabula
nova crystallis and since then
they put out a few trailers
talking about the stories a bit
and six years later there's nothing because it came out in japan
um there hasn't even
been present at e3
but that's not my point
now last november square announced that they were
going to release final fantasy 10 again and needless to
say I squeed my voice horse
um after that nothing so this
brings me to my point is there going to be
is this going to be a trend with square
announce the games that won't come out for years and years and let's
face it look at what happened to duke nukem
forever oh that game was
crap um one last note
to lookies I'm aware you're
smart with modding and
computers correct okay so
two questions firstly
um my boyfriend's computer
doesn't have the programs installed onto his computer
is there a way to fix that I don't
it says
sorry for bad grammar but honestly the grammar
is so bad that I can hardly make heads or
tails of the lines
doesn't have the programs
installed I
guess to mod then
install the programs where do you
recommend to go buy a new
hard drive for a ps3 and what's the larger size
you can get uh
ps3 can fit any hard drive that you can
fit in the bay that's in there it's two and a half
um inch
sata drives laptop sata
drive so you can put
whatever I think I put a 500
gigabyte one in mine and
it was a
scorpio
blue I think
or something like that I don't remember what it's called
western digital or something like that
um just look online for
uh hard drives that'll fit
I think you have to watch out when you get
really big hard drive sizes
the actual hard drive itself gets
thicker and it might not fit in the actual
um bay that they have
so you have to kind of watch what you can fit in there
uh at least I know that's the case with
um with the xbox
when you're modding that
as far as modding like I'm assuming they're asking
about modding the ps3 stuff
um just download the apps
you may have to check out some of the websites
like there's uh
dashhax.com
or dot net or something
dashhax is the website they have
information about doing hacks
on playstation 3
psp vita when there's
that stuff available you know pretty much
any consoles and ios
and phones and that kind of stuff so
that'd be kind of a good source for finding some of
the tools to flash a custom
uh
firmware or what not
to your playstation 3
at least that's how I did it when I did mine
then I flashed it back to stock because I just wasn't
using
you know I wasn't pirating games or anything on that
cause you know games are fucking
huge cause they're blu ray games so it's
just I had nothing I really wanted
to even I would want to even
pirate so um I just buy games
now but um
so yeah so there's that
just look online
there's youtube videos out there that'll tell you how to do it
alright so next email
yes
okay uh like I said
that's from um hasayasumiragawa
so um hello guys
and girl and darksacro okay
I just wanted to talk a little bit about
my favorite portable game of the past generation which you
briefly mentioned in the past
two weeks releases I am of course
talking about bokuakoku
kansai kansai kan
for psp which is
um I am an air traffic
controller airport hero um
unlike games with similar names on
aya such as flight controller pocket planes
this is a real puzzle game based on the very
real intricacies of air traffic control
basically you play the role
of the five people in the atc tower
at the same time telling pilots what
routes to take um
coming into and out of the airport giving
permission to land and take off giving
taxing instructions and confirming flight plans
as the stages get harder more
and more plans arrive in your airspace more plans
prepare to take off you have to juggle up to
ten different pilots vying for your attention
with only five radio channels
take too long and the pilots get stressed push buttons
without thinking and you'll cause a crash
it's hectic, frantic, and utterly gripping
um he's got a video up
um of what it's like so
uh I'm not gonna go too far into that
it says the 3ds version um came out
last week is pretty similar but with cuter graphics
and I would urge anyone who enjoys
time management puzzle games to look into this
as you read this I
will likely be in Disneyland Paris
watching new Disney dreams nighttime spectacular
wish you were here
and that's uh from pikaruno
oh well you did say wish you were here at the end
so I can't be too mean bring me back something duffy
and last email
uh
this uh
this is hello olr after a long time
I finally got to play binary domain
I wish some interest
I had some interest in it but I somehow never
compelled to buy it thinking it would just
be another shooter my girlfriend got it for me
a couple days ago and I started playing
and just could not stop this game
is awesome I was told
to sing it by the way
and you did and I did
sure it's not perfect
controls aren't always spot on and the voice recognition
isn't very good but the deep story
future Tokyo environment graphics
voice acting and sound make it
a very good game you can literally
shoot robots to pieces and it isn't that
same gritty and brown
world you see in countless other games
this is the very first game that gave
me goosebumps while playing the end sequence
that's saying a lot when I get emotional
about a game Sega should be deeply
ashamed for not promoting this game more
binary domain vanquished bayonetta are all
games that deserve better when you
get the chance buy this as it is very
cheap that's all I have to say at this time
as always thanks a lot for
making an episode of OLR every week
you guys are amazing yours truly
I'm just going to say first name Fabrice from
Belgium
yay international emails yay
I want to go to
Belgium and not
for the waffles Loki
but you
would have to have a waffle while you're there just to see
no I would have to have
chocolate chocolate and trapeze
ale there you go just saying
she may she may comes from Belgium and she may is
fucking amazing
alright it's time for us to get a little bit
angsty here with the F
use of the week
where is my
angst music
music
um I guess fuck you to
concrete and the person in the Toyota
who didn't use their turn signal at
all and then tried to stop
in front of me no you're a dick face
um and
uh
I really don't know I guess
me for changing
my schedule to seven in
the morning but at least I'm only
out 30 minutes of sleep and
I don't have to deal with
crap traffic in the morning also
I really want a bagel but no
wheat wheat is bad for me
bagels are so good though
alright hush
Loki uh I guess
the only really F you that I can think of
would be the F you too
the person that's in front of me while I was coming into
your um your apartment
complex um they
decided to park in front of the gate like they
drove through the gate wow
and then parked right there I'm like are you
kidding me and he's just sitting there I
he looks at his mirror
what oh
I guess I'll pull forward
a little bit it's like dude you're in the fucking
middle of the god damn entrance it's
just like selfishly inconsiderate what in the
hell find a parking space
entitlement and don't think there's anybody else in the world
it's like I don't know what's wrong with these people
that's it
my view of the week goes to the web and on this
computer right now I don't get what the hell's going on but like
everything is like timing out I'm
the same to me yeah I'm having to like run shit off
my iPad right now I don't know it's
weird I don't know luckily the stream
is staying up and that's the most important thing I just hope
Skype will stay up as well it's doing
the same thing at my house but like
I can't do I'm
really upset because somebody had a funny joke
earlier when Jim Sally sent the email about
what sexy games do you want to see on the
sexy island dark Tetsuya
in chat said miss nude world 96
which was a perfect excuse for me
to play that everybody move your body
clip but thanks to the web errors I can't
get the clip up
F you to the web
for making me lose out on the funny
hate
two more
news stories then phone calls
first Loki I'm even turning off everything on my
iPhone just to see if it helps
so there's a few demakes
we should talk about the first being
Borderlands Borderlands actually
was demade into a 16
bit top down shooter game
for your browser
so you can check it out it's
they call it the border lands
and you
can check it I love this website
you can check it at
www.wubwub.eu
slash demake.php
wub wub wub wub wub
amazing
so that's pretty cool and then
since we were talking about Atari 2600
earlier somebody has decided
to demake the Super Mario Brothers
for the Atari 2600
now or at least
it's done in the Atari 2600
style and he's got
I guess a demo with
level warp pipes
yellow blocks and flag poles
and I guess 15 levels
up to 4-4 is what he's
hoping to do and have a Koopa Kid
at the end of each world as a boss
pretty cool
and if you want to check that out
indiegames.com has got
the link for that
I'm surprised it took that long
for a Super Mario demake surely this isn't
the first it's just the most recent one
yeah we go to the Atari age forums
there's a
bin file for
your
emulators
alright well if you ever saw the movie The King of
Kong you did not
see Hank Chien in that movie
even though he is now the official
world record holder of Donkey Kong
he came after the movie
thank god that wasn't one of the titles for the contest man
the whole back and forth what?
the Ready Player One contest
oh yeah right
thank god it wasn't because
Hank Chien would have won it again because guess what
he broke his own record
so you got to appreciate a guy who will keep
challenging himself
like there's none of this you know
Steve Weeby and all this stuff going on here
he's challenging himself
so he beat his previous record
1,110,100 points
the new record
1,127,700 points
that's the new
score from Hank Chien
if you haven't heard that name of course
he was the Donkey Kong world record holder before
after that whole movie mess and all that stuff
I believe
what is it by day he's a plastic surgeon isn't he?
and that's how he can afford
all these machines
you pay him for a new
well I noticed in this picture he's posing next
to a Donkey Kong machine and there's a moon patrol
machine in the background too
now I don't know if that's because he's at an arcade
like maybe some type of publicity event
cause I know Fun Spot
he's got way too much smug on his face
eh I don't necessarily think it's smug
some people just take interesting pictures
those machines aren't that terribly expensive
he could be a nice guy
for an arcade game that's not bad
yeah the Kong Off 2
that's what they call a Kong Off
sounds like something dirty
but anyway the Kong Off 2
is where they gather the best Donkey Kong players
at one location for glorious live
competition
not that they're saying he's gonna be in it
but there's obviously a lot of pressure
for him to show up which would be pretty cool
so
SSJ100Matt in our chat room
at chat.orangelandrater
not that one
live.vognetwork.com says
look guys it was 9 years of one particular website
SSJ100Matt says and Billy Mitchell
zero fucks given about him
or his damn hot sauce
I hear the hot sauce isn't bad
just saying
alright that takes us to
the skype part of the show
that's the part of the show
where we're gonna open up the skype lines
at 1-877-GAME-OLR
and take your phone calls
live on the program
we will get to the twitter as well
twitter.com slash olr in just a moment
but first we're gonna go to the phones and
oh we already have a call on the line let's go to it
hi you're on Orange Lodge Radio who's this
hey guys it's Jason
hey Jason what's up
so as you so wonderfully
alluded to earlier in the show
I was at
the Wii U consumer experience
here in Denver just yesterday
apparently I think my friend
told me they've been in since Thursday
and since he went to E3 he had codes
assigned me and a friend up and we all
got to go out there and see the
I'm assuming they're all gonna be
launch titles or something that's gonna happen
within the first couple of months
and it's just really interesting
cause I was hearing obviously you're cross with Bobby
and you guys were really
putting the Wii U down
it's kind of astounding
to me
I understand in the fact that it's
gonna be a lot of the same thing
and you have to get a whole new console
just to be able to use the tablet even
though everything else is gonna be the same
controllers, the Wii Fit balance
board and all that kind of stuff
but I don't know
that speaking as a gamer myself
somebody who will pay the money to get something
like this and not the common
people that paid 200 bucks to play
Wii Sports forever
Jason I'm more worried about the games
it's not the console myself
or the console itself
but I see a lot of what was happening with the 3DS
happening here, you have a lot of mediocre
launch titles and I
don't think any really big standouts
here's your chance to change
my mind, what did you get your hands on
that you are excited to drop money
for a new console for?
They didn't really speak release dates
and actually as a matter of fact when the event was wrapping up
they had this little quick little
trivia session, they were giving out a bunch of
silly little prizes and one of them
was a trick question, when is the Wii U
coming out, the answer was holidays
but there's otherwise no specific
date barring what Loki
said earlier about the 13th
you know that the correct answer is November 18th, I would have got him
even the people putting on this event
wouldn't know that though
yeah it wasn't NDA'd
it wasn't sales, it wasn't media
this is just bring your friends
and let's play some really cool games
we'll show you some stuff, and it was really fun
the boost that they set up, the things that I actually
had, I didn't get my hands on everything
but they had setups
for Nintendo Land cycling
through some of the mini arcade games
Game and Wario
Super Mario Brothers Wii U, Zombie U
Batman Arkham City, Pikmin 3
Just Dance 4, Wii Fit
U, Rayman Legends
and then two non-finally
named Project P100
and Sing
and they
looked good, that's all I really
have to say about it
on the surface is that these games
looked spectacular
Super Mario Brothers, exactly
as it was on the Wii, I love
that art style, I love the way it played
the tablet integration looks fun if you happen
to have a second person to play
with, but then Pikmin
looked gorgeous and the new effects
that they're
they're not, if they support 3D
TV that's news to me, but the fact that they
were actually throwing things
at the camera and whatnot and actually
given this serious
spatial angle to it and not just
you know, a bird's eye corner
view of it, it just
looks like it played marvelously well
Alright, so it's the Nintendo
stuff you love in HD
but again, did you
get your hands on the games? Did you play any games?
Which ones stood out for you?
I played Super Mario Brothers
Wii U
Super Mario Brothers Wii U
I played a couple of the games from Nintendo Land
and then I played
as far as I understand, pretty much a whole level of
Game and Legends
As I'm sure a lot of people know, Nintendo Land
is mostly a series of
mini-games that are developed to really take
advantage notably of the tablet
but also give you a really good multiplayer experience
The very first
thing I did was play Luigi's Ghost
Mansion playing the flashlight tag
where the ghost is playing on the
tablet and is invisible for the large
part and then the four players
with Wiimotes have to move
around, have to move around the
mansion, the maze trying to find the ghost
and reviving players that go down
anything else like that
These games
I could not say that these games
were not complete and ready for retail
release
It was a two hour
event, tops, and we
were playing in increments
of like ten minutes at best
usually much shorter than that
I can't
really find the words for it other than the fact that
it feels like it will be a more complete
library than any other
system launch that I've actually
jumped into at the very start of it
and then especially things like
Zombiou and Batman Arkham City look
absolutely stunning
I've played Mad World
and yeah, that's not supposed to be the
realistic graphics or anything
but Arkham City and Zombiou looked
absolutely fantastic, this wasn't
the thin arm red
steel or any other nonsense like that
Out of curiosity, have you played
Arkham City on 360 or
PlayStation 3? Unfortunately,
no. See, that's
where I have to admit, not that
I question your opinion, but I go, well
it looks beautiful on the other systems too, and it's
been out for a year
And it's not just about the graphics, but the fact that this is something
that's going to be available at some
point within the launch
within the general launch window
means that this is a
big tier title
that's going to be on Nintendo's system
that a lot of people already own
because it came out last year
also true
I absolutely will not deny that, and like I was saying
at the start of the call, I think
that a lot of people
are going to paint a very negative
picture of the Wii U after it comes
out because it's not going to have
the runaway success that the first Wii did
because all of the
casuals, all of the people that
otherwise have never owned a gaming system
won't see the reason to
buy this, maybe
and so it'll, it
won't sell, it won't take
off so ridiculously like the original Wii
did, but that's not a bad
thing because this is, this
is Nintendo, in my
absolute opinion, this is Nintendo making things
better for gamers at large
Project P100 is
a very Pikmin-esque
action game, which
is great because there's finally a
second game with that low army
control mechanism
and it's set in a very, in a much
more technological, like in a
scene that a lot of people would prefer, I'm sure
I just, I have to
admit, Jason, despite your enthusiasm
I'm not sure I'm completely sold, and it
comes down to the games issue, and it's
really about what
I just, it's not,
and to be fair, to Nintendo's credit
it's kind of the same mistake as the Vita
too, is that the Vita
did come with a few kick-ass launch
games, and there was certainly a lot to look forward
to, but I don't know
what's been delivered on hasn't
exactly matched the hype, and
this is all about the games department
and it's kind of what I worry about with the
Wii U as well, because we haven't seen a lot
past the launch window, and you know
there's not a lot to just
really, really get excited about
because I played a lot of these
Mass Effect 3, Arkham City on
360, and I'm not really
interested in playing them again with tablet controls
because it doesn't sound like it's going to change that much
so I have to look to things like
Nintendo Land, and Pikmin 3
and New Super Mario Brothers Wii U
and all this to pique my
interest, and it's just, I'm not
I'm not as excited as
say, the hype behind the
original Wii, and how we felt
about that Zelda game, was a
phenomenal launch, I mean
has there ever been a better
launch game for a console since the original
Super Mario Brothers?
Certainly not one I've actually been there for
Than Zelda for the Wii?
I mean I guess I was just hoping for something of that
magnitude, and Nintendo Land
ain't it!
The thing that really sets this apart
one of the feelings that I did come away with
is that, you know
true to Nintendo's spirit, this stuff
works, a lot of the things that they were showcasing
make it really compelling
for local multiplayer, you know
knock Nintendo's online services
all you want, I completely agree with it
but having that
second player, or in some cases
that fifth player, to be able to take over
controls with the tablet
is actually immensely fun, the fact that
me and
one of my two friends that were there with me
were planning on who wants to do
which function of the game, just
added a really different element
for example, Rayman Legends
the Wiimote
or actually in this case it was the
pro controller, whatever they're
going to call it for the Wii U
the standard controller user is controlling
Rayman, throwing shots
jumping, all that kind of thing, jumping on
obstacles, attacking, where the tablet
is manipulating the
environment, it's moving platforms
around, they had the whole rotation
demonstration where you're walking
Rayman's running through a maze, and the
person holding the tablet has to orient
the level by turning the
entire device in order to
allow them to jump to the next
ring, land on solid grounds
lands not on spikes
and the biggest thing that
they showed off, as I said
was that with a second person
these games just got
ridiculously more interesting
Zombie, you had this
capture the flag
not capture the flag
the game mode where you have like three
or five waypoints that you have to
capture and defend and that kind of stuff
and the player
with the standard controller
owned the TV
and would attack
Zombies and was pretty much the one man army
and then the person holding the tablet
had like a real time strategy
kind of interface where he could take
hordes of Zombies and send them to the
particular waypoints and actually drill
into this real time strategy that's
not really been seen at the
same time like that
with a lot of the stuff though
all these games are reliant on
you having about four or five
people in your living room
it's all local multiplayer
where's my online multiplayer for
to Nintendo's credit
that could be an ace in the hole on September
13th, we still don't know what
Nintendo Network really is
despite the fact it's being branded on Nintendo
cartridges, that could be
coming and I'd be okay with that if there's
a huge unveil on September 13th
so I would wait on the online
piece to be too critical about that until
we have that event, but if we still don't
hear about it at that event, that it ain't coming
with the release of the Wii U and now we should be concerned
but let me ask this
this call's going a little long and that's okay Jason
because we love you, but I want to ask
I want to ask you one more question shaped off
a chat comment we got here at live.vognetwork.com
and ShadowNextGen
in chat who's agreed with you
in many ways and I saw it throughout Bobby's show
tonight, he kind of didn't
he thought
what I was saying was kind of wrong and he's
more supportive of the Wii U, he sounds a lot like
you and what you're saying and
he says, what this says to
me is more people need to get
actual hands on time with
the Wii U, so let me
ask you this Jason, you've had hands
on time with the Wii U, I haven't
Loki hasn't, Dark Sakura hasn't
what do you think, and you
you are clearly in love with this
thing more so than us skeptics here
what do you
think you gain that we're missing
having had hands on time with the system
see and that's
that's a really funny question I'll try to
summarize in the fact that I
me and Ryan don't play a lot of the same
games and I'm hoping she's going to be
interested in the aspects that are opened up
with this simultaneous multiplayer of standard
controllers and the tablets, but that
that is absolutely like Nintendo's
biggest deal that they're trying to
push here is that this is going to be great
for families of at least
two gamers because
in their whole demos you know they
can play a standard game reserved
solely to the tablet and give the TV
back to someone else, that is
killer, and this is a fully fledged
game that's not confined to
a phone that has a limited amount of
controls and you can do
all sorts of media while giving the TV
back to somebody else, but for
these Wii U optimized games where you
have your hands on the tablet, this is
engaging somebody else at
the same time, usually in a completely
distinct way, you know what that also means?
That means both people
get to play the game in two in times
completely different methods.
I mean for all the replayability
complaints and what
we complain about in modern gaming, this
is two different ways to play the same
game. That's
ridiculously cool
to me. I was sold on the system before
I went to this event, I touched, I
had my hands on it,
I am 100% sold on the system
now. I will absolutely say
that. I am like so with you up to a point
Jason because I do really want, no I really
do want to love this system and I want to,
I'll probably get one anyway, who are we kidding?
I mean I've said that since day one.
I'm skeptical as all hell
but I'll still fucking buy one because I'm a
consumer of horror.
God damn it, I lost
my train of thought.
Where you don't, this is where you don't agree.
No here it is, here it is.
Where are the games
that substantiate what you're saying?
I know you
brought this up before, which of these, do you
remember my list of games at the very start of the call?
Yes. Do you
know what the launch dates,
what the launch, oh Jesus.
What games will be launched
in the holiday window?
Pretty much everything that you named is in the
holiday window. And that's not enough to
start a system?
Yes.
When half
your list is stuff that's already
been out with a new method that
again, now we go back to the phone
conversation about
games that weren't developed for that system.
Don't know, I mean, yeah, okay
so we'll have this tablet interaction, but these games
weren't designed with the tablet thing in mind.
They're kind of trying to shoehorn that
stuff in there, which is fine, whatever, show off
the system, but I'm not that, I am not
excited about Arkham City with the pad.
I'm not, I am not excited
about Mass Effect 3 with the touchpad.
Sorry, I'm not.
So, you know, that's half the games right
off the table. Now my interest is
peaked, my eyebrow is raised a little bit at things
like Zombie U, Peekman
3, I kind of consider
New Star Mario Brothers Wii at this point.
It's half rehash, half
a successful formula just being
done again. But
a couple games, no, it's really not
enough. Look at the 3DS.
Look at the 3DS, I think
they're making the exact same mistake, I really do.
Look at the Vita launch, I mean, they had a ton of games
that a lot of them were original
and that still didn't help the system.
Yeah, and SSJ100, Matt, thank you, you fill in the
gap here really well. I want to know what's coming
out after these launch window games.
What is Nintendo going to do to warrant this investment
because that's what console games are, investments.
I think that is what Nintendo
really has to show us September 13th
if they want to woo some of the skeptics over
because I'll tell you, they come out and they show
off that 3D Zelda game or they
whip out F-Zero or
a Metroid Prime type of thing that's in that
HD experience, I'm totally
on board.
Final thought? Yes. You are going
to love Sing.
Provided the song list pans
out and it's not more
freaking LMFAO
We'll see.
Provided the song list comes up with some really good gems
you are going to adore
Sing. I can pretty much promise you that.
Will it be all ABBA
songs? Because otherwise Sing Star ABBA
still has my heart.
The only songs they had
were Shoop Shoop
Party Rock Anthem and Call
Me Maybe and they haven't really let on
what else is going to be there. Oh god, that's like
my personal hell.
Those sure, like I said, provided
the song list is actually worth it and I
have to hope that we'll sing is going to be
spectacular for parties. Jason,
I got to let you go. Some of the chatters think you're a
Nintendo sales person in disguise.
I got to let you go. Alright. Thanks guys.
Have a good week. You too, buddy. Take care.
Alright. VX Jason
XV. We let his call go on a little long, but that's
alright. I mean, he was there. He got
hands on. We're skeptics. Whatevs.
Let's do like one more
call. 1877 Game OLR or
username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
While we wait for those calls to come in, let me
quickly see if I can do a Twitter topic here.
Tiger Claw
links us on Twitter.
This is one
that I read in the news that
forgot to mention on the show tonight,
but it's important. Uncharted
film has burned through yet another
director.
I'll have to read more on this after another
call because the phone's lighting up. Hi, you're on
OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this? Holy crap
it's Ranma and I get the ass into the Skype
chats. That's sweet. What's up,
Ranma? Not too much.
You guys are talking about
Kickstarter and stuff like that, so I've come
across something that's quite interesting.
Well, when I was at
Otacon last month, I was in the game room
and they had this game called
Epic Beatdown
Otaku Style.
What? Yes.
Okay,
is it something you actually brave to try
or... Yes, it's
an anime equivalent of
Double Dragon meets Scott Pilgrim vs.
the World, the game.
Wow. And you can
check out their plans on
StudioNasu.com, which I am posting
in the chat room right now.
It pretty much,
from what I understand,
you're at Otacon and you're just
pretty much beating up on the fanboys,
more or less.
And as
somebody who goes to anime conventions
quite frequently and all this stuff, how do you
feel? Hey,
I'm all for it. You talk to somebody
at any given time who has a weapon on and
you're trying to help somebody. You gotta be able to laugh
at yourself first. I'll put a weapon
as a can of deodorant.
Well, one con
actually put
soap in their bags
and people got pissed at that so they decided
not to do it again, but that's besides the point.
Alright.
Did you just call to whore this con
going game or what else is going on in your life,
Rama? Yeah, that's more or less
it. Well, you know, that and we've already discussed
New Super Mario Brothers 2, so my two
cents on that doesn't really count. Well, what
is your, no, of course, every
gamer has a voice. Every gamer
has a voice. Use that voice. You are
Black Luigi after all. I want to know what
Black Luigi thinks
about Mario 2. It's important, dammit.
I'm a Luigi, number
one gaming star.
So what do you think about Mario
2 on, excuse
me, New Super Mario Brothers 2
on the 3DS? It
lacks. Ooh,
sick burn. Why is that?
I don't know. It's, you know how you play
a game and you just look at it like it's just
lacking and you can't put your
finger on what it is, but it's just lacking
something. I mean, I like
the fact they brought back the raccoon tail,
so I'm thinking, oh yeah, Super Mario
Brothers 3. Rama, is it
originality?
Mmm.
You say it lacks? Yeah, I don't know.
I mean. It only has 85%
of the feels. Yes.
I don't know
if you listened to last week's show, Rama, early on
or whatever when I was talking about the game. Well, yeah, I caught the podcast
because I was out last week. But I'm just
okay, here was my whole thoughts on the game is that
like, it's pretty much a formulaic
Mario game, but is that
really such a bad thing? No,
not at all, but this
is what I think would have made the game better.
Now, you remember in Super Mario
3, you could travel all
over the map area
to go to different levels. I understand you could
do that in the new SMB2,
but it's only like part of the
screen that it takes up. It would be nicer if
it was the full screen that allows you to travel
from the different levels.
I understand that they brought back some of the
music from SMB3. They
could have brought back some of the classic matching
card games or matching
up the mushroom, the fire flower for 1-Ups
and stuff like that. I like the little
giant glove that punched the 1-Ups.
That was kind of cute, actually.
Yeah, bring back Kribo
2. Maybe
I was thinking it would be more
like Super Mario Bros 3, but better.
Well, I don't know.
I didn't dislike it by any means,
and when I write my VOG review, it'll
probably be on the positive end of things, but
it's just, you know, I don't know. There's just something
I'm not as like, oh my god!
Ermahgerd about it as
previous Mario games. Hey, Ranma.
Do you have a
R4 or anything
like that for your DS?
Yes, and when you first mentioned a long
time ago the new Super Mario Bros 3
ROM hack, I went and downloaded it
like 10 minutes after the
podcast. That game is hard as fuck.
That's what I'm saying, though, but I mean,
it's pretty awesome. They did all
these original levels plus the levels from
Super Mario Bros 3, and
that took some effort versus
rehashing the same old
shit again. Yeah.
I mean, as
I'm controlling the game, I'm not too fond of how they
changed how you control Mario, but
eh.
Alright. Ranma, I gotta wrap up, let you go.
Any final thoughts?
Erm...
Actually, no. Alright, take
care, buddy. Alright, later. Bye.
I guess we can do one more call. I've seen
this one calling in. We'll do one
more call. Here we go. Hi, you're on
Orange is Orange Radio. Who's this? This is
Cody. Cody!
What's up, Cody? What's up?
I'm actually a first time
caller. Long time listener.
Long time listener, first time.
I was gonna say, I don't recognize this Skype
picture. I'm a very visual person. But I like bow ties.
Bow ties are cool. It's a very, very nice
bow tie. That looks like, did you tie that bow tie
yourself on your picture? That is actually,
that is a Doctor Who brand
bow tie. Oh ho ho. See?
Very nice. Do you also wear a fez?
You will fit in well here at the Voice of Geeks
Network. I do own one.
Alright. What's up, Cody?
I wanted to call, actually,
first off, the whole Wii U thing.
I'm kind of the same. I'm
on the fence about it as well.
About the only thing I use
my Wii for right now
is Netflix and Skyward Sword.
So, I mean,
and I really, I've
seen a lot of stuff going on
with it. Different networks talking
about it and, you know, everybody's just, has
kind of the same, same
take on it, you know? They just,
they need to play it. They need
to play it and not a lot of people get to play
it and I think that's what somebody said in the chat
is that not a lot of people get
to play it and they haven't had hands on so
they don't know how it's going to work. Well, it's, yeah,
it's Shadow Next Gen and VXJ
both are in chat now kind of talking it up
because they both are like, you guys need to play it,
you guys need to do the hands on experience, but
and I'm sure as
the, you know, announcements are made
as we get closer to launch day, we're going to start
seeing those displays at Best Buys,
Game Stops, yada yada, so everybody can
get their hands on time, but
I don't know, I still
am highly skeptical.
But that's not a bad thing.
It's not a bad thing. I don't
hate the Wii U. It's not a bad thing to
question, especially after the
3DS launch. I don't think it's a bad thing to
be concerned. I don't want the Wii U to be.
Not at all. Not at all. And I,
you know, and I'm so, I
was excited about it, you know, especially like you said,
Zombie U, when I saw that I was like, whoa, man
that looks like an amazing game. And you know,
I just, I'm scared that it's
going to be kind of like the Vita, and I believe
Loki said something about, you know,
it's
the Vita, you know, had this huge
launch of original games and
everything, and it still didn't help it.
And I think, I
kind of think that that's the way that the Wii U is going to
turn out, but you know what, we haven't seen it yet,
and that's the thing, is you know, we just have to wait.
And once we
see it, then we'll know.
So I, you know, I'm just
waiting.
Alright, did you say you have something else you want to talk about tonight?
Because you said that you got derailed by the Wii U talk,
but was there something else on your mind?
I just wanted to throw that in there. Also, no, I wanted to
say, I actually, I'm an
Oklahoman, I think you have a couple Oklahoman
callers, or listeners
actually, and
I was going to say that, I don't know if you guys
heard about the Gearbox Community
Day?
Yeah, I have heard about that. I did hear about that, yeah.
I'm actually, I'm trying to
go, I want to go, and I
want to bring, I actually want to
videotape as much as I can, if they'll
allow it. But,
I'm a big Borderlands
whore, I mean, like, I play that game
like, constantly, and I think it's
because I love RPGs, and I love
FPSs, but I suck at FPSs
and I'm good at RPGs, so it kind of
mixes the two together, and so I think
that's why I like it so much. But, I didn't
know if you guys heard about that, and
I mean, it just looks like a really fun
thing to go to. I've never been to any
kind of conventions or anything like that, so
I'm pretty excited about that.
Where are they having this? In
Texas.
Dallas, yeah.
So, they're doing,
it's not just Borderlands 2, it's
also Aliens vs.
Predator, was it Aliens vs. Predator?
I'm sorry, Aliens colonial
marines. Yeah, colonial marines.
And then one more
thing, I do know that Allen
plays a lot, he's a big
fan of Half-Life,
and
I don't know if he's played this
mod before, and I really don't know how long this
mod's been out, but it's a Garry's mod,
and it's called, oh,
Trouble in Terrorist Town?
That doesn't
sound familiar to me, but he's listening,
he's unfortunately not here in the house, he's
at work tonight, so I can't ask him in
person, but he's listening, so he might
pop up in chat or whatever, but it
doesn't sound familiar to me. If he
hasn't played it, he needs to, because it is
the, oh my gosh,
it's so fun. It's the
most fun of Garry's mod
that I've ever had, just with
the funny things that happen in the mod, with all
the randoms that get thrown in, you know,
if you don't have a group of people
that go on.
It's just so fun. I'm gonna grill you like
I did the Wii U lovers. Why?
Why is it so damn amazing?
I, you know, I don't,
I'm not really into a whole lot of multiplayer,
and I think it, when it
happens, when it comes to like FPS's
and stuff like that, I don't really like that a lot.
I don't know, it might be because I
just am really bad at them, but this game
kind of, I don't know, it's just, it's really
fun, and it has a lot to do with, you have
to figure out who's the traitor
in your group, and you have to, like, there's
a detective, a traitor, and then I think
there's, there's one more, I
can't even think of. Is that like
the wolf game, or the mafia game,
you know, those games that are popular on
web forums and conventions and all that?
That's kind of what it sounds like to me.
Yeah, I mean, it's sort of like
that. Sort of. Yeah,
but, I mean, it's really fun. See if he wants
to check it out. I mean, it's, I think it's a, I'm
pretty sure it's a free mod, obviously, but
but, yeah, check it out.
I mean, I've, go on YouTube,
look up all these different, you
know, gameplays of it, and it's just so, so
hilarious, so. Alright, I'll make
him check it out. Sounds great.
Alright, well, Codeman, thanks, or excuse me, Cody,
thanks so much for calling into
the show tonight. I appreciate it, and
yeah, you call in any time.
No problem, and, you know, I was
actually, I had a tweet last week
telling
you guys about a Borderlands 2
giveaway, and I don't know if I remember. Oh, that was you!
It is me! Yeah, it was you!
Okay. I was an
idiot and didn't link the freaking
YouTube video. Alright, plug
away. Oh, um,
I actually, I have a small gaming
channel on YouTube. It's not huge.
I don't get paid for it or anything like that. I just enjoy
gaming and showing people my games.
Hey, it's what we're doing here. It's the exact same thing
we do here, except we're audio.
Oh, yes.
And my channel is just funny commentary,
but, yeah, I'm giving away
a copy of Borderlands 2.
I mean, it's any platform
out there that's,
you know, gonna be out PC, PS3,
360, Steam, any
of that, so, um,
but, yeah, it's, um,
actually, my YouTube channel is
linked in my Skype, if you wanna,
but I can say it on here, if you want.
Yeah, you better say it, because it'll take me too long
to bring it up, so go ahead. Spell it or whatever.
Um, it's, it's, uh,
www.youtube.com
backslash ctaylor1785
ctaylor1785.
You know, I gotta be honest,
buddy, you wanna get some more hits on your YouTube channel,
you're gonna have to come up with something really catchy.
1785 is hard to remember,
so, we'll see.
Well, it was kind of funny, because I
came up with the YouTube channel a long time ago,
but never did anything, and so now I can't
change it, and now my channel's
called Codeman Games.
Okay, that's good. That's good.
Or I was gonna say, like, how about, like,
Tailored Games or something silly, I don't know.
But the video,
if anybody's wanted, the video is
called, um, I believe it's called
That Robot Has a Temper. I actually have a cell
phone call with Claptrap, and he's, like,
cussing and all this different stuff, so it's
pretty fun. And, uh, yeah, but just
tell me, you know, if they want a free copy, you know,
just send them on over. Alright.
Poor people who love
Borderlands. Hey, I'm poor.
I got a four month old.
You're not that poor if you're giving away a copy
of Borderlands 2. No, I think that's great.
I, I, uh, I,
I fully support the indie press in all forms,
so go check that out, everybody. Alright, good luck
with your YouTubes, and we'll talk to you in a later week,
okay? Alright, thank you, Rob. I appreciate it.
No problem. Take care, buddy.
You too. Bye.
Alright, that's gonna do it for the Skype line tonight. That was a good
guy. I love the long time listener
first time callers, and he handled that very well.
He didn't, he didn't freeze up.
Sometimes people, when they're new, like, hello, hello,
am I on? Hello? Hello? Echo? What? Hello?
He was... Very good, uh, phone presence.
Yes. You get a, I don't,
I don't know if we could give a gold star for that,
but you would definitely get, like, a silver star.
Alright.
Platinum for me.
Alright, uh, that's gonna do it.
For the bow tie, for the bow tie. Yeah, that's true.
The bow tie was pretty awesome. Alright, that's gonna do it
for the, uh, Skype calls tonight.
If you didn't get through, don't be mad.
Send tweets. You know, TigerClaw's
like the only one that's been sending tweets this week,
so you can either send tweets, or, you can send us
an email. Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Speaking of TigerClaw's tweets,
I did want to get through these real quick.
Uncharted and The Director Changeover.
Uh, David O. Russell
had been on there. He had made the movie
I Heart Huckabees. Well, he's not there anymore.
Neil Berger left the project.
Uh, who is on the project now?
The, the writers of
National Treasure,
Marianne and Cormac Wiberly.
God, I hate Nicolas Cage.
It's like, I have no frame
of reference, cause I refuse to see those movies.
You know what? The only good thing
he did was raising Arizona. They seem
topical enough.
I don't know. I guess I could see
a movie like that leading to Uncharted, but
alright. So, there you go.
Um,
let's see. Oh, Neil Berger
directed Limitless,
and he left, and then he
he had replaced somebody else.
So, who's directing it now?
I don't think they have a
director right now. I'm looking right now.
It's not gonna happen. Who knows?
They may still make one.
Nope, they just say
somebody left. Alright. Uh,
one more. Oh, I like this. This is
nice. Out
of all the bad news we've had
tonight, I like
a little bit of good news. So, thank you,
Tigerclaw, for sending this. And I think this is
a good note to end on tonight, although Loki
may have last minute stories. Actually, no, I want to end on
this. Loki, do you have any last minute stories before I get to this?
Eh, some, some MMOs
stole a map from Counter-Strike.
That's all we need to know. Big deal.
Alright.
Here you go. A nice thing to end on.
Thank you, Tigerclaw. Microsoft
is throwing an industry mixer
for the folks from OnLive
who are affected by the restructuring.
Uh, they are scouting
for Xbox-oriented positions
for Mountain View, California, and
Redmond, Washington. A quote from
Microsoft on the public invitation,
We are eager to speak to individuals and teams
affected by the OnLive transition.
We are looking to add key
players who want to make a real impact
in creating groundbreaking new products
and services. I gotta
say, what a great way to answer
Sony getting Gaikai.
Just hire the old OnLive employees
for your company. Sounds good.
Amazing. Amazing.
Oh, Dark Tetsuya sending a late tweet here.
I finished updating the wiki
with recently found episodes.
So, Dark Tetsuya doing a wiki
update. Thank you, Dark Tetsuya.
Thank you, fans, for updating
that wiki. You guys are amazing.
orangeloungeradio.wikia
W-I-K-I-A dot com.
You guys make sure that I don't repeat games.
You use it as a source.
I use it all the time.
It impacts what we do here on the show.
Alright, I see you guys are packing up. I know you gotta
get out. We all got work tomorrow. We've gone
long tonight. But thank you guys for staying up
late with us. We really appreciate it. We can't
end the show, however, until we get to the final thoughts.
So, let's do some final thoughts.
Um, Dark Sakura, start us off
tonight. I don't want to go to bed.
Uh, Loki,
your final thoughts tonight? Um,
I don't know.
I want to wear this shirt to work.
I'm going to. Alright,
you should. Um, my final thought
is, because I neglected to say
it at the start of part B, as
I plan to, I do want to say
rest in peace to Neil Armstrong.
Um, but what an amazing
life to have actually gone
to the moon. I mean, that's something we all dream about
as kids. And, like, he actually did it.
So, yes, it's unfortunate that
he passed, but let's not focus on the
fact he died. Let's focus on the fact
that, like, like
he did something that all of us dream about.
And I think that's just amazing.
So, a tip of the hat to Neil Armstrong.
That's going to do it for. Well, that doesn't
directly actually go with video games, too.
How so? Do you know that?
Because Buzz Aldrin was the voice of the guy in the end
of Mass Effect 3. Sure, sure.
You know, they were all kind of. That's a tie.
I'm just trying to say. But, yeah,
that was pretty. And Phyllis Diller.
Yeah, rest in peace Phyllis Diller.
She was so awesome. We've lost a lot of great people
over the past couple of weeks. It's really sad. And the guy who was the
Count. Mm-hmm.
And Cry. Yeah. Tragic, tragic.
And the lady who was the astronaut.
Sally Ride. Yeah.
That was a few weeks ago. We didn't
mention it on the show. It may have been a week you weren't here,
but. That means just, like, a bunch of people just.
Yeah. It's very unfortunate. Very unfortunate.
But, um, you know,
look at accomplishments. Look ahead.
Look ahead to two weeks.
We'll be back with an all new episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
Have a wonderful Labor Day weekend,
you guys. Be safe. Enjoy
catching up on video games.
Um, thank you for supporting Independent Radio.
If you like what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio,
remember, we don't have multimillion dollar
magazine contracts and so forth.
We don't have a gigantic website backing us.
It's all community based. It's all about you guys.
If you like what you hear, tell a friend
or two about the show. Help out by
leaving a nice review on iTunes.
Share the show on Stitcher Radio
and help promote us over there and
wherever podcasts can be
heard. We'll be back in a couple weeks to do
it all again. Have a wonderful break. We'll see you next
time on Orange Lounge Radio.
Good night.
See you next week.
Bye.