Orange Lounge Radio
Here's your hosts, Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loku
Tonight, August 12th, 2012, Amazon starts a new game studio
Valve is set to use Steam for non-gaming applications
and has an R-rated version of a Super Nintendo game been discovered?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice, it is Orange Lounge Radio
for this August the 12th of 2012 and the 400 and, wait for it
69th episode of our show
That doesn't imply anything by the way
No, not at all
My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours
to talk about video games, gaming culture, and so forth
with my co-host and those of you live and participating with us at VOG Network
but I'll get back to that in a minute
First, let me introduce my co-host
Say hello to Dark Sakura, or Jamie Summers
It implies that Rob has an internal 12 year old girl
What?
That's giggling at the 69
You have a little girl inside of you? That's really weird
Well, funny enough, I was playing Disneyland Connect Adventures today
which I didn't think we were going to get into gaming weeks as fast
but okay, why not, it's a special night
I found my inner little girl
because you can choose to be a boy or a girl
and I was like, well I'll be the little girl with pigtails
because she's cute
so maybe, Dark Sakura, maybe there is some truth to what you're saying
Well I was just like, 69 tee hee
Yeah, I know, when you say like 69
and start talking about girls, it is a little bit of a creeper zone
so we probably shouldn't go there, it's just a little creepy
I like pie
Pie is good
Pie is great, so is coffee
Also over there, say hello to tech master Loki
Hi
How you doing, Loki?
I'm doing fine
So what do you say?
For old times sake, let's get Karaoke Revolution out
No
No one plays that anymore
Okay, well I have SingStar
No one plays any karaoke games anymore
SingStar ABBA?
No, I'm sorry, that's not acceptable
Oh my god, SingStar ABBA, we totally need to do SingStar ABBA
I think we should do some live on air SingStar ABBA tonight
But I won't sing
Would you like to maybe do a duet on SingStar ABBA later?
Maybe
Maybe just for the listeners for the occasion?
I don't wanna talk
Come on, come on, you wanna do it, alright
Say hello as well, we have some special guests in the studio tonight
Please welcome back to the show, I'm always very happy to see him here in studio
And part of that is because he has a very sexy radio voice
Say hello to Jason
And I'm always glad to be back in California
Welcome back, even in the triple degree heat?
Uh, it's no uh, 68 foggy San Francisco bay, but I still make the triple
It's 69 foggy Sacramento bay, excuse you
Uh oh, right, right
I'm gonna milk those jokes for all they're worth tonight
Loki just gave me a look
God, I wish it was a- I mean, I don't wish it was a TV show, but like, I do sometimes
I wish Loki had a camera, that's the only one that needs to be on cam, is Loki, let's be real
I don't need to do that
That's the only one that people wanna see
His stealth webcam, considering the ones persistently pointed at his face
I do have a camera like, faced right at me, like the entire time
We need like the type of like, you remember like MTV back in the 90s where it was like audience cam
Where they had music?
Candy cam, yeah, back when they had music and like remote control and stuff
Like we need that zany audience cam, that's like, just like Blair Witch Project style shaking and all that
Japanese variety TV shows usually have one of the comedians or talents
They'll basically picture and picture the person right in the corner
So that when the news is interesting, shocking, whatever, you get that reaction cam right away
Something like that would be perfect
I love that
And they do it like all the time when I was watching Morning News with me
Alright, we have another guest here in studio tonight
And I'm so happy to introduce this person to the show
Because I know it's somebody who's been a long time listener of OLR
And she has finally made it to the studio after a 469 week pilgrimage
What can I say, she walked, no I'm kidding
But we're so happy to welcome, what am I calling you tonight?
You better introduce yourself because I don't want to call you the wrong thing tonight
Well I always went by Rai Chan and that's what I am on the chat, so hello
Hello Rai Chan, welcome to the show
I just call you Rai for short because I don't know, I heard Jason calling her that one
So I was like, I like that, Rai works for me
So Rai Chan, how are you?
It's good to finally be on vacation, it's good to finally be out here
Yeah
Awesome, so how long have you been listening to Orange Launch Radio, it's been a while right?
Yeah, I started about the time when Jason and I actually met
So it's been about 8 years or so
So you used to play, back in the day you used to play DDR and all that stuff?
Yeah, that's how actually Jason and I met, so
Okay, I want to hear the story, how did Jason and Rai meet over DDR?
The couple, the particular points that were interesting were
Obviously her living in Colorado, myself living in New Mexico
I being a mod for the Southwest part on DDR Freak
It all started because I told her she was breaking the rules
That was my first reason to explicitly
Did you give her a point?
Never, good choice of words
Back to the story, did she
I didn't say did you give her a prick, I said did you give her a point?
The DDR Freak rules were outside of the imaging forum
That pictures couldn't be more than 300x300
And I used it as an excuse to private message her and say
Well the rules say this, so could you please do that?
And she was very, well and how dare you, posted image over 300 kilobytes on a forum
Shame on me
So we all kind of started, her and myself and a bunch of other people
Started getting on aimchat rooms just talking for all hours of the night
Whatever random things
We were actually talking about this, we were over at Iguana Girls House
New place earlier this morning
And I actually mentioned that both Rai and myself were on LiveJournal
And I saw her commenting on a post of Iguana Girls
And I found out that she was on LiveJournal as a result
So I started checking out her posts and commenting on them
Oh my god, we're talking about DDR freakin' LiveJournal
Tonight's show is like 10 years in the past
This episode of OLR was brought to you by a...
Hey, I'm in a time warp tonight
We're out doing the take to late for NBC
Alright
It's the OLR time capsule
Bringing you live coverage tonight of the Sydney 2000 Olympics everybody
We actually recorded this show 10 years ago but no one even knows
We're just playing it back
Okay, so Rai, obviously, I mean we go back to the DDR days
But I know you're a gamer girl
What types of video games are you into? Or computer games or what have you?
Mostly RPGs, puzzle games
Diablo
Lots and lots of Diablo
Lots of Diablo
I've got two level 60s and I'm working on a third
Addict
I play a lot of World of Warcraft
A lot of World of Warcraft
And every time I sign on
There's always at least one person on my real ID
Can anyone guess who is always on real ID?
Signed in playing Diablo 3
That would be me
Okay, so Diablo 3 has taken a lot of shit out there
But obviously you don't care because you're playing it
So why are haters hating on Diablo 3
And why can they go just hate in the corner?
You know, with me, I started with Diablo 2 when I was in high school
It's one of those things that I have always really, really liked
So I waited for it to come out
People hate, people always hate
Let them hate, I don't care
Haters to the left
Okay, we're just gonna play a little bit of word association
I'm gonna say a phrase, you tell me what comes to mind
Alright, you ready?
Real money auction house
Don't do it
I've sold a couple things on there
But otherwise I don't really participate in it
PVP patch
Not something that I care about
You know, you wanna go through and kill other players
Go for it
Activision
I just gotta laugh
And that's about it
Well said, well said
Well, welcome to the show
Rai, I'm sorry she's a little quiet you guys
She's actually, because we have five people tonight
She's actually having to share a mic with me
And the me mic
Rob, don't shut up
That's right, I have a very loud voice
So the me mic is tuned for my voice
So when Rai talks in it, she's a little quiet
But I appreciate your prompt attention to Rai
And the things she has to say
Hey, we do tape live at the Voice of Geeks Network
vognetwork.com is where you can join us
And in the chat, live.vognetwork.com
Is where you can participate, check in
Get loot and VoG points and all that stuff
And have your chat comments
Possibly read here on the show
And some folks here in the chat room
Let's see, BlackWolf is reminding us
That tonight's show has been tape delayed ten years
Yes, Frisbee says
Live from Salt Lake City
Close, Jason might have gone through there
On the trip here, right?
Uh, Provo and
I-70 goes through both
The rail takes a destination that goes through Provo
And has a stop in Salt Lake City
There you go
I want to talk about presents
Because Loki was really awesome
And brought Dark Soccer and I presents
And I guess they were like early Christmas
Slash late birthday
Whatever the reason was
Those were awesome
Yeah, I loved it
So tell the listeners about what that was
Okay, so
After, and I really do blame VJHS
For this, after VJHS
After I kickstarted
That, or pledged to that
Kickstarter, I started
Getting into the habit of browsing Kickstarter
For things, and one of the things that I saw
There was a custom
Card deck for
There's a bunch of companies doing custom cards
And stuff like that, so one of the decks
That was on there was
The Grid, it's like
Tron themed cards, but not quite
You know, because they can't do it without the licensing
But it's
Tron-esque cards, you know
That very neon black
They're pretty cool looking
So it was a limited run
I think they only did about a thousand of them
And so I pledged to
Get a bunch of, well, a few of the decks
So I kept one, I gave one to my friend
I gave one to you guys
And
Yeah, so, it was cool
Yeah, I gotta say, I don't even want to open them
I'm like, I do need a deck of cards
For card games, but I don't want to open them
Because they're so awesome
It's like, you know, not wanting to
Open toys, just use them
I can show you a picture of what all the cards look like
If that'll help
Okay, that'll work
Now, despite all the fact that we give Kickstarter a lot of
Crap here on the show, you know, a lot of that's been me
Although Jamie's had her fair share in giving Kickstarter
Crap
And it's
Again, it's not necessarily the whole website
That I have a problem with
There's just some people on there
You just have to be buyer beware
Just like eBay
Not all eBay auctions are evil, but some people
Put up shady stuff
It's that thing that's being perpetuated as well
Like, you want to make millions?
Go to Kickstarter and just like
It's everybody's easy button answer right now
When things in life aren't that easy button
So it's like everybody's just swarming
It's like the gold rush
Everybody's just swarming on it
You see, that's where most of my problems lie therein
There's been some good Kickstarters
I have come this close
This close to donating
To one of the Kickstarters and I still might
And that would be my first Kickstarter ever
And that's the GamerCon one
I'm seriously considering supporting
Well, they've already hit their funding
I was just on Kickstarter about a few seconds ago
And I saw that they had hit their funding, I think
For that, but that's still cool
They can always use more funding
I'm kind of obligated
To go to GamerCon, you know
It's in San Francisco, I mean
It's right up the street
Yeah, but you can also go to YowieCon
Which is also in San Francisco
YowieCon is fun
But GamerCon is about video games
YowieCon is about
YowieCon has electronic tools
No, it has the electric
469, folks
This guy was selling
These glass tubes
That attach to an electric current
And it shoots electricity across your skin
And I had him turn it up all the way
Because I have nerve damage in my hands
So I didn't feel it
And he's like, are you alive?
Yes, I want one of these
It kind of tickles
Alright, so Loki, Kickstarter
You've kind of become a little bit like
You kickstart a lot of stuff
You have a lot of feet
A few things, I mean
I don't know, I like independent projects
Sometimes and I like stuff
I like getting things in the mail
I don't know
That's not
That's not why I do it
I don't know why that's so funny
But because it's episode 469
I like getting things in the mail
My mind goes to porn
Dildos, lube
I have never gotten porn, dildos, or lube
In the mail
Yet
I guess that does open up opportunities
I have
And I didn't even order it
Get return present for Loki
One of these days
The UPS delivery man is going to be like
Somebody just ordered you a 10 gallon bottle of lube
So
Thanks
No, there's actually a website called
AlienDildos.com
You're going to have to get one of the pumping mechanisms
And I found it through
A mass effect forum
Alright, anyways
I back a few projects every now and then
And actually I've done a few recently
But yeah, the second project I backed
Was those cards
Because they were pretty cool looking
I was like, oh sweet, Tron cards
Well this would be a great gift
That's exactly what I thought
I'm like, this would be a great gift
So I'm going to do that
And so that's what I did
I opened my cards and yeah, they're pretty awesome
I don't play a lot of card games
But when I do, I'm going to use those
I think you just became a gift
Did you hear that? I don't play a lot of card games
But when I do
No, but
You heard it too, right?
But when I do, I play them on the grid
No, but seriously
There's been some pretty cool projects on there
For example, Cards Against Humanity
Was one I wish I had gotten
In on because that would have been awesome
But they have that
I backed Ouya recently
Which we'll see what happens with that
I'm pretty faithful that
It'll come through
I know a lot of people are like, oh
It's going to be like a phantom
It's going to disappear like a phantom
Up in smoke
Gone
But yeah, there's a lot of things that I back on there
That's where the cards came from
They actually have another set coming out too
This 4pm studios
They have a Cthulhu themed set
That looks pretty fucking sweet
I'm really into what you're saying
Usually I wouldn't go on these tangents
But thanks to the closing ceremonies
This will be our lowest rated live episode
In 4 years
What in the actual fuck
Are you looking at on that computer dark
Sakura?
It's the funniest website
I've ever seen in my life
What is that? Rule 37?
What do they call that?
This is a Rule 37
It's a website that I actually found
Through a Mass Effect Tumblr
Of course
Well I have to say that this episode
The TTP has only been 26 minutes
Wait a minute
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
Tell us what the website is because I want to come back
To this whole discovery of the website
What is the website? I posted it in chat already
Could you share for the podcast listeners?
AlienDildos.com
I don't know if we should be going down this path
There's already an explicit tag
There's no stopping this train
Tell me in what part of Mass Effect
Fandom
Would we require
an AlienDildos.com
You're taking this femshep
Garris thing a little too far
When you want to model
Of his wiener as a butt plug
No
Do not want
Turian butt plug is taking this obsession one step too far
There's an FAQ
For a comic that someone was doing
And someone said
What do you think Turian cock
Looks like?
And she linked to the site
And the artist
Linked to the site
Who
Who cares
Rule 37
And the internet cares
That's a true quote
If I've ever heard one
We usually
Like to start the show by talking about our gaming
Weeks and the type of video games that we've
Been playing this week
I just wanted to mention one thing since we were
Previously before the Dildo Talk
We were talking about Kickstarter
Which I would like to mention
I asked him to call in too
Maybe he'll call in later
Speaking of Kickstarter
There is a Kickstarter
That's being done by
One of our listeners
He is a part of his company
And it's for a game called Evilot
Evilot is kind of a
Dungeon
Defense game
And they've got
A pretty low goal to hit
But of course they
Need all the help that they can get
So if you guys can go maybe back
If it looks good
For $15 you get the game on every single platform
That they're releasing it on
Did they pay for that commercial?
I'm just kidding
I will support
A foodie monster
He's doing animation on
He hasn't listened in a while
What ever happened to him?
Foodie monster, where are you?
Well foodie monster
I want a Skype call in the coming weeks
If you're going to get your
Kickstarter wares out there
Evilot
They're about $3,500 of a $10,000 goal
That's not bad
Still 3 weeks to go
Still be relevant for that call within the next couple of episodes
Good job
I backed them
We're going to make a game for the Ouya
I need some games to play
On that console that may or may not disappear
Into the mist like the Phantom
Like the Phantom
Oh a link
Give a link in chat
Alrighty
Moving on, let's get into our gaming weeks
And the type of video games that we have been playing this week
Dark Soccer, start us off
I'm playing Mass Effect 2 for Becky
And I'm playing Mass Effect 3 for me
And World of Warcraft
And
I played
Droplets on my phone
It's not as good on my phone as it is on
Steam, just saying
So you went from Turian dildos to Orcish dildos
No
Ew
Everyone knows Orcs don't bathe
My bad
Alright, Loki
How about your gaming week?
I actually played some different things
Pretty much also the same stuff
Played a lot more Minecraft
Finally got to do some more co-op stuff
With my co-worker
It's still getting a little boring
I actually just purchased it on PC
Which I'm looking forward to playing around with the mods and stuff
Because my PC probably can handle that
Also
Played a bit of Call of Duty
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3
Still fun
Looking forward to the Black Ops 2
And then the new thing
I actually played this week was Sleeping Dogs
Which is a pretty awesome game
For those who are not aware
It's what true crime Hong Kong
Was
It was going to be true crime Hong Kong
Before the IP got sold off
So now it's this brand new
Open world action game
With a lot of kung fu
And
A lot of homages to classic kung fu
Films and
Crime dramas and all that
It has that feeling of
A Hong Kong action film which is pretty sweet
The combat in it
Is pretty good
Because it's a little bit more sophisticated
Than Grand Theft Auto where
Combat is just there as a side note
Because it's mostly guns guns guns guns guns
This though
Because it does have all that Hong Kong
Influence
It's a lot of kung fu in there
So you're having to fight a ton of people
All at one time
Having to do counters and stuff like that
For me the counter system doesn't
Always work right
Because they flash red
And as long as you hit it while they're red
It should counter
But it doesn't work sometimes
It's a little annoying because I keep dying
Over and over
But that's probably because it's not button masher friendly
But the game is really cool
I know it's been getting a lot of coverage
In the blogs recently
Definitely one to check out
Especially if you're a fan of Grand Theft Auto type games
You're not getting a new Grand Theft Auto game
Until at least next year
Sometime
Saints Row
I do need to go back and play Saints Row though
Um
Did you just say fuck Saints Row and then I need to go play Saints Row
Well I need to go finish my achievements
But yeah fuck that game because
They just
Saints Row 2 was so great
Those were two similarly different phrases
That you just used
Rob wins
And I can't say that they've fucking driven it into the ground
Okay it
You know
Saints Row 2 was a great game
It was over the top
They had made it a little bit more over the top
Than the first one
And they expanded the features and stuff like that
Saints Row the third looked like they were going to do even more with that
But then they just went fucking crazy with it
And it makes no god damn sense whatsoever
It's like
If you were
Imagine if you will
With the Christopher Nolan
Batman's okay
And then all of a sudden the last movie is a fucking
Joel Schumacher Batman
That's how the fucking series is gone with Saints Row
It's just like
Okay that's kind of cool
Okay that's even cooler
What the fuck happened?
Why are these things happening?
Why is there a sky fortress flying around?
You know
It's just really weird
You have to admit Saints Row the third is really funny
It's a fun game
But they hoard out the DLC
All the DLCs sucked
The game was Batman Returns
Where it's like
Okay it's a little different
A little zany, Jim Carrey is in it, he's funny
And then the DLC is just
Batman and Robin
There they go, perfect example
And then look at what they were trying to do
They were like oh yeah we're going to do this
Enter the dominatrix thing as a stand alone game
Which right there
I don't know about that
And then they were like hey you know what
We're going to take the milking of this property even further
We're just going to incorporate that into a
Brand new Saints Row the fourth game
Or Saints Row the fourth
Oh thank you
That's going to be fantastic that you're recycling this game
We actually have an exclusive clip
From some unreleased DLC
For Saints Row the third, let's hear it
Well that sounds like a pretty cool expansion
I'm going to tell you right now
Okay if the next Batman game that came out
Was based on
Batman and Robin, I would actually probably buy it
Because
Batman and Robin should be a video game
As fucking terrible as that movie was
It's funny
No one is obviously taking this movie seriously
If you're casting Arnold Schwarzenegger
As Mr. Freeze
That doesn't make any sense whatsoever
That's like
Casting Tara Reid as a scientist
Oh wait that's been done before too
But you know
That movie also sucked, Alone in the Dark
What up G in our chat room says
Bane was much better than that Bane
That's true
But I loved the voice they gave Bane
In the movie
He sounded like Count Chocula
He sounded Belgian
Didn't Bane in the movie sound like
Count Chocula to you?
Let me remember him
That's what he sounded like to me
He sounded like Count Chocula
And I couldn't take it
Because I'm like Count Chocula just
Oh I shouldn't spoil
Alright
Well that also wasn't a very good movie
Speaking of 13 year time warps
Count Chocula is kind of an asshole
Alright
Anyway
Your gaming week
Yes my gaming week if Loki is all done with his gaming week
I actually had quite a bit of a busy gaming week
I have three games I want to talk about
Let's talk first about Pit
I'm sorry
Sorry sorry
There's one thing that is worth mentioning
The Ready Player One contest
Oh yeah alright
Fair enough I'm ready for an update
Alright so the Ready Player One contest
Remember last week the whole thing I bitched about
You know fucking
You bitch!
At the break of world record
And it is basically impossible
To break the world record of
The four games that they started off with
At least it was impossible
For
You know Black Tiger
But I was willing
To buy Black Tiger
And make the adjustments
So that it was exactly
Like the machine that had the world record
I was all ready to do that
Right before I actually purchased anything
I went and checked the update on the blog
And sure enough someone had beat the world record
On Joust on 2600
And it has been confirmed
That was going to be the easiest one to beat
That was the only accessible one
That was the contest
Really
All that other stuff was just a red herring
But it was poorly run in the first place
You keep adding games
And changing the rules
Within a couple days
It was ridiculous
But congratulations to the guy that won it
Of course it still has to be confirmed by Twin Galaxies
But it's been confirmed by
Whoever is running the contest I guess
It looks like it's legit
Was it Joust that you guys were saying takes
Like four days to meet the record?
That's the arcade version
67 hours or something like that
Okay so it certainly has been long enough
Since this news broke that they could have actually pulled it off
On the 2600 I think it was
Different scoring
But yeah console versus arcade
Alright
Thank God too I was like
Maybe I should check something before I make this purchase
Because I was like okay I'm going to buy this
I'm going to buy
My pants laughing
If he comes to the show and just dumps
A black tiger motherboard on the table
God dammit
Seriously let me put it this way
Rob if I was to buy a black tiger
Board I would be breaking the world record regardless
Of you know
It's a thing I forgot
Now it's a thing
You talked about this last week it's a thing
Exactly alright anyways I'm done
Are you sure you're done?
Oh Dark Soccer I thought of something else
No I'm very sad because Joe Kubert
What?
Joe Kubert died
And who was he?
Uh born 1926
Did a lot of DC stuff
Well that means he lived a pretty full life though
26 that's
I thought for a second there she was saying Joe Kubert
And I was like is that his first name?
I kind of thought that's what she said at first too
But then I'm looking over her shoulder
At Tumblr and I'm like no
And he did like a lot of Superman
Well I mean sorry to hear he passed
Yeah
We actually unfortunately have news about another passing
But we'll get to that a little later in the show
Because I don't want to down the show too much
Because I want to talk about my gaming week
And there's three games I want to talk about this week
First off on the iOS platforms
Pitfall which I guess is the 30th anniversary
Edition Pitfall or what have you
They really should just call this game
Temple Run 2
Because that's exactly what this game is
It is Temple Run 2
The only connection
To the original 8-bit Atari 2600
Version of Pitfall
The little opening movie you see it for 5 seconds
And then it transforms into
The new Pitfall
So wasn't there a marketplace
Or something like that out there that said
They were going to try to eliminate
Kind of these copycat games
Was that Android or something like that?
Well technically
You're not supposed to have them on iOS
But it's Atari
We're going to let them slide
Activision in this case, even better
It's just enough different than Temple Run
That it's not really a copycat
I mean you still have the sliding
To turn around, you slide up to jump
You slide down to go over the tunnel
But now you tap the screen
To whip snakes that might be standing in your path
Which the original Pitfall did have snakes
So they kind of figured out a way to
Incorporate that
Now I will say this, to the game's credit
The graphics are above and beyond
What Temple Run's got going on
Not that Temple Run's a bad looking game
But you play it so much you kind of see the same thing over and over
The cool thing about Pitfall is that the
Environments start to get varied
Like you get to a certain length in the game
And now when you get to 2500 meters or whatever
Now you start running through a cave
And it's like drastically different looking
And then I know in the box teaser
The teaser images that are out there
There's one that's like a minecart in a fire cavern type of thing
So that's kind of cool that they varied it a little bit
As well as when you start the game
It's kind of like from the side
And then like the camera rotates
To be behind you more like Temple Run
Like the way the engine works
It seems like it's capable of more
Graphically than Temple Run is
But um
If the graphics were that great
You shouldn't have frame skipping happen
Especially in a game where
You know, precision is key
And the frame skipping kind of screws it up
And here's the other thing about Pitfall
Like Temple Run, you have all these
Mini transactions that you can do
Within the game
Pay 99 cents for a token
And you can continue from where you left off
Or pay 99 cents for diamonds
And you can dress Pitfall Harry up in a bear
Costume or a pirate
Or a tooth fairy
I kid you not, you can dress him up
It's just called fairy
You can dress him up as a fairy
Can you do pretty princess or something?
I don't know because I'm not going to pay the money to do it
Now I guess technically you can
Grind the silver bars
Which are basically the version of coins or whatever
But it always leaves a
Bad taste in my mouth when you ask me
To pay for the game up front and then you
Try to shove these transactions down my throat
And I do not like
These constant pop-up messages
That are like, don't you want to spend money
To continue from this point?
Don't you want to buy a costume? No!
I don't!
But he doesn't look like a fairy yet
Don't you want to play as a fairy?
I am hating
Based on the fact that you have Grindr
Installed on your iPhone, we think you might like
This costume
But look, I don't like this whole
And I will never turn
Push notifications on for these things
Either
So that's the other thing
If I had those on, I'm sure I'd be getting messages
At two o'clock in the morning
Don't you want macaw tokens?
We miss you, don't you want to play some more?
So I kind of hate
This whole free-to-play thing
Is just, I mean, I realize
It's not really free, it's still 99 cents to get the game
It's not free
It's still paying money for it
Just wait until it goes free, if you even want to play it
Yeah, uh, Temple Run is free
It's pretty much the same game
But Pitfall has some varied environments, that's all
You gotta do it free so you can pay those microtransactions
I'm just, if I'm gonna pay the money
For those transactions, maybe we should do something
About the frame skip, can I pay 99 cents
To have a smooth running game? Thanks
Alright, meanwhile
That's enough about that, other games I played this week
So for 20 bucks at Fry's
On sale or clearance or whatever
I got Connect Disneyland Adventures
Cause, you know, this game came out last holiday season
And it's Disneyland
And I consider myself a bit of a Disney affectionato
So I wanted to check this game out
And I played this game
I played it for a good
Hour or so
And this is where I really, truly realized
That I hate the fucking Connect
I really
Like
It really is the same mistake all over again
Like what we have with the eye toy
It's miserable to control
It is an absolute miserable experience to control this game
It's like, you have to hold your hand out
To turn
You have to put your hand out this way to go forward
And then
Like, if I want to do a hug
I'm supposed to reach out
And try to hug
But then it'll think I'm dancing
Instead and like all this stuff
I'm just like, can't I just pick up the controller and play
Like, I realize the name of the game
Is Connect Disneyland Adventures
But for a bunch of cute minigames
About a place I really love
You know what, I'll pay 20 bucks for the controller experience
Can we just take the Connect part out?
No
You can't disable the Connect in this game, unfortunately
I think that's too bad
I really do think the killer app for Connect
Is, uh, dancing games
And that's pretty much it
It's really the only thing that succeeds on that
And even then
Dance Central and maybe Dance Paradise
Although that game has it's issues
Just Dance
Isn't bad either
Anyway
So I don't know, like
I also have to remember this game is made for kids
And here I am
30 and 100 years old and I'm playing the game
It doesn't matter though, I mean that's even worse
Because kids don't have patience at all
So if something's
Going wrong or it's not working they're just gonna
Kick the TV or throw
Throw the Connect through the window
Frisbee in our chat
Room at live.vognetwork.com says
You have to walk around Disneyland like a zombie
With your arms out, totally true
That is, you have to kinda like walk
You can't really do both hands out at the same time
Because then the game doesn't understand if you're trying
To go left or right, but it's just silly
Black Wolf
From the Bobby Black Wolf show
Which tapes before us at VOG Network says
The killer apps for Connect are all the
Non-games like hospital apps
No, obviously those are killer apps for the
PC because the PC
The PC can handle the bandwidth
And they can basically, I think it's like double
The data you get from the Connect versus
The Xbox 360 which has to
Share the bus between all the USB ports
On the actual system so it's
Limited to what you can do
So yes, all the
Hacks are, you know, where it's at
But they're gonna try to sell you
On Connect 2, they're gonna say it's better than the last time
But
Just like they told me it was better than the vision camera
And that was better than the eye toy
It's like ehhhh
Here's the tragic thing about Connect Disneyland
Adventures is that I actually
You know, despite the fact that the game is made for
Kids, as somebody who really loves Disneyland
I really did kinda like just walking
Around the virtual park, it's a pretty decent
Recreation of the park, I mean you can't
Go in every store or whatever, but
I mean they have the frickin' corn dog cart
Represented in the game
This way for corn dogs
And it's kinda fun to see the characters that are out there
And I like that they have the churro ride
They have churro carts
But you can't really do anything
There's lots of characters to find
They have a
World of Warcraft-esque, believe it or not
Questing type thing
Like you find Mickey and Mickey will be like
Hello, find Goofy's autograph
It's interesting
But it's ruined by the Connect
It needs the people movers and that'd be awesome
Because in the world of
Connect Disneyland Adventures, people aren't
Dumb and can't fall off those things
Or to have the gondolas again
It would be even better if you could have like archival
Videos of Disney or Disney ride
Videos or something that I know Disney would never
Allow to be put in there, but I just think it
Really enhanced the experience
Like, I think this idea should be
Revisited without the Connect at some point
Seriously, I really
Wanted to like this game
But I don't
And that makes me very sad
I definitely agree that the killer apps for the
Connect are hospital apps
Oh, I'm putting this scalpel forward
Crap!
Thanks Bobby
That's the other thing that would be interesting
Because you know how we always have these apps that are like
Okay, look, I got this game to work with Connect
I want to see the opposite, I want to see Connect games
Working with a controller
Okay, rdgsinge
In our chat room has a good comment too
The move of Eden was good, right?
No!
Not with Connect as the controller
With the controller it was great
The Connect thing was interesting to play once
Kamehameha!
Yeah, but it wasn't super responsive
Apparently the PS3 version is pretty good with the move
Because the move
Sadly enough
Isn't it tragic that the move actually ends up being a pretty good peripheral
With no one curve?
The move is actually a really good peripheral
It seriously is an excellent peripheral
And it works
But the thing is, no one fucking cares
It's like Sports Champions
It worked pretty much the entire time
Yeah, you had to calibrate it a couple times
But that was super quick
And you still have to fucking calibrate shit in the Connect
But on Connect you have Lady Gaga
So everybody's like
Oh, Connect!
Yep
Anyhow, one more game I want to talk about tonight
Sound Shapes
Which is uh
Sorry, that's the spouse
Did that go over the air?
You just got an extra life?
Apparently for plugging Sound Shapes I got a 1up
Oh, Dan is evil, my husband's evil
One of our yogurt places has Nutella frozen yogurt
That sounds great
Now put your phone on vibrate
Alright
Alien dildo
Alright, Sound Shapes
On the Vita and the PS3
Which I love that you buy it on one
And you get it on both
How it should be
I didn't love that the cloud syncing isn't really working
Or at least it wasn't early in the week when I played it
But supposedly
You're going to be able to have one save file across the two
But whatever, I was at least able to play the game
Is it a music game?
Kinda
But it's not a music game where
A note is falling and you do something
When the note hits the line
That's the neat thing about it
I mean, don't get me wrong, I love those kinds of games
Clearly, however
I'm ready for something kinda different
And the cool thing about Sound Shapes is, it's kinda different
I think it's like a music game like Pot upon was a music game
Not even that
It's just that the things that you collect
The music is all in the stage design
That's what it really boils down to
The stage design is where the music
It's not necessarily you
Interacting with the music
It's the environments interacting with the music
Which is what's kinda cool
It's almost more Child of Eden and Res like
In that regard
Since those games were brought up
I would say those would be a better comparison actually
But this is more like a Little Big Planet style game
And the game that this has the most in common with
Not just Little Big Planet
It's Super Meat Boy
In a way
Because it's that whole idea of
You can die very easy
But you just start from the last checkpoint
And try to get over these very difficult parts
Over and over and over again
There are stages in the game that are just
Really cool
Like the Beck stage
Beck has three stages
That first Beck stage is like the equivalent
Of Shinen in Luminous
Like really
It's like the defining moment
When you're playing the game
Because the song kinda goes
It's going along and then the lyrics
One part of the lyrics goes
Move a little
Turn a little
And like while the lyrics are doing that
The little platforms
It moves a little
Then it turns a little
Then it breaks apart a little
And then when it goes hurt a little
It turns red which is the bad thing color
Which will kill you if you're still standing on it
And like when I was playing that I was like
That's so cool
And even Alan was watching over my shoulder
And like just the little
He'll just sing this ahhh
Thing in the background
That you can use that say ahhh
On them and just like playing that stage
Was just so cool
Like it was neat
And that's how it kind of interacts with the music
It's very much the environment
Otherwise it's kind of a platformer
And it plays a lot like Meat Boy or Little Big Planet
Obviously because of the online element
Is a huge part of it too
All these stages you can get online
That people have made
All their own levels and so forth
Is that very Little Big Planet element
Just like Little Big Planet
90% of them suck
But it's kind of neat to see what people
Come up with. I think the online mode
Could have been implemented a little better
It is early on
I think the interface doesn't work too well
For the online mode but
At least you can kind of track what your friends
Are doing and that gives me hope that there's
Something a little better
In there somewhere
But overall it's a game, shit it's a great deal
You get the game on two platforms
It's only 12 bucks
It's kind of limited
By the number of stages that are actually in the game
I think there's about maybe
15 stages in the game
But it's only a $15 game
And you do have the online stuff which is virtually unlimited
I think it's pretty good
I had a good time with it
So
This is sounding like Sound Shapes is a music game
Like New Super Mario Brothers is a music game
Lots of colorful interactivity
Admittedly with Sound Shapes
More things are happening as a result
But with New Super Mario Brothers
One of the cutest parts of the game was the fact that
The backgrounds and everything else would
Have very distinctive cues
That go along with the music and then things like the Yoshi
That add the new rhythm and what not
It was a really
It was one of the best aspects of that reboot
Actually, yes, I didn't even think of that
But you're right
The music in New Super Mario Brothers
Was really under appreciated
Yeah, there is kind of an element to that with it
You know that goes all the way back to the original
Super Mario Brothers
I'm sorry, not the original, the original Super Mario
World on the Super Nintendo
Because whenever you got Yoshi
You would have that little drum beat
Oh yeah, that aspect of it, yeah
I'm thinking of like the normal
The hills will be dancing along the background
Oh yeah, I love the way the little Koopas
Yeah, the way the little Koopas go
The little dance is so adorable
New Super Mario Brothers was a great game
And I can't wait for two
Loki might have a word to say about that
Alright
Coming up on this episode of Orange Laundry
I was reading Kickstarter
Not paying attention at all
Again, alright, so I do recommend Sound Shapes
You don't even necessarily have to like music games
Because it's not really a music game
It's a platformer that incorporates music elements
And I think that's a really good way
You know, it's that New Super Mario Brothers
Wii cranked up to 11
In a way, so
That's a review I write for VOG Network later this week
So I'm gonna steal that
I need a few points for that, I think
VX JasonXV, contribute to this report
I'll see what I can do, alright
Moving on, speaking of Jason
I'll let you go next with your gaming week
What types of video games do you play this week?
Oh boy, most of my week was lost
By preparing for this trip
But I will say that when I was on the train
I was trying to play things that
I didn't think would be particularly susceptible
To interference by the train
Rocking back and forth, yeah I was wrong
Limbo, Cave Story
Braid, and other various
Puzzle, platforming, adventure kind of things
I thought that I could
Manage, but with as violent
As the train gets, especially in like Nevada
My hands were completely off the keyboard
Flying all over the place
Couple DS games
A friend of mine let me borrow
Kid Icarus Uprising, and so
Now my hands are completely cramped
Because it's just, like the
Original DS that just doesn't fit
My hands just don't fit that system very well
I've been trying some of the alternative
Control configurations, but then you
Lose all precision and the game just
Gets bad. I wonder if it's gonna feel better
On the XL that's coming out very soon
I've been considering hitting the Best Buy
To see if they have Kid Icarus
On demo and see if that alleviates
The problems, but I think that
I think the size
Of the DS is wrong, but the bulk
The weight of the XL will be too much
And it'll just cause the same thing to happen
I don't know
I finally got
Starcraft working on my computer again
Since Mountain Lion kind of broke a couple things
My Diablo's still busted, but my Starcraft 2
Is working again, that's
Pretty much the week in a nutshell
Let me go over to Ryan, check in
How her gaming week was
It's okay, you don't play Diablo anyway
You're about to make up for it
Yes, I've been playing a lot of
Diablo, it's kind of my social hour
I also picked up
Kingdom Hearts, the 3DS version
I just barely started it
Otherwise, just kind of
The find me and the
Puzzle stuff, because I just picked up my 3DS
This last week
Which is that amazingly awesome purple color
I'm sorry, there's a part of me that wants to go sell
Like, I'm having such a Shane moment
I really hope he's listening
Because I am having a total Shane moment
Because the minute I saw that DS, I'm like
I'm about ready to take my DS and sell it in
And get that purple one
And the XL is on its way out
If I'm going to get a new 3DS
I need to get that one
That's the prettiest color handheld
I think I've ever seen
For real
It was one of those things that I told myself
If the purple one came stateside
That was going to be the one that I got
Kind of held off for the color that I liked
And of course, Kingdom Hearts came out the next week
So, yeah
Good opportunity
I know you haven't played a lot of Kingdom Hearts yet
But any early impressions
From what you have played?
It's a lot to take in
In the very beginning
I'm still struggling with all the new
All the new things that you can do with it
And by the way
I have a supporter in our chat room
JV Mon says the purple 3DS is beautiful
I'm right with you, Rob
Thank you
At least it's not just me
Kingdom Hearts
I saw this hilarious thing floating around Facebook
Which was literally a 40 page Google doc
To try and explain the plot
With pictures and arrows
Is that the type of thing we have going on in the intro?
Sort of
It has its own little tutorials
For each little thing
It's just so much to take in so quickly
It's
And this is a kids series
This is like a soap opera for kids
And adults
A lot of adults playing this game
I think the first one was kind of marketed at kids
Probably, and it's Disney
Who else would the target market be?
The official Disney parks continue
To ignore Kingdom Hearts
Makes me so sad
Anything else for your gaming week, Ry?
Not really
Alright, well you throw something at me
If you want the mic to say something a little later
In the meantime, I'm going to plug
Some things around the interwebs
To register participation
For this week's episode of
Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase
Diving
Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio
As well as Twitter.com slash
OLRs where you can follow us
And of course, once again, please be sure
To visit our home station
The Voice of Geeks Network
Vognetwork.com
Lots of great programming throughout the week
On that website
If I'm able to get my work done tonight
We're going to have a little more music
And rotation. I'm adding a little bit more to the
Music rotation for this week
For those folks that are actually listening
And playing games
To the VoG network
I posted something in the forums about how you can play
Beat Hazard
You can actually use internet radio on Beat Hazard
Well you can load VoG Network as one of the custom
Stations and play Beat Hazard
To the music on VoG
Or, if you're so daring, you can play to an
Episode of Orange Lounge Radio or Pod Culture
Or Girls Gone Wow or whatever
During the week. It's kind of fun
A little weird, but fun
Alright, let's get into some gaming
News now that we're an hour into the show
Loki. Sounds good. Alright
So let's talk a little bit about
What could possibly be the worst thing that
Happened with gaming ever
Windows 8
At least according to a lot of people
But, something else that they're adding
To some of the games that you may waste time
With in Windows
They're adding achievements
To the games you know
And love from back from
Windows 3.1 I can get 20
Points for beating Solitaire
Yes Yes You can now get
Achievements for Minesweeper, Solitaire, and
Mahjong But if you
Want more deck backs, you're gonna have to spend
Microsoft Space Bucks
In order to unlock
Watch. Fucking watch
I'm
Not upgrading
Do you want mine hints for Minesweeper?
Here's what I wanna know
Do you want new faces that will explode
When you click on a mine? Where is that
Go-kart game or that
Was it the bumper card game
From XP? Why do
I not see that listed there?
I forgot about that game, damn
That game is awesome
XP, that was 95 plus
Oh yeah, oh yeah
What about that? And
While we're at it, you know, what about
Didn't they have a bunch of Windows games like
There was Chips Challenge? Where's Chips
Challenge? I want some more Chips Challenge
That was a fun game
Maybe that will come in Windows 8
Service Pack 1 But like, they also
Had all those, like, was it the
All the different Solitaire games and Mahjong
Games and stuff like that that came with that pack
It was just like, eh So how are you feeling
About Windows 8, Loki? Are you kind of in the
It stinks camp, but you're an achievement
Whore? No, I'm not
Not to that You used to be
I used to be, I'm a recovery achievement whore
Well, admitting you have a
Problem is the first step No, I honestly
Windows 8 does not look
Good at all to me
I mean, there's nothing so far that's told me that I need
It's gonna be for me, it's kind of like one of those
Intermediate, you know
Versions, like, I didn't jump on Vista
And I went to 7, so I'm thinking that
Windows 9 or whatever the next one's gonna be
It'll probably be a little bit better for me
Um, yeah, actually that's kind of the way it's been
You know, I've always skipped, you know
A generation, I didn't do
I didn't do 95 to 98
Skipped ME, went to XP
Skipped Vista
Went to 7, so, yeah, this'll be
This'll be the operating system I skip
Windows 8
Is interesting
That's kind of the reaction I have to it, but
Interesting is also the word I use to describe
The commercial for Boo Boo Honey Child
Whatever that show is on TLC
So, um, I don't know, take from that what you will
It would be cool, Windows 8
Would be a better operating system
If touch screen monitors
Were more mainstream
Like, if my laptop
Had a touch screen monitor on it
Then yeah, Windows 8 would be pretty awesome
Because you can do all the touch screen stuff, but
I just don't think it's
Necessary right now
Alright, before we get to the next story, let's go to some comments
From our chat room at
Vognetwork.com
DarkSakura, why didn't you say this in a microphone?
She says, I do believe
There is Kingdom Hearts stuff at Disney C
So, correcting what I said earlier
About why does Disney ignore the
Kingdom Hearts
Because this is America!
America! America!
We won the most gold, deal with it
And I really wasn't saying it in reply to you
I was saying it to somebody in chat
Yeah, Rob
Let's see, and uh
Excuse me, AlphaKnanogram is correcting me
Whatever I said, it's Honey Boo Boo
Here comes Honey Boo Boo, that's not my pad
I'm so sorry
Porkchop says, who the fuck plays
Minesweeper anymore?
Um, you know
True story, I work in an adult
Training environment, I teach
You know, adults in a corporate
World basically, like how to do their jobs
And if we ever get people coming through the door
That aren't very comfortable
With using a computer, because sometimes you get
Some like, retired folks
That want to take like, kind of a new job
Or a new career
And they might not be as seasoned with computers
Or whatever, we will actually assign them to go
Home and play solitaire
To get better use with a mouse
And kind of get that coordination, it's a very
Good way to
You know, kind of get used to that
Whole hand-eye coordination, which
Many of us take for granted, we all grew up
On that stuff, but for people that didn't
Grow up on it and kind of have to learn it
Solitaire is actually a great way to learn it
Just, you know, think about it that way
And then when they come back and tell you, okay, I played
Solitaire with my card deck, how's that supposed to
Teach me computers, is this some sort of
Crazy karate kid thing where I go
Wax a car and I'm supposed to learn
Kung-Fu, is that how it's gonna work?
If I ever had a student say, it's a crazy
Karate kid thing, I'd just give them
An A. Alright
Let's be real
Alright, uh, move
What else do I want to say, uh, oh
Good chat, yes, thank you, the other comment
From GameGuru in our chatroom says
I see you are playing Solitaire
Would you like special Clippy themed backs
For the game?
Go to hell
This is an honest question because I don't know how to
Do this, is there any way to turn off
Beacons from other people, because
Let's be honest, I have someone that's on my friends list
Probably one of our listeners that has a beacon
That says, hey, I want friends to play
Minecraft, cool
I know that already, I'm already playing
Minecraft when I get your stupid notification
Yeah, I never realized those things stay on like
Forever, because I have- How do I turn that off?
I think I had one set for like, Mass Effect 3
Or something, I don't know, it's just like, everybody's like
Gets a little beep
I remember when I learned about how terrible
The notification system is, that I shut
Mine off, in order to
Not get them from your friends, I
Don't think that's possible
De-friend them, maybe
No, don't do that
Why don't you just send them a message that says, fuck you, you fucking
Fuck, turn your beak off
I'm already playing it, why don't you come play it?
You wanna play apparently
Alright, let's uh
Move on with some more news
And that would be me, talking about Amazon
Game Studios
Yeah, you know, Amazon, the website
That used to sell books
Sorry, I love Rageinator's comment
What was that? If Windows 8 is interesting, then by that definition
So is a lobotomy and colostomy bag
Fascinating
Anyhow
Also interesting, Amazon
Game Studios
Uh, yeah, Amazon of course, you know
They used to sell books and only books
And now they sell books and
Groceries
And probably sex toys
For all I know, probably Alien Dildos
Probably has a shop front on Amazon.com
I'm not sure, but
You can't buy vibrators on Amazon
For the listeners here
I was looking up
Vibrators on Amazon
Think of an excuse, quick
Mass Effect 3
I was looking up Mass Effect
For the record, I know this because
When I was a massage therapist, I was looking up
Electronic heat packs for necks
And it came to a list of personal
Vibration assistants
You want happy ending?
No
Yay, happy
Alright, so Amazon
They've sold books, they've sold vibrators
And now they sell games
But I don't mean, like obviously Amazon sold games
Already and even on the phones and so forth
Now they're making them too, Amazon
Game Studios
The first game that they have launched is
Living Classics
I guess it's a hidden object game
But they're calling it a moving object game
Alright, guess what, it's a Facebook
Game
Yeah, looks amazing, here's the trailer
We can look at for Living Classics here
The launch trailer
Oh, you can find
Moving objects
Oh
That looks like a waste of time
Perfect for Facebook
By the way, Amazon
Is hiring and
Alright, good luck with that Amazon
Let's just hope you make some games that I want to play
Out of curiosity, I went ahead and looked up
Electronic heat packs
On Amazon
And they have the weirdest shit
There's no vibrators, but there's like screws
The Sims
NASCAR 2002
The Sims?
NASCAR Thunder 2002
How the fuck does that have anything to do with electronic heat packs?
There was some kind of bullet casing
Or something in there too
And vibrating in it
Whatever
Let's move on with some more new Star Sakura
I was looking at vibrating heating pads
Oh, well there you go, vibrating
They're
Really good to loosen up someone's neck
Before you work on them
Or loosen up someone's
Never mind
You're all children
Yeah, speaking of ten years ago
Well, how about
Some Silent Hill news which has nothing to do with
Vibrations and everything to do
With a dead nurse rape
Okay
Well, it's true
Red Pyramid
Anyway
As we all know, Silent Hill
HD Collection is shit
Because it was built from unfinished code
End of story
Well, there's going to be a patch out that's only available on PS3
So, uh
People who got it on Xbox 360
You screwed, Konami don't care
Boohoo, go cry a river
Build a bridge and jump off it
What's that?
But I was reading something that
As long as you have your receipt, you're able to send it back to
Konami and they will send you
A new version of the disc
Okay, but Silent Hill HD Collection
Came out in what, March?
Who still has their receipt?
You've got to be one of those anal retentive people
That actually went and bought a receipt scanner
So that way you can scan
Your different receipts in here
So what if you buy it now
And then show them a receipt
And then you have them send you a free game on top of that
Well, let me read
From the official news source
Facebook
And Konami's page
Attention Silent Hill fans
If you purchase Silent Hill HD Collection
For the Xbox 360 new and from a
Recognized retailer
Oh, so that's how they're going to get around it
A recognized retailer
Oh, we don't know about this GameStop shit
And still have the original receipt
Please send the receipt to Konami
Customer service for verification
Further details, it's only valid for
Silent Hill HD Collection
Xbox 360 version games purchased
On or before August 8th
On or before August 8th, Loki
All requests must be made in
Writing and submitted on or before
October 7th and it is subject to
Availability
Well they're screwed because no one knows how to write anymore
Can't we just comment on the Facebook post
But it does say note the patch for Silent Hill
Downpour for both Xbox
360 and Playstation 3
Is currently in development
And scheduled for a release at a later date
How about this, why didn't they just finish the damn
Version
How about you just make it right the first time
I'm glad I didn't buy it
I still have Silent Hill 3 the good version
And that's all I care about
JVMON in chat says I keep all
My receipts, really?
Ragingator says I have receipts dating back
To 2002 and Stan says
I keep my game receipts for some reason
Wow, I'm just
Actually, Dan and I used to save all of our receipts
For the electronics that we bought, we still have the receipt
For my Wacom
I understand, for big huge purchases I get that
Like when I bought my old TV
At Costco, hell yeah I kept the receipt
Because Costco has an awesome return
Policy
Yeah, I mean they used to
Knowing things like that, hell yeah
I'll keep the receipt, but
I don't really ever save them for games
Maybe I ought to start
Dan still has his box for his DS that has a post-it note on it
That says, this is Dan's DS, don't buy it
I also love this
When we talk about recognized retailers
Monty Boggs in our chat room
At live.vognetwork.com says
Kmart? The fuck is Kmart denied?
Hey, I bought a Sonic shirt there
That's about it
I bought, I bought
A Super Mario Brothers shirt
There, I was very happy
Jvmon in our chat says
I still have the receipts for those Dunkin Donuts
K-Cups I got you, lol
I drank one
Yeah, don't take this the wrong way
Because the Dunkin Donuts K-Cups were great
But they're like half gone now
So even if you had the receipt
The store's not gonna take them back
I done drunk them
And they were terrible
Give me my money back
No, they were good, they were good
A little sugar, a little creamer
Apparently you don't know how this works
Grab coffee
Alright, let's move on with some more news
Hey, agreed porkchop
Please don't fuck up the Zone of the Enders HD collection
Cross his fingers
Co-sign to that
Exactly, it's like, oh hey, yeah, we don't wanna patch this
But buy our new Zone of the Enders
Oh, and by the way
We're still selling this
In case you do want a broken game
So anyways
There was some rumored
Next-gen
Kinect images
Released on Twitter
By a guy that goes by the name
SuperDAE
Who also apparently has no sense of humor
Because I made a comment on his little post
And he said, don't be an idiot
Bastard
Don't be an idiot
I just made the comment because you know
It's got the little neon character
The depth map on there
And it kind of resembles, you know
The image from Just Dance
And I made the comment and I'm like
Well, that's not an image from the new Kinect
That's just from the new version of Just Dance
Apparently he has no sense of humor
Because he didn't even say haha if I were funny
He said, don't be an idiot
Well good, I'm not gonna be an idiot
Like someone that would try to buy his
Development kit for the Durango
That he just now put on eBay
That's up to $15,000
And basically
You're taking his word for it
That this is actually an Xbox Durango
Development kit
And it looks like a PC
Because that's what the development kits look like
And there's really nothing that guarantees you
Anyway that
This is gonna be a development kit
Other than the fact that I think some other developers
Have a picture of it and they're like
Yeah, that looks like a development kit
But who knows
But yes, so we'll see if this is legit or not
Because if it is the real deal
Then Microsoft will probably pull it off of eBay
But as of right now
It is
Oh, it was ended early because the item was sold
For $20,000
Well $20,000 was the last bid
But it says the listing was ended by the seller
Because the item was sold
Interesting, so like ended early or whatever?
Yeah
Surprised you could do that with bids on it
Yeah, I didn't think you could do that, that's interesting
Now the question is
Who bought it, Gizmodo?
We'll see
Alright
Meanwhile
Be careful
If you are a Blizzard
Or battle.net customer
Oh yeah, that
Because guess what, they got hacked
You know the old saying, hackers gonna hack
But to be fair, battle.net was
Pretty upfront about what happened
Because I think we've learned from history
Don't try to hide this shit from your users
They're smarter than that
So Mike Morhaime, the CEO himself
Wrote a little letter that says
You know what, even when you are in the business
Of fun, not every week ends up
Being fun
And they found out that there was an unauthorized and illegal access
Into the network at Blizzard
And they did confirm
No financial information such as credit cards
Billing addresses or real names were compromised
Thank God
I was surprised they went this far
They said some data was illegally accessed
Including a list of
Email addresses for global battle.net
Users outside of China
For players on North American servers
Which generally includes players from
North America, Latin America, Australia, New Zealand
And Southeast Asia
So instead of saying it was everybody, they said
They targeted these specific regions
They got the answers to
The personal security questions
And information relating to
Mobile and dial-in authenticators
That's pretty bad that they got
The personal security question answers
Because if you use those
Security question and answers on other
Sites
It's just like having a password anyway
It is
So that's pretty bad
Now they do say
Cryptographically scrambled versions
Of battle.net passwords, not the actual
Passwords were taken
But they do think with brute force
You could decode one at a time passwords
But who cares if you've got the
Answers to your secret questions
You don't even need to do that
So in the coming days they are going to prompt
Folks to change the secret questions and answers
Through an automated process
Also the mobile authenticator users will have to
Update the software and so on
So highly recommend at this point
If you play World of Warcraft
If you play Diablo
If you play Starcraft, any of those games
They're all on battle.net
You need to change your password
On battle.net right away and you can do that
At battle.net
Slash account slash management
Slash setting, you know what there's a link right there
At battle.net
I had forgotten to do mine so I just did it
But can you, other than changing your passwords
Because that's not going to matter if they have your secret questions
Can you change your secret questions?
Not yet
So then what the fuck's the point
We have an authenticator
I don't think the secret question alone
Will get them into the account
Especially if you've got an authenticator
Attached to it
I believe the secret question can only be used
To generate a reset request
Which still goes to your email
So this is the other important thing
Your email password
Needs to be unique
This is, I mean, in a perfect world
Every password is unique
But I understand not everybody can realistically
Do that with all the websites we sign up for
So your email password
Needs to be unique
This is just internet security 101
If you do not have a unique
Email password you are setting yourself
Up for trouble because think about it
Somebody gets your battle.net password here
Or they got your Playstation password before
Your Xbox password or whatever
They're going to use it to get in your email
Once they get in your email, you're fucked
Because all those reset requests
Everything goes back to your email
The guy who got hacked through the whole
iCloud reset or whatever this week
For the record, when you do change your password
It also does send you an email
That says if you didn't make the change
Click the link so that you can recover your account
Well his hacking thing was a little different
That was just security flaws with whole social
Networking and stuff like that
Basically people
Called up, added a fake credit card
To an Amazon account and then
Called back up using that
New credit card as
Authentication for other information
Porkchop in our
Chatroom says, anyone see that guy Francis
Rage about the hacks on YouTube
No I didn't, but I love
I love internet rage
He tried to eat his authenticator
Oh that's old
That was about
Diablo 3
He did a new one
Because he's a persona
It's just a persona
It's all for hits
It's not as funny when it's fake
You know what's fucking hilarious is that
Twilight girl
That's the stuff I live for
On YouTube
Why would you cheat on him?
Why?
Really?
Oh yeah, Brittany
Really? You've never seen
The crying chick over Twilight?
No because I have a life
Tigerclaw, can you find me a link please?
I need to show Jamie this
Please find me the crying
The girl who's losing her shit over Kristen Stewart
I usually have better stuff
You know the best thing is
Oh she quit acting, when did she
Start?
Well Jamie if you wish
To take us back on track then by all means
Give us another news story
Sure as fuck ain't about no talent bitch
You know what
I accidentally closed my story
Oh yeah here we go
How about
Diablo
Um, it was funny
I had a friend in Alabama who played a lot of Diablo
Except with a thick southern accent
So it was Diablo
Blow
So anyway
Diablo
Occasionally
La la la la la
I don't need to know that
Well
How about some
Changes from Blizzard
There's gonna be a new patch
1.0.4
That will be out the fourth week
Of August
They like co-op and they want more people to do it
So this is so that you can play more
Co-op
They are
Trying to make things a little bit more attractive
So they're gonna be removing the
Averaging of magic find and gold
Find in multiplayer
So that you will benefit from full magic find
Independent of other players
Okay wait
I gotta go
Let's let Jamie finish and then I'll go to Ry for reaction
Well they added it in
They added the averaging in so that it didn't
Involve people stacking adventure stats
To detriment the party
But I guess no one likes that
I don't know I never did it
Usually anytime someone joined my game I quit
The last
Four times I played someone joined my game
I quit
Alright let me go to the resident
Real fan girl to check in on patch news
So that's why you said it
So that people have to ask
I did
They still joined my game
Really? Yes
Of course this was before any patching had been done
Gotcha
On the whole magic find gold find
My shit is my own
I build up my gold find
I build up my magic find
That shit is mine
It should not matter what yours is
If it's me
Then it just makes it worse for me
So you know get out of my game
Well
And this is why I'm still level 22
When she has 260's
There's more
But wait there's more
Weapon damage is also
Going to be retooled
So basically
It's
I'm just going to read the quote
That I like to make to our item
Game addresses the difference between an item having
A chance of being good versus knowing
The item isn't going to be good before
You can even identify it
So they're basically
Trying to
Have a raw damage level between
61 and 62 weapons
So that it can
Hit the top of 63 I think
However they explained it
I have no idea because like I said I didn't play that much
And then
Enraged timers are being removed
From champion and rare monster packs
They will still be on bosses
But they will
Not be
Basically they don't want to have you have to do a
DPS check
What?
Hey
Ryaz do you know what that's getting at?
No idea because all I know is enraged timers and wow
So inferno is where
They brought in enraged timers
That if
You don't beat an enemy
A stack of enemies within a certain amount of time
You'll basically start taking like poison
Damage you'll be standing there and your life
Will just drain away
So instead of
Trying to figure out
Your strategy on how you're going to beat that group
If you take too long it's just
Going to kill you
Wow
That's stupid
Another thing too is that
Repair costs are going to be on high
And items are going to be decreased by 25%
And
A bunch of other changes
That are going to come out later
It's on the development blog
Diablo 3 patch 1.04
Seal of approval by Ry
And sorry
Still no PVP
Maybe I'll play again
It was free why not
I signed the blood pact
We're going to get into release dates
But before we do
Let's do a culture lesson
On him and saying that she's sorry
Like that makes it okay
I feel like everybody needs to back off okay
This is none of your business
This is none of anybody's business
But her releasing that statement
It's like
It's like saying
Hello world come on in
It's like saying it doesn't matter
It's okay
Oh I don't understand how she could do this
Let me fast forward a little bit
Because I want to see if there's
More breakdown
I love him
I love him I'm so sorry okay
If you loved him that much
You wouldn't have done it
If you cared about him that much you wouldn't have done it
And if you wanted people to back off
And not be involved then you wouldn't have posted
That statement but
You see the thing is you were stupid enough
To get photographed doing it okay
Don't be so stupid
I can't help it
But that accent's awesome
There's like a level of sophistication
I was going in between
Going that's a pretty cool accent
And then going but she's so
Stupid I want to point this out
She's very much
A fan of this person so I mean
But her accent is awesome
This is when fandom goes sour
This is 2.5 million
Views on YouTube
And you just added to it Rob what the hell
And by the way bless you tiger
For finding this for us
I can always count on you 2.5 million
Views on YouTube
Do you know how many people listen to this show
Far less
But my favorite is
My favorite is the related
Videos on the side such as
Tom Cruise liked my nail polish
Oh it's her too
She's been to McDonald's for breakfast
There's a stage at the top and there's going to be a band playing
But we don't know who
I want to get to Tom Cruise
Where is it
Library day
Ok Breaking Dawn Part 2 trailer
Reaction I've seen this before it's so
Amazing this video is like
Where she's crying
Through the whole thing
I don't think we know the truth
Maybe we can convince the Volturi to listen
My family is in danger
Oh my god
That was me watching the trailer for Mr. Pandaria
Actually
It can still be
Anyone watching the trailer for Breaking Dawn
Because it is that bad
We need to do one of those for showgirls
And send it to Peaches
Oh actually
The trailer just came out for the
Mass Effect 3 Leviathan DLC
And we actually have
Shane's reaction here on video
Volturi
They're coming for us
We love you Shane
He's not in chat
I don't see him
Is Shane there?
He went on a work trip so he's in another
City right now and he's probably asleep
Because he was up for like 27 hours straight
He said he was gonna try and listen on his phone
Tonight but he's gotta be asleep
Which is great because I've talked shit
About him like 3 times so far
In tonight's episode
Well maybe we'll find out in about an hour
No I would've got a text message
By now
I'm not that bad
Just say jerk
Alright
Oh Shane
Let's travel around the world and look at some
Release dates
Loki start us off with the US please
Can I do reactions?
Yes
DarkSakra and Rob do reactions to the US release dates
Here we go
Coming out of Nintendo Wii the last story
Oh god
I've been waiting for this game
This game
Operation Rainbow
I love you so much
We did it
It's finally coming out
Everybody else
Doesn't like the Wii anymore
But I
I love the Wii
I love you Wii
I love Wii
I love Wii when nobody would love Wii
Rob there there there there
You can love your Wii
Alright
I was out there getting signatures
Outside of Gamestop for Hyper Ace
Right
Alright
Let's move on to Darksiders 2
I love Darksiders 1
Sleeping Dogs
For Playstation 3, Xbox 360
Also on PC but digital version only
You have to get that on Steam
And then
One week from today
New Super Mario Brothers 2
For the 3DS
As well
It's new!
As well as the bundle
With the 3DS XL
And also the 3DS XL in blue and red
Coming out on the 19th
That is it
Let's travel to Japan
Check out the Japanese release dates
Maybe we'll get some reactions from Loki
If I can actually get the Japanese
I'm just building up the moment in anticipation here
I was just so excited about it
I have to tell you about my fun Japanese moment
Alright great
There was an exchange student in line behind me at Target
Nevermind
Actually this did happen the other day
That was the worst story ever
Congratulations
Actually this did happen is that I helped her pick out a flavor of breath mints
True story
Cool story bro
And Rob
What?
Alien Delo
On the Playstation 3 in Japan this week
From Hamster
Is the group putting it out
Heavy Fire Afghanistan
Is coming out this week
On the Playstation 3 in Japan
Going to the 3DS
Uwakoku Kansai-kan
Airport Hero 3D Honolulu
I don't know if that's kind of like the flight game
Alien Dildos
No I don't think it's Alien Dildos actually
And lastly taking a look at the Vita real quick
Next Revolution
Takenshiken comes out
As well as Tokushu Hudoubu
Comes out this week
Kind of a slower week in Japan
Sorry to say
But a game to get really excited about
I know this is a game many of you at home
Would be losing your shit over like the Twilight Girl
Hatsune Miku Project
Sadly she wasn't joking
That from Sega coming out on August 30th
What?
Alright
That's it for Japanese release dates
Let's go to UK release dates
On the 13th of August we have Iron Brigade on the PC
I was just trying to make it sound more authentic
15th of August
We have Dust
An Elysian Tall
Is what it says
God do you know what it says Tall?
I'm like what the crap
They need to fix their typefaces
And on the 17th of August we have
New Super Mario Brothers 2
On the 3DS
Now available at the retail in the U
And that's it for the UK release dates?
Yeah
Alright let's do a couple more news stories
And then the classic game of the week
Cause we need something this week to keep the show classy
Loki
Alright so Valve discovered that one of the
Custom made weapons
For
Dota 2 which surprised me
Cause I didn't realize Dota 2 was out already
But apparently it is
And apparently someone copied
A mace that's from
The MMO Aeon
And
Just so you know I don't think Dota 2 is officially out
I mean Chatroom correct me if I'm wrong
I think it's just one of those betas like everybody's in
Oh
I think that's gonna work out
Anyways so
Apparently they discovered this
You know this
Weapon in there and of course they removed
The item and issued a warning
To the players that
You know this kind of crap is not gonna be tolerated
Not only did they do that they also
Removed the maces from everybody's inventory
They replaced it with a new item
And they also banned
The um
You know banned the person that made
The actual weapon
And stripped his account
From all the proceeds
From the sale so apparently there's real
There's real money transactions going along
With these weapons I think it's kind of like the hats
And Team Fortress and all that stuff yeah
And of course
Reminding everybody that you know you must respect
IP of other companies and
Encouraging their community to report
Infringement this is how the fucking shit should
Go down for anything on Apple's
Marketplace when they discover hey
This is ripping off some shit they should well of course
I think that's the whole problem is they don't know
Burn it in ten thousand fires
Basically you know they they don't have enough
People saying you know there's
I guess not enough people looking at stuff
That's on their marketplace maybe that's the problem
Because they do I know ban people when stuff's
Discovered but
And thank you chatters GameGuru confirming
It's not out it's still in beta and
Photoshop says it's been a beta for ages now
So basically it's like Gmail
Like Gmail was in beta for what five years?
Alright
Okay
Alright it's just a new layer of beta
Something else has been
Sitting dormant for years and years
This is crazy oops
I didn't mean to like have that autoplay but there you go
The sounds you hear in the
Background the sounds of the NBA
Jam triple X
Prototype is what they're calling it around the internet
That doesn't mean NGA
NGA
NBA Jam
Acronym fail with boobies okay
That's not what they mean by triple X here but it's actually
The original cartridge got shipped
To this website NintendoPlayer.com
Where they like to discover these prototypes
And whatever and this particular
You know
Board got sent to them that was an
NBA Jam work in progress
And it has Jam written over one little
Chip there and then XXX over
The other chips so I don't think
It was like meant to like have that name triple
X but it's kind of funny that it does because
Basically all it is it's the
Same NBA Jam that was on the Super
Nintendo but it has
Some R rated outtakes
That are inserted in the game instead
Here's an example this little YouTube
I'm going to play right here
He's cooking up
Yes he just said he's
Fucking up
Get that shit out of here
No fucking way
He's on fucking fire
So lol the F word is all over
The game basically right
Well some folks obviously are questioning
Its authenticity including the guy
Who did the original voice overs himself
Who basically said oh wow
That's pretty crazy
Somebody sounds just like me out there
Doing these acts on the internet
But it appears this website
Actually released they say
Download right here you can actually download the ROM
And try it for yourself so I don't think
It's just the YouTube you can actually check this out
So they did dump the ROM and you can check this out
And I don't know if you would just be able to
Insert in your own clips or whatever
I think you could ROM hack that
And then you can burn the ROM chips
Onto the cartridge
Yeah but I think it's also plausible you know
When you're in the sound booth doing recording
And this was even said on some website somewhere
Some forum post I got linked
And I apologize I don't have it in front of me
But it totally made sense
If you're doing voice overs for hours and hours
Of these lines you're gonna do some funny ones
You're gonna have some zany outtakes
You're gonna have some moments of stress relief
Where you just go how many times do you need me to say this
He's on fucking fire you know
And then so yeah there's probably a programmer
That thought it would be funny
That thought it would be funny to put those in the game
But put it under lock and key so that nobody ever would get it
Hot coffee
Have you
Lock and key but still in the game
I remember a video that I saw
I don't know quite a couple years ago about
Basically outtakes of Casey Kasem's top 50
Or top 100 whatever he used to do
That he would be recording bombs for radio stations
It's like the home of the best
Radio in Illinois
And that's the cut of the take and then
How do I fucking know they're the best
And similar similar similar situations
Like that I mean
I was able to for somebody to
Have a similar voice plus effects sound the same
Back to the future release
In the last two years
Well there's also the outtake of
Oh god I can't remember his name who was Elmer Fudd
Or Porky Pig sorry
It said
Son of a gun you thought I was gonna say son of a bitch didn't you
And I'm really sure it's Christopher Walken
Doing all those playthroughs of different games
I'm really sure it's him you know
Watching the playthroughs for that
Or reading you know
What things are and all that stuff
Bless you internet
We're up to our long distance dedication
But he was most certainly a part of let's go start again
From coming out of the record
Play the record okay
Please
See when you come out of those up tempo god damn numbers man
It's impossible to make those transitions
And then you gotta go into somebody dying
You know they do this to me all the time
I don't know what the hell they do it for
But god damn it if we can't come out of a slow record
I don't understand it
Okay I want a god damn concerted effort to come out of a record
That isn't a fucking up tempo record
Every time I do a god damn deaf dedication
Now make it and I also want to know what happened to the pictures I was supposed to see this week
We'll do it live
Essentially so
Those things can happen y'all
No I'm not saying this announcer guy lost it on Casey Kasem or Bill O'Reilly levels
But you know
His show would be even better if he did it that way
Transformers
He was the voice of several transformers
You're in a confined booth for god knows how many hours
You don't think moods start to change
Go a little off script
Anyhow I don't know I mean the fact that there actually is a ROM of it out there
Makes it a lot more believable than just the video
Granted a lot of work but why would somebody do that much work?
Just to put the F word
Especially in a website that's dedicated to this kind of crap anyways
I don't think they'd go make something up
Maybe if it was April 1st or something like that
It's like stock photo sites and how they're stock photo of the most absurd imaginable situations
What was the meme?
Naked in front of a refrigerator getting a salad or something completely ridiculous like that
What?
You basically go for absurd stock photo pictures
And the people that have to take these pictures come up with the most ridiculous scenes ever
And so there is a whole series of censored naked people eating a salad
Are you tossing the salad?
No that's another site Rob
Kotaku will run a...
Kotaku will run anything
I understand this but I'm just saying they run a feature every week
It's about stock footage of people playing games
And it's just like weird shit
There is the one where this emo chick is playing this game
Laying off of a couch somehow
And her friend has a hookah next to her
And it's just like a non-lit hookah smoking it
It's like why would you need stock footage for that?
Hipster gaming
You want to get high and play some sound shapes
More like whatever sinks your battleship
Let's go back to a time when games were so much simpler and pure
Artist!
10 years ago right Rob?
Going back to the classic game of the week
A nice G-rated experience for everybody right DarkSakura?
Who's going to dip into the vault right now and find a game that she thinks
Hey you little shit I mean sucker
You should play this video game right now
If you're into shirtless bestiality you want this game
And what game could you ever be talking about DarkSakura?
Altered Beast
Which I really don't think I've ever done
Rise from your grave
There we go we got to have it
In Japan it was called Juloki
Which is Beast King's Chronicle
Came out in 1988 by Sega
And it's a go around beat shit up game
It's set in ancient Greece
And it's a centurion who is resurrected by Zeus
To rescue Athena
Like Zeus ever cared about his kids
And so he is able to turn into different beasts
When you get this little power up sphere thing
He just turns into big dude and then turns into animal man
It came out on several video game consoles and computers at home
It was a pack-in game for the Mega Drive
And one of the designers for this was Makoto Uchida
Who was the creator of Golden Axe
So stylistically you can see things in between the two games
So anyway the centurion is dead
So basically you're playing a zombie
And you have to beat some dude named Nef
Well a demon god named Nef
And so you can become different types of aminals
When you get to hell or Disks I should say
You face Nef who becomes a huge rhinoceros guy
And then a blue bird comes out of the ground and turns into Athena
So it's very acid trippy too
It is side scrolling and it has been on damn near everything
So the orbs that you get through the game
Will make you bigger and bad-asser with huge muscular thighs and abs
And you turn into a werewolf, a weredragon, a werebear, a weretiger, or the golden werewolf
There's other different beasts in the Famicom version and in the Gameboy Advance version
And sometimes you get lightning power
At any rate you also have some very weird unicorn creatures in one of the levels
That just sort of tries to headbutt you to death
The dry queen unicorns, they were my favorite
The dry queen unicorns
It's like I would always laugh my ass off seeing them
So what it came out on is
I hear giggles
It's just the chat room acting up
Let's kneel
Travis I'm gonna bench you over my knee and spank ya
And not in the good way for the 69th episode
The fuck he said
Nah it's not that, don't worry
Get back to the classic game
Alright
So it came out for the Sega Master System, the PC Engine, PC Engine CD, Famicom, Atari STX
Spectrum, Commodore 64, R.O.B.
The Armstrad CPC, Commodore Amiga, and DOS
The Mega Drive slash Genesis version is important because it was a pack-in game for North America, Europe, and Brazil
And then it was replaced by Sonic the Hedgehog
There is a handheld version of the game done by Tiger Electronics
God what is funny?
I'm not allowed to smile
But you're doing the nose laugh
I'm laughing because Travis spoke up in chat and said, yeah baby
And I tried to spank him so I'm laughing
Remember, it's only porn if you tape it
So
Yeah baby
The Mega Drive version is on several compilations
Including the Sega Smash Pack, Sega Genesis Collection, and Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection
And on the latter two they are unlockable
You can get it on the Virtual Console for Wii
It is on Xbox 360, on Xbox Live Arcade
And on the Playstation Network as the arcade version with HD support
And has online
What?
Sorry
Online leaderboards and network play
There is an iOS version of the Mega Drive version
That came out in 2010 for the iPhone and iPad
Because all the good stuff comes out on iOS and not Android
There are a lot of the lower versions
That only had single player and four levels
And had different beasts like a human shark in the NES version
It was very weird
But yeah, now there is this thing called Project Altered Beast
And this was a Playstation 2 title that came out
Excuse me
In 2005 in Japan it was called Jewel Key Project Altered Beast
And Altered Beast in Europe
And it did not come out in North America
It was 18 plus rated in Japan for being intensity
But in Europe it was rated 12 plus
But it had like tons and tons of gore in it
And it basically was kind of unrelated to the original game
You played as a dude called Luke Custer
Who was a genome cyborg
And his DNA and genetic makeup was screwed
So that he could turn into a werewolf, a merman, a garuda
Which basically is like an eagle
A wendigo, a minotaur and a dragon
And then you could also be like a weretiger and a grizzly bear
So bears in video games huh
And then there was Altered Beast Guardian of the Realms
Which was developed by 3D6 Games and published by THQ
That was a sequel for the GBA version
And you could turn into a werewolf, a snake man
A dragon, a tiger man, a spiked turtle
A shark man, a rhinoceros man
An eagle man
A scorpion or a chimera
Or
Yeah
So that's it
Alright there it is, your classic game of the week
One last thing
Altered Beast
Neth, the bad guy
Will be in rhinoceros form in Wreck it Ralph
Oh okay
In the bad guy's anonymous scene
Nice
Alright Altered Beast, your classic game of the week
Now some folks in chat are thinking
Wasn't this a classic game of the week before?
Actually it wasn't
Here's where it came up on the show before
Not that long ago the Genesis collection or whatever
The reimaginings that were on the Playstation Network and Xbox Live Arcade
They went free for Playstation Plus subscribers
That same week I signed up for Playstation Plus
So I went back and played through this entire game
And I think I did this whole rant on those unicorns
So I have talked about this game on the show previously
But it wasn't technically a classic game of the week
That was a little while ago at this point
So just to clear up any confusion
But I do remember when I played through it
Can I check the list?
It's pretty terrible
Now keep in mind I had to play the Genesis version
Not the arcade version
We actually just I think played through the Genesis version
Not long ago
We had
Pretty bad
No I take that back, Sega Ages
We played through
Alright
Alright so there it is your classic game of the week
Altered Beast
Let's take a break
Obviously it's been a lullsy show so far
But the best is yet to come
Nah I don't know I'm just saying that
But you don't know what's gonna happen on part B
Of Orange Lounge Radio
We're gonna get to the emails
FUs of the week and phone calls
Oh anything can happen during phone calls
All when we come back with more
Of Orange Lounge Radio
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
Episode number 469
Already in progress
We've had quite the night so far
Okay
I have coffee
I was talking to Alan in the other room during the break
And he's actually listening to the show while he plays Mass Effect 3 multiplayer
Which by the way
He has a disgusting collection of Mass Effect 3 multiplayer
I saw the guns
Pretty outstanding huh
He said he was about ready to come out here and tell us
No stop it stop it
During the uh
During the release date segment
But anyway we'll see what happens
In this part B of our program
The song was not about alien dildos
Pork chop
Now the podcasters will have no idea what you're talking about
But during the break we played a song for Mass Effect
The long song that's the credits during the first game
Unless you have DLC and then the song was seriously stopped
And you still have credits
Right
Actually that was me in Mass Effect 2
I had like another
Same length of the song plus some
Of no music
What?
For Mass Effect 2 I had so much DLC
Oh
Because I bought the collector's edition
Because it was 11 bucks and came with the first Mass Effect
Which I already bought
Right
That I seriously had the length of the song
Plus some of nothing
So I just went to the bathroom
Cool story
Alright
Let's get into some rapid fire news
And some quick stories about some things going on in the gaming world this week
Logie
Alright so Minecraft Pocket Edition has gotten an update
Where they've added a few things that you can find in the full fledged version
On PC and Xbox 360
Well 360 not being entirely full fledged
But you get the point
Anyways
They've added skeletons and spiders
As well as bows
So now you can fire bows and arrows
Or fire arrows at a
Spiders and skeletons and bows oh my
I'm surprised I thought they already had skeletons in the game
But maybe I'm just mistaken
Maybe there's always zombies
I haven't played much of the Pocket Edition
But I do play it sometimes
When I'm stuck somewhere and I'll have my phone
Skyrim is getting the 1.7 update on consoles
Becoming out and of course it includes a number of bug fixes
And optimizations and stuff like that
And they'll be coming out on Xbox
And also PC at some point
Or PS3 at some point
And still no word on Dawnguard
For PS3
You don't get it yet
Because they're just not satisfied with
When it's ready
Exactly
Well we're satisfied
And then last but not least
Cabela's
You know they're really trying hard to figure out a way to make Cabela's interesting
And so now the latest thing that they have
Is they kind of modified their top shot gun
Because they actually for the last few games
They've had this gun peripheral
It's a wireless gun that goes along with
The Xbox 360 and PS3 versions
But now they've retitled the gun the Fear Master
And what makes it unique is that it has
A sensor built into the actual handle of the gun
That senses your heart rate
And I guess based on that it will affect the game
So is that like the Wii Vitality sensor?
Sort of
Okay
But you know had they pitched it instead of saying
It'll make you healthy and blah blah blah
They could have made it you know
The Wii Vitality sensor
We're gonna throw dangerous animals at you
I mean that might have been a little bit more interesting
Like the Wii Vitality sensor had been for like Tokyo Jungle
Which is a PlayStation game so I know that makes no sense
But you know
Work with me here for a minute
Yes
Something like that
But that's coming out on the 23rd
That's Dangerous Hunts 2013
Cause they have two
Two Cabela's games that come out each year
Actually last year they had three on the same day
Why?
Oh that also happened to be the week before
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3 came out
So no one gave a shit
Can I interject a little story about something like this?
Of course
I actually hadn't heard of this before
And something kind of interesting that
Not a lot of people know
May know as a result of the situation
Fatal Frame 1 through 3 were all PlayStation 2 games
And then Fatal Frame 4 came out on the Wii
And actually incorporated motion controls
Etcetera, etcetera
In Japan and Europe they re-released Fatal Frame 2
Under the Fatal Frame 4 controls
And it's amazing
Like I wasn't a big fan of 4
First three games
Absolutely love them
The relevance here is that Fatal Frame 2's re-release
Has mini games
And they actually implemented something like this
They attempted to
Where you basically walk through a haunted house
In a Fatal Frame 2 scene
And they basically measure fear
As a result of movement in the nunchuck and the Wiimote
Obviously they're not going to be picking up your heart rate
Or anything like that
Which would have been a better indicator
But they'll throw sounds and ghosts and spirits
And you know the Fatal Frame kind of situations at you
And the goal is to keep the Wiimote and the nunchuck
As steady as possible
Now that would have been a pretty good use of the Wiimote
Yeah, it's a nice little implementation
The re-release happened mid, late last year, earlier this year
I don't think it's going to come out in America
But the situation, the fact that they actually took something like that
And went forward through it
It's kind of a cool application
Because the Wiimote's going to know when you throw your hands up
And freak out
As, well, a little kid would anyways
I haven't, I swear
Ry, would you care to comment on that?
Actually, he's pretty calm when playing those games
It's very fun to watch Jason play those
Does Jason ever lose his shit over any video games?
That's a good question
That is a really good question
I don't think I've really seen him lose his shit
I've seen him where he'll pause it
And kind of look away and that kind of thing
But nothing like getting up and screaming
Or jumping from something that's bad
Not like the boys at Four Player Podcast
Yeah, not like one of our other friends
He's very, very scared of him
You can tell
Has he played much of, was it
Amnesia? Maybe that's the game we need to be adjacent to
No, well there's Amnesia and then there's also
What is it, not the
Yeah, Ender
Amnesia's on my list
I do have it in Steam and it's on my list eventually
Even when I played Silent Hill 3
Slender, I'm sorry, not Ender
I've been confusing Minecraft again
Well, it's Slender
It's based on the Slender Man stuff
But they have Slender
People get fucking freaked out by that game
What is this on?
It's on PC
One of my coworkers was talking about it
And it's one of those things that I forgot the name of it
So I couldn't come home and say
Hey Jason, you need to play this
So Slender and Amnesia, huh?
Slender is all about walking through the forest
And you get to find notes
But the Slender Man, you see, he stalks you
And occasionally you'll walk into
And it's all at night with a flashlight
And if you look at him
You know, the longer you look at him
The more damage you take
And you're not supposed to look at the Slender Man
I'm intrigued
I will say that
Just before Silent Hill HD Collections came out
I actually went there and replayed
Went to go play through all of Silent Hill 1-4
The ambiance of 4 and especially the ending
It terrified me
I could not get more than 15-20 minutes into Silent Hill 4
The quietness, the...
You didn't even start Silent Hill 4
It was the opening video
I took steps through the room
I got to the point where the room started to transition
Which was, okay, maybe it wasn't 20 minutes
Maybe I'm giving myself a little bit too much credit there
I started the game
I looked outside
I saw the other apartment complex
And the couple of people you could see moving
But as soon as the wall started changing
Plus the intro video
Can you imagine?
I can't wait for in the future
When we have these reaction videos
But instead of the reaction videos
People watching the screen
It's like a VR heads up display
Or something like that
Where you're just completely immersed
And you turn around
HOLY SHIT!
Immersion is going to be the best thing
And the worst thing for me
For the record, you know the only thing that creeps me out in Silent Hill?
The rabbit
We need to get the video capture
For me it's that hospital room
Where you go in the room and then all of a sudden it's the giant head
And it's like
I can tell how scared you are right now
Well I really think what we should do
We need to make it a priority to get the video capture set up in this place
So that for Halloween
Or somewhere around there we can do a
Scary game marathon
And make me play these scary games
And I will cry
I will throw things
Nothing will match that experience
Where I was playing Silent Hill Homecoming
And the ceiling falls down
In this one random part
And I was playing in the middle of a rainstorm
And our front door blew open
And I swear to god
I jumped in my bed and went under the covers and started crying
I couldn't handle it
It was too much
And Homecoming wasn't even that great
All things considered
It was alright
Anyhow
I have some news for you guys as well
Unfortunately some sad news
I have to start off with some sad news here
During my part of rapid fire news
Paul Steed
He worked on bringing Wing Commander to 3D
He also was part of the original Xbox launch
Unfortunately he passed away
We don't have a cause of death or what have you
But he was a very important part of 90s gaming
He worked on some big big PC titles in the 90s
Wing Commander
Wings of Glory
Bioforge
Quake at ID Software
And he also made the crack horror player model
Yes that was a thing
So unfortunately he did pass away this week
According to the Jace Hall show
Which there is a YouTube clip of him there
He leaves behind a wife and child
Sorry to hear that
Moving on
To news about the Wii U
Wii games apparently going to be playable
On the Wii U gamepad
That's very interesting
We kind of expect that Nintendo platforms at this point
Are going to be backwards compatible
With the prior platform
It's been a very common thing in the handheld part
And then of course we've seen
You know how the Wii will play GameCube games
Well the Wii U will play the Wii games as well
And what's interesting is that you can actually play them
On the little gamepad
Because those gamepads have the little sensor bar
In them
So yep you can point with the touch screen and so forth
Using a Wii remote
However I want to point out
This is still apparently a rumor
That it's a Spanish brand manager
And not an official Nintendo source
It kind of makes sense though
It would be a great reason to sell a mini-mote
A mini-mote
A little keychain mote
How big is this screen?
Not even 4 inches or so?
Well it's not the size, Jason
It's how you use it
4-16
I can't imagine playing a game
With that small of a pointing radius
No I understand
Because even when they were showing
The Wii U
The Wii Fit U stuff
It was just like
Ok that's fucking ridiculous
You're going to have this little thing set up
While your wife's watching TV
And you're going to be exercising to this tiny little screen
Come on, I mean that's a little
Little dumb
But there's other Wii games that would work
Like Mario Galaxy
New Super Mario
Virtual Console games
New Super Mario Brothers
I was actually just thinking about that
That's kind of worse for one reason
Certain power-ups
You're holding this
What I'm expecting to be rather
Hefty tablet
Less because it's not the whole guts
But you're holding this tablet in your hands
Oh I need to throw a fireball
Let me shake this ridiculously oversized
Controller tablet
In order to spin jump
Propeller
That thing had a built in projector
That little tablet thing had a built in projector
That would be fucking cool
Wasn't that the early rumors about the revolution
Was that it's going to project
3D out its anus
Onto your wall
Remember that shit?
No remember that was the console was the
VR headset
That's what the thing was
I remember the whole
The Wii is like fucking holograms and shit
I remember those were early
When it was the revolution and they said
Oh it's the Wii
And you're like nope that's not going to be revolutionary at all
Anyhow
We took this really kick ass name
And we cut its balls off
Speaking of Nintendo news
There are some more details for Animal Crossing
3DS
I don't know how I feel
Total KK Total KK Total KK Total KK
Animal Crossing was awesome the first time
It was one of the best games ever on the GameCube
Back when it had the NES games unlocked
But now I don't know
I'm getting a little bit
I'm feeling a little burned out on this series
But I'll give it one more go with the 3DS version
It was educational for me
Oh with the whole, you're talking about the
Animal Forest with the Japanese letters
Yeah because I was using it to practice reading
Anyhow
Here are some things to look forward to in the brand new
Animal Crossing Jump Out
Which by the way is the title
Oh my god
Well because it's 3D so the pictures they just
Go out
Yeah
Loki these are the things you have to look forward to
Because I know you're a big fan of Animal Crossing
Oh I can't wait to pick it up for my 3
Oh wait no I can't
An all new gardening store where you can purchase
Plants
Fantastic you know instead of having them at Nook's
Where they've always been let's separate it into
Yet another fucking store I gotta hike to
That has different hours in Nook
Raccoon housing which will be run by Tom Nook
A wider variety
Of fish and fossils which you can
Donate to your museum
An exhibition room
And shop in the museum which will be open
24 hours
I don't know of any museums that are open 24 hours
Actually a lot of like
National parks and stuff like I'm thinking like
Washington DC a lot of people don't know this but like the
Lincoln Memorial and Washington Monument they're all 24 hours
Those are all outdoors I mean
A museum that you, ok sorry
Rapid fire
When it's run by an owl
He can stay open all night
He's a night owl
Touche
A miscellaneous goods store
That's what it's called
The Able Sisters Clothes Shop
Oh wow that's a new feature
Roofs, doors
Posts and fences can be
Customized
So I'm gonna have a pink
Fence I can't wait till I have a lesbian
Again I can't wait either
Brand new furniture
Including mermaid
Items
Under the sea
We need that little singing crab
A player will be the
Mayor of his or her town
So now you're in control
Oh but I like the mayor
He died
Well he was pretty fucking old
Can you evict citizens as the mayor
That would be awesome
I would have an all lesbian
Community
A thrift shop
Will be available
It makes sense Goodwills are popping up
On every corner in this day and age
So it's basically
As opposed to like the recycle bin that you
Free shit out of now you're gonna go buy it
Alright a shopping mall
Will be available
And lastly
A shoe store
Oh my god shit
All they're doing is fucking separating
Everything out even more
Than it was before
These aren't new features folks
These are just the same goddamn features
Just spread out even more
Between like each store instead of nooks carrying
Pretty much everything it's just like
Nooks is carrying
No I don't even know if there is a nooks in this game
But it's like a store carrying this type of item
This store is carrying this type of item
This guy says you know
It's all fucking filler is all what it is
Where's my store that sells classic NES games
I'm not fucking there so that's why I'm not buying your damn game
Oh I'm sorry that'd be the eShop I guess
Yeah that would be the Nintendo store
Wouldn't that be hilarious if there was a link
Within Animal Crossing to the eShop
There's how you can integrate
Some stuff in
That would be true innovation like the NES
Carts are back oh but you have to buy them
As DLC now
People do that
And you know I could see people doing that
But it'd be cool to have like
Demo versus fuck that you know what
It's just still stupid because they don't have the classic games in there
I would be scared for them to have demos for one reason
Look at the demos that they had in Smash Brothers Brawl
I can play the
Oh the first minute of the game
Over and over
Oh look at the progress I'm not making
AcidicVampire in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com says
I was hoping for a shoes store
You know now that I think about it
I'll be able to make my character wear high heels
I'm a lumberjack and I don't care
I'm okay
Sleep all night on a wiggle day
Anyhow
Dark Sakura let's move on with some rapid fire news
Well how about something for a game that's been out for two years
Scott Pilgrim vs. the World is getting new DLC
Yes
On August 19th
And it was
It's going to be on the two year anniversary
Of the Xbox Live release
That's a long time to go by
It's going to be a $5 pack, 400 points
And it has a new character
Wallace Wells
So you can be fantastic
And he doesn't actually need weapons
So I think he's just going to text people to death
And it will be on PSN by the way
This occasion calls for some
Animanguchi
Animanguchi I can never say their name
I like the theme
The theme was great but Another Winter
The very first level stage
Actually you know what one of my other songs on repeat is?
Threshold
I love the picture
We've seen them live
It was fantastic
In other news
Jet Set Radio
Will be back for 9 bucks
It's going to be a PS3
And
The PS3 version will be
Available for Playstation Plus users
On September 11th
And September 18th
The version will be out for everyone else
Xbox Live Arcade and Steam versions will be out
On September 19th
Also for 10 bucks
Vita version will be out October 16th
It doesn't really say anything else about that
So
I'll just hook up my Dreamcast
And play the good version that has Bjork in it
And birthday cake
Shut up and eat me
Too bad no Bon Appetit
And then
They Bleed Pixels
Which is the best name of the game ever
It's going to be out for Steam
Instead of Xbox Live
Indie games
So
That was the official word by
SpookySquidGames which is also a cool name
Basically
Their creative director said that
They want to reach a larger audience
And PC and Steam is just the place to do that
So go check it out
It's supposed to be really
Freaking hard
And this says the more and better
You kill the faster you fill your checkpoint meter
I like killing
In games
Alright is that it? That would be it sir
That's it for rapid fire news
Let's get into the Fookal Question of the Week
Thanks for having me
Fookal
Every week on our Facebook and Google Plus communities
We like to ask a question and get your feedback
And you put Facebook and Google
Together you get Fookal
And it's just fun to say
Fookal
Alright our question this week
Is
Where the hell is it?
Tonight
I forgot how to navigate Google Plus
I'm sorry
Nobody left a comment on Google Plus tonight
There is officially nobody left on Google Plus
Little tumbleweed rolls by
Alright well here
Let's assume people that use Google Plus
Also watch the Olympics on a six hour
Tape delay so
Here's the question anyway
Tonight we have a story on a game from the Super Nintendo days
Where it was discovered this week that an unofficial
Never released version of it contained some pretty
Salty language which obviously was the
NBA Jam game we were talking about earlier
This had us thinking about
Shocking moments in video games
Have you ever been shocked by dialogue
In a game or something
That just happened in the plot
I wasn't necessarily going to like F word shocking
Just like were you ever like
Oh my God
What about something that just made you say
Oh no they just did not
What was a video game moment that had
You shocked
You spoonie bard
Was that really a shocking moment for you?
Considering I didn't play that game until it was released on the Playstation
That was more of a WT
I was like what's a spoonie bard
I just thought it appropriate after I read the question
Alright we have some great answers tonight on the Facebooks
So I'm going to go through and read some of the answers here
Picaruno says
You have to be pretty fucking filthy to shock me
Although I think Brutal Legend handled the
Swearing gore in a funny way
Stopping the action just before an F bomb
Or beheading to politely ask if you would like to enable
The fucks and guts
Was that really what it was called? Fucks and guts?
Ragenator says
I'd have to go with an unconventional choice
The Super Nintendo port of Mortal Kombat
Ported by Acclaim
For what was included in the game, but for what was not
Included in the game
Meaning that the game was sanitized
This port has become the poster child of why games
Shouldn't be censored
And has given Nintendo a proverbial black eye
For a good many years
That was an interesting interpretation of the question
Because he took it to mean I was so shocked in a bad way
Like I was shocked at how shitty this turned out
That's kind of an interesting way to go with the question
They're punching the sweat off my face
That sweat is so shocking
Let's see, moving on
Stan says
I just watched a battle scene for Persona 3
For the first time ever
And my jaw seriously dropped when I saw that they had
Summoned their Personas by shooting themselves
In the head
I'm sure that that reason was explained in game
But WTF
Ratchet Tag says
Silent Hill 2
I was playing through for the first time and there was a scene
In which you're walking down a hall and see Pyramid Head
Doing really unspeakable things to mannequins
I was a bit young so it was pretty shocking
And disturbing
If you have played this you know what I'm talking about
He included a video with his answer
And I think we all know that scene in Silent Hill 2
And of course the preview kicks in
And tells you exactly what the video is
In advance
Which is both a helpful and hurtful thing
Now Shane replied and also said something
From Silent Hill 2
I'll just put a spoiler warning out there
Even though this game is almost 10 years old at this point
It's when you find out that James smothered
You with a pillow
That was ridiculous the first time you found out
It's a 10 year old game people
Especially because they showed him doing it
Runner up would be when Kaiden
Got his head bashed in on Mars
In Mass Effect 3
I literally got up from my computer right after that happened
And walked around to try and lose
Some of my anger I was filled with
This brings us to a very interesting question
A Shane question that I would have to ask him someday
And that would be
What if
Let's say that BioWare
Never plans to make another Mass Effect game
But
They'll make a Mass Effect 4
Only if Kaiden dies
In the first 5 minutes
For good
Or Ashley depending on how you've played the games
Then what do you do?
Do you take another Mass Effect game
Because hey more Mass Effect
And have your favorite character die
Or do you say you know what
I choose to remember these games as they were
Not dead
That's quite the dilemma isn't it
What would you do Dark Sakura
Let's say Mass Effect 4 with Garrus dead
In the first 5 minutes or no more Mass Effect ever
What would you do?
No more Mass Effect ever
Interesting alright
Well I don't know because if they said it in another universe
Totally then that's fine or in the future
It depends on the situation
Alright
Let's see
Ospher says Soul Calibur 5
When Maxie beats Astaroth
He stares at the camera angrily and shouts
God damn freak
That's just rude
Irene replied and said there's some obvious ones
Chrono dying, Eris dying, Samus being a girl
Justin Bailey, the upside down castle
That was like 7 answers
But one that kind of threw me off
Was the revelation about the main antagonist
Lady Mamiya
At the end of Sweet Home
No spoilers in case someone actually wanted to play through it
It just seemed intense
For an NES game
By the way I just got a text message
No more Mass Effect
Thank you Shane
At least we know he's listening now
Even though he missed the first half
Shane, yes no more Mass Effect
Except I would cry if there was no
Now if there was no cadence
Sorry I wouldn't care
Monty Boggs in our chat room says
Ashley just tried to kill me so whatever let her die
Well you can let Garrus shoot her
Alright
Mandrew replies and said
You don't know Jack
A buddy of mine and I were playing
And we had to type
And we had to type an answer for a question
And he typed in fuck you
Jack responded with fuck me
No fuck you
And deducted like 10,000 points or something
When you're in 6th grade that throws off your guard
That's awesome
I never knew that could happen
But that's hilarious
Extifer replied and said
Hellscream called Sylvanas a bitch
In Warcraft
I'm sure there are several I'm not thinking of
But it all comes back to wow right
How about the dead babies in wow
You know what I'm talking about
I think so yeah
Where the troll lady is and she has all the babies
And then you have all the skeletons behind it
And the leather tents that the gnolls have
That are made out of peoples faces
Clover Nikon replied
And said Silent Hill 2
Which it was referred to earlier with Pyramid Head
And the Amanakans
Kareem J replied and said
Gears of War 3 a certain character dies
I won't say who but I thought it would be a character
They wouldn't kill off
How many games have we talked about tonight
That are upwards of 5 years old
And have danced around spoilers
And now we're talking about Gears of War 3
Well I think it's nice that people are trying to be respectful
I'm not going to criticize people for being respectful
Of the spoilers
Dark Charger replies and says
Eternal Darkness
Oh
That's a game they need to bring back on the Wii U
Don't they
That's a game that would
The problem with bringing a game like that
Is now it has a standard
For what's going to be scary
And you can't do the same thing
You can't do the same things all over again
Unless it's like literally a
Graphically improved port
But people would be like this game isn't scary
Oh
You can't redo a game like that
It's not going to happen well until there's a
Dramatic shift in technology
Like immersion we were talking about before
Until you can really have
Something different to
To throw at the player again
It's not going to be interesting
Oh wait let me get right on the mic here
But imagine the things that they did with
Fatal Frame 4 and the remake of Fatal Frame 2
Add that to the whole sanity
Thing and all the things that they could do
To fuck with you with Eternal Darkness
Yeah but the Haunted House and Fatal Frame 2
For people like us is stupid and boring
Yeah but I'm sure that they could do some
And that's what I'm talking about
The bonuses and the extras and the things
That they would be throwing in nowadays
Are dumb and boring
And Eternal Darkness as
Kinda cheesy as the game was
The effects were really good
And it made for a good way to keep you
To keep you through the game
Alright let me finish the comment here from Dark Charger
If you went in there spoiler free
Random noises, skewed perspectives
And even a blue screen of death made you question
Your own sanity as you played through
Chiggers replied and said
The first time I ever heard shit
In a game was when Barret said it in
Final Fantasy 7, I was awestruck
Uh actually
Sit your ass down in that chair
And drink your goddamn tea
And lastly Tigerclaw says
To me the most shocking moment in a video game
Was in Bionic Commando
When you see Master D aka
Hitler's head explode
That's pretty awesome
I read all the answers cause they were all really good
Thank you guys at facebook.com
Orange Lounge Radio
What about you guys?
Shocking moments in video games
I'm gonna go with a really cliche
One that was already mentioned but it really was the most
Shocking moment for me was when Aris died
In Final Fantasy 7 like for real
For real I was like
That just fucking happened
Really? Like they're gonna just off
A character, video game characters don't die
They just regenerate
I cheered, I cheered
There's not really much that shocks me in a game
I mean maybe
Selly's throwing herself off a cliff
I was like, did she just throw herself off a cliff?
Stupid bitch
Other than that
I was like, oh
I haven't really had a shocking moment
Um
Oh I know one thing that actually
Did kinda gross me out
Well okay first of all Robbie the Rabbit
Always kinda creeps me out
The big head in Silent Hill 4
And I knew the big head was there
But even seeing the big head was like
Ugh stop looking at me
Cause I have a thing about big heads
And I don't like them
Like we had
Like the um
The clown face in Fun House
The pinball table
That thing creeps me out
I mean it doesn't matter that
The goal is to hit it with a pinball
It's still creepy
And that's in pinball
I'm gonna say a really recent one
The most shocking moment for me a recent game
That I actually played again this week for the first time in a while
Journey on the Playstation 3
Because I had no idea
Going into it that it was a online
Game and the moment I saw another person
There was kind of shocking like
What?
And the fact that they weren't acting like
Jason saying go up here
Go over here
Journey
Is such a fucking
Great game like it's just
I played through again
This week and it's just oh my god
Like the way I'm like talking to people
I was showing the game to Extifer and like
I was like yeah and that's another person and then
The person was like trying to like
Do the little singing to tell me
That there was a thing I was missing
In the little place where they were standing
And it was just I don't
I don't know how to explain it it's such an experience
I still need to play that game
You really do Journey is an outstanding game
It damn well may be my game of the year I'm not sure yet
Uh
Do you have any shocking moments?
Yes Loki shocking moments
I don't actually I was trying to think of something but
No
I have two interpretations of them
One of them Ryan reminded me of
The one that I have in mind
Literally shocking in terms of like
The frame one and two
To like an added effect
Really did have a pretty profound impact on me
I've always been weird when it comes to ghosts
And that kind of stuff and the whole
The lore and the situation
The sound the ambience that kind of stuff
Those games really creeped me out for a very long time
I could talk about this for hours but this is a
Three oh wait four hour show
The example that Ryan reminded me of
That's actually really true
Braid
Braid was an amazing game
Great platformer great everything
I absolutely loved it it's one of the few titles
That I've actually 100% achieved
And in general just sat down
And worked my way through with very
Little to distract me in between
Um but the story of it
Is also ridiculously profound
And the very last level of Braid
After you do all you get all of the puzzle
Pieces you put them all together and you
Do the final like unraveling
In technically world one
Um
How do I do this spoiler free
Um it's just the best representation
Of two sides of the story
That I've ever seen in gaming
And really in media in general
We have actdeft in our chatroom
At live.vognetwork.com says
Braid sucks I hate the game haters to the left
Alright
Uh Ry
We'll end this with you any shocking moments
Of course since I asked her
Back channel if she had any suggestions
I just took away her suggestion but that's okay
I was the one playing it anyway
Ha ha ha
Um
I mean I was happy that the fact
That Diablo 3 nothing got spoiled for me
So um things happening
In that one I was pretty surprised
With but
Antishock
The Diablo
Uh
Whimsishire the Diablo
Pinata there that's the word I'm looking for
My Diablo Pinata? What about it?
Oh it was hilarious to me
When I was going through Whimsishire and I found
The big Diablo Pinata
It's even more awesome when I broke it and I got
The Horadric hamburger
This very
Demonic you know undertone
Dark game and then you have Whimsishire
I mean that's classic Blizzard
It's beautiful but that was fun
Alright we're gonna move on with some more
News for you guys and of course emails coming up
As well as phone calls
Uh Loki
So there's already been hints that this was coming
But Valve has
Finally made it known
That they're gonna be rolling out
Other
Non-game software on Steam
Coming September 5th
And these will include other
Include I guess Steamworks functionality
Allowing automatic updating
And cloud storage
As well as other Steam features
And they have everything from like
Construction to accounting, animation
Design, illustration, photo editing
Software training, web publishing
Etc
So lots of stuff
Interesting and then of course
I guess titles will continue to hit
Steam after the initial
September 5th launch and they
I guess developers will be able to submit
Their perspective
Pieces of software via the
Steam Greenlight program
Did Steam just reinvent
The starter?
Um
Maybe
It's not
To their credit it's not hey
I want the game so I'll
Fund you this $5 but it's
More crowd sourcing the idea
In the first place
It has it's own potential but I'm sure in time
We'll see it's own demise, it's own draw
Not it's own demise, it's own drawbacks
Um
Kind of brings more light to a comment that was made
A couple weeks ago when we talked about
There was something where um
And it always seemed like a weird comparison
But Gabe Newell from Valve
Said something about yeah we were talking to
Adobe and trying to convince them that
Photoshop should be free and I think a lot
Of us were like alright whatever they were talking
And now we're like oh
That's why you would have had
Valve talking to Adobe because they're trying
To get some of that software on this new
Thing and they're trying to have the killer title
So that they're the additional
Content of the store is actually
Relevant to people
It's interesting do you think this could be successful?
Yeah definitely
I do too
They should make the entire suite free
And give it to me
Looking forward to that Steam holiday sale
Wait a minute didn't you say you didn't want Photoshop
To be free I seen you remember on that episode
I just want it free for me
Oh okay
Not free for all
Group of designers
That clears everything up thank you
And InDesign
Well this won't be free
In fact it will be $109 if you
Miss the Kickstarter
The oh yeah
The oh yeah got funded and all that
Good stuff boy did they get funded
$8.5 million
It was supposed to raise
$950,000 which was a pretty lofty
Goal to begin with
$1 million in 8 hours
$8.5 million
After all was said and done when the Kickstarter closed
According to CEO
Julie Urman of the oh yeah
We've been blown away the whole time
So there you go
Also in news there
It's $109 like I said before
So it's a little bit more expensive
Than the $99 during the Kickstarter
It's $119 if you
Live in another place
Not the US somewhere foreign
You get the little console
You can pre-order it now
They're saying now delivery is expected to commence
In April of 2013
Is that because they're going to do the Kickstarter people in March?
Yes Interesting
So they're not just subtly
Rolling back the clock already
No they even said
To ensure that they can get the Kickstarter ones out first
Interesting
Also in oh yeah news
Four controllers will be supported and
Namco Bandai is in discussions
With the company
So I'm sure that just means oh hooray
Another re-release of all those Namco classics
Like Pac-Man
I think they were talking about Soul Calibur
The Android
Like how they have the
Slightly toned down versions for
Android and stuff
Interesting
Very interesting
And
Hopefully
Rich Racer
Although
I hope it's not Ridge Racer
Like it was on the Vita
Because that Ridge Racer sucked balls
Ridge Racer
That would be great if that could be a
Launch title
It does launch on every system
By the way I love this comment from Bobby Blackwolf
In our chat room
Namco Bandai in discussions
Indie game heaven
Remember how this console was going to be the indie console
It's going to be as good for indie games
As the Xbox is
Alright moving on
Dark Sakura
Well
Star Trek Infinite Space, I'm sure people
Saw all the ads all over Facebook for the beta
And everything, guess what?
Canceled, not going to happen
And they even, it was supposed to be set during
Deep Space Nine and they even got like
A bunch of the cast
From Deep Space Nine to lend their talents
And nope they couldn't
Get any funding
They couldn't find a publisher
So it's not happening
Sad face
The demise of MMOs
Has begun
No publisher for an MMO? How does that happen?
The fact that all Star Trek is right now is the Abrams movies
I really wish there would be a new series
Cry
As long as it's nothing like Enterprise
You know they have a
Kickstarter right now that actually has
Michael Dorn in it
Oh really?
It's a freaking Kickstarter
It's a Star Trek documentary
With Star Trek actors
Yeah
Because there haven't already been
At least two
Is Kickstarter Rule 35 now?
If it exists there's a Kickstarter for it?
Possibly actually
That's just what I got from
A couple of instances in this episode
Alright a few more news stories
For you guys and then we're going to get to the mailbag
And before too long the Skype line at
1-877-GAME-OLR
Or our username on Skype OrangeLoungeRadio
But first
Boy Rhode Island really put their money
In the wrong company
So 38 Studios
You know of course they kind of
Tumbled and failed
And yeah
So now Rhode Island owns
The rest of 38 Studios
Including the assets, the rights to the single player
Game that they put out
And of course their unfinished
MMO project
And now they're trying to sell off
These assets to recoup as much
Of the loan as possible
And so maybe
That means that we'll see a new Kingdoms of Amalur
Game
Or whatever it's going to be called
Because somebody will have to buy the rights inevitably
But it's going to go at bargain basement prices
Which is kind of too bad
Hey EA, you want another franchise?
The first game wasn't terrible
I don't know
Do you think that's what's going to happen?
Do you think EA will snatch it up?
Do you think anybody's going to be interested in this?
I think someone will snatch it up
I'm not sure if it's going to be EA
It could be Ubisoft or something, who knows
Well whenever that game comes out
One thing you could use to buy that game
Because you know it'll cost 60 plus dollars
Is trade in credit
In fact GameStop came out this week
And said that 70%
Of trade credit is spent on
New games
That's totally hurting the games industry
With all those used game sales
To me this is kind of a duh
This comes from
GameStop president
Paul Reines
Talked to Gamasutra
And basically said this in an interview
That was about the total sales numbers
And the $11 billion and so forth
And basically was talking about
Everybody always criticizes about used trade ins
But he said
We're really not cannibalizing new game sales
It's a common misconception
So my answer to developers is that we are driving growth
In a category that needs to grow
We think there's a real lack of awareness
As far as how trade ins are good for the industry
He may have a point in a way
Because yeah, this is so obvious to me
Because A, for one
GameStop gives you more money
For the games than they do for cash
Right?
And they give you more money when you're pre-ordering
They'll give you bonuses when you're pre-ordering
As well and kind of like reinvesting
Your money into the games that way
Games are fucking expensive
$60 for a new game
Is a lot of money
Exactly, and also that money can go
To points, cards, whatever
To buy more DLC
So that's why I never understood
These people like, well we need to get rid of the used game market
Yeah, go ahead and do that
And then you'll see your fucking numbers drop
Because no one's buying your games
Because one, they're fucking bitter at you for
Getting rid of used game sales
Or the campaign or DRM
That you're putting in place there
And B, they're not going to have the money to do it anymore
But my whole thing is
I just prefer to cut out the middle man
And sell him on eBay
Exactly
And use that money to buy whatever I want
A new video game or
Maybe my shiny new iPad
I understand, and sometimes
It's a matter of convenience
Sometimes you don't want to wait for that
Or you don't want to go through the hassle to do that
And the opportunity costs
And you can either get X amount of money now
Or you don't
And that's the thing about GameStop
Is when you go in there
At least that should be the way
You go in there, you say, okay here's the games I have
What will you give me for them?
If that's not satisfactory to you, sell them on eBay
I mean, you can figure
You can call them up
I don't know if you can call them up
But you can go down there and say, here's what I have
If that's not enough money for you
What are your game values?
Some games they do
I don't think they do for all of them
And I'm sure it will vary based on
The condition your games are in
It's not like they're forcing you to
Trade this stuff in
Sorry, you already gave it to us
You can't have your games back
They're not going to do that
Or even on top of that
You can take them to another game store
Not GameStop that also does trades
And ask them, hey what will you give me for this?
Figure out who's going to give you the best value
Rama in our chat room says
I don't trade in games
When I do, it'll never be GameStop
Well certainly other companies are trying to copy
What's happened with GameStop's success
I think Best Buy did it
I don't think they do it anymore
I think Amazon's still doing it though
Because Amazon's got everything
We already learned that
Best Buy still takes in trade-ins
The one that's close by us
They actually have a whole little station
With a counter set up
And somebody dedicated at that counter
I was not aware
I don't usually look into that here
And also too with GameStop now
What they're trying to do to get more people to trade in
Stuff is they don't just sell games anymore
They sell electronics, phones
But the nice thing about Amazon
Is that you can trade into games to Amazon
And then put that money towards a vibrating heating pad
As we learned about earlier in the show
Or alien space still though
If they have that, you know
You never know
Gonna trade in new Super Mario Brothers Wii
And get some hot Turian cock
Alright
Mmmmmmm
Don't make me make the noise, Rob
Alright, let's
I will make you make the noise
Of opening the mail
Oh, there you go, no more noise
Not that
How's that? Alright
Let's go to the mailbag
Every week, DarkSakura opens the mailbag
Mailbag at OrangeLawnsRadio.com
And read some of her favorite emails
For you right now
Sure
Okay
Um, this one's actually a contest
A contest
A contest?
A giveaway
And wants me to do it via email like this
In the email
There's lots of giveaways
My gosh, I've got a code I've got to try and give away at some point
And we also still have to pick the winner
For when Brad packs stuff
No, it's not
I saw that one in the mailbag earlier
I will read it
Hey, OLR crew, I apologize for intruding in your mailbag segment
But I would like to give away a PlayStation Network game code
To one of your live listeners in the U.S. Canada
Of Puerto Rico
The code is for
Dazimon Kids
An import PS1 classic side-scrolling shooter
The let's play
I should keep it, never mind, no I'm kidding
So the let's players design their own levels
Just to keep this contest simple
I would like for the lovely DarkSakura
Or equivalent sassy mail host
To say
Hey
To say the code at the end of this email
And leave it to the first listener
Who can claim the code to win
Dazimon Kids can be played on a PS3, PSP
Or in the near future, Vita
The code can be redeemed from the PlayStation Store
App on a console
Or at account.sonyentertainmentnetwork.com
Good luck to everyone
This comes from the Nasty Canasta
I love that name
So are you ready?
Get your pencils, get your keyboards ready
Get a free game, here you go
Picture pages, picture pages, time to get you
Nobody gets picture pages?
Bite me
T-H-P-N
P-L-N-P
T-M-N-3
There you go
Not saying it again
I want to know who wins it
Alright, next email
Yeah
Um, this
I had to laugh, I had to laugh
There's a kickstarter to do Cheetamen 2
So that they're fixing it to make it playable
This is Konami Be Ashamed
Oh, I'm not even gonna bother
Okay
The subject of this one is Trainer
Dear DarkSakura, which would offend you more?
Me saying Samantha Trainer is a hotter piece of ass than Garos Vakarian
Or
There's a link
Says this
This being the song Windows Down by Big Time Rush
This song that samples Song 2 by Blur
And if by sample you mean rips off completely in ruins
Ugh
And that's Stay Black Entertainment
Um
Well given that I can't actually listen to it
Because I have the sound off
Um
Well
If Damon Auburn sued the crap out of Big Time Rush
Then that's okay
Um, Samantha Trainer is just annoying
And everyone's entitled to their own opinion
I would say she's a hot piece of ass for what it's worth
The shower scene
Like, I'm gay
And I still kind of get a semi on that shower scene
It's really hot
She wasn't even naked
What's up? Who showers in their bra?
Motherfuck
Moving on
Cock teases
Given that this is a lesbian shower scene
Would it be a clit tease?
It'd be doubly hot because there's lesbians involved
Yeah, but Shepard wasn't even naked
Or in her undies
It's called, they didn't want the game to have an AO rating
So she had a bra on
I think it should
It's like Showgirls on VH1
Have you ever watched
I posted something on Tumblr a while back
And if someone can
If you can find it on my Tumblr, relink it
It's the romance scenes in Mass Effect 2
Done with fly cam
So you can see all the little rendering cheats
That they did and like how Garrus' hand goes
Like right through the middle of her chest and everything
And it's really funny
Calima
Yeah, I know
Hey, OLR, I'm writing you from my phone
So please excuse my lack of form slash grammar
Slash bad spelling
Lack of bad spelling? Why would I complain?
Or anything else that relates to improper use of the English language
It looks like Rama says
He got it, by the way
That code earlier
And Black Wolf says, well sorry podcast listeners
Guess you aren't a part of this
Well, how about this
This is your code
And this is a code for
Insanely Twisted Shadow Planet
Oh, I can't do it this way
Because then somebody who's listening live
Is gonna go to the podcast as soon as it comes out
And pull this code out of it
So I have to think of a way to give this code away
I have a code for Insanely Twisted Shadow Planet
That was generously donated by Pika Uno
Email
Random picked email
Random picked email? Alright, fair enough
Send an email
The 15th
Alright, send an email
To mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com
And tell us how jealous
You are
That the live listeners get all the good giveaways
Tell us about your insane jealousy
And you may win Insanely Twisted Shadow Planet
We will give it to
The
What, 15th person email
Or whoever's the most fucked up
No, because you can't say that's too vague
You have to have a definitive answer
It's gonna be the 15th email
And if for whatever reason 15 people don't email us
We'll randomly draw one
Then we'll randomly draw one
So there you go
Insanely Twisted Shadow Planet on the Xbox 360
Just for the podcast listeners
There's one they can participate in
Can I finish reading this? Yes
I have two questions for you tonight
First, is there a way to stream the show
From an Android device
And if so, how does one go about setting that up?
Well, first of all, you sell your phone and get an iPhone
Stop, stop
To stream the show via an Android device
Go to vognetwork.com
The good news is, the website's in HTML5
So you actually should be able to
And this works just for the record on iPhone as well
You should be able to go to the site
And just hit play
And it'll work
If for whatever reason that doesn't work
There is an app, and I know it's on iPhone
I'm pretty sure they wrote this for Android as well
It's called TuneIn
And that will allow you to listen live
If you've been here last night from the gym
Yes, by the way, I joined a gym
Which is a whole other story I'll have to get into at some point
But actually, listen to the conversation live
On TuneIn
So, I don't recall ever hearing anything
About how one goes to set this up
One email per person, you smartass listeners
I will check your IP
I don't recall ever hearing anything
About streaming since you switched to VoG
Please provide any
Okay, we already did all that
Second, what do you believe to be the main cause of rhythm gaming
And we'll be seeing a return to the genre soon
Well, anything that goes down has to come back up
Some people attribute it to Guitar Hero oversaturating the market
While others point the finger at Rock Band
For their spamming of DLC
Which separates friends who have more money
To spend on games than others
Who don't necessarily have as much disposable income
I've been playing Guitar Hero since the third one
And Rock Band since Rock Band 2
And I've watched the community decline steadily
And now it's a very small and tight-knit community
That's all fine and dandy
Because you get closer with a regular group of friends
But now it's a sad state of affairs
Because neither Guitar Hero nor Rock Band
Have any games coming out
I'm not counting Blitz because it's not a main series game
I have an answer
Stubbornness killed the music game franchise
Konami's unwillingness to support the franchise killed it
We went how many years without a DDR game
In the arcades
And one might say, oh well arcades were dying
Or oh well it wasn't successful enough
So they would have made another bull to the shit
Because the problem with that logic
Is that you're pretending
That America didn't import
All of those games
Like did you know you're not supposed to have
A Max 2 in America
That was never released
Max never released
Extreme never released
That's the problem
Konami of Japan did not believe in the franchise
And when they would make the games here
Most of the time they were half-assed
When they were coming from Konami of Japan
There were two people
Slash groups that believed
In Dance Dance Revolution
And the Bomani series in general at Konami
One of them was Jason Enos
Without him you would have never had
These games in the first place
And what we did get in America
And on the Playstation releases and so forth
The other was Konami of Hawaii
Which unfortunately their first release on the Xbox
Wasn't
I get the sense maybe
They didn't have as much freedom with that first game
Because again the later Xbox games
Ultramix 2 and Ultramix 3
That's the shit that should have been in the arcades
Those would have been great
American DDR releases
And we say this with our own
Personal bias having been in the scene
As long as we have been but
Isn't VR pretty
Wildly
Popular in the arcades with the
Ones that actually have X and X2
I mean I'm not
Out of the scene I have not been playing the game anymore
And if I'm gonna pick anything
I'm gonna go back to basically Extreme and Below
And a couple of gyms from afterwards
But let's not kid ourselves
Isn't DDR still doing pretty
Damn good now that it actually has an American
Song list? Well enough
I think although the home releases seem
To have dried up I think actually
Americanizing the song listed too much
Is kind of because the whole point of DDR
Was you take songs that are good
But people might
Take you to new music
Now I think the whole licensing with all the synth pop
Stuff was pretty awesome
But I loved a lot of Dance Mania stuff
Because it's like okay I recognize that song is kind of
A remix you know
Oh this is kind of a neat take of this song
Or this is a unique song I've never heard of from a Korean artist
Or something like that or the song we played before
The show I was like dude that'd be a perfect DDR
Song nowadays
I would definitely tend to agree
That DDR
Introducing me to Dance Mania is probably one of the best things
Like my last decade of music
Just lastly real quick I'm sorry
The last thing I want to say on this is that the other thing
That really screwed them
Guitar Hero was only a rampant success
Because Konami was too stubborn to realize
Those games would work here and they would have never paid
For the licensing and the case
I mean who made the first Guitar Hero
Harmonics
But who did they team up with to get that done
Who planted the seed
Great Red Octane
What started Red Octane
What kind of company was Red Octane
DDR Pads and Guitar Freaks
Third Party Guitar Freak Controllers
And these mysterious Third Party Guitar Freaks Controllers
With five buttons
The Saga Red Octane for us is pretty sad
My Guitar Freaks Controllers were in the background
When we did the thing at my house
With the news
And what happened when Rock Revolution came out
It was dismissed as a shitty ass Guitar Hero
Clone and why
The song list sucked butthole
Because it was a bunch of bad covers
And that was a very clear indication
That Konami of Japan was not willing
To put the investment or the risk
And in order to get rewards
You have to take a risk
Konami of Japan was not willing to do that
Therefore, Bimani died
To finish reading the email
Go ahead
This will spiral out of control
Because I have a few
Agreements and disagreements
Those of us who are still playing regularly
New instruments
Because all of ours keep breaking over time
Due to where we weren't able to find them
Anywhere short of eBay for less than $100
For a damn guitar
Dimple
It's a used movie
And game and records and stuff
I find guitars there all the time on the cheap
And usually in great condition
And all of mine are still in perfect shape
Because you have to clean them out
And take good care of them
But other than that
Thanks for answering, sorry for ranting
Listen live at work tonight
Brownie, that's it
The only thing I wanted to interject is that
As far as I know, Rock Revolution
Was a mostly
Japanese
Developed, you know, license
Acquisition was responsible
By the Japanese Konami
Outfit
The music culture in Japan is
Ridiculously different from America
And so for them to take that
Something original
Put it on us
Put it on the common American base
And be surprised at the failure
To me
From the limited amount of knowledge that I have
It already makes sense that I could just say
Well, you're not making an American game
You're making a Japanese game and pushing it in America
And something as cultural as music
That's a pretty big deal
Alright, anyway
We could spend more time talking about this
But we did already spend five years talking about it
So, was that it for emails?
Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
If you want to send us an email
In the future
I guess what's funny
Because the live listeners are complaining that the stream went down
Which is weird because I don't see the time out
That usually comes up when that happens
But I guess maybe a little hiccup
I guess what happened, I said
Bamani died, and as soon as I said died
Is when the stream went down
It's almost like the watchful eye
Of Konami Japan just fucking pulled the plug
On my internet when I said that
How dare you
But we know it's just because Comcast sucks
After the mailbag comes the FUs of the week
So let us get a little bit ranty
We usually start the FUs with Dark Sakura
But she ran out of the studio for a minute
So I'll start with the other lady
We'll let the other lady's first night
Alright, do you have an FU of the week tonight?
I don't think I do right now
FU for being too nice
I might think of something
Alright, then how about Jason?
The other half
FU for getting a coat
And anything else at home
Because it was ridiculously cold in the bay last night
It sucked to walk
Fuck the bay
Five degrees here and you're like
I need a jacket
And I think I had something else
But, eh
Uh, Loki
Uh, FU being burnt out at work
Uh, my FU of the week
Goes to my abs
And Extifer for showing me
That little ab machine
Extifer convinced me to join a gym
There's a lot to be inspired about with Extifer
Because Extifer used to be a big boy
And he lost
A lot of weight
Through a pretty intense program at the gym
Over the course of like a year
So I just, I don't know
I'm kind of at the point where I'm like, you know, I would like to lose a few pounds too
Um, so
I joined a gym
And he showed me how to use the little ab machine
And it really hurt the next day
These things are evil aren't they
Also, FU'd that
It's not a Stairmaster
But it's like this escalator that never ends
That type of thing
That thing's a little fucker
Alright, and
What gym are you going to?
24 hour
Oh, I'm so sorry
I had a better experience there than the one you were recommending previously
But that's alright
Different strokes for different folks
Well, um, my FU
First of all, these tips are fucking delicious
But hot, but peppery
And, um
The car accident, my lower back for hurting
A bitch after my adjustment
Um, and
The rental car that I have
I like that the stereo has the Bluetooth hookup
For the phone
But I miss my car and I don't like being
Blown around like a leaf in the wind
On the freeway because it's so lightweight
I would rather
Have had a Corolla S than a baseline
Corolla, I feel like I'm driving a mommy car
Oh yeah, one more
FU'd a BurgerTime
For reminding me of how bad I suck
At classic arcade games
And viewing angles
Alright, Tigerclaw
In our chatroom asks a very good question
This is a very good question about the whole gym thing
Tigerclaw says, Rob, when you went to the gym
When you went into the gym, it wasn't intimidating
And I have to admit, that's part of what held
Me back for the longest time
The whole
Doing that in public type of thing
People looking at each other in the gym
I was a little weirded out
By that whole thing at first, which is why
For the longest time, I wouldn't go
But finally, it just
Kind of hit me, like this whole thing
What am I going to see any of these
Assholes outside the gym
I'm not going to see these people anywhere else
Whatever, I'm just going to go and be in my
Own little world and listen to my headphones
And if these people want to stare, then let them stare
Because I'm hot
And that's pretty much where I ended up with
Also, it really helped that when I went to the gym for the first time
I definitely saw people uglier than me
And that helped a lot actually
In a very superficial kind of way
Right? Am I right, Jamie?
It's a relief to go in the gym and see people uglier than you, right?
Sometimes
But the gym that I go to
Actually has a lot of
Track and ROT
ROTC people there
But they're doing the harder intensity stuff
And I'm like, I'm just going to walk over here
Thank you. I do the rowing machine now, though
Tigerclaw says
Or nervous, because you walk in there and you see
A bunch of muscle-bound dudes working out
And they see a weakling walking to the gym
Hey!
Why did you just call me?
Um
No, I don't
But if the muscle-bound dudes are looking at me
And they're judging me
Then they're checking me out
And that's their issue
Sorry, I'm hot
Well, you know what I would do
Dan has a big thing for the circuit training
They have this big circle thing where they do circuit training
I go hang out in the dude section and lift weights
Because
I have a weak ankle
And I can't really do much of that
So I just go lift weights with the dudes
And I get weird looks, but I don't care
Fuck them!
There just comes a point in your life where you just
I'm really not interested in them, thank you
There just comes a point in your life where you have to say
Hi, haters! You know?
And just deal with it
Deal with me
Monty Boggs says
A new challenger approaches
I don't want to talk it up too much
Because I just started
Literally last week
And the last time I joined a gym
I went once
So I never went again
But this time I'm hoping for better results
So I'll be more excited about this
If I'm still going in two months
I'll let you know how it goes
Hopefully my abs will stop hurting
Because that machine is evil
I already got a text message from Christopher today
So, did you go?
And I'm like, yes, I went on Saturday night
Thank you very much
I'm a real winner, I go to the gym
On Saturday night, I didn't go to the club
I went to the gym
And then pizza on Sunday
And then I ate so much pizza on Sunday
But see, here's the thing, Jason
I would have eaten that pizza anyway
So
Alright
There's usually a good diet to go along
With these kind of things, but eh
Dark Tetsuya says instead of listening
To USL, no, I listen
I just said, the TuneIn app, I listen to the first
Hour of USL from the gym
I know that Dark Sakura talked about the
Rocky rehearsal, and I know that Travis talked
At length about the Mars landing
And how happy he was about that whole thing
And how he made the graphics during OLR
Ha! Alright
Anyhow
Someone needs to take these chips away from me, they're freaking good
Okay
Yes
Someone in chat was asking your chips
What brand and such they were
I told them, but it's Trader Joe's rice and bean
Chips with adzuki beans
And they're very peppery
Alright, let's do it, it's already past 9 o'clock
And we haven't even gotten to calls
So let's do these last few stories pretty quickly here
And I've got to do
I've got to do Twitter topics as well here
So, Loki
So, more Zinga news
Of course they're worried that people are
Flocking away from the company
They're going to try to retain some of those employees
They're giving them free stock
Free, worthless stock
Fantastic
There were some of those stories out there on one of those websites
I can't remember the name, but some of the stories from actual employees
And just about how the stock
That they were given to work those long hours
Is just plummeted
It's actually kind of sad
Because as much as I can't stand Zinga
And the games they put out
That's not a problem I have with
The line level employees
So to speak
The people that are actually doing the art
Or the programming
It's the way that company is managed
And the way they make some decisions
I bet there's some very talented people at Zinga
That would like to do something original
I know there's some talented people there
Some of my friends work there
And they're very talented individuals and artists
But I can't see their talent being utilized
At all at this company
Which is why I kind of feel bad
Everyone talks about how evil they are
Which is an evil company
It's not necessarily
It's not like those artists are evil
Or the programmers are evil
It's just that the decisions are evil
So there you go
Alright, is that it for that story?
Wow that was quick
I said quick and you said you did it
Alright then lastly I'll do this one real quick
This is an eBay, this was brought up earlier
An eBay auction that has a lot of people turning their heads
This is a guy who's basically selling his whole damn life
On eBay for 3.5 million
A 29 year old
Who owns, which first off
Props to him for establishing
3.5 million dollars worth of stuff
At age 29
I'm older than 29
And I'm not even worth a tenth of that
I think I saw
On a website the other day
OrangeLoungeRadio.com is valued at about
$1500
Yes
This guy made 3.5
Or asking 3.5 million
I could ask $1000
And I'd have to split that three ways
Really four
Because it's Jason's site
And Deep Man designed it
Five
Anyhow
All kidding aside
This guy is selling on eBay
$3.5 million dollars
His entire
Basically assets
His automobiles, the collectibles and so forth
He's the owner of R.U. Game
Which is an independent retailer
It's in Gainesville, Tampa
And Brandon, Florida
We have a couple listeners in Florida, I don't know if there's any in that area
But he owns these few stores
And I love the little
Derpy Mario that's in the videos
There's like this guy in a Derp Derp Mario costume
Whatever, anyway
He says he'll even hang around for six months to help the
New owner, he didn't really say why
He's doing it, it might have been in the video
But I wasn't going to watch the whole thing
It's because he wants to just start his next thing
Or whatever that is
So it's like I want to start my life over
We are starting over
Maybe he's Buddhist
Maybe, who knows
But anyway, he's selling the whole thing off
No words yet if there are any serious bidders or whatever
But you know what, I say hats off to this guy
Because a lot of people think it's fake
And it's just for publicity
And in which case I say, hats off to you dude
Because you got covered on every game
Blog this week with this little story
And you know this industry
They need to run something every day
On the websites
So this was like the best commercial you could ever
Not buy
I tip my hat to you
Doesn't RU Games
Sound like it might be like a place to buy
Russian import games though
Like when I first saw the name I kind of thought
Oh, RU Games, it's like a Russian game store
I thought that that's
I didn't think of a stupid Facebook game
It's an industry that works with these types of stores
You would not believe how many
Generic sounding game stores are out there
It's like, yeah
I'd like to make my game store
It's called
Well, I'm trying to remember
It's like
It's something like GameStop
But it wasn't GameStop, it was very close
Game yield
Game go, go game
No, it was like
Go GameStop
Something like that
Why are you naming?
Go GameStop, that's kind of
Video game center
Game store
The game place
I named the game store the Danone, did you know that?
Oh really? Game on
That ended up being a show, right?
Well this was years ago
Game shop
I've seen that
There's game trader that uses the same
Text and colors
Monty Boggs in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
Answered the question
Yes, I am game, are you movie?
Laughs
I'm sorry
I found that response to be hilarious
Like I just want to walk
Into the store, why yes I am game
Are you movie? Well here's the thing too
He's even admitted, even if it doesn't sell
Or he doesn't get a
Buyer for it, it's great advertising for my
Store, because he got all these
Blogs talking about this store
So he could
Props to you and your derpy ass Mario
Mascot guy
Laughs
You know Nintendo might see that
And get a little upset
Just saying
I'll see derpy Mario fight
Mario Mascot
Laughs
Maybe in the next Smash Brothers
Dr. Mario vs.
Derpy Mario
Laughs
Oh my god mushrooms, oh my god
Mr. Derpy Mario
Oh my god mushrooms
If that doesn't just epitomize this episode
Oh my god first floor
Oh my god Zelda chic
Laughs
Sigh
Orange lounge derpio according to the chatroom
Thank you, thank you guys
Alright let's go to the skype
Line, we're gonna open it up now
1877 game olr
Or our username on skype is orange
Lounge radio, we can't wait to take your
Call, in the mean time
We'll do some last minute stories
I'll do a couple of these quick tweets here
Let's see
Gamer girl was responding a little late to the
Facebook question on Twitter
I think she's being ironic
First game that ever shocked me was God
of War when you go into the ships cabin
And you get to do the girls for more orbs
Oh yes
Sex and in my
God of War
Shocking, but in a good way
Ooh I can't believe
That just happened
Oh we have a phone call, hi you're on orange lounge radio
Who's this
Hey how you doing
Oh hey
Sup
Not much, sup
Just chilling, enjoying
Good stuff
Interesting little story
I'm chilling, I'm watching My Little Pony
Just kicking back
That's what's up, that's how I roll
Alright what's up
I have a funny little story to have a nice interesting
Story about Microsoft and I'll be on my merry little way
Okay
First story is, oddly enough
If it wasn't for Raichan, I wouldn't be a fan of the show
And I wouldn't be pestering you guys for all these years
Now, oh
So you are a fan of olr
Thanks to Raichan
Me and Raichan, we go back like
Ten plus years, hanging out on
On a forum site, wbs.net
Can you hold on a minute
Yeah, yeah
God damn you
You ruined everything
Oh shit, was I not on mute
Hey Rob
Can you scream a little louder
I don't think the dead heard you
You know what's funny, apparently right when I screamed
The internet went out again
Which isn't, you're still on Skype
So I don't think that's possible, whatever
Alright, so anyway
That'll be one for the pod
And the podcast listeners
Supposedly don't get any love
Anyway
Sorry, where were we
I was explaining how I became a fan of the show
Yes, please
I mean, I'm just chatting online one day
And she just IMs me on ICQ
She's like, are you to like, be mining DDR
I was like, what here
And she's like, check this out
What was your number on ICQ
You just aged everything ten years
When you brought up ICQ
Well, we're already on a ten year delay
I'm still logged on to it right now
My number is
10719559
Uh oh
That was my old boss's message tone
Well it was everybody's on ICQ
No, no, I mean on her phone
Uh oh, ew
Okay, so she messaged you on ICQ
And your computer went, uh oh
Yeah, pretty much
And then everybody in OLR went
Wait, was that right
And then everybody in OLR
went, uh oh
Ah, that was great
Oh wait, here we go, here we go, here we go
This is great
Uh oh
Oh, that's the sound I make every time
Oh look, the phone's lighting up
And it's Ranma
I wonder if there's somebody out there
That has their ringtone or text message
For their phone
How about the ICQ sound remix
That apparently exists out there
Oh god
Uh, OT pain
Is this dubstep?
Not yet, not enough screeching
Okay, anyway
Hi Ranma, what's new?
That's a notorious SKIE, huh
I'm sorry?
Yes, oh
Blackwool says the ICQ song needs to go into rotation
Take a vote on it right now
That's right, looks like
Dark Tetsuya voted for it too
So I think that passes
We're gonna get that in the vlog stream
ICQ remix coming soon
Alright, Ranma, anything else
you wanted to share with us
I think I overran my time
So I'm gonna get a bun out of here
Love you, mean it
Sure you do, you mean it for every bullet so far
Love you too
I'm out
Bye
It is strange how
well some people's voices lend them to
recreate sounds like that
People, I don't know if I've ever
really been pitchy on the show
1-877-GAMO-LR, or username on Skype is OrangeLawnsRadio
I don't know if I've ever really been pitchy on the show
I know I've laughed pretty high pitched a couple times
tonight, but I would never have expected you to be able
to recreate that tone, ever
There's a lot of things I can do
you can't even possibly imagine
Episode 469
Live
I do the Muppets too
Their voices, their voices
Near
Far
Oh god
Kermit the Frog
Hi ho, Kermit the Frog here
Do I really want to go into an inside joke like that?
Probably not
Live radio
It's moments
like these where I can only
think of this
Call
Hold on
We got a call coming in? Here we go
Oh hi, who's this?
Hello
Manomina
No, that's terrible
Who is this?
It's Shane
Hey Shane, what's up?
Nothing, I just realized that
I can't really plug courthouse this week
because I won't be on it
So did you call into my other radio show
just to tell me that?
Yes
I already figured that out actually earlier
I didn't
So I thought you should be the first to know
Well thank you for that important announcement
Hey guess what y'all, Shane will not be on
Hoard House this week, in other news
this is the week to listen to Hoard House
Wow
Just kidding, I'm kidding
Who's gonna do the Facebook
Who's gonna do the Facebook question of the week now?
I don't know
but it won't be me
What, you have no Google Plus listeners at Hoard House?
I don't even think Hoard House
Is that one person not listening?
I don't even think Hoard House has a Google Plus account
sadly
Is that all you called in to talk about?
What?
No, I called in to say everybody needs to also
purchase Guild Wars 2
because it's fantastic
Ah yes, you've been playing in the beta
What's so great about Guild Wars 2?
It's pretty
and the combat's fun
and it's also free to play once you buy it
It's pretty fun
Did you say it's free to play once you buy it?
Yeah, like there's no monthly fee
No subscription, yeah I got that
So it's similar
It's similarly different to World of Warcraft
You stole my word
Alright
You're full of hate tonight
It's a problem
Ah, that's great
I learned from you Shane
I learned from you and since you're not gonna be on
Hoard House this week I had to make up for it
Clearly
I'm
What am I not full of hate? Alright
I don't know
You're extra hateful tonight
So are you allowed to talk about where you're at
right now or should I not talk about that on air?
Why is it confidential?
I don't know
I don't know either, I'm asking you why is it
confidential? Because
of the nature of your work now, I don't know
No
I'm up in Redman, Washington
training at Nintendo
Are you having fun?
Yes, it's very pretty here
Like everybody should just look to Redman
because that's what I want to do now
The Pacific Northwest is really beautiful, I haven't been to Redman specifically
but I love Seattle, Seattle's great
Should go back for PAX
That's next week so I can't
Is that really next week?
Isn't it?
PAX is over Labor Day weekend again, it's the same time as
Dragon Con
I thought it was the end of August
Which would be next week
That's like three weeks
Oh, I don't know
I can't go
That's too much money, but I would love to now
I always want to go to PAX if it's up here
August 31 through September 2nd
That's what, three weeks away?
That's the same time as Dragon Con
Well, Redman
is like a little village inside a forest
It's beautiful
It's like a little village inside a forest
How far are you from Seattle?
Like 30 minutes
Oh, that's further than I would have thought
Well, that's how long the cab ride took
The $81 cab ride
Holy moly
That's a ways away
I didn't pay for it, so I don't care
Alright, well I want to hear all the dirt
even if you can't talk about it on OLR
I want to hear all the dirt about your first trip to Nintendo headquarters tomorrow
That's fine, I will do that
And let us know if you bump into Reggie or anybody really exciting
How is Reggie exciting?
I don't know
Be sure to ask him if his body is ready
I'm sure he hasn't heard that enough
Oh god, that really was the highlight of E3
He did say Reggie
I don't even remember that
He did say Reggie OR somebody exciting
So, okay, if I meet Mario tomorrow
Like actual Mario, not Charles Martinette
I'll let you know
Or Derpy Mario
I don't know if you've been listening to the show
But the Derpy Mario from Florida might show up
I don't know
You know what, in fact
I think you need to report Derpy Mario actually
I'm going to help you out
You need to put that in a feedback box somewhere
If there's a suggestion box on the wall
Please arrest Derpy Mario in Tampa, Florida
Well, I would need some sort of like
Like proof of Derpy Mario
The picture is on Kotaku
It's on, alright, I'll email you
I'll email you the link
Alright, I gotta let you go to get some more calls
Anything else?
No, my whole
Studio
Hotel room is powered by a key card
That I have to plug into the wall
And if I take it away it turns everything off
It's weird
Those hotels are actually really nice
Yeah, it's $300 a night apparently
Wow
It's like
Guy from middle of nowhere, Kansas
Ends up in the big city or the village in the forest
Where you have to plug things into walls
In order to get power
It's weird, you have to make power
Like a freaking water
What are those called?
Those water wheel things?
Hydroelectric power?
Sure, there we go
Alright, I will talk to you later Shane
Take care
Bye
Let's try to fit in at least one more call
For the night before we say goodnight
Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio, who's this?
Hey guys, it's Porkchop
Hey Porkchop, how you doing?
Not bad, just on all you guys who are all
Knowing, I heard you talk about the move
And I'm just wondering, I'm thinking of buying it
But what exactly can I do with it?
I mean I have a couple of games I can use it with
But is there anything else that I could really do with it
That's worthwhile
I'm sorry, but all I have to say is
And I know this is a radio show
Your Skype picture is cracking me
The hell up
I'm glad, I didn't think you could see it before
But I'm glad you can see it now
Yes, we can all see it here in studio
And it's cracking me up
Because to describe it for listeners at home
He's literally wearing a tinfoil hat
That makes him look like
It's a tinfoil helmet
He looks like a superhero or something
But he looks like
Sir Tin of Foil
It's a very phallic, foily head
That he's got there
Sir Reynolds of Rap
He's like a metallic luchador
Thank you
He's a metallic luchador
But the expression on his face is like
Hey
He's like the happy luchador
I'ma body slam you now
Anyhow
Episode 469
Thank you
You should get the PlayStation Move
To play it in that helmet
And upload those videos to SingStar
You would be the number one ranked player in the world
I would do that just for you
Seeing as you ask so nicely
I would do that if I can get SingStar
No problem
And please make sure it's SingStar, Abba
Loki, you have some suggestions
What could he do with the move?
Well, there's
All their first person shooter games support the move
And they have also their gun thing
I don't remember what it's called
Well, Sports Champions
Is pretty fun with the move
Also, apparently
Child of Eden is really good
With the move
They've got some move exclusive games
But they're kind of just so-so
I don't know
Let me put it this way
A lot of that move stuff is probably
Really discounted right now
So you could probably take a pretty good
Look through a dump bin
Somewhere or a discount bin
In one of these stores and find a bunch of that move stuff
But yeah, I'd say
Probably Sports Champions is really good
Although, if you want to wait, Sports Champions
2 is coming out
I don't know if it has some of the
I think it has some of the same events in there
But I mean, it's got frisbee golf
That's kind of fun, I played the archery
Archery is really cool
How is LittleBigPlanet's move implementation?
It's supposed to be pretty good
They've got a lot of new stuff with that
LittleBigPlanet 2 would be a good one
If you like Heavy Rain
I don't know how good that would be
Yeah, I got that
You can use it as a mouse
Yeah, that's hacking stuff
Actually, yeah
A lot of the games are pretty accurate
It works pretty well with whatever
It's just whatever type of games you like
I know they tried some of the party stuff
In the very beginning and that was kind of crap
But stick with the sports games
If you like the dancing games
I'm sure it works well with it
You could basically pretend you're playing Wii games
That work
Yeah
Well, I got Heavy Rain and Resident Evil 5
So I think that should pretty much
Keep me going until I can pick up some other ones
That sounds pretty good
Sounds like a lot of stuff you're going to find in the clearance bin
Pretty soon, unfortunately
But hey, however you can find the deal, right?
I picked them up cheap anyway
King Star Abba, that's on my list
Alright, as it should be on everybody's list
It's fun
Alright, Porkchop, before I let you go so we can close up the show
Anything else on your mind tonight?
Yes, Konami, if you fuck up
Zone of the Enders HD collection
I will fucking kill you
In that helmet
Yeah, he will wear that helmet
Professor Chaos!
That's it
You need a battle axe made out of tinfoil
I just need a special move now
Wait, I have to say it
Because over here it's aluminum
There's an aluminium
Really?
We just said tinfoil
Why make it so damn complicated?
We're that lazy, we don't give a shit
Cover your food with it, that's it
Tinfoil
Make hats, make axes, whatever
I love it
Alright, Porkchop, I got to let you go to Close Up Shop
Have a good one, buddy
Have a good one, Rusty guys
Will do, bye
I love the listeners
187, oh wait no, I'm closing up Sky
I'm sorry if you didn't get through
But it's like 9.30 already
And I want a milkshake
We need to wrap up here and get out of here
What? Milkshake
Does it bring all the boys to the yard?
I don't care, it brings fat to my butt
It's the Dark Sakura version
Wait, hold on, hold on
No
You asked for it, you asked for it
God, you're awful
No
La la la la la
Ha ha
Ha ha ha
Thank you for YouTube ads
Alright, here we go
Unmute me
My milkshake brings all my fat to the butt
And I'm like
Damn right, it's fat on my butt
They all want me
When I walk into the gym
Like this
Damn right I went to Pinkberry
And I was like
Yo, supersize
You can't have mine
And there's your singing
For episode 469
Is there a meme
We haven't covered?
Okay
Oh, I think I need to do um
I need to do Twitter topics
Are you
feeling a little emotional, Rob?
I'm so emotional
baby
You had to bring
Whitney into this, can't you let that poor
woman rest in peace? Never
Damn
She's still got a movie coming out, alright?
She's dead and got a movie coming out
It's amazing what they can do with technology
Alright, look, tweets
First off, Tigerclaw
They actually tried that with Bruce Lee
and Tupac
Alright, uh
Great, Travis
is inviting me on Understation live next week
and do white boys sing along
Why not, sure
Alright, Tigerclaw
tweets us
and you'll be interested in this, a fan-made
Mass Effect adventure game that surfaces
Is that that Mass Effect universe?
It's called Finding Shepherd
and it's on the Adventure Game Studios
It's created by one of the users on the forums
Nightfable. Finding Shepherd, it's in
progress right now, but it's set in the Mass Effect
universe directly following Mass Effect
3. It assumes that you took
the destroy ending, that's all we're
going to say about that, but what's cool about
this game, if you kind of look at some of the early screenshots
it looks like a LucasArts game or something
That's kind of rad
Do you press S for Shepherd?
Shepherd? Shepherd?
You seem to have Mass Effect
confused with heavy rain
Alright
Uh, let's see
Tigerclaw
also sends us one more tweet about how
GameStop is one of the worst places to
work in America
It's just number 10
Is it really? It's only number 10? Yeah, it's number 10
Uh, actually I had pulled this up
Number 1 is Dish Network
Number 2 is Dillard's
Number 3 is Radio Shack
Number 4 is Perch
Number 6 is Sears slash Kmart
Number 7 is
Robert Halfer International, which I have no idea who they are
Kmart is tough to work for because you have to work
with mummies Number 8 is Hewlett-Packard
Number 9 is Rite Aid
and number 10 is GameStop
followed by Bank of New York Mellon
Sears
slash Kmart? Was that a tie?
Or are they the same company?
They're the same company Kmart and Sears
had a merger with Holdings
Oh, imagine that
Babymon, who wants to plug his best friend
made some Papercraft Legend
of Zelda, which is available as posters
on Etsy
I got to admit, some of these are really cute
They're kind of the Phantom Hourglass style
That's cute
You should plug that in the chat room
That link's a little long for me to read on air
But it's on Etsy, just search Papercraft Zelda
I guess
Oh, sends a tweet with more pictures
That one's really cute, I like the Mario one
I would hang that in my house
I want this game now, because you play as Jack
Anyhow
Thank you for the tweets
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
to send us tweets in a future week
But you know what? We have got to close up the show
Oh, last minute stories
Let us Jack have a picture of Miranda in a room
I have no last minute stories
Well then I guess it's time to end
episode number 469
So
First off, I want to thank our guests
for being here tonight
Thank you so much for making the drive
All the way from Colorado
Huh?
It was a drive and Colorado was involved
But I'll take it
Thank you Jason for being here tonight
Appreciate it
And do you have any last minute thoughts?
Final thoughts?
I cry from laughing
Way too much
Ryan, thank you so much
You made it finally to a show
Yay, finally
And I'm with Jason
My head hurts and I've been
laughing so hard I was crying earlier
All the feels
Is that your final thought tonight?
I think so
Alright, well thank you for being here and please
come back again sometime
And I swear I'll get you a better mic next time
Alright, let's see
Dark Soccer, your final thought tonight?
I want a kitten, but Shermie is too fat and would sit on her
Loki, your final thought tonight?
I drink too much water
And my final thought tonight is
La la la la la
Thank you guys so much
I thought your final thought would have been
Uh oh
That's what happens when you drink too much water
See that sounds like either
ICQ or lemmings
That's what happens when I eat at Chipotle
Uh oh
Followed by
Oh I'm so glad we could have a poop joke
before the show was over
Thank you, Loki
We've already had dick
I'm sorry, alien dildo
Really? We got dick? Where?
Alright, that's it
We're done. Thank you guys so much for downloading our show
or listening to us live however it is
and checking out. Thank you for participating with
Orange Lounge Radio
You made it all the way to the end of the show
I really want to thank you guys
for your continued support week after week
You guys rock, thank you so much
Please, if you enjoyed what you heard
Just tell a friend or two about the show
Because if you can believe it, we've been doing this for 469 episodes
And we're somehow still not
number one on iTunes
In fact, we're like number 204
I look today
So, please tell a friend or five
about the show
Spread the word, iTunes, Stitcher Radio, whatever
the kids use these days to listen to podcasts
The podcast app on iTunes, whatever
Listen to the show, spread the word
Tell a friend
Thank you so much for being here
And I guess we'll come back next week to do it all again
How's that sound?
I guess
Have a great week everybody, we'll see you next time
here at Orange Lounge Radio
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio
is a production of
OLR Studios
To join us for a live show
tune into
vaughnetwork.com
Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific
9 p.m. Eastern
The views and opinions expressed
in this program do not necessarily
reflect those of the staff
of Orange Lounge Radio
or Vaugh Network
But you know they were all still true
See you next week!
We just don't want
the party to stop y'all
We forgot to do this during the live show
so we're gonna attach this on here
at the very end. We just had so much stuff that was
given away tonight between that code that the
emailer had and then the code that you were gonna
email us for. We forgot to
announce who's gonna win this and get
Bradley's bag of PAX shit
that he got. That's right, that's the
sound of the bag. So now you're getting
a bag of PAX stuff that's been fondled
by Jason
That just increased the value
by.01 cents
He totally felt it up while we watched
Amazing. DarkSakura
pick a number between one and
what I told you before we started
Four. Four! One
Two, three, four
Congratulations William Murderface
Yay!
And what a lovely pleasant name to be giving
a bag of crap to. It's from
It's from Metalocalypse
It's from Murderface
Somebody you could take home to mom
There you go
Really weird looking dude
So now we're really getting the party
Thank you for staying all the way to the very very
bitter end podcasties
Congratulations William Huggleface
I'm gonna change his name temporarily
Yeah, that's it
On to your next podcast
Thanks for watching and have a great day!