[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, March 23, 2008, Puzzle Quest on Xbox Live gets a new expansion, GIFs ensues even more businesses over Guitar Hero, and could Kid Icarus be really making a comeback this year?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm full of waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Full of waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoying the Easter waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't this a tradition in your fam?
[SPEAKER_02]: You and Dan always... With our big group of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although it seems that every year there's a new baby added with our friends who join us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because like one year they had Bob.
[SPEAKER_02]: The next year they have Tatiana is her name.
[SPEAKER_02]: They call her Tater.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a nice name for a child, Tater.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's a cutie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't doubt it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Babies are cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: and um um we basically just you know went to Marie Calendars and got well everyone goes to I finally learned my lesson after doing this for eight years is um they always go through the um the omelette line and I get sick on the omelettes every year for some reason so I was like screw your omelettes I'm having eggs benedict and waffles and I had waffles and chocolate eclairs
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, then happy Equinox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just happy day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy day, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tech Master Loki also here every week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you do anything special today?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did the Easter Bunny leave you anything good?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I just went over to my mom's house and we barbecued ribs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mmm, ribs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys have interesting ways of spending Easter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, interesting good, not like interesting bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But more food.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or as Frisbee in chat room says...
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrainer.com, the always present fourth guest on the show, Waffle Lounge Foodio.
[SPEAKER_05]: That could be the name of the show, Waffle Lounge Foodio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could play the Waffle song from Mystery Science Theater.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we're not going to play the Waffle song right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to get into how was your gaming week, but first a teaser, a little teaser.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have big news to talk about, like big, like we just found out 30 minutes ago big.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be talking about that in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of people in chat are kind of going like WTF because they can hear us on Justin TV talking and like want to know what's up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, someone died.
[SPEAKER_02]: I killed them.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no one died.
[SPEAKER_05]: The ferret died.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where has he been for the past year?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I found the ferret the other day, and then I put him back in the dusty corner I found him in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, you should have brought the ferret out.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was uneventful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was uneventful.
[SPEAKER_05]: No DSing?
[SPEAKER_05]: No Ragnarok?
[SPEAKER_05]: No nothing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I played Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, of course!
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course!
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that goes without saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I actually did not touch my DS all week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I moved that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game that Dan brought me home that I'm not going to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Professor whatever the fuck it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Professor Layton?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I've heard a lot of good things about that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might actually want to check it out at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's House DarkSakura's House DarkSakura's House
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the ones that's been removed on there, so I'm going to slap that back on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they can fucking replace the thing, because I'm not touching it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and I'm addressing this comment in chat, because some people may not know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mike W. says, how many 360s does Loki have again?
[SPEAKER_05]: So please refresh us.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many 360s do you have?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have six.
[SPEAKER_05]: And why that many?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we land them in a game room.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I got them for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I had five originally, but then I bought one to replace another one, but I ended up fixing the original, so we have six.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: One that hopefully will be fixed here pretty soon, because like I said, it's not three-ringed anymore, but I think it may have overheated so many times that it's damaged, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then this last one, which I'm sending to Microsoft, so that will be fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hopefully it will all be fixed at one point.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's not very promising that three out of the six have died within the last three months.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's all I really got around to playing this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have a lot of stuff lined up for this week, including K Project, which is that res beta that got released out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I want to try that because that looks cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to dig out my Dreamcast for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then Final Fantasy VII Crisis Core.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, actually, I played a little bit of Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: this week, but just Space Emissary stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and I added everybody in the goddamn friends code list, so stop your bitching.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody was online when I was online earlier, so you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop complaining.
[SPEAKER_05]: Talking about the Orange Lounge Radio forum thread, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I thought, yeah, I added everyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I didn't add everyone, but I added most people.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think I might have added everyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and trying to unlock everything in the gallery.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know, play Five Brawls with Princess Peach to get Super Mario 2 and things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been trying to do as much of that stuff as I can.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: And otherwise, I haven't been playing a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went back to the Xbox 360 and just played some random old stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing really of note was playing some World of Warcraft, but I was out of town this weekend and I was staying about a block from the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't even think to go there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not what it used to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, if you were there next week, you could actually go to a Crisis Core launch party.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, I do have to go back to San Francisco next week anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, maybe I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's like Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going on a weekday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so that does... Yeah, no new games to review this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of odd.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing Scrabulous on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like Scrabble.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just depends on your bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have dial-up, you might have a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you have dial-up, I don't think you're going to fucking be watching or downloading a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: One gigabyte file?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: No thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just... Oh, I want to hear something funny, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I have a friend at work right now who's really into rock band, and he keeps playing all the hard songs for me and unlocking me achievements.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, I can't fucking play the game on hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: What am I talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can play guitar.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't do drums.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I played Rock Band this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played a lot of Rock Band this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why you take it to parties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because of that new, and I don't want to spoil the story that's coming up, but some of you guys know Rock Band had some enhancements this week, and we'll talk about them a little more a little later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I went on to check them out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I haven't checked the Rock Band store in a long time, and I forgot that you can get some Nine Inch Nails songs that are pretty cool, and I got that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the B-52s have a song on there, so I had to get that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I went shopping on Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: because I heart microtransactions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've spent way too much money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really, but yeah, I've spent way too much money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, way too much on Rock Band, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: But just think, the next party we have is going to be so bitchin' with Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we need a Rock Band party.
[SPEAKER_04]: The thing though, they don't make it very easy because of that stupid digital rights management.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, anything I download and if I bring it over here or whatever, I have to be logged in on live in order for all that content to be available.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it really blows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft is crying in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, Mexico still can't access the music store and rock band.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: In some ways, it's a good thing because then you just start spending money so stupidly because you're like, oh, I have points.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could just spend them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That sad face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: That is sad face.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is sad face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very sad face.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, let's get to the big news and it actually really sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, there's really no easy way for us to kind of mention this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This...
[SPEAKER_05]: and literally we just heard about some of the changes that have been going on with our streaming provider which is Live 365 literally about 30 minutes before our show went live tonight and the long and the short of it is that Live 365 is making some obscene changes in their pricing policies and they are going to be upping their
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be upping their rates to these obscene amounts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, right now, we pay about $60 a month to have about 100 live listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: We would have to pay under this new plan $120 a month for 60 live listeners, which would only barely accommodate what we do on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_05]: Usually, we don't talk about ratings.
[SPEAKER_05]: We get about 50 to 60 live people on a good Sunday night, and we've actually gone beyond that before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think our highest show had 70 or 80 people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say we have, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just sucks because it kind of came out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Supposedly, Live365 sent an email a month ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never got it, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're upping these rates, and even if we could afford it, we kind of don't want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've made a decision that we will be leaving Live365 effective April 12th.
[SPEAKER_05]: and so that really sucks because that means the feed that we started in May of 2002 is going away.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I wish this was an April Fool's joke, chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is completely legitimate.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is not an April Fool's joke like a preemptive strike or something because it's not even April yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we have no choice but to leave Life365.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: We found out about this 30 minutes to an hour ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: so we're still trying to kind of scramble too but regardless our live feed will be closing effective April 12th meaning that those of you guys that listen at work to the lovely video game music that plays all day long and the retro lunch and all that it's going away and what I feel most horrible for are the other live folks that we've had bless our stream with their presence for their hard work in live shows over the years including
[SPEAKER_05]: DMN, including Travis Donovan, of course, including, you know, Extifer back when he had his show, including the three of us that do our spinoff shows when we feel like it, and the things that we had planned that we wanted to do with the live feed that now we're, all those plans are effectively off, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: and obviously we'll do whatever we can for our friends that broadcast as well but we have to kind of like our number one priority right now is relocating our Sunday show first and then we'll see what we can do after that so Actdeft asks what's going to happen to DM Insanity and TDL I hope they keep going I hope they keep going somehow but unfortunately Orange Lounge Radio won't be around for them to do that with so
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio kind of ends in a way on April 12th because Orange Lounge Radio was the radio station.
[SPEAKER_05]: This show is actually Orange Lounge Radio Live, but obviously over the years it's just been Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The next week's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's the news.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you have suggestions or offers, I guess, I don't know, send us an email.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can contact me in my personal email box, rob at orangelaunchrader.com or our general email bag, mailbag at orangelaunchrader.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We think we know what we want to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We think we know the option that makes the most sense to us, but it involves other people.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to make sure they want to do it too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got anything else you guys want to add?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've kind of been dying.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't like what's going on, you send your emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd say the life...
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, you know, in turn, they hopefully will send emails to whomever is charging them, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, I think that they probably know what's going to happen because they're raising all the rates on their stations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, a lot of people are just going to forego paying those rates and just quit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: or find elsewhere, and that's unfortunately... I imagine we're not the only station that's doing this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure that they didn't have, you know, it wasn't really their choice to do that, but that's kind of, they have to... It does go back to the royalty things you've probably heard about from the past year, at least that's what they're blaming it on, but I still think it was kind of a bit out of left field.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're taking advantage of that situation for their own personal gain.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't help but feel there's a little of that going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything you want to add, Jamie, as somebody who's been a live broadcaster for this long?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that it hasn't already been said.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll make some refuse.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: RossDLUT says, Live365 is simply using the RAA boogeyman as an excuse to screw people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to knock them right now, but let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the money to keep going if we wanted to.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could do the 60 listener limit, but we just kind of don't want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: We think we can do – this is more of an incentive.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of shows us that like, hey, Orange Launch Radio, you guys have been kind of lazy the past six years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just stay on on Life's Just Five because it was convenient and it was there, and you could just touch a button and everything is all set up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is really going to kind of force us to explore alternatives, and it could be exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be the beginning of big change, big change.
[SPEAKER_01]: When one door closes, another opens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just going to –
[SPEAKER_04]: Check us out.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is also another option right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have actually people that do hosting for our unlimited listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see over the next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're exploring lots and lots of ideas.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously our number one priority is keeping this show going.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that many people's worlds will be crushed without a 24-7 music feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I apologize to those that have been listening to our 24-7 music feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know there are some that do, but obviously Sunday shows the priority for us right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's get into other housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other housekeeping tonight, of course, a happy Easter or whatever it is you celebrate today.
[SPEAKER_05]: If nothing at all, then happy Sunday to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: To all of our Orange Lounge Radio listeners, yes, we are here live on Easter because everybody, I guess, did their stuff this morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to the Bay Area this weekend, had a very lovely weekend in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and the thing is that they do Rocky Horror Picture Show and I've been involved with that for a long time you know the show I did before Orange Lounge Radio actually started because of Travis and I's mutual love of Rocky Horror Picture Show under Station Live I still am involved with that not as heavily as I used to be but I still respect the scene and the counterculture that it provides this is very rare to have this show on the big screen this is probably the only time this year outside of a convention this will show on the big screen anywhere
[SPEAKER_05]: Gary Shale, Oscar Drill, Live at the Show
[SPEAKER_04]: The Orange Lounge Radio Wiki
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, I showed you that before the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that awesome, the Orange Lounge Radio Wiki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it, but you're missing some jokes.
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to go old school.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have, like, you know, death cake.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's lots of old school jokes, but I've got to say, I'm very impressed with the work that the folks that have been working on the Wiki have done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, the place that the Orange Lounge Radio Wiki is at, orangeloungeradio.wikia.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: and just to give you an idea what's there, and this is all the listeners that have been doing this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is incredible.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a page of like inside jokes from the show that includes like the Loki is tingle bet and just some of the other things that have come up on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's been...
[SPEAKER_05]: They can hear the plane over the live feed right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can they hear that on the podcast?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they hearing that on Justin.TV?
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably Justin.TV because the mic's right by the window.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, because the window's open.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they probably can hear the plane outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, yes, we live by an Air Force base.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's not actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a helicopter.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was an Air Force base.
[SPEAKER_03]: It used to be an Air Force base.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it CHP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, somebody's breaking the law.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't live that far.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't it now like a business airport is what they use it for primarily?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's a commercial airport.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like FedEx and air shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and air shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, the air shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the Blue Angels kind of get old to me after the first couple times and they're so loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to go see the Blue Angels when I was a kid, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how fucking old they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we've always lived by the airport, but now it's just tonight the window's open because it's hot here now, so we have the fan on in the window.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think it's bad now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It only gets to like 110 outside.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I found out the information for you in an air conditioner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk about that later.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's Classic Game of the Week
[SPEAKER_05]: BD Live
[SPEAKER_04]: and it will allow you to do different things with your movies including they will have additional downloadable interactive content as well as like interactive games with leaderboards and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: All stuff that you can kind of throw together on a Blu-ray disc which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other cool stuff that they're enhancing, you'll be able to play DivX in Windows Media files larger than 2 GB.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the music and photo playlist can be exported from the PS3 to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: DVDs and Blu-rays will resume playback for the moment you last stopped them.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PSP can be used as a remote control to play music on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the web browser will feature a faster page loading times and the ability to save links and stream linked videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also I guess another thing they called Mosquito Noise Reduction will be added to AV Control Panel for Blu-rays and DVDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the fuck that last part is, but I'm sure someone out there does.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea what that means either.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was that called?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mosquito?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mosquito Noise Reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: My guess may be like... Is that to like filter out the planes that fly by while you're watching the movies?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe like line humming or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It removes the hum off the line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I thought Blu-ray was supposed to be perfect anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is there doing line noise?
[SPEAKER_04]: Your Blu-ray may be perfect, but your theater setup may not be perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my god, that sun is so fucking bright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Through that window.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just like blinded by that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure the Justin TV people that are watching us on there can see.
[SPEAKER_05]: But as we're taping, you know, just the way the sun is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: The sun is shining like right on Loki and I during the entirety of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm hiding in shadows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we know, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: We know.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why don't you just like duct tape a towel up there?
That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's just re-situating.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm moving the sun.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, what'll be funny is that then later the sun will move slowly and hit you in the eyes again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't it going that way?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, like last week, it kind of went down.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's shining through the last window right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Constant exposure to your eyes will eventually give me a headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm already starting to get one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's why I had a headache earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stories!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: PSP 3.93 Internet Radio Feature
[SPEAKER_05]: and that's really it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I imagine it probably closed some loopholes in the hacking world but my other question would be has this already been hacked, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it hasn't because really all it did was add just those 20 stations so they have a workaround to add those 20 stations if you want but otherwise they're not worrying about cracking it because it's basically just that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That seems a little silly to do a whole firmware upgrade just to add those better be 20 damn good stations 20 damn good stations better be in there
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, does 3 Speech have their own radio station?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure No, I think all games where we're syndicated on Monday nights and Tuesday mornings I think they're on there So that's all you really need, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not on there because Live 365 doesn't go on Shoutcast So we've been paying all that money, why?
[SPEAKER_05]: When we can't even get listed on PSPs Oh, forget it It's old hat now Things are going to be changing soon I have two words for that
[SPEAKER_05]: Alpha Canogram says it's not stations, it's players.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess I'm what, like different skins and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's even lamer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tony, play us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rosteel UT says OLR should be on three-speech radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we could talk about all the great things in the Sony world and nothing else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about all the good things in the Sony world.
[SPEAKER_05]: And our show would be only five minutes long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I have some great things in the Sony world to talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, then please do share.
[SPEAKER_02]: More like Sony being fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, um.
[SPEAKER_02]: basically EA put out a patch for the orange box on PS3 that's supposed to address these problems with connectivity and frame rate issues and slow loading times but they haven't put out any other documentation to really say what else it's supposed to do and the thing is like 128 meg so it's kind of big and
[SPEAKER_02]: No one else really knows what else it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the whole thing is, it's not really Valve that did it, it's from their third party, so, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at least it's not like, um, I was gonna say, like, Bully got patched recently, and apparently the patch didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, see, see, Valve, this is what you get for having software on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, RustyLUT in chat says the patch does nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they said what the patch did, it's just, um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I am looking that up right now, because I don't remember off the top of my head, because I don't own the PS3 version of the Orange Box, and you know me, I don't care about anybody but myself, so, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't have the PS3 version either, I have the Xbox 360 version, and keep in mind, the only version worth having is either PC or Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3 is, it's not meant to be online.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I don't know if they're going to actually scale it back resolution wise I mean after all they did allow them to break the barrier for Street Fighter 2 HD Turbo Remix whatever the fuck it's called now I think that that was the last announced thing though that they were having to scale it back because the game wasn't quite working at the full resolution I'm sure Microsoft will let them bend the rules a little bit to make it work with a big game like that okay
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, since we've wasted enough time, now I can tell you what was in that patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: They fixed graphical issues where a player would have the explosion effect left on the end of their rocket launcher while attempting to rocket jump.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some memory leaks fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fixed an issue where the player's name would not appear on the stats comparison screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an issue that would cause the vote tallies to disappear when you viewed a scoreboard between rounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Online server issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: An issue with players not always being added to the player's menu across MediaBar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fixed a bug where a player viewing a friend without an EA account would have an empty entry in their friend's leaderboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: And fixed an issue where it was not possible to connect to EA's servers if you have more than 30 friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it sounds like they fixed a lot of issues, but nothing really important like frame rate issues or anything that really needed to be fixed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh, unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, speaking of Valve, you know what I checked out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally, after all this time, and I know some of you guys are going to be like, oh my god, Rob, you're behind the times.
[SPEAKER_05]: I finally downloaded and checked out Steam this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: After all this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a nice little front-end program.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of reminds me of X-Fire, but like with game purchases available inside it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I actually thought about getting Portal, just so I can have it on the computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm a sucker for that game, as a lot of people are, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um,
[SPEAKER_04]: Persona 4 Persona 4
[SPEAKER_04]: All sorts of stuff from the new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Persona 4 is coming to Japan in July.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting enough, it's actually coming out on the PlayStation 2 and not the PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it looks, you know, to me, I think it looks 100 times better than Persona 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'm sure a lot of people will be very happy about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word of what's coming over to the US, but seeing as they've brought over Persona 3 and Persona 3 FES...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: That is pretty interesting that they're packing all that in a PlayStation 2 game, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: That they're still cranking them out for the quote-unquote old system.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I guess there's still tons and tons of PS2s out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still one of the better-selling game systems, eh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: It has some more in common with Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game is starting to sound more and more like just another Street Fighter 2 port, but just like completely new graphics and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like Street Fighter 2 Turbo HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, but yet, you know, it's got the whole, it's 3D-ish element and, you know, the whole new characters and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, the fighter guy and the, what was her name?
[SPEAKER_05]: Crimson...
[SPEAKER_05]: Viper, whatever her name was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it'll be very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the news that was announced this week is that not only are there some small cosmetic changes in the game, but that the old combos will work exactly the same way in the new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that means the old combos from Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you got a Guile combo down that you used to use in Street Fighter 2, apparently you can use them in Street Fighter 4 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's just... Have you ever played against, though, one of those people who are just like the combo people?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's painful.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, strangely enough, not so much in Street Fighter II, but in Mortal Kombat, I used to get those people all the time, and it used to piss me off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was one of those people on the beta version, though, just because I learned Kitana's infinite combo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which was funny, because people get mad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of pain... I gotta say this real quick in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob D says, uh, there's no way they could get away with skipping those combos.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is nothing new.
[SPEAKER_05]: They never change mechanics that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: True, but when you consider the age of Street Fighter 2, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kinda, kinda cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I get on with the pain?
[SPEAKER_05]: You may.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bring on the pain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, pain is gonna be on PlayStation Network, um, at least for, uh, the PAL PSN, um, for, uh, 499 pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's a game where you throw stuff for points.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't really describe it much else than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't you buy Pain?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not bought anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, other than Flow, I bought that on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But other than that, I have not bought a game on the PSN because I do not like their payment method.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like jackass in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like using real money.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, the whole point of pain is that, you know, you're causing misfortune in people, and people grow up and laugh at them.
[SPEAKER_02]: They get laughed at.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, that's sort of what pain is about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, to get back to the story, there are also additional packs that are 69 pence each, and it will be the Scurvdog Muffy pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Santa, Hung Lo, Ginger, Cookie, and Fun With Explosives packs.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last one is supposed to be a freebie.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, but any game that combines Santa and Fun With Explosives you think would be instant win.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they had a band, it would be named Fun With Explosives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: But also, the store also has the Stranglehold pack for $9.99. $9.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, again, in pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: That has multiplayer maps.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually should be the one they got on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should see if that name is taken in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun with explosives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if not, then I would be stealing the one from Clerks that Dan came up with this morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Making Fuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably taken.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't doubt it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I have the name Emergency Kittens, but there's no one in the band.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's move on to some release dates for other things coming out around the world in the regular stores, the big box stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, this week we've got some pretty cool stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, winding down a little bit until we get to Mario Kart and Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sector on PS3 and Xbox 360 Viking Battle for Asgard on PS3 and Xbox 360 Final Fantasy VII Crisis Core on PSP
[SPEAKER_04]: also this week we've got Opuna on the Wii that's that Koei RPG that you can actually control the entire game with the nun check only I'm actually very curious to check out Opuna I definitely want to check out that game there's a little budget puzzle game called Octomania $19.99 for this game and you can play it online with other people so that's not bad at all
[SPEAKER_04]: Also this week, Naruto The Ultimate Ninja 3 on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obscure the Aftermath on PlayStation 2 and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: A really crappy game called Backyard Baseball 2009 for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what number release this is this year, but one of the billion releases for Harvest Moon this year with Harvest Moon DS Cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninja Gaiden Dragon Sword, also on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, that'll be fun too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does Ninja Gaiden still have the epic cinema scenes like the old school games have?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I hope so, on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is the DS, but the whole game is controlled with the stylus, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've also got just some more crap here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, oh, this is also coming out on the 31st.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monochemia, Alchemists of Al Rivas.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that is a new RPG by Koei as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, for right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know next week there's absolutely shit coming out, so... Enjoy it while you last.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's travel to Japan and check out some of the releases that will be coming out in Japan very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Xbox 360, you get Dark Sector comes out, as well as Raiden Fighters Aces and Tomb Raider Anniversary all come out in Japan on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, a DVD lens cleaner, if you need one of those for your Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lyra Nobuken
[SPEAKER_05]: is the name of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming out on other systems on the Nintendo Wii, Lego Star Wars The Complete Saga also on the Nintendo Wii, Ninja Reflex, Nitro Bike makes its way out of there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a spoiler for Japan, Nitro Bike sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how do you know that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I played it and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: What Sucks About It
[SPEAKER_05]: GS68, by the way, refers to one of the earlier titles we mentioned in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, Golden Kump Ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Golden Kump Ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 2 sees Guilty Gear XX Accent Core Plus comes out, as well as Neo Angelique Full Voice in a premium box and a super premium box, as well as the original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silent Hill Origins makes its way to some Asian regions this week, but Korea is the only one we see mentioned, so be sure to check.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be a little bit longer before it makes its way to Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobunaga no Yabu Online comes out in Japan this week as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see real quickly what's coming out on the handheld systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Nintendo DS, we have Business Ryoku Kente DS comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Katekushi Hitman Reborn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bungle Shiki Taisen Battle Sugoruku comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Baseball game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that it says Hitman Reborn in it, in the middle of it, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of makes me think of a different type of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's baseball with Hitman.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need Battlefield Baseball.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Simple DS Series gets volume 35, the Genshin this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lost in Blue 2 gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Mobile Suit Gundam 00 comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mina de Flash Anzen DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mina no Atsumare Quiz Party comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, wait for it, the Golden Compass on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check in real quick to see if anything's coming out of note there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monster Hunter Portable 2nd G. That might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: As well as Tomb Raider Anniversary comes out on the Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well I have for our UK listeners another set of release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 27th, the Gran Turismo 5 Prologue.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've heard us talk about this, so don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Golden Horde on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 28th, we have Coded Arms Contagion, Football Manager 2008, God of War, Chains of Olympus, King of Clubs, Naruto, Clash of Ninja Revolution, Powershot Pinball Constructor, which sounds pretty fun, that's on DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pro Evolution Soccer 2008 on Wii, Sega Bass Fishing, Universe at War Earth Assault, Viking Battle for Asgard, Warriors of the Lost Empire, Warriors Orochi on PC and PSP, and Worms Space Oddity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out here not very soon, but soon enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: In June, Activision actually announced that they will be bringing Guitar Hero on tour to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you may be wondering, how the hell are they going to do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's actually a brand new peripheral that they're releasing along with it called the Guitar Grip.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has four fret buttons and a wonderful little hand strap to put your hand through.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you use that just like you would, you know, the fret buttons on an actual guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you strum on the touch screen with a stylus, or actually a pick stylus that comes with the game to do that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, you know, plays just like Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to have 20 songs, or more than 20 songs in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And 80% of the songs will be original master recordings.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've
[SPEAKER_04]: My memory serves me right, it's $49.99, comes out June 22nd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, just in time for my birthday!
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, they've wasted no time in whoring this game to the masses.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you guys ever visit Yahoo.com, like just, you know, out of the blue, but it's one of the pages I'll go to, you know, for like news and search and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's a little flash ad that pops right up there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's already whoring the Guitar Hero on tour.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are wasting no time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I would recommend pre-ordering this if you're really interested in it because like most other Activision games that include peripherals, especially brand new peripherals that they're breaking ground on, this thing will be hard to find.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frisbee asks, is anyone honestly going to buy this crap?
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually have mine pre-ordered already.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm not going to probably play it because that's what I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm interested enough where I at least want to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I want to drop, what you said, $49.95?
$49.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I want to drop $50 on it, especially if it's only 20 songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm interested in checking it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it would be that difficult if it's only four buttons if I can already play five-button mode on the... Dude, Konami really missed out, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could have done Guitar Freeze with three buttons.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm saying that for a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I'm interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me ask chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many folks in chat are interested in picking this game up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar Hero on tour.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quick poll of chat because I imagine most of you that own DSs or if you don't own a DS, imagine you did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you pick up this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: and Frisbee says, please just smack yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I feel so sorry for Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in Fry's the other day and that game's like on clearance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tons and tons of copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't buy it anymore, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, hey, here's the thing, and I don't know if you should start getting worried about this or not, but they're really whoring Guitar Hero out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Activision, I don't know if they're going to drive it into the ground or what, but, I mean, we've got, actually, literally a week after this, Guitar Hero Aerosmith coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then you've got Guitar Hero 4, and who knows how many other shit, you know, games that they're going to throw in the middle there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're really whoring that franchise out, and people are kind of really buying into it, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's look at our instant poll results in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to read the nicknames because that will take me too long, but really quickly, here's some of the comments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Question was, are you going to buy Guitar Hero on Tour DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not.
0%.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just get a PSP and DJ Max.
[SPEAKER_05]: Depends on the song list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only for the peripheral to make it easier to play Puzzle League.
[SPEAKER_05]: Strap for the win.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the game has songs I like, I might download, I mean pick it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I may get it if they guarantee cheap expansion pack song cards minus peripheral.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never, ever, ever, ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will purchase Guitar Hero on tour after I'm done burning $100 bills.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, nope, you'd look like a damn fool playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, not ripped off.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Khan.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's your instant poll results.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I was just thinking, I mean, this is a good game for kids, you know, especially when you're taking them on the road and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can play their Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, you can play Guitar Hero in the car.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only reason I'm buying it is so we can show it on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much the only reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, don't waste your money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hey, just because I ordered it doesn't mean I'm going to actually buy it, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I don't have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just put it on order to kind of hold my spot.
[SPEAKER_05]: RossDLUT says, Loki, you're high.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll bug mommy even more with this game by singing along.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, maybe my wife would do that, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just don't put songs with words in them.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go into more lawsuit news from Gibson.
[SPEAKER_05]: We already kind of talked about this last week, but if you can believe it, even more lawsuits coming out from Gibson.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember Gibson sued Activision, they sued Harmonix last week, all over the fact that Gibson says they have had a patent for electronic guitars for...
[SPEAKER_05]: And get this, this week, now they've sued GameStop, Walmart, Target, Kmart, Amazon, Toys R Us All these major retailers that sell Guitar Hero games Seeking basically to stop the sale of the games Did you see they also sued EA?
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though EA doesn't make Guitar Hero at all It's crazy, yeah I was going to say in the next piece here They sued Harmonix, Viacom, and EA now as well
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I guess they want to sue as many people as possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This makes no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're looking for money.
[SPEAKER_05]: But why would you sue the retailers to get them to try to stop selling the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're trying to make a big stink.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to file an injunction.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to make a big stink and seeing who will give them money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki says the EA suit is over Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's over Rock Band because they mentioned Guitar Hero in the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it because now Harmonix is a part of... Oh no, I guess it was just an agreement.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That just sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's sue everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that comment from Gerardimo in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you gotta wonder, is this Gibson thing legitimate or not?
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's actually an analyst out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, we love analysts.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this is actually a legal analyst working for...
[SPEAKER_05]: Wedbush Morgan, he's an analyst, he says this about the lawsuits, quote, this is, Michael Pastors' name, quote, this is a poorly masked attempt to extort money.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are using any way they can to have Activision write them a check.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, this is the third game, I mean, well, the third major release of the game that's been out so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think at one time they had Gibson guitars in the game, I want to say, I don't know, I may be wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Konami, and if I remember correctly, I thought Activision was licensing the rights to use that from Konami, and not Gibson.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I gotta say is the next fucking guitar games you guys put out, just forget about Gibson.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's plenty of other guitar manufacturers out there you can license guitars for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyhow, this news, I know, makes me angsty every time I hear about this, and I'm sure you guys feel the same way.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you know it's time to bring on the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess life 365 goes without saying, so I'm not gonna really go too much in depth on that, um, but F you to, um, having way too many people in the house when I had a doffy to work on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Suddenly got her blushed and I haven't finished with the rest of her face.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, F you to, um,
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That fucking sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to Live365, goes without saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, I think when this show comes back in a non-Live365 place, we should actually probably rename this segment to the Live365 Memorial FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but also I want to give an FU to the cat scan I had on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was so miserable.
[SPEAKER_05]: And look, I still have a bruise from where they gave me the little shot thingy, or the iodine thing, bleh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate, oh, it was so miserable.
[SPEAKER_05]: So miserable, I reacted so bad to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, I had to have a CAT scan because I'm still having those pains that I've been having.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're not going away, which sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't get the results back till Monday, so F you to waiting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell you what, though, this is the best diet I've ever been on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll eat, like, a couple things and I get extremely full.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like I had gastric bypass or something without having to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that does it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, wow, we have almost like a whole segment of music game news, don't we, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, how's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, you know, before they're screwing us over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, MTV has said that they've sold, what was it, more than 6 million, I think, songs and rock band as downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now Harmonix is bringing in the Rock Band Music Store for PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: so that you can actually download your songs in-game without leaving the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so you can sort them by artist, genre, album, title, pack, and other ways, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's album art.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can listen to song previews and difficulty levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the patch is actually supposed to be out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe it's already out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the patch had already... Didn't you say that you... I did, and it's lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I just... He's eating toast.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I give that F you to not being able to eat, and then I'm eating.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excuse me, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, I did download the music store, and it's actually kind of cool because you get the little album art, and you can download the song previews now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, like, if you're not sure exactly what a song is, like, I think I've heard that song, but I'm not sure, you can download the little song previews, and it stays on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So when you're scrolling in the list in the future, you can kind of hear it like it was DDR or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, the music store kind of looks like a DDR selection screen to me, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the fact that you can actually preview the songs, you know, something that I thought should have been on there in the first place, instead of having to buy these songs blindly, unless you have, like, a YouTube link where you can watch the video or listen to the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's smart.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the whole thing was smart because I realized there were songs in there I didn't, like, I wanted that I didn't realize I didn't have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because it's hard sometimes, especially when you recognize a song on the radio by the song, not necessarily by the title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you might not even know who the artist is.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just recognize the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Press Start in chat agrees with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: The previews in Rock Band are evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: I downloaded like three more songs because of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there was a little bit more that I saw about them trying to add more features that were based off of requests by the community, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be...
[SPEAKER_04]: new content every week through 2008 so that's pretty cool that's of course only in the US right now that's pretty cool you know what I'm surprised they don't have yet is vision camera support or like you know camera support to basically film yourself doing your little rock concert shit you know in front of your TV or whatever with your friends and then posting it like a YouTube thing
[SPEAKER_04]: with some sort of contest maybe lumped in with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although at the same time I'm kind of glad they don't have that because that would be a motivation for some other people to try to get me to do things I don't want to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week we've got a new download pack coming to Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually six songs from Boston and quite a few that you'll probably like here.
[SPEAKER_04]: including, let's see here, Hitch a Ride, More Than a Feelin', Peace of Mind, Rock and Roll Band, Smokin', and Somethin' About You.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can buy that in a pack for 800 Microsoft points, or $10, or individually for 160 Microsoft points, or $1.99 each.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you save $2 if you buy it all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever happened to you getting that rock band stage kit?
[SPEAKER_05]: When is it not out yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: When does that come out?
[SPEAKER_05]: June.
[SPEAKER_05]: June?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have to wait that long to rock?
[SPEAKER_04]: And we won't even be able to do it on Live 365?
[SPEAKER_04]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of those things that we need to have a camera for so we can see the entire garage being filled with smoke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a little clip of Boston if you actually need a reminder.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the same song that's in Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it's also in Chariots of Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boston is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boston is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, though, I want my Queen pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Journey pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's my Journey pack?
[SPEAKER_04]: I need me some Queen, because that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: She was funny in Cry Baby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, I love Tracy Lord as an actress.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yes, she was on the NBC show.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was it, The Pretenders for the longest time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I thought you were talking about a fourth.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, not that type of actress.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, you know, sure, people everywhere can appreciate her fine work there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, something else you folks can appreciate is free stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who doesn't like free stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't if it's yours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something, well this isn't Yaris, it's actually on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sort of a, we're sorry, please forgive us type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember how the whole Wii Guitar Hero, oh excuse me, the whole Guitar Hero, I eat toast and I burp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember how the whole Guitar Hero 3 on the Nintendo Wii only had the mono sound in it?
[SPEAKER_05]: And they have to do all these replacement discs for the stereo sound now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you're also going to be getting a Guitar Hero faceplate.
[SPEAKER_05]: A free Guitar Hero faceplate.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually kind of neat looking.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like fire a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's red and yellow and black, and it looks like a phoenix kind of rising up from this fire-ish looking thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's small black leather, and it says, Please don't sue us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please don't sue us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please no class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: By accepting this faceplate, you agree not to do a class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, don't you think that looks kind of cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks better than the guitar I have in the living room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate how the Wiimote goes in the guitar like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I guess it makes sense and probably makes things cost less.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, free faceplate for those of you that are going to be getting the replacement discs for Guitar Hero on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to understand, it hijacks Wi-Fi like a college student in an apartment complex.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we please move on with the gaming news at this time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually were saying that there may be another version, another song pack for Guitar Hero that would be all Beatles stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's pretty cool, although I've been corrected as far as information in the article that their catalog cannot be distributed on iTunes because of a lawsuit going on between Apple and Apple Corp.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to go into all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Read Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they said that they're trying to work about bringing a few songs out for a particular song pack, so I think that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't they have to get the rights back from Michael Jackson?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or did he sell that stuff when he started becoming poorer?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not the expert.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, another bad idea sounds like something coming from Ubisoft with their brand new title in their Imagine series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine, people actually buy this shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is absolutely in no way a ripoff of Rockband, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it kind of revolves around fashion and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually, the Imagine series is meant for girls aged 6 to 14.
[SPEAKER_04]: or in the case of Jamie, she likes Imagine Babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it will allow little girls, I guess, to be able to play drums, guitar, bass, and piano with each other via Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And each instrument has its own unique control using the DS stylus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And players will be able to customize the look of each bandmate and create the most stylish rockers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only girls can play?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not fair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine, you two can play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: And they worked their way up the charts to become the number one recording band.
[SPEAKER_05]: How is that different from Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you get to dress your characters in Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to understand, this is shitty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band, not so crappy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine MasterChef Imagine MasterChef
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hear them, I don't want to say defend themselves, but let's hear about their contributions to the gaming scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like to hear from the horse's mouth.
[SPEAKER_04]: I make fun of them because it's not my demographic.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a problem with a lot of games not being focused towards girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so they are kind of working that market.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same with UFO Interactive.
[SPEAKER_04]: They make a lot of these, like, was it,
[SPEAKER_04]: Smart Boys Game Room, Smart Girls Dream House, type thing like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's games that are aimed at kids that are three years old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, really get you hooked young.
[SPEAKER_04]: Start them young.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's nice that they're aiming for this demographic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, though, it's easy fodder for us in the press to just kind of make fun of it because...
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't understand it, and it's different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back in my day, we had Mario is Missing, and we liked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario is Missing was great, and besides that, I personally, for some of these, I don't really feel like perpetuating any type of stereotypical behavior or traditional roles.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that it's up to... It's just like when Nintendo tried Super Princess Peach, and that flopped, and so they said, fuck it, boys will play games, girls will do nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I play games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Super Princess Peach.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screw you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like shooting things in games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like... You will play your Kirby and your Peach games and you will like them.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the chat room is just going off with all these different Imagine things, but Amaze Hatsuma, I like this one, says, Imagine these games in a landfill next to E.T.
[SPEAKER_01]: I...
[SPEAKER_01]: I like violent games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee says Peach is awesome in Brawl.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually true.
[SPEAKER_05]: The two characters I use most are Pit and Peach.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like the Foo Foo Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the Peach Pit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_01]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like Foo Foo Games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why do you think I have to play Foo Foo Games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want Explosive Portal.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you like Final Fantasy Tactics?
No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then this is not for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy Tactics A2!
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy XII Final Fantasy XII Final Fantasy XII
[SPEAKER_05]: A little bit, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check that out loosely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another way to whore that series even more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop whoring your Final Fantasy series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Final Fantasy XII was a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make one game, move to the next number.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do not need to expand upon this series in tactics games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And besides, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Revenant Wings, did you play much of that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool, you can be the killer tomato in this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or at least I think you fight the killer tomato.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game actually looks kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still need to beat Final Fantasy XII, though, and that other Final Fantasy game you bought me on DS, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks like fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure we'll be hearing from our listeners on this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we hear from them about everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, hi!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, um... We know Codemasters, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're familiar with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: They, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Codemasters Online Gaming basically said that they want to do two MMOs for home consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were saying that they've had a little bit of success already in the market, and so they're looking to bring stuff out for PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one of the ones listed, and they're saying that now is the right time to hop on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not anything specific yet, but they said that they're really going to gear it for the consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I personally don't think MMOs work very well on consoles unless it's like, you know, PSO.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what I'm hoping, and I know they don't make this game, at least not Codemasters.
[SPEAKER_04]: APB, that game that's coming out that's just like Saints Row, but it's an MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope to God that I don't have to pay month to month for that thing, because I really want to play it, like, badly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, most MMOs you do have to pay month to month for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but Guild Wars you don't, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: And they really need to follow that line of thought there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody, look at Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Learn it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of games out there that are free to play and you buy download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what they should do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just give out free games and then I'll pay for download content later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Second Life?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Second Life is stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like if I wanted to go pick up Virtual Horde.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the game's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is free and you get what you pay for.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you pay for your downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, but that's a game that... You just described Second Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Second Life's a bad example, because that game sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not really a game, it's just an addiction.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the MySpace of MMOs, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: But it does specifically do what you were suggesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it does, but it sucks at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what I'm trying to say, though, there's other games out there that are also free to play, and most of them are Korean, because apparently they understand how to make a good MMO.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or apparently Malaysian, like one of my friends was on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go figure, Malaysia, where a lot of piracy used to come out of, and yet they're making good games that are free.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I digress.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's kind of a little bit of a different topic here, but once again, and we haven't heard about this in a while, Massachusetts now is considering the whole games as porn bill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: House Bill 1423 House Bill 1423 House Bill 1423 House Bill 1423 House Bill 1423 House Bill 1423
[SPEAKER_04]: And with the assistance of, or from, of course, well, this right here is why the bill is bad in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Voldemort was the, you know, inspiration on that bill.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, legislative sponsor, Republican Linda, or I'm sorry, Representative Linda Dorcina Forey, who happens to be a Democrat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, of course, you know, this thing, much like all the other ones in the past, will fail because it's not constitutional.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, at the same time, you know, what do we gotta do to stop these people from wasting our tax dollars on these bills that they know they're gonna fail?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's like the fuckin'... Is it so that when they rerun for office, they can say, like, hey, I took a stand against this...
[SPEAKER_05]: Video games are poisoning your children and I take a stand against this.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob and I approve this message.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's really for their own personal gain and it's still wasting taxpayers' money.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the more reason you should hate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do our children really need to be protected from games?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, do we really need the government to step in to tell our children what's okay to play?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, are we that retarded?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know some people are that retarded, but I would like to think that, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Most of us are not that retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if we're all that retarded, then who the hell are we going to elect in as president?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I promise you shiny things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you got my vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm sure we'll hear about this game later when it fails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meanwhile, or the bill, not the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meanwhile, we're going to get to the end of Part A of our show here, but not before we pay a little respect to our elders in the segment we always do every single week here on the program.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's DarkSakura's Classic Video Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, DarkSakura, you've dug through the archives.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've verified this pic is not a duplicate per the wiki.
[SPEAKER_05]: What classic game should the kids be checking out this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jackal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jackal is a great game because you drive tanks and blow up shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best game ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, I'm talking about the Nintendo version specifically.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen to the music, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to play this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Akari Warriors, but you're in a jeep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this is the game, though, that makes me think of that line from Hot Shots.
[SPEAKER_02]: War is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, which I don't really believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, I love Jackal just because, okay, I actually have memories of this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before my papa, who is my dad's dad, before he died, we would actually sit in front of the big screen TV, and we're talking like, you know, early 90s style big screen, so this is a big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Playing the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: and playing Jackal with Papa.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, the game actually, um, it was, um, an arcade, um, released in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was called, um, Tokushu Butai, uh, Jakaru, which would be Jackal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, Special Forces Unit Jackal, which was released in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: as Top Gunner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, basically the whole point of the game is you go through and you can, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: Run over... Well, I like to run them over, but you can shoot down enemy soldiers wandering around, and you rescue POWs, and you have to actually take them to the extraction point where a helicopter will run off with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um... Then you fight, like, whatever your boss is at the end of the level.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um... Again, it came out over here in the arcade as Top Gunner, but it did come out as Jackal on the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, though, for, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: anyone who happened to be one of those few people who has a Famicom Disk System, it was brought out as Final Commando Akai Yosai, which basically is Final Command The Red Fortress.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's just really fun, and on top of that, when you play two player, it does force you to cooperate because
[SPEAKER_02]: There gets to a point where if one person's going one way, it won't let your other person advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sometimes one person can draw fire while the other person goes in and does something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really a cool, I think kind of a unique one for the whole run-and-gun sort of series.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually blow up different areas in the game where there's hidden stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get extra power-ups.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get...
[SPEAKER_05]: Rocket Launchers I actually preferred to keep the grenades because the grenades would go over a wall whereas rockets just sort of explode on the wall It was really cool I like how you pick up the little dudes I didn't play this game a whole lot I think I remember playing it once and I just wasn't that into it I guess when I was younger but I like how you pick up the little dudes from the houses and then drop them off at the plane and it's like a rescue mission thing It's cool
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can keep upgrading your missiles to where you get your missile launcher, you get one with a higher range, you get one that produces shrapnel, and an area damage missile that shoots out from left and right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still preferred the grenades because they went over the walls.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can also control which direction you fire in, which was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you can turn and fire forward in a different way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's like a tank.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of my favorite ever games.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, I actually have really good memories of the game, so it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, there was a bootleg version of Top Gunner that would let you use the Ikari Warriors style controls.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had a version on the IBM PC in 1988, like I said, the Famicom Disk System, and I wouldn't mind seeing a sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or the inevitable Xbox Live Arcade port at some point, probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could you imagine this high-res?
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, there it is, your classic game of the week, Jackal, in this case on the NES, but on a variety of systems, as DarkSakura pointed out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and that's our cue to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's exactly what we're going to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to take a break and we'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.