[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this Easter Sunday, March 23rd of 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had some unfortunate news a little earlier on.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't heard it yet, go back and listen to Part A. Big changes coming to OLR very soon, and hopefully next week we'll have more information on that for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But in the meantime, the show goes on, and it will go on as it always has.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will go on right now with Loki spreading the rumors.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Horse Pick
[SPEAKER_09]: Copiers, Plagiarists How do they know it's in the works?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't fucking know, nor do I care
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, I think you underestimate the fanboys I'm
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say that it'd be cool if a Kid Icarus game came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think it's the game he's talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Animal Crossing is the game he's talking about, but if there is a Kid Icarus game in the works, I mean, they'll be pretty big, but I don't think it is the game that they're going to be announcing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it could be a game they're announcing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a game, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo of America's history dating all the way back to the NES and you know no surprise this game was going to be a big seller but this was a like really big seller.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is sold at a rate of more than 120 units per minute between the day it launched March 9th and March 16th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that is a huge selling game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Ross2UT, though, is the first to point out.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's Debbie Downer UT right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, still slower than Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, it is kind of a good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: It didn't sell quite as much as some of the guys on Xbox did.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still a huge seller for Nintendo, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also you have to remember, too, I mean, that they don't have as many units of the Wii yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now, as of the 360, they're still number two in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, I mean, not by much, so that doesn't really make a big difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it a big deal that it didn't meet up to those Halo 3 type numbers?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't think they were ever, you know, I mean, it's, you know, it made history for Nintendo, so I think that they're more than pleased about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so going back to the story earlier about Kid Icarus, would it be a game that people would recognize or not?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a huge game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pit is a character in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does a good job at kind of reminding you that Kid Icarus is out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: What with the virtual console thing and the stages and the music.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what they need to... No.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what they need to do with Rob the Robot?
[SPEAKER_09]: They need to make it, like, one of those fucking, you know, RoboSapien things, or, like, fucking Furbies, where you can program the shit out of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or the, uh, what, Ibo?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ibo, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just, like, something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just, like, really crazy, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: Get people to buy that shit that wouldn't have a Wii or something like that and just go crazy with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, I don't know about you guys, but, like, when I was playing Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl and I played that subspace emissary mode and I saw the Kid Icarus thing and with the music and him flying through the air, flying down to Earth, and with the music playing, I'm like, God damn, we need a Kid Icarus game now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, that was initially the first thought in my mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think we might have even been broadcasting on Justin.TV when I was doing that in the game and I seem to remember exclaiming, God damn, we need a Kid Icarus game right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make a new one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw says if they do the new Kid Icarus, it's no doubt that they would also have to bring back the Eggplant Wizard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Eggplant Wizard was also a very memorable character.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody knew him as the annoyingest little fucker in video gaming history.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the most annoying characters, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's great, though, about being turned into an eggplant, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that if you press down to where you can see his feet and then you slide across the floor as an eggplant.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like Metal Gear Solid Eggplant.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I love that too.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just hope that nothing saw you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can even hold it down and jump as an eggplant, and that was great too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And who knew that hospitals could cure the eggplant curse?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, you could also turn into an eggplant from watching too much TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, anyhow, huge numbers for Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl, and I'm sure this game's just going to continue to sell through Christmas, so we'll see how it holds up throughout the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in other news... Okay, well... We know we were talking about how Namco was talking about, you know, not too many people are playing their games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I should say Bandai Namco.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now they're talking about, actually they also blamed it on the Wii too, which I think is kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now they're talking about bringing out games that will combine the arcade and Wii titles to where I guess they'll share scores or that they'll have some sort of interactivity, but it would be for a data exchange between the different versions of the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what I have to say about that, Neo Geo?
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know what I have to say about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: F-Zero GX And you know what I have to say about that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing, I just wanted to join in.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, seriously though, I mean, they were part of the whole Triforce system that, you know, I think that was only pretty much used for the F-Zero GX stuff, but, you know, it had cross-platform stuff between the arcade and the GameCube, so let's do something similar with SD memory cards, because those are widely available.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's smart to make arcades like a gamer's hub.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know that kind of sounds like a big duh type of answer, but I think it's smart to kind of make your arcade games somehow talk to the console games and give gamers a reason to sort of convene in one place, in real life, outside.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, not having to use Xbox Live and rely on that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think these kind of ideas are smart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you imagine like a Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: arcade game or something like that, like done on a huge screen, you know, with four...
[SPEAKER_09]: Joy6, you know, set up and stuff and they have like additional characters and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or things that unlock based on what you do on the home version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, Loki, one could dream.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree, one could dream.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see what happens with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another cool thing that probably will never come to fruition, but you know, at least with all the
[SPEAKER_09]: Buzz that's going around about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But a fan of Metroid 2 is actually working on a remake of the game that he's been working on right now for about three years now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Metroid 2 Return of Samus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome looking thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's using sprites from Metroid Zero Mission as well as the remake of the classic Game Boy game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And some other sprites.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's also hand drawing from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess Metroid Fusion was the other game he was using.
[SPEAKER_09]: and using the program GameMaker7, the guy who goes by DrM64.
[SPEAKER_09]: And totally awesome looking game so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've actually got a, I guess, not really a beta or demo, but a proof of concept demo, I guess, that you can download and play straight off of a bunch of websites.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you're interested in checking it out, it's Metroid2Remake.blogspot.com for the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we have a little YouTube that Tiger Claw sent us of this in action.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat, looks like Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I imagine that's not the sound in-game.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they actually do have an in-game... I don't think this is it, though, is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's the actual game, but that's not the... Damn, the game looks good, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice, wall jumping.
[SPEAKER_02]: I approve.
[SPEAKER_02]: This looks good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I hope the project doesn't get shut down by the way it ends up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would do, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Macman says, oh shit, I thought it was going to be a Rickroll.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I trust Tigerclaw's links.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of you other people, I don't know so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might get Rickrolled by you, so don't think I'm...
[SPEAKER_09]: Rick Roll, you get blacklisted.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, you Rick Roll me, I ban you.
[SPEAKER_02]: That shit was funny like three months ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little old now, so please do not be Rick Rollin'.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, Metroid 2, yes, I approve.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hope the project doesn't get Rick Rolled by lawyers.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would suck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like, was it the 3D remake of Chrono Trigger?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's, oh, that thing looked hot, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo Mii's, as in the characters that you create on Wii's, were being used to advertise Easter service at a San Francisco church.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: They used a little Mii that looks like Jesus standing next to a bunny that looks a little grumpy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the little postcard says, Come and follow me, Mii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was Easter Sunday, which was today at 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: at the Mission Bay Community Church.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just clever ways of advertising.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like churches that are hip and with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like churches that don't feel like they're still living in the Old Testament.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you see the one that was the wedding invitation that had the two me's on there?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't think I saw that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then when you open it up, it says, Wife Get.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like something that Mel and Mel, my buddies, would be doing for their weddings.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like something they would do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: That actually, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is very cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like cute, innovative ways of doing things.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, bless you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm allergic to... Something here in the studio?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you allergic to me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you allergic to Jesus?
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be a problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mildly.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hopefully you're not allergic to mail, because this is the part of the show where you're going to read some for us as the listeners email us at mailbag at orangezonsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we get better participation this week than last week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we did get some interesting emails, and one of them is from our friend Rob with two Bs.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he didn't provide the link to the article in the email.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he's basically just talking about an article about the outcome of the guy who... I'm just going to read this from the start.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a pretty good article on the outcome of that guy who bludgeoned a baby to death for accidentally breaking the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some interesting stuff in that article.
[SPEAKER_05]: One, the article does not imply the guy was playing his Xbox at the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two, the article does not specify if the murder happened immediately after the Xbox broke or when Spellman, the convicted, discovered it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three, social workers visited the house regularly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And four, the autopsy showed evidence of prior abuse.
[SPEAKER_05]: It implies a pattern of abuse that shows the man was a ticking time bomb.
[SPEAKER_05]: As you said when the story probably came out, it wasn't really about games at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's no surprise that the media hopped all over this trying to make it a video game thing when it really had nothing to do with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No surprise there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But thanks for the update, nevertheless.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not saying that at you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying that in general, like,
[SPEAKER_02]: There it goes, the media again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video games are evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big surprise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Naj linked me a story on CBBC that is actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more just pictures of a bunch of people, a lot of people dressed up as Mario, but also others dressed up as different characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a giant Spyro here, which is a very well-made costume.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of anime conventions, I was told via a text message earlier this week, I don't know if it actually ended up happening or not, because I didn't get any text messages tonight, but I'm being told that our show is right now being played at Anime Boston.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if that's true, a big hello to you kids at Anime Boston.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know who sent me a text message, so I know for a fact you guys are listening in there, because I don't see anybody in chat or what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, my phone's in the house, so maybe that's what happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you've got mine, text me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game's Characters
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so you guys have to dig through your luggage and get your game ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just gather a whole crap load of Guilty Gear cosplayers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll be happy and done.
[SPEAKER_09]: And remember, would Naruto count?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because technically they have Naruto games, but Naruto is an anime character.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of a gray area.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, a lot of anime characters are games in Japan, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it counts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, yes, next email.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is from GS68.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, OLR Crew, since DarkSakura, if I recall correctly, isn't going to Final May this year, will you still do a panel there?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one of the things I looked forward to last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we are invited to, then yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see why not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we always submit?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought somebody submitted for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: You always have to submit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I submitted the last two years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are they accepting right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess we have to submit then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, are we still going to do a panel?
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: A bit about me, yes, I'm an actual DJ and I live in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcades are still alive here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I usually mix anime and video game music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I DJ anime conventions.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got my start as a DJ at FanimeCon 2002.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be going to San Japan Con to meet with SmileDK.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might faint when I meet them.
[SPEAKER_05]: He he.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other conventions I'll be attending are Anime Jam in Fresno, California and Anime Vegas Con in, wait, wait for it, Las Vegas, gasp.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yes, I have a Wii, and I will be waiting for Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised that they removed snaking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh well, I'll find another new strategy to overcome that muahaha.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm also surprised at how easy it is to find Brawl and still no Wii consoles to be found.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't eaten at Olive Garden yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to have my first Olive Garden experience with OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can only dream.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye, DJ Junai.
[SPEAKER_05]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: You pronounce my name right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You win an internet and a Mudkip X3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ironically enough, I might actually be going to Vegas in a couple months, so it's on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Olive Garden, like what?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a good Olive Garden in town, which I hope there's got to be in Las Vegas, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's got to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's got to be an Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, there's no Olive Garden in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Suck for Vegas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some like...
[SPEAKER_02]: I seem to recall I was in the middle of BFE Pennsylvania and there was an Olive Garden there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't be surprised if there was the Olive Garden Casino in the works.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Chenai is in chat and says, yes, there is an Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mmm, if I get three breadsticks, does the machine spit out never-ending breadsticks?
[SPEAKER_05]: And Sauce confirmed that there are a few.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the reason I pronounced your name right is because I'm not Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Rosteel UT has a good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, why would you go to Vegas and then go to Olive Shit House?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know where I want to... That's actually a good point, because Vegas has so many great restaurants.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why the fuck would I go to Olive Garden?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell you where I would want to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would want to go to the Rio and go to the seafood buffet.
[SPEAKER_05]: The massive seafood buffet that I went to on the DDR Freak Moderator trip that ate a lot of my money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to go back to Quark's Bar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get me a Warp Core Breach.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can do one of those myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am so going to Vegas in a couple months.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: My 30th birthday...
[SPEAKER_05]: I still have to get you your present, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey guys, let's have tea here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool, I'd like some tea, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wish I could be listening live tonight, but I'm on a plane right now flying home, so there's not really internet access on airplanes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, years back, Rob did a review on Trace Memory for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trace Memory is actually called Another Code outside the US for any international listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he went off on how amazing the game is.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: But that rarely happened in Hotel Dusk.
[SPEAKER_05]: The puzzles in Hotel Dusk are generally pretty neat and are excellent ways to use the touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game is so incredibly well written that it feels like you're actually interacting with the other people in the hotel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for those of you who have no clue what Trace Memory is, it's a point-and-click adventure game that uses the DS hardware to the fullest.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game is filled with all sorts of little puzzles that you have to solve, and most of them are very well thought out.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's even one puzzle where you have to shut the DS just so that you can see the reflection from one side of the screen and the other in order to understand a riddle.
[SPEAKER_05]: At any rate, check out both of these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very good buys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, all, and please don't forget to save the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll need something to listen to on the flight back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got it taken care of now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never played Trace Memory, so I don't know how I reviewed it on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a feeling it was Miklatov that played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was Miklatov, not me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been advised that you need to go to Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, Margaritas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm down with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey OLR, Sharon here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going through some old episodes somewhere in the late 100s and noticed that Rob at one point brought up Feel the Magic and repeatedly griped about Sprung.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Tsukihime or Clannad, two of which have been fairly popular anime based off of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, FSN and Clannad, there was no Tsukihime anime.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that just fan art?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I did have one, and I actually heard of this one when the Sega CD was new, and it was called Takeru.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it actually...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd remember seeing that they were going to bring it out in the U.S., but it never did on Sega CD, if I recall correctly.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, I have a PC version of it that's fully translated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've definitely heard of Clannad before, but I haven't played it myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard of the band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I hope I'm not getting it confused with the band.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm pretty sure I'm not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's Enya's sister.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a few of them that I've heard of, and they sort of did something like that one for the Silent Hill comics, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least they tried to, but it didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was more just like, oh, we're going to have dramatic music with the comic book panels.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so that wasn't quite the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, the next question involves an email you received last week that concerned the length
[SPEAKER_05]: of arcade shooters like Gradius being too short.
[SPEAKER_05]: I completely agree with Jamie that taking the time to get a high score or playthrough on one credit in games like these gives bragging rights.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is doubly true of much more difficult games like Japanese Danmaku or bullet hell shooters like Ikaruga, Radiant Silvergun, or Mushihime-sama.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this leads to my next question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have any of you ever played any games from the popular PC danmaku shooter series Touhou?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Touhou game started on the PC-98 with a game called Highly Responsive to Prayers.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game series features a perpetual protagonist named Reimu Hakurei, a miko who operates an unpopular and out-of-the-way shrine in the land called Gensokyo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Toho's first appearance on Windows was the embodiment of Scarlet Devil, so if it catches your interest, I would recommend starting with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: The games are very popular for their music, art style, and curtains, fire pattern, and sense of inner-game character development.
[SPEAKER_05]: The games are available for free download on doujinstyle.com, and I would definitely advise anyone who still has fond memories of Radiant Silvergun to check the series out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep up your exemplary work, Shaoran.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have not played those games, but due to that well-worded free plug, I just might.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen, I mean, I'm very, I'm familiar with Toho's games, but I mean, if it was PC, I hardly played it, so I was more of a, you know, like, I'd brought up Bangaio before.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it was more of a recent one, but I like those kind of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I really, really love Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well then this sounds like something you ought to check out too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I was actually pretty thrilled that when, that had the aforementioned DDR Freak moderatorship.
[SPEAKER_05]: We went to this place called, I want to say Game Land.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've gone out of business since.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was probably in 2000 something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really remember when.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I found a Radiant Silvergun arcade machine and played the hell out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone's like, ooh, Mambo A Go-Go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go play that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm like, fuck no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mambo A Go-Go was kind of cool, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I was too busy on Radiant Silver Gun and Biohazard Gun Survivor 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's it for the emails?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you have to say no more emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: No more emails!
[SPEAKER_02]: She said you wanted some type of sound effects.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was really tragic.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's more humorous.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to send us an email, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, we get back into the news, don't we, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_09]: So hopefully you haven't bought this already because if you did, you just wasted some money.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Bungie is now going to be putting out the Halo...
[SPEAKER_09]: 3 Legendary Map Pack I believe it was previously $10 and included 3 maps out for free starting at 2am this Tuesday so that sucks but hey it's free and you know what though if you're still interested in spending some money on maps there are some more coming the next map pack which is going to include a Signed Winder remake
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, no, I only download them after they're free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need to pay for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't know, I used to play Halo 2 with my college buddies a lot, but we really haven't been playing Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: They had a map that they released in the last map pack that I want to say was empty.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was just this big empty warehouse that you could build stuff with.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's like, but you can build all these cool things and forge with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, thanks, but you really didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just made an empty warehouse, you idiot.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you can check that out soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one guy who might actually be back into checking this out was the really depressed guy who had his Xbox 360 ruined by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you remember this?
[SPEAKER_02]: He had his personalized 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was white clean when he did the whole Red Ring of Death fix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_02]: They cleared it all away.
[SPEAKER_02]: PR Nightmare, the story ended up on blogs everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: So he got more than he had before.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, he got like a care package from Bungie and also from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Way to kiss ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this will probably be the last time you ever hear about this story on the blogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now everyone everywhere is screaming, Microsoft, fuck up my 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a cool little care package like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, the art's pretty cool on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo, watch this guy just turn around and sell it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be tragic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want them to draw on my Xbox now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have a service where you can send in your Xbox and get it drawn on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that is a little silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would be happy to provide that service.
[SPEAKER_02]: You pay me $200 and I will customize your Xbox 360 with a Sharpie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I'm actually not joking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send me your faceplate and I'll customize it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, we should do that as a contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should get a blank faceplate.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have blank faceplates, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: We can customize it somehow.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got some of the Ace Combat ones that we can paint over.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that'll work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you can just get a faceplate off of a core system or something and they're white.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or actually, all the original faceplates are white.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have some extra ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there's some information that's out now about Bionic Commando Rearmed, which is the 2D-style Bionic Commando that they're coming out with.
[SPEAKER_05]: The title is supposed to be out in May, and it will be on PlayStation Network and Xbox Live Arcade for $10 American.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there will be a PC version, but they don't have a price on it yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the Xbox Live version is going to actually be for 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: The PlayStation Network one is $10.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that it will, for the PC version anyway, it will require Windows XP or Vista.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least 512 megabytes of RAM and 650 megabytes of hard drive space.
[SPEAKER_05]: So.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it may or may not have unique content.
[SPEAKER_09]: It may or may not.
[SPEAKER_09]: May or may not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, thank you for covering the full spectrum of possibilities.
[SPEAKER_09]: This game may or may not be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have more information.
[SPEAKER_05]: The minimum specs on this is XP Service Pack 2 or Vista.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, I have a pinning for 2 GHz or an AMD XP 2200.
[SPEAKER_05]: 512 MB of RAM, 650 MB of hard drive space.
[SPEAKER_05]: 128MB DirectX 9C compatible card or NVIDIA GeForce 6600 or ATI equivalent DirectX 9 compatible sound card, internet connection, keyboard, mouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their recommended ones are actually quite a bit better, but, you know, honestly, why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess there's like...
[SPEAKER_05]: You can download minimum content or you can have the maximum content that's saying you want two gigs of free hard drive space.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's just the minimum requirements versus the maximum.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can either install the entire game off the DVD or you could just run it off the DVD and some of it on the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's been some stuff leaked out from the German ratings board, the USK,
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, they had leaked out some stuff a while back, including the translation of Catan and Kassaron to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now they have another board game turned Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you mean Carcassonne?
[SPEAKER_09]: Carcassonne, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Casserole?
[SPEAKER_09]: You said, like, casserole.
[SPEAKER_09]: Carcassonne.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, you finished?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, one of the games that they had on there was Ticket to Ride, which, if you've played it, it's a train-themed game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some other games that they've also, you know, were revealed on there, of course, Penny Arcades games, On the Rain, Slick Precipice of Darkness, Rugu, and Golf, Tee It Up.
[SPEAKER_09]: And at least, we don't know when they're coming, but at least they're on the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you giggling at?
[SPEAKER_02]: TheRobD in chat says, I'm going to go play that Super Mario Goulash game next.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat room's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat.OrangeLawnRadio.com Yeah, chat's just perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also love more Xbox Live Arcade games as long as they don't suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, it might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fable 2 is going to be interacting with apparently three different Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was recently revealed this week in an interview with the guy behind Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And money that is won in one of the games can actually be transferred to funds in Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: We already knew that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Carbonated Games has made apparently some casual games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's three titles involved.
[SPEAKER_02]: One is called Keystone, one is called Wizard's Tower, and the other one is called Mage Dice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when you play these games, which involve a little bit of gambling in them, you get Fable Gold in them, and you get to use that Fable Gold in your Fable game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just looking forward to co-op in this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know you can't wait for co-op in Fable 2, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, the only bad thing about Wizard's Tower is it's really just Yaris renamed Wizard's Tower.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up, really?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I was going to say, that's horrible if so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if these are going to be free.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, duh, they're gonna, of course, have, you know, stuff like that, as well as, like, I don't know, Kill Your Dog, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, like, the original Fable sounded so freaking awesome, and then it was kinda... It was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm definitely interested in checking this game out, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, there's another game that I think is... Well, okay, I never played it, but I know a lot of people did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puzzle Quest?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Puzzle Quest was doing pretty well on Xbox Live Arcade, so there's actually going to be an expansion, and they're asking the players to name it for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you actually go onto the contest website, which is at puzzle-quest.com Ooh, actually, it's already over.
[SPEAKER_05]: It ended on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dang, that went by fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't even open when I last checked earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It ended on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, damn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to try to get our chatters to spam them with Puzzle Quest Orange or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, at any rate, they said that once they've decided the name, then the expansion's going to be out in the spring over Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, have fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what about all the other places they hoard Puzzle Quest to?
[SPEAKER_02]: They just get shafted, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have never thought Puzzle Quest was going to get an expansion or any type of microtransactions whatsoever because of the fact it was on the DS and all these other systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm kind of surprised at this news.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how else to explain it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't expecting that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you expecting an expansion?
[SPEAKER_02]: I sure wasn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: An expansion?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, because I thought they would just hoard that out in Puzzle Quest 2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, I guess something to kill time until Puzzle Quest Galactics comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Galactrix or whatever the fuck they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The I Can't Believe It's Not Puzzle Quest?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so this weekend there's been a whole bunch of drama revolving a supposedly leaked game, Sonic Unleashed, with tons of screenshots out there available for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: People are wondering, is this an actual game that got leaked?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this an April Fool's joke?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, first, you know, it started off, eh, it's probably fake, you know, who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: But then there's like a hundred-some screenshots for this, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it is fake, it's one of the most elaborate fakes I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then apparently now, there was news that, you know, Sega of Europe said that it is official and that they were going to be announcing it during their May Gamers Day event.
[SPEAKER_09]: and also make an official announcement at E3 but then there are some sort of wishy-washy stuff going on with that and now it's maybe not real again.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think at this point it's safe to say with the video out there, with the screenshots out there, I would say it's real.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see how it can be a fake at this point based off that video because that video is pretty kick-ass which is out there on YouTube somewhere, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic 2.5D
[SPEAKER_09]: and also that there's going to be some stuff run in the official Nintendo magazine, the UK one.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be, I guess, the cover in August for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: So right now we're speculating that it's coming out for the 360 and probably a version for the Wii and you can probably assume that there's a version for the PS3 if there's one coming out for the 360, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft in chat says, hope for Sonic's future equals rising.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really hope so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the last few Sonic, you know, in creations in a row, you know, minus his appearance in Brawl, have all been very disappointing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, God, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really hope.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you hope, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope they got it right, finally.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can hope.
[SPEAKER_09]: The screenshots are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean... I watched the movie file.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looked pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think... Like I said, you know, if it was a hoax, I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: Then the hoax game needs to come out, honestly.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is one hell of an elaborate hoax to fake, I don't know how many screenshots of this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or even a mapped level.
[SPEAKER_04]: The video followed the level all the way through.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's very unlikely that it would be an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Credit to them if it is an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you fooled us.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was one of the most convincing April Fool's jokes I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: April Fool's Joke
[SPEAKER_02]: And some of our listeners may not even know this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may have just saw the news earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yes, it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: GoNintendo ran a report with a video from the guy who actually created the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he kind of shows how he did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was actually meant to be an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently what happened is that he posted the joke in IRC trying to get some feedback from some of the folks in IRC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, hey, is this believable?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, some of the folks in IRC sent it to Joystick and it got out there a little bit early.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, unfortunately, it is fake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wario's Woods not coming to WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least this one, I mean, but then again, you never know what Nintendo might have up their sleeve.
[SPEAKER_02]: It may not look like this, but as far as I'm concerned, whatever artists did these did a pretty darn good job, and Nintendo maybe ought to think to talking to this guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they ought to cook something like this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: But sadly, no Wario's Woods on WiiWare anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless Nintendo's getting the last laugh, who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, something that came out in the April issue of UK's official Xbox magazine said that Ikaruga was out now and was getting a 9 out of 10 from the magazine with no actual release date.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this real?
[SPEAKER_02]: April Fool's Joke
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's the April issue, so this hasn't... Well, the game is coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had a story on this before.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not No Fools.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just for a moment, when you were talking about April Fool's, I was like, wait, they better not be taunting me with Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I hate April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, seriously, it's going to be like this for the next two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they did have it out at the Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just wasn't thinking that it was out quite yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Ikaruga is like one of the best, best shooter games ever, so that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's Treasure...
[SPEAKER_02]: GS68 in chat says, game publications should be banned from making April issues anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's just me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, if I were a game publication, I would just flat up post a little editorial in my magazine saying, while certain other magazines and publications may want to...
[SPEAKER_09]: Joke about April Fools and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would just say we don't do that and we figure that you would appreciate more accurate coverage than something that may confuse you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is I think the kind of stance we take on this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually our jokes are pretty obvious.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't think we're going to do one this year now in light of the other news that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: The joke is we're going to stay on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, moving on with more news then, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we don't like to talk about him too much, but there was a brand new story this week about our friend Jackie Poo, or Voldemort, as you may know him.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Florida Supreme Court has sent an official notice to Jack Thompson that he now must have...
[SPEAKER_09]: An attorney to basically approve any further cases he has.
[SPEAKER_09]: The court's ruling is basically saying that the numerous abuses that Thompson had made, including submitting pornography and stuff like that, is a relentless and frivolous pursuit for vindication of his claim that he is being victimized by the Florida Bar.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the continued ability to maintain the minimum standard of decorum and respect for the judicial system in which the litigants and especially the attorneys must adhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because of this, basically, the motion has been made that for any lawsuit that he is now putting forward, it must be signed off by, I guess, an accredited attorney or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, he needs a babysitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully we'll see a lot less of him unless he gets some other retarded person to kind of help him along.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's about damn time.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's wonderful.
[SPEAKER_09]: and here's the best part about the whole thing after this ruling came down apparently Thompson sent out an email describing the Supreme Court's order as both good news and idiotic yeah, because he's got them right where he wants them now does he live on another planet?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know speaking of crazy stuff
[SPEAKER_02]: There's that new Street Fighter movie coming out, Street Fighter The Legend of Chun-Li, and it's getting a more full cast.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Chris Klein is in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He plays Guile's friend, which apparently is a big role.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Charlie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, Charlie Nash.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kristen Crook, who is the Lana Lane, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Lois Lane?
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's Lois Lane on Smallville.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's playing, no, I guess it would be Lana Lane because it was a daughter, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't watch them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's going to be Chun-Li.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet half the guys who watch her don't even know what her name is.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just watch her.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's going to be Chun-Li and Michael Clark Duncan is going to be Balrog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Taboo from the Black Eyed Peas is going to be Vega.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the guy with the long hair and the black eyed piece.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's going to be Vega.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neil McDonough is going to be M. Bison.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've never really heard that name, but then when I see his picture, I'm like, okay, that guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I've seen him before somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I agree with SSJ100 Matt in chat who says, this movie fails for one reason, no Kylie.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this guy was in Star Trek First Contact.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why it looks familiar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minority Report, Band of Brothers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, he's been a handful of films.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know why this movie also fails?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh, why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's a Street Fighter movie, and anybody that thinks of Street Fighter the movie is always going to think of the last horrible Street Fighter movie that killed...
[SPEAKER_02]: I just realized why this guy looks so familiar to me, but I almost don't want to say why.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's because of one of the movies he was recently in.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the last movie I saw on DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was I Know Who Killed Me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually watched that on DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did you watch that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I have to see... Okay, when a film wins the award for worst movie of the year, I have to see just how bad it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: They give you fair warning that it sucks, so why do you need to... I like bad movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I love Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Showgirls is one of my favorite movies of all time, but it's one of those things where it's so bad, it's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we actually had a discussion about this at our friend's house the other day, and the movie actually came up as Caveman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you seen that movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really, really not a good movie, and it was one of the 70s, and like, the dinosaurs in it were all claymation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was so awful that it's a great movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen Teenage Caveman.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was like Mystery Science Seeker 3000.
[SPEAKER_05]: Manos, The Hands of Fate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, can we please move on?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have some stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, I don't know how I feel about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, again, with all of the movies coming out from, you know, video games, and especially since the, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: The horrible, horrible UiBull is associated with this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Name of the King, A Dungeon Siege Tale is going to be out on April 15th.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I knew this like a long time ago and I wish I had thought about this, but I figured it was an UiBull movie and no one really cares.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will have deleted scenes, behind the scenes featurette, and trailers.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: The suggested retail is $27.98, so look for it in the $5 bin at Walmart in a few weeks after that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if anyone else saw the news this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're running a website for Postal the movie, because it's launching the same weekend as...
[SPEAKER_09]: Indiana Jones and they have Vern Troyer dressed up like Indy and it was like I don't remember what the phrase was it was something stupid like I have a message for Indy fuck you or fuck you up or something like that I don't know I'm sure it's supposed to be parody but half of me still thinks that they literally think that they're going to beat Indiana Jones in the box office
[SPEAKER_09]: Somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Delusional.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's going to happen when they go back to work Monday morning after that weekend?
[SPEAKER_09]: Vern Troyer's going to go drink some more?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, he's about as delusional as Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically just going to be, you know, he's going to think it's a great victory for him and that, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: It may make him the most money out of any of his movies or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: He'll have renewed hope for making more video game movies or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of miss when this show had a soundboard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think in our post-Life 365 era, we need to bring back the soundboard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of miss having one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call of Duty 4 is a very successful game.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are going to be getting a brand new Game of the Year edition, which is going to be coming out in April.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, April 3rd for the Xbox 360 version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Along with that, there will be a brand new map pack that's going to have a few different maps of Creek, Broadcast, Chinatown, and Killhouse.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be available for $10.00.
[SPEAKER_09]: And as you might guess, in the Game of the Year edition, you get a token to download that for free.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you haven't bought the game yet and are thinking about it, you may wait for this one to come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It should be noted, though, that for some reason whatsoever, the PlayStation 3 version is coming out a few weeks after the Xbox 360 one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't get that, but that's what's going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually have the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I can see this little picture of the games actually kind of hanging around the collar of the shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can get both for $12.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of a neat little concept.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is strange to see at Target, though, of all places.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I would not have expected this to be at Target.
[SPEAKER_04]: EGP Apparel.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would expect to see that maybe at, like, GameStop or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, or, you know, some other type of nerd store, like Hot Topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of nerdy, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: EGP Apparel.com if you want to see more about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy the shirt and get the game for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tower of Goo sounds funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Macman in chat says Target and Kmart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tower of Goo is coming to WiiWare also.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I didn't realize?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not realize until like just last week that Destroy or Defend Your Castle game that's coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not realize that it's based off the old Flash game where you throw the guys up in the air and watch them explode into millions of pieces.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: XGenStudios.com slash play slash castle
[SPEAKER_02]: That game is so much fun, even though it's like years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's been on the internet for like three years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me post that in chat there so our lovely chatters can take a look at that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But don't get too distracted because it's time for us to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, it's the part of the show where we let you guys interact with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to give us a call at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the part of the show where you can do that and interact with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be taking calls, I'd say, right about right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: A different homebrew kind of hack thing that they had going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I told you it would take like 15 seconds for Nintendo to patch that shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's not the one you're thinking, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's this thing called a Trecha Signer.
[SPEAKER_09]: It basically allows them to create, because all the files on Wii discs are encrypted, so this will allow you to create the key and basically put your own files, make your own homebrew discs for the Wii, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got somebody on hold.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, what's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is Ross DLUT.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, you're really good at getting through first.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're like the new Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever happened to Raven's Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he abandon our show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Raven's Dolphin, where are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ross DLUT, you're cool too.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, first off, I'm surprised you didn't mention this early on in the show when you were talking about the Gibson lawsuit bonanza.
[SPEAKER_07]: But...
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's a link that talks about the patent.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to put it in the chat right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, what's happening is that the diagram that goes with the patent shows a stereoscopic headset, an 8-channel mixer, effects processor, among other crazy-ass shit, and an actual musical instrument.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you can see the picture from that link.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I'm looking at it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I didn't want to spend too much time on that whole Gibson lawsuit because I think it's retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to get to that actually in a few seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you want to say then, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, basically, here's what Harmonix's response to the Gibson lawsuit was.
[SPEAKER_09]: This lawsuit is completely without merit and we intend to defend it vigorously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gibson's patent filed nearly 10 years ago required a 3D display, a real musical instrument, and a recording of a concert.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock Band and Guitar Hero are completely different.
[SPEAKER_09]: Among other things, they are games, require no headset, and use a controller only shaped like a real instrument.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's unfortunate that Gibson unfairly desires to share the tremendous success enjoyed by the developers of Rock Band and Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, looking at this little picture of the guitar, I mean, I know pictures and patents aren't supposed to be the end-all, be-all.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like a MIDI guitar.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've seen others throughout the years, but this looks nothing like the game controller that they're using.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I mean, it looks so far removed from Guitar Hero and Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't even see where Gibson's coming from.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not going to win this, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not even close.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not even, not even.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm shocked seeing it that they'd even bother.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, we've seen more stupid lawsuits before.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yes, there was one other thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rainbow Six Vegas 2 came out last week, and if anybody's listening and is thinking about getting it, I would stay away from the PS3 one if you're interested in online, because the online is broken.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh great, what's broken about it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'm finding myself unable to get into most games, and the few games that I can get into...
[SPEAKER_01]: I get booted off right away, and it's not just me.
[SPEAKER_01]: In those few games, I've talked to the people there, and they're having the same problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it's not me, because I'm not having the problem with Vegas 1.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not having a problem with a lot of the other PS3 games, Call of Duty 4 and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was actually rather shocked, especially since the game had a release day patch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't worry, a patch will fix it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That seems to be the thinking of video games in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like the patch that came out when the game came out?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_01]: I pre-ordered the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got it first day, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And I go home.
[SPEAKER_01]: Literally, immediately, PlayStation Network's like, yeah, we got a patch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Download it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I forget it was a multiplayer patch, but apparently not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Patches should be for like what Rock Band just did.
[SPEAKER_02]: It added a whole new feature to the thing that maybe should have been there in the first place, but oh well, it was a new feature, something new and neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, that is an acceptable patch to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: An unacceptable patch to me is, oh, I don't know, Bully?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or countless others?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's another one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another thing is, this isn't the first time we've seen an
[SPEAKER_01]: Ubisoft game with a patch to fix things that were either broken or they were too lazy to get in.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you guys remember Naruto Rise of a Ninja?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like a week after the game came out, they came out with a Japanese language patch.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is literally 52 megs.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, they're basically unlocking it off the disc.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, 52 megs doesn't sound like a key.
[SPEAKER_09]: Usually a key's pretty small.
[SPEAKER_09]: 52 megs, that sounds like actual dialogue to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no possible way.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all the voices in the town and the cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot more than 52 megs worth of dialogue going on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all voices.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't see how that could be all the dialogue.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just too much.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know...
[SPEAKER_01]: either way, we don't see it as much as we did when the 360 came out I think companies are getting better about it but we're still seeing this sort of ah, suck it, rush it out, we'll patch it attitude and it's going to start hurting companies especially with these consoles getting more popular because you know the majority of them aren't going to be online it's just a numbers game
[SPEAKER_01]: and I really feel sorry for the people who are going to get stuck with unpatched versions, especially with what Rob mentioned, Bully.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Ross, to you too, we've got to wrap up so you can go, but any other quick thoughts you want to get out there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, except for the whole
[SPEAKER_02]: Ubisoft buying Tom Clancy thing the only thing I was surprised was that they hadn't already done it yeah that's kind of I would have thought that was already a relationship that was but there you have it alright Ross have a good one buddy you do the same bye bye alright if you want to give us a call 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype Orange Lounge Radio any other stories you want to share with us Loki while we're waiting sure
[SPEAKER_09]: There's apparently some pretty cool mods.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, never mind, we got a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Rob D, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hello, long time no talk, Rob D, how are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah, I've kind of been working and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I work most Sundays and I close, so that kind of disables me from actually listening to you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Work?
[SPEAKER_06]: What is this work thing you speak of?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know, uh,
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to actually abandon my job and only play games for a living.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: See how that one goes for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, what's on your mind tonight, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I've got to say, actually, just listening to RawSteelUT's call, now that Ubisoft actually owns a Tom Clancy, we're going to see Tom Clancy's, I don't know, Tom Clancy's Naughty Toad, Rise of a Ninja, or Tom Clancy's Enchanted Arms now that they actually own the property.
[SPEAKER_02]: I somehow doubt that would happen, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: usually that's kind of like the same thing with the whole when Activision bought Blizzard or whatever the whole World of Warcraft will come to Guitar Hero tomorrow that'd be great but I gotta say the reason I called in is I don't really have a topic to discuss but I need to just express my joy as a fighting game fan of just the titles coming out this year because you've got King of Fighters 12 you've got Super Smash Brothers Brawl Street Fighter 4, Super Street Fighter 2 HD Remix, Soul Calibur 4
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember a crop of fighting games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tekken 6?
[SPEAKER_06]: At the very least, with this pedigree.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: With this pedigree for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see if all these games end up panning out to be good.
[SPEAKER_06]: That obviously remains to be seen.
[SPEAKER_06]: As a fighting game fan, I just haven't been this excited for games, especially to see some of these franchises go online multiplayer for the very first time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was just looking at some screenshots for the other day for King of Fighters 12, and it looks pretty hot, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they redrew all the animations for all that, so I'm looking forward to seeing how they'll actually turn out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trucker Terry is back, so for all the Terry Bogard, Ingrish, Hey Come On Come On fans, that should make many of them pleased.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of old school fighting games from SNK, you know how your pick, your classic game of the week last week was The Last Blade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually went, they have it on GameTap 1 and 2, so I went and played it for a little bit, just because I had never really played it before.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I was using a keyboard, and fighting games with keyboards are always kind of wonky.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got to really use a joystick, but I had fun while I was playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a really stylish game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's definitely stylish.
[SPEAKER_02]: I couldn't figure out any of the fatalities, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the part I was looking forward to doing, but
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, sorry, I didn't mean to derail, but what do you think about the whole Street Fighter 4?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think it's shaping up to be pretty awesome, or is it just like Street Fighter 2 10 years later, or what do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's nice to see that they're actually modernizing the look, and I think this is an important step for the franchise, that they're moving finally from sprites to some modern graphics that aren't done by, what was that company that did Street Fighter EX?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Akira or something like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even remember, frankly.
[SPEAKER_06]: to me it all depends on how the game plays you can't really determine until the game actually comes out I think it's going to be disappointing if the game doesn't really come out with anything particularly new in the fighting game engine especially since SNK has been changing up their fighting game engine practically every year and with King of Fighters 11 they really pulled out all the stops with the super cancels well not the super cancels because that's been there for a while but the dream cancels the saving shifts um
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of things that actually changed the gameplay and just really helped it out as a franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd really like to see how the game plays.
[SPEAKER_06]: Considering I really doubt that it'll actually make any kind of a splash in American arcades, we'll probably have to wait until it comes out whenever it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think American arcades can be saved, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not with how online play has just proliferated over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Japan, I don't think that's really as much of a concern since they're not really into shooters as much as we are, certainly.
[SPEAKER_06]: They haven't had Xbox Live, or at least they don't support Xbox Live as much as we do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really doubt you can get gamers that gathered again out of their homes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can count how long ago it was when arcades were still like, they might have been getting closer on its last legs, but this show started due to hanging out in an arcade, so
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have fond memories of playing Neo Geo games and playing, you know, the old X-Men arcade game, Turtles in Time, especially.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can still play Neo Geo arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they have a Neo Geo arcade machine at Jim Boy's Tacos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you seen that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't eat at Jim Boy's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, but, well, okay, well, they have one there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be worth looking at.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a bajillion Jim Boys around, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know which one you mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the one over on...
[SPEAKER_02]: Folsom and Sunrise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know that makes no sense to our other listeners, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I used to go to Rico's Pizza and play the DDR there while I was eating pizza and 18 Wheeler Pro Trucker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, remember when pizza parlors had hella arcade games in them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it was like pizza slash arcade and now, like, you're lucky to go to a round table and see, like, two games and a pinball table.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're lucky to see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we were just talking about, just for the pinball aspect, we were talking, because...
[SPEAKER_05]: Crane Games
[SPEAKER_06]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the Pizza Parlor was where I first played Street Fighter 2, so... And actually, the first character I ever played as was Dhalsim, or as my mom called him, Mr. Stretchy Arms.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I've always kind of had a soft spot in my heart for Pizza Parlor arcade games.
[SPEAKER_05]: My first Street Fighter 2 was at a 7-Eleven.
[SPEAKER_02]: My first Street Fighter 2 was at a college arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: My college arcade... I can still remember the lineup for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had...
[SPEAKER_05]: Cyber, not, what am I thinking of?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember, Cyberstorm was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was sort of like a virtual on ripoff, sort of.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we had Killer Instinct, we had World Cup Soccer 94, which became my favorite table and I own one now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had Dark Stalkers, we had KOF 94, and a bunch of other machines that I usually ignored.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt says yeah I remember when 7-Elevens had arcade games here and I was going to say it wasn't a 7-Eleven but the same type of thing a little convenience store chain was one of the first places I played Mortal Kombat 2 good times 7-Eleven actually went out of business in Alabama a long time ago I was really surprised when I moved out here and saw 7-Elevens but I would go to any one of them and there would always be some sort of game whether it worked or not was another story but there would be a game there
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now you can find good arcade machines, though, at TrekStops.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found Derby Owner's Club at TrekStops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, Rob D., we've been on the phone a while now, so I've got to ask you so we can get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any last thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Any other things you want to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh... How I dunk!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just end it there.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, have a good one, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you guys later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess he was getting some bad echo on the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how that happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happened, happened, happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: You can give us a call if you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what was that story you were going to read for us earlier?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, apparently there's some really cool mods, character mods you can have for the PlayStation 3 version, or actually the PC version also of Unreal Tournament 3, including Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also have the guy from Crysis.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also some, of course, Marcus Fenix and Cloud...
[SPEAKER_09]: and Spawn.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually, the one for Halo, I gotta say, looks better than the Xbox 360 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, sweet Jesus, I finally got in.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's DJ Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, DJ Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was surprised y'all guys didn't talk about Guitar Hero DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: We did.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might have arrived late to the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was early in Part A.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I remember I saw a peripheral about it, and all I could think of is, ugh, major cramps for that game, I swear.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's going to be just like you're holding the guitar, usually, but I think it would be very comfortable, actually, because the keys are sideways.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not like on top.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would cramp your hands, but your hand actually slides through like a little Velcro holder thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It still looks like a carpal tunnel nightmare to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, like I said, it'll probably work out, but just me, I know in my case, the way my hands are, I know it's not going to work too well for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was thinking about something else that totally slipped my mind because that was the main thing I wanted to talk about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Talk about the live 365 thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That does suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: That does suck major balls, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucks and it's nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hearing from people who are offering to help pay for the increased fees and all that, which I think is really nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want everybody to understand part of the reason that we're leaving is because we disagree with the rate increase of such significance and the fact that
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's just time for the station to have a kick in the butt and try something a little different.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we've been doing it the same way for five and a half years.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're just trying to see the positives in what is kind of otherwise a depressing thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know it's really going to suck because it displaces our weeknight shows, at least for right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we're hoping we can take them with us wherever we end up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, it's going to be some growing pains.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm hoping in the long run it actually ends up as a good thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I gotta say, if you ever need a spot for Shoutcast, we got lines open.
[SPEAKER_02]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know a lot of people are saying Shoutcast, and it's definitely a possibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have ideas, and we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: The thing about Shoutcast, too, is you gotta pay for music licensing if we were gonna do something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, we're all in video game music.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think no matter what happens, unfortunately, we're gonna have to get rid of our licensed music in terms of
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it comes to video game music, it feels differently to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think, you know, it seems like a different realm.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would go underground with video game music.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we'd be okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I said, good luck on that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I said, other than that, though, of course, me being the Phantasy Star Universe fanatic that I'm finally back on the game and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's officially White Day in the game and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I keep meaning to sign on and just kind of like play around in Phantasy Star Universe and see if I, I don't know, like it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I keep getting sidetracked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid WoW and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Gary said you can't really enjoy it unless you get the expansion, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once you get the expansion, then yeah, you can enjoy the newer stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean, if you still just have the basic ones, you won't be able to do all the new stuff and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Expansion is what?
$20?
$15?
$20? $20?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know on live you can download it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I have to uninstall it.
[SPEAKER_02]: 40 bucks?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, like I said, I still play that game because it keeps me from playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the only game I play on my PlayStation 2 now.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the sad part.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't play anything else on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else you want to share, Dark Knight, with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But permission to plug?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, hell, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we like you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of blend my voice to two shows on a radio station called This Is Genius Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: One is my show called DJ Dark Knight's Ninja Dojo.
[SPEAKER_08]: And another one is called Anime Damashii on there, which is hosted by the Rob D, me, Foodie Monster.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I guess the others, which is basically anime podcast shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tune in if you like.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got a podcast out and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy your Easter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Talk to y'all later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: One more call?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll do one more call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uno mas.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we are going to be doing a break from live broadcasting for a little while and going to tape, we will be sure to have more time for calls next week as we say goodbye to Life Thieves 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because believe it or not, next week is going to be our last show on Life Thieves 5, no matter what.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of odd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of scary, in a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why Loki's attitude.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have any other last minute stories for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, this week in the U.S., Virtual Console will be getting King's Night on the NES and Powerball on Genesis.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what either one of those are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, that was something else.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm saving it for later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, what have we got here?
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently some idiot is working on Mac OS X or something that resembles Mac OS X for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's some homebrew thing that someone made apparently that will remove duplicate channels that you may have from playing import games.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: Some rumors from EGM, including Tecmo Bowl is heading to the Wii, and the classic version of the game is coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently Warren Spector's new Disney project that he's working on is a platformer, and the goal is to give Mario a run for his money.
[SPEAKER_09]: The star of the big platformer would be none other than Mickey Mouse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're actually going to go ahead and close the Skype line because I just realized we are running a little bit long.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's already midnight on the East Coast, 9 o'clock here, so we'll take plenty more calls next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go ahead and go around and get everybody's final thoughts, though, in the meantime, because we're about ready to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, DarkSakura, your final thought for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Milkshake.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is I would really like my appetite back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is this chair is really uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, if I can find another fluffy chair like DarkSakura's for cheap, I'll get one of those.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is metal, and that's why I keep standing up, because it... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: and help Independent Radio break through because we don't have advertising dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have big magazines behind us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have any of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So until next time, my name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: And together, we are Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production For more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!