[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday evening, March the 2nd of 2008, where we're taping episode number 269 of Orange Lounge Radio live, as we do here every Sunday night, at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: In part A, you missed a whole bunch of Sony news.
[SPEAKER_03]: We talked about Metal Gear Solid 4, some of the new bundles that are coming out, the departure of Phil Harrison, just a lot of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we're going to get into some Nintendo news in this segment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, of course, like most things, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: We Date, but that doesn't mean that retailers haven't figured out when it's coming out, including such wonderful websites as Gamefly, GameStop, Circuit City, and I think a few others, have it listed as April 27th, that's two days before Grand Theft Auto 4, and that would also be a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this going to happen or not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think they're doing that to specifically get the jump on Grand Theft Auto 4?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or is it kind of one of those, eh, I don't really have a clue.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're going to be out of, you know, they need to press them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need to have enough time to press those discs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, the other thing that's really going to hamper that game is the production of those fucking wheels.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's absolutely retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you were a bet,
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good odds on that bet.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, maybe one thing that the game has been put, because it was originally supposed to come out late last year, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't it originally a Christmas release that got put back a little bit?
[SPEAKER_03]: Something like that, our first quarter?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyhow, perhaps one reason they pushed it back is because, guess what, guys?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Kart Wii, it looks like Nintendo has finally caught on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Kart Wii is going to have online chat in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Xbox has been doing this for years, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Kart Wii will be supporting online text chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll be able to send text messages to your friends over Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Provided that they are on your friends list, you have their friend codes and all that stuff, you will be able to text.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do it before matches.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's assumed you can do it after matches.
[SPEAKER_03]: or, you know, Good Game and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, for real?
[SPEAKER_03]: For real.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's not like as cool as you would think.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's their way, I think, of trying to control the game right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the Disney MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, the news must have changed slightly since the initial release that IGN did or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, okay, so now it's been... It's like the Disney MMOs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, if you've ever played, what is that, Toontown, I think it is?
[SPEAKER_03]: You only have a list of preselected phrases you can use.
[SPEAKER_03]: SAD, SAD, SAD
[SPEAKER_03]: RansteelUT, their names are very similar tonight, I think that's Ranma under another name, RansteelUT says, text chat, better than hearing F-M-G and N-I-M-E-R and all that stuff while playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think that, in one respect I think it's a good idea, you know, because they are trying to make an effort to protect
[SPEAKER_04]: Their intended group, I should say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which was why, you know, Publins just needed the same thing with theirs, because they don't want something with their name on it, for lack of a better description, corrupted by the people playing it, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, in that way, I think it was smart.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just plain waste, damn safe, that's all it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and Ran still, if he continues in our chatroom, chat.roman.com, but if you're playing online with friends, then you should be allowed to say whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I would like to see a mode where, you know, okay, yeah, maybe it's off by default, but maybe I can go in there and turn it on or something, where, you know, if I want to call my friends gay while I'm playing, I should have the right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's a thought, I don't know, maybe filter the obscenities.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, that's so hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, it's stupid is what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's absolutely stupid that you should jump through all these hoops to just friggin' play the game with your friends, and then after all that stuff, why even include text chat?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, basically, as so they can put a big sticker on the box, supports online chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: As to, yeah, IGN did a report on this, and basically, you know, selected limited selections, automated statements, or responses while playing the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, hello, I'm sad, I'd say welcome, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: RossDLUT asks, and yes, this time it is RossDLUT, asks in chat room, why even make the stupid game online?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, for me, it's kind of like the DS games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, how often do you go on a DS game and somebody is already there online waiting for you?
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: You prearrange those matches over the internet on AIM, or you prearrange them over the telephone.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm thinking, fire up, guys, there's voice chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here's another thought, and this is the kind of,
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, supporting that feature, because this may be also the chat with the other people, not necessarily your friends that you're playing with as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wish they would also have normal chatting in there as well on top of this stuff, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking at the Justin TV chat for a minute and usually I don't take a chance to read it, but our old buddy Akuma JP is in there and says, type while driving better.
[SPEAKER_03]: As if talking on your cell phone while driving wasn't bad enough, now you can type while driving.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, well, it's a wee remote, you know, you really only need one hand to kind of do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I put on my makeup while I drive too?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, that'd be an awesome one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woman driver of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, drag queen driver.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that's better.
[SPEAKER_04]: That has to be kind of hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to put on your makeup and your stilettos while you're trying to drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Put on your furry costume on the way there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And change the radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Mr. DJ.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we move on, please?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, something that is actually fairly cool about Mario Kart Wii is that there is an 8-finger fast mode, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it looks like you'll be able to...
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait for Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm more excited about this game than Brawl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm not really into the fighting games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart, I love Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought every game system or every Nintendo system for Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, even Double Dash?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I even bought Double Dash.
[SPEAKER_03]: But did you like Double Dash?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Battle Mode in Double Dash really sucks balls, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, sorry, Jamie, but what do you think of 8-Player Battle Mode?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, is that a game-selling thing for you, or?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I was probably going to get it anyway, but I think that that's very cool, especially since I know enough people who have a Wii to facilitate that much play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wish it would, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was thinking what you could do is have a laptop in with Ventriload.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then do your snack talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I don't, like, for me, my computer is all the way out here in the dungeon, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_03]: garage, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_03]: OLR makeshift studio, and then the Wii is all the way in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I can't really do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just here for myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got my laptop.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got your MacBook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you come over and set that all up?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's too many wires.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I can get the Best Buy people to install it for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's what I wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were like, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did we cover that story?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it got cut from the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: At Best Buy, there was a sticker on an Xbox 360 game that said, have Geek Squad install this game on your Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just somebody got sticker happy and put stickers on the wrong things.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eject, put the game in, drop it down, push eject button again, game goes in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that'll be $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, maybe the PlayStation 3 installation, that might be something because it takes so long for some of those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well we'll be battling it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my full cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a game that I played a while back, and I think maybe during one of these shows back at our old apartment we were off, but it's a game called Defend Your Castle.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little flash game where you defend your castle against stick figures, and you get archers and all sorts of things to defend them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, basically what you do is you use your mouse to throw the stick figures away to keep them away from your castle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now this is going to be coming to the WiiWare service as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually going to be completely from the ground up, and it's only $5 for 500 Wii Points, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, they've built some new features into it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently, unlimited levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love games like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The old school Atari 2600 games never ended.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Kaboom.
[SPEAKER_03]: It didn't end until something was Kaboom.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was no ending.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was going faster.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another game that they've already announced coming to the service a while back was Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles My Life as a
[SPEAKER_03]: Wee Point, and we'll be joining some other games as well, including, of course, Defender, Castle, and this one didn't make the list, but the major league eating the game, which looks like a piece of shit, and that will be But that's not what you're eating.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not a piece of shit that you're eating, but the game looks like looks like pooey.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like dump on your wee.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one likes dump on their wee.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never heard poo like an adjective, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's coming out May
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about that, but they need to figure out something with the whole Wii memory shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if you can put these on
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to think that maybe they can do an upgrade right when the WiiWare comes out and then you can start using flashcards, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing that Nintendo can get right, though, is the peripherals, I mean, they will crank out those Wii wheels for Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing, though, that's kind of weird, is that it will actually be sold separately other places.
[SPEAKER_03]: Famitsu over in Japan has revealed that Nintendo is going to be selling the Wii wheels separately for about $11.
[SPEAKER_03]: No word yet if we're going to get that separately as well, but you know that if Nintendo doesn't officially put them out themselves, which they probably will,
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to have third-party developers of the Wazoo doing this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it does kind of make sense to have the separate Wii wheels because, you know, the same reason you have separate DDR pads.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes you want to play two-player.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will be coming out separately here at the same time as Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know this to be fact.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there you have it then.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's the same reason why because little Screaming Billy wants fucking, you know, his own wheel.
[SPEAKER_03]: He doesn't want to share it with his sister or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: He has to buy two fucking plastic wheels.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just plastic wheels, folks, and seriously, you can buy them now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, just third-party things, and it's completely, absolutely useless.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you don't need this thing to play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love this.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is my favorite comment in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob says, guys, save that the DDR pad has functionality and the Wii is a dumbass wheel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just like the fact that this game controls with as many
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTsuyu says, I wish there was a wheel that let the Wiimote fit vertically so I could use it on Need for Speed Carbon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's the thing, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the other thing that pisses me off about this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you've ever played one of these games that uses the wheels sideways like Mario Kart does or like, say, like some of these other games that use the wheels, it's really
[SPEAKER_03]: In related news, I still kinda like Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they need to fucking make a new one!
[SPEAKER_03]: My wife has finished the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the love of God, give Loki's wife a game to get excited about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make poor tracks if you don't want to make a new game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will buy them for whatever price you want to charge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just need some more Excite Trucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to have to buy Motorstorm 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1 wasn't very impressive.
[SPEAKER_03]: That and custom soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Excite Truck was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can understand Excite Truck, that's fine, because that game really does need custom soundtracks, but Endless Ocean, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need custom soundtracks in that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't swim through the ocean and rob zombies.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's too slow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excite Truck is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could play through Excite Truck for the multi, not only the long.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's funny, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time I hear a Justin Timberlake song now, I think of Excite Truck, and, you know, I used to play it to, like, you know, really cool shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, that thing is hilarious, that commercial.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if they were to do, like, a different type of vehicle for an Excite something game?
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as they just say, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excite Boat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excite ATV.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be Moon Frasier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excite ATV on the Moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they didn't have a space level.
[SPEAKER_03]: You remember Nebula?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, it's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we've turned in our most current news thing about Mario Kart Wii into Excite Truck Remedy thing somehow, so
[SPEAKER_04]: I have some Wii-related stuff, only it's more for a virtual console, and specifically for our friends in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: The games that are coming out this week from HAL region is Super Turrican, that was the Super Nintendo game, and Psychosis, that was on the TurboGrafx-16.
[SPEAKER_04]: Factor 5 made Super Turrican.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's 800 points.
[SPEAKER_04]: It uses the classic and GameCube controller in Psychosis.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's set under B-Point and it also uses the classic and cube heads and also uses the V-Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for anyone who hasn't heard of Psychosis, because I know that TurboGrafx tends to be on the obscure end, it's a side-scrolling shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also position satellites around your ship and kill stuff with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Killing with satellites is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray, killing!
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you don't want to mod your Wii, there are other options now for you to be able to play in-court games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks to the freeloader, of course you may remember that from the GameCube as being able to play wonderful in-court games then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kojilskis is now offering a freeloader for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to do a bunch of other things, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be for $19.99 in the U.S., U.K.
[SPEAKER_03]: for $9.99 pounds, I believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's going to allow a couple different things to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: One, it will stop any updates that are on the game disc so you don't end up with duplicate channels.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you import stuff, that's kind of what happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a big deal, but annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it will also be kind of invisible to your console so that, you know, they hope that there will be no updates to destroy it like they did with the GameCube one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is available now, and hopefully it won't be broken soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, we had a little bit of controversy last week, and I'm sure it's going to continue on into our Mailbag and Skype segments this week, but would you say there is a legitimate, non-shady purpose for this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like on my GameCube, I had Phil Caliber 2, and I also had one of the Battletoe Fighters.
[SPEAKER_04]: you know, back before they decided to release them, all of them over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if this was more like, you know, the DS or something like that, where it was region-free, I think you'd see a lot more people buying games for other reasons, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my crowd, or here's my question to the crowd, about, you know, because we had kind of two different, very opposite sides talking about whole modding and all that stuff last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: My question is, to the people that are not, that do not support mod chips and piracy and all that stuff, is the freeloader ethical?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my question.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, are you okay with the freeloader?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seeing that there is a very legitimate purpose to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would think so because you can't pirate games with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, as far as we're aware, I mean, you can't pirate games with it, but... Is it one of those it's just a matter of time things?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, with the freeloader, I mean, I don't think... He can change the region on it, so... Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, because it's obviously tricking the console into thinking something that, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: My thing would be, like I said, you know, because now we're getting these staggered release dates, you know, like Mario Kart in the UK is coming out, you know, a couple weeks before, you know, the US release.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you really wanted to, you could actually get that name early in English and be able to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ross DLUT says, well, if you can't pirate games, then by all means.
[SPEAKER_03]: Son of Dad says, yes, I just want to play the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Janai says, yes, I want to play all games no matter what.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another thing, too, that actually was mentioned on the blurb on the freeloader sales area, was that for people who have non-region systems, that this is a way to play local games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I've, you know, I actually have key friends who, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm sure we'll be hearing some feedback with some of our listeners, because I know we have a lot of listeners that are into import gaming, because we're one of the fewer gaming podcasts that actually cover kind of the import scene outside of just America, so I'm kind of curious what one of our listeners, some of our listeners should use this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you getting one, Loki, or are you not bothering to get one?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not bothering, but I have a bodship, so... DarkSakura, you are thinking of getting one, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am going to get one next payday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me know what you think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because, I mean, there's... I don't have any import games, because that's not except for my game people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for borrowing this match, brother.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get into import games enough to get one.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only import game I've ever really gone crazy for was BVNia 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said you forget crazy all the time on PS2, but you know, even a little quick thing is, you know I had to get Bust Move back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I actually had a Japanese PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if it worked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a Japanese Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: For some reason I decided that Wangan Midnight for the PS3, that was a mistake, and I thought, I won't import any more PS3 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it not good?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it play?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I played this fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've played Region 3 here, Region 3, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on, because speaking of the mailbag, I know we want to get there, and it's coming right up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But real quick, I want to give you one more Wii story, and that's about Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wii Fit has been given a price in Europe.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to buy the game in the UK, it's going to be $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking, I'm thinking, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd buy that for $89.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, in Europe, unfortunately, you are paying more for games usually.
[SPEAKER_03]: So while we might get it for $89.99, might get it for $89.99, we possibly will get it for $89.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys will have to pay $89.99, which is considerably more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to break it to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's open up the old mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love to hear from our listeners, and every week you guys email us at mailbag at orangelongradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura likes to dive in the mailbag headfirst and pull out some of her favorite emails, and she's going to read them right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my snorkel ready.
[SPEAKER_03]: And your rubber glove?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm wearing a snorkel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just in case it's by Ambrex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, can I draw?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I have, well, no, no, no, no, no, I have something far better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about bad 80s bands, not the, uh... I like Anthrax!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me, Anthrax and Public Enemy is like the best combination ever, hi!
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of great bands of the past, do you know what band really needs to, I've decided after all the commercials on TV, do you know what band really needs to come to Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to see the Lost Odyssey commercial with the White Rabbit music, it's pretty awesome
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why we don't have text chat in Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was wondering what other good games are on there that I should get.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks guys, you get me through the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, you did not get Super Metroid!
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was Alien Crush, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guardian, or Gunstar Heroes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gunstar Heroes, Alien Crush.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, your list needs more Sega.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that there was not enough Sega in the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was there more like 3 hours?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, yeah, I think they all are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Kart, 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe Mario Kart, like, yeah, there's another Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I bet there's something more Mario Kart we've got here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want Super Metroid now?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, chat room wanted to see if you would get this reference.
The bass line is opening the...
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't really like that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it does have a sweet bass word.
[SPEAKER_04]: The bass word is what made me think of that word, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did just see this really awful band, and we went outside, and their bass line, it was a band called 8-Bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: They weren't very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were rapping, wearing hazmat suits.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we were coming back from drinking at the Pyramid across the street.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is at the Gilman in Berkeley.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we came back and stood outside and their bass line was the Legend of Zelda theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their bass line was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were awful, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Babyland played that show, so Babyland, Ricky, did the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it seems like there's some head tracking popping up lately in console world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone keeps looking at Sony One at GEC and I'm surprised nobody knows what the track are that's been going around for years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have one and it works great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is only for the PC though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has six degrees of movement and you can use it as
[SPEAKER_04]: A mouse control that you can use with any game that doesn't have direct support for the track IR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really huge for racing and flight games.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is one FPS game that it does support, and that's from Pendragon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess this game should be used for Marvel Madness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heck yeah, that's a game we need to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or even better, to watch
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, DarkSakura, and Skye, with regards to the call in last episode about system hacking, I have to comment, true, if there was some of the content that it hacked from or allows you to play games without paying for them, even though this can be seen as wrong, I think that it's kind of funny that they can do this in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: But some of the firmware is better than the proper firmware.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, a Skype program is only for thin TFCs if they can get to work on 6 TFCs more power to them, as it is more fair if everything works on those systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, if they can get 3 games that people make to work as cool as handmade games are good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also believe that if you do stop talking about hacks, then you would miss out on a huge part of the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm just saying this only as a reply to the call, I know you won't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Secondly, you often talk about how the PlayStation 3 is a giant letdown, but I have to say this
[SPEAKER_04]: Fearplay, that there are a lot more games in the Xbox 360, but I am the only person in my group of friends to have a PS3, and I will think every single one of the others' Xboxes have three rings at one point or the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, keep up the good show and help Sky feel better, like Anna.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am feeling better.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, you do bring up an issue about the whole, you know, the firmwares definitely do serve a legitimate purpose.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's how kind of a lot of people get away with this and get them to the radar because there is a legitimate purpose for a lot of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think it just becomes a moral issue about how you choose to use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you choose to use it to get Skype on your PSP, which is free anyway, that whole thing, you know, I don't think that's as big of a moral problem, so to speak, as, you know, getting this on there so you can hacksore all the NES games from your past, or, you know, better yet, download all the PlayStation 1 games you always wanted to play and all that, or PSP games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, that's just a moral question.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying one's right or wrong, because there's a lot, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of people steal music like there's no tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's a lot of legitimate things that they've started in homebrew that I think Sony has saw and they're like, hey, let's throw that into an official release.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, for example, internet streaming radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's been available on the homebrew scene for a long time now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they, what, last up, they finally implemented some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of stuff that comes out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have YouTube stuff that you can view now straight on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had stuff that hooked up to your GPS a while back, even before they had the GPS for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now they're coming out with purple.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like tilt-centered stuff at Chromebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, you have the force.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's your choice if you wish to choose to turn to the dark side.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next email?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey OLR Crew, I was just emailing to give my side of the modding talk.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was apparently crucified simply for asking about the illegitimate question by Rosso UT Hold up, is this the email, this is the one that Rosso UT had called in to respond to last week, same person, I'm assuming?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, just curious, just wanted to get that out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, because he doesn't agree with modding, modchips are part of gaming culture and community just because they can
[SPEAKER_04]: What did I do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he must have typed this immediately.
[SPEAKER_03]: He probably typed this right as he was listening to the call.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, give it a little flex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not all of the people who did mod are people who sit behind our computers wearing ski masks trying to steal games from the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: People back up their DVDs and music CDs, so I've seen their reason why it's such a gray area when it comes to games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people use modchips to preserve their investments, others are interested in the technical aspect of it, and yet they are a group who simply wish to steal games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like hearing Loki's talk about him trying to fix his 360 and all the modifications he does to it, along with his V-Mod.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just part of gaming culture, and I'm glad OLR doesn't filter topics like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wish that someone would jump down the throat for people who are interested in modding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next time my $50 game gets destroyed out of my hands, I'll send you anti-modder for the bill.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Loki, you helped me a lot with your tips.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got my chip successfully installed so no more coasters for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Epic win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you feel better this week, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: This email is sponsored by the Olive Garden, home of the never-ending salads and breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to have Olive Garden night pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or some real Italian food for once.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can actually go to the Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just ate there a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally agree with what he's saying about that it is a part of gaming culture and that's what we're all about.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why we need to cover it on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he made some good points.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the cog made some good points.
[SPEAKER_03]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here, I don't know, kind of taking it a step further, as long as this stuff continues, it's going to be interesting because I think the game industry has the potential to turn into almost kind of what the music industry is doing, where I think especially through things, that's why I said last week, I think that XNA thing is such huge news, because I think in the future you're going to start seeing a lot more download your games onto the, you know, and indie developers making things in-house that you download, you know, just kind of like music is turning into, where, you know, in
[SPEAKER_03]: More stuff is getting out there because of iTunes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, I think we're about five, maybe even ten years away from that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, anyhow, that's my ramble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, my little ramble.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no easy solution.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nothing any of us are going to say that's going to please both sides of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, though, we're doing a disservice by ignoring it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, ignoring it's not going to make it go away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, personally, I have no problem with that, that someone wants to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not my place to tell anybody what they can or can't do.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just up to them if they want to deal with the consequences of being caught.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, and here's one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Realize
[SPEAKER_03]: At any time, one of these companies may come up with a magic patch that's going to nerf your Wii if you mod it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's going to be no choice.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to have to install the thing to play the latest game or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's not just going to render the game in Apple.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to completely nerf your freaking Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your freaking iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your freaking iPhone and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's the chance you take.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someday your thing is going to get bricked.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, that's the chance you took.
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mary Allen.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: For me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Skye, Loki, and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm emailing on behalf of the semi-obliterated PS2 sitting in a bag in my room.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other day I arrived at school suspecting it would be like any other day when one of my friends informed me in his wisdom that the PS2 stopped working the previous afternoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, he took a hammer to the case and smashed it open.
[SPEAKER_04]: The irony here is that before the fan had only chipped a few teeth, and now the cage is bent forward, the metal things on the inside are bent and the laser may be broken, but I'm not sure, and one of the ribbons has been damaged.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've taken the console from him, and I was just wondering whether any of you know a good site that I could get spare parts from, and particularly if Loki knew a fairer way to test the laser.
[SPEAKER_04]: With love, Heart's Lonely Nagel.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you can order replacement parts from Tony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you could for the older stuff, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you can still order stuff from him.
[SPEAKER_03]: but I was going to say, I don't know, the only way to test the laser I would think is to put a game in it and actually test it.
[SPEAKER_03]: For spare parts though, you might be able to check out llama.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've gotten some Xbox 360 mod stuff from there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if they carry Playstation 2 stuff anymore, I think they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do they have like official, I'm sorry, did they have like official Sony repair centers like they have for some other types of products?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, maybe there's a place you can take your PS2 and get just the laser thingy tweaked?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: How old, I'm sorry, I might have missed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: How old did you say the PlayStation 2 was?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you say it was like an old school one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, maybe they did not say.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if it's one of the old school, you know, huge, uh, you know, PlayStation 2s, the old model, it might just be time, because obviously by the time you fix some of this stuff, you're practically paying what you pay for a PS2 mini.
[SPEAKER_04]: People put broken ones on eBay, though, too, don't they?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can, I mean, they're kind of getting cheap now, and you can probably find a cheap PS2 for, you know, nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean... Let's test the theory.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the system isn't too bashed up, you can get it fixed at www.oldschoolgamer.ca, but that indicates it's Canadian.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that would work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's an example.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your cables and stuff, your ribbon cables, those are about $10,
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and then the lens is about $40.
[SPEAKER_03]: So right there at $50 is half the price of your PS2, mine is $5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm looking on, um, GameStop's website, and I need, I don't know, we can go and buy from GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, but the, um, the, the, uh, old style PS2 refurb is $79.99, so the new style is $99.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, and you'll, and if you find them at just the used ones, they'll be cheaper than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: and some of that is pointing out that Target was actually having a sale on PS2s last week for 99 new.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep an eye on those websites.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure that's not the answer you wanted to hear that we're telling you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, go buy a new PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: But keep an eye on those websites like CheapAssGamer and some of those other video game deals websites too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once in a while something might pop up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, always keep an eye on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you do want to get your old system fixed,
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, there are ways that you might have to have a professional step in, or you're gonna void your warranty.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just might as well at this point just to buy a new one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there's a point you gotta say, well, it's expensive to fix it, just buy a new one.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, uh, Ross, CLUT, and Chaperones have a good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, what if he's a Final Fantasy XI player, then EPS2 won't support the HDD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then buy an older one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And quit Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, you gotta go with PC version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: More email?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I was a controller player on this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how you even play that game on controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just call me Joy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I just, and it was designed for controllers, the hilarious thing, but I cannot play that game on anything but a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: The macros are so easy with triggers.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're really easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, hang on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, hey everyone, before I begin, there's a couple things I must say.
[SPEAKER_04]: First of all, hail Jamie Worship.
Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Baja.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got me some new shoes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Secondly, I want to say that I look forward to each episode of Sunday Night and the podcasts that get me through my daily commute to and from work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that the formalities are out of the way, just let me say this.
[SPEAKER_04]: As I listen to Roscoe UT's Thoughts on Mining, I can tell that you, Rob, weren't too happy about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can tell in your voice that you...
[SPEAKER_04]: weren't that happy about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me just say that my PS2 has been modded for three plus years.
[SPEAKER_04]: During that time, I have over a thousand dollars worth of bootleg games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Simply put, I do not have the money to shell out each week to buy these titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all isn't lost.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the positive side, playing copied games allowed me the chance to play and try out some of the games and see if I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, no one here wants to drop 40 bucks on a PS2 game and find out later that the game sucks and it's a waste.
[SPEAKER_04]: Having a modded console allows me to check out imported games as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I write this, I tend to think of myself as a hypocrite because my real substance is to fix some computers with bootleg software.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tell customers not to use bootleg enterprise corporate software as well as software that belongs to a friend of theirs, but alas, some will not listen, and unlike also UT, I do not take this to heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Overall, I do not see a problem with modding consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mods allow us to break things with consoles, not just copies slash burned games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if I download a game that's really good and I would go out and buy it, case in point, Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a friend who is in the gaming industry that gives me grief about copy games, to say that, I say to her, are you going to buy me this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, I want to see if the game is actually worth buying.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if it is, I'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, leave me be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Overall,
[SPEAKER_04]: Roughly Pete, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leave us modders alone.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are not damaging the gaming industry at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: From my knowledge, there's no proof of that as either.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's usually what it comes down to, and this is the same argument with MP3 downloading and stuff like that, is everyone... That's the recycle thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just the recycle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's not that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just people...
[SPEAKER_03]: The industry doesn't actually lose money from these people because these people are never going to buy the product in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you didn't miss out on a sale because they were never going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same with people downloading import games or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They weren't going to buy it in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the modern thinking is it's not going to hurt anybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, obviously, still, they could import it and spend the money and do that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's immoral, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: is it really hurting the industry?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, not quite, I don't know, I mean stuff like say for example a lot of people are burning copies of Halo 3 or something like that, yeah that's going to hurt the sales of that game, especially if they were intending on buying it in the first place, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why a lot of companies
[SPEAKER_03]: And here's another thing, maybe, you know, people will respect your games more, like, you know, stop putting out shovelware.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looking at you, Destineer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, and just to address the part of the letter that talked about me, uh, getting kind of, um, I don't know what he said about the call, but I was... He didn't seem happy about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't seem happy about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing, well, A, I was sick last week, so cut me some slack, and so that kind of, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: Lens My Sense of Professionalism
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of knew.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's interesting in a way, it's part of the charm of the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We open up the sky's line, anybody can call about anything, you don't know what it's going to be, and we're going to deal with it and talk about it on air.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of part of what makes the show unique.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when the call came in, I kind of knew that it was opening a can of worms, and that's why I wasn't happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that I wasn't happy with the opinion or whatever, I wasn't happy because I was just kind of like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh boy, I know there's going to be emails on this next week, and probably some more calls later on tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if this was an epic battle I was awaiting.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rest of this email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for reading my letter on air, and Rob, I apologize for using your show to call out a fellow OLR listener, but I do not reject and allow a travesty of a comment of rawful UT's to go by unnoticed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock on and have a most triumphant week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's DJ Ranma S. P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: If roughly you two want to comment back, by all means, my email, Addie, is listed, and I guess you can P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they're both in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hug it out, boys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hug it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he wants me to plug his podcast, so I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anime Jam Session at DJRanmaS.net slash Anime Jam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go listen to it, but not right now, because we're live.
All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any other emails, or was that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, dang, we've got talent emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's get through them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, OLR crew, I have a question for DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said months ago that you put Pump Up the Volume on hold after your laptop got fried.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was after my PC got fried.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is that coming along?
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be great to listen to Pump Up the Volume again someday.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's nice break from what the 24-7 stream provides on GS68.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, there's progress in this today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a computer that I could use, but the problem is that I want something with a bit more on the graphic capabilities side, just for the sake of all the other projects I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I have been using my laptop, but my laptop likes to run really friggin' slow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'm actually going to replace all the memory in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we have gutted out one of the VAIOs sitting in our garage.
[SPEAKER_04]: And although one of them is promised, that sort of leaves the other one up in the air because it might be promised as well, we are looking into putting a VAMP graphics card in it, my old hard drive, basically building a frankie-cooter for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That wasn't, you know, what my old computer was, sort of a Frankenstein of parts, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pump Up the Volume, it all goes to plan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking for a return of Pump Up the Volume soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I'm also going back to college, which I don't know if I've mentioned to my co-hosts here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I am planning on going back to school and I'm finishing a degree this year and finishing one next year too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am a year away from an AA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm another year away from another AA.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I can gloat.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, for those that may not know, because we do have the podcast, but when she speaks to Pump Up the Volume, she's talking about one of her weeknight shows.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was last night, and it didn't stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we do have a couple of weeknight shows, just a handful right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've got to be honest, if I didn't have a full-time job, just trying to manage all that stuff is difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We may soon try to hire for the pay is great, nothing, but some type of director of weeknight programming that could get some of these great podcasts that deserve to be heard on the live stream.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to try to sort that all out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then we have our website needs to get updated too much time.
[SPEAKER_03]: No time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, good news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheeseburger is taking our advice.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, buying Super Mentor?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Swell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, one more email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dun dun dun.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is worth it, because this is our buddy, Warrior Bob.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, emailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so good to hear you mentioning the old Apogee and Epic software games last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brings back good memories from times when computer games looked like computer games.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a topic that's been coming up recently in looks to my friends and me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back when these games were the forefront of computer entertainment, back when Windows had version numbers, PR made adventure games and Duke Nukem games were named after the development time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a certain look and feel to computer games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Visual animations and effects were the product of teams of technical artists so much as they were the result of clever programming tricks done by empty people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Things like single pixel particle effects, characters made of multiple sprites, color cycling distortions, that sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel that it's kind of gone now and I realize I missed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong, I love the new ideas too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to see games like Shadows of Clocks and Rock Band ever since I was a little kid with a bunch of game design scribbles in my notebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time, the only recent game I can think of that had the same computerized feel I grew up on was Cave Story, a freeware indie title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Entrenched as you all are in the video game scene, have you come across any games that still embody this aesthetic?
[SPEAKER_04]: I find I play games more for the experience than the challenge these days.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I'd love to find something like this and see what people with new ideas have done with old styles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks again, as always.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep up the excellent show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Warrior Bob.
[SPEAKER_04]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess he meant that for my hoodie.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was supposed to be on the show this week, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why I think he put that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, and the head didn't come, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my crazy thought, is that they don't make these games anymore because they just didn't sell?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to say this, is that, and for lack of a, you know, I'm not trying to be mean to anybody, but honestly, the market today is a lot more fickle.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want it to look pretty, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't care as much about the game, you know, the way the game plays.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't care as much about the experience of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want it to be pretty, and automatically, if it's not pretty, it's shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's what's happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're playing to a superficial market.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you're kind of right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that is kind of what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's when computer games kind of lost their distinctive look, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then I look at a game like Sam & Max and to me that game is like a, it's almost a throwback in a way.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is kind of like those old LucasArts games, but in a newer cartoony, visual-ish style.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, they're out there, but yeah, it's not like it used to be then.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember walking into Egghead Software and you'd have like, you know, Legend of Kyrandia and King's Quest and all this stuff for sale and
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, those were the days, but, you know, then again, a fake headstopper went out of business.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that tells me that, or at least they're online now or whatever, so that tells me that, you know, they just must not have been selling as well as consoles really took off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Kyra India.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me too!
[SPEAKER_03]: My sister still plays, in fact, she is playing King's Quest 7 right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you what was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is, uh, I can't very close to downloading money.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's people who still do them.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's BBSs set up so people can play Legend of the Red Dragon still online, which is like hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: And The Pit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, we need an OLR BBS so we can play The Pit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what my first, I would have to say, real MMO was?
[SPEAKER_04]: Gemstone 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was all text.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, how can we set up an OLR BBS?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's going to be possible if we tell them that or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: How can we make that happen?
[SPEAKER_01]: That shouldn't be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody email me if you know how to make that happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't think that would be too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, it's all on our BBS.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to play The Pit with our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be bomb.
[SPEAKER_03]: Warrior Bob is actually in chat right now and says, see, yeah, that's just it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Famimax looks like a new 3D game.
[SPEAKER_03]: No big pixels or clever animation anywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, I think just the market big pixels didn't sell, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, if you want
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm playing Ragnarok online, and honestly, I've read up on Ragnarok 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And while, yeah, it's cool facial animation, I like my cutesy sprites.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that I can play it on a system that I'll have to have a whole bunch of crap for, because it still plays pretty damn fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I like Lume.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Lume.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lume is such a good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lume.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I miss my old, um, pixel-y, um, games like Doom and Hexen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Hexen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've covered Hexen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's it for now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get a piece of the war.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dang it, there was a lot of mailbags this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mailbag to OrangeLawnTrader.com is the place to send your emails.
Get them!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: The segment's running low tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, that would be News Witness.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this whole Activision Blizzard merger thing happened a little bit ago, you know, when they merged with NVIDIA.
[SPEAKER_03]: And because of that, some investors think that they're getting the bum end of the deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in fact, actually, it's an Activision investor who sued over the entire merger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their complaint was that NVIDIA actually comes out on top of the merger with a 50% majority ownership of Activision.
[SPEAKER_03]: And because of this, didn't think of the stockholders, or didn't think of the stockholders when they accepted the deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that is their complaint, and now they're pissed off about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I mean, shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we must live in a sue happy world because that wasn't the only lawsuit that happened this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Capcom officially got sued by the MKR Group.
[SPEAKER_03]: over the game Dead Rising because the MKR group, they own the rights to the movie Dawn of the Dead by George Romero.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even though Dead Rising has a big old thing on it that says not Dawn of the Dead, essentially, I can't come back to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's interesting because I don't think they're going to win because of the fact that, I mean, can they really do 4 AM?
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're zombies in a mall is a very narrow market.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's just not room for both.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the lawsuit states, quote, in both, that the recreational activities of the zombies and absurdly grotesque kill scenes provide unexpected comedic relief.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I kind of agree with what most of the people in chat are saying, is that they're zombies and they're in a mall.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the characters aren't the same, the plot's not really the same, it's just zombies in a mall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here's my other thought, is that if Capcom hadn't put that thing on the box that says it has nothing to do with Dawn of the Dead, do you think they would have gotten sued in the first place?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because my thing is that by putting that thing on there, it's almost like they admit, yeah, there's a similarity here, but we don't intend it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: because then they could claim that they were trying to trick the consumer into thinking it was a Dawn of the Dead type thing, but this is just them kind of trying to, they were trying to be preventative about it and cover their ass saying, no, this is not what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: They think it's one more than Dawn of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my other thing, is that, I mean, if somebody buys Dead Rising, are they not going to buy Dawn of the Dead?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, is that, and because, you know, to sort of,
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100 Matt says, why can't they make something original like zombies eating someone's neighbors?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well the next game supposedly wasn't going to be in a mall.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not Zombies on a Plane, Zombies on a Train?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zombies on Moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, exactly, Zombies on Moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyway, this whole Sue happy world we live in just makes me angsty, and people just need to get over themselves, so I think we need to
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a big SU toward drama and death.
[SPEAKER_04]: And tragedy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have friends that are going through some crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a big SU to the crap they're going through and the sources of said crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a pretty heavy FU though, so not that I'm wanting there to be more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to Microsoft, and you know, kind of a little bit of rant.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure everybody's heard about the digital rights management, how it's all fucked up, where you have a console that's basically free-ringed on you, and content you purchased on there, now you can no longer use on your new console unless you're logged in live.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really retarded that they do that in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've had that problem because, of course, I have a new console, even though I fixed my old console, and it's funny, it still doesn't work on my old console now either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Why hasn't there been a lawsuit over that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't seem actually legitimate that they can have a lawsuit over it instead of complaining about live outages or the three rings of death or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that they should sue them over this digital rights management stuff because if you've got content
[SPEAKER_03]: OnLive, and now you can't use it because your system broke because they're faulty, and Microsoft isn't doing anything about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's countless stories on the internet about this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, why isn't anyone suing them over that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to give an FU to the antibiotic I'm on this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Levvaquim or Leptixim or I don't know what it's called.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some antibiotic the doctor gave me.
[SPEAKER_03]: A, it's a brand name drug, so I have to pay more for it because they don't make a generic of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And B, it's the slowest antibiotic I've ever had.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm allergic to penicillin, so also FU to the fact that I'm allergic to penicillin because then I can just take that and I'd be better in no time.
[SPEAKER_03]: but the antibiotic I'm on now is the slowest one I've ever taken and it was more expensive than C-Pro or any of the other ones I've taken before that are just fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know you're not supposed to take the same antibiotic as any buildup of an antibody, blah blah blah, but... No, we just now have a drug-resistant bacteria.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Lepoquine?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what the hell it's called, I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, F-U to my slow antibiotic, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's all my FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you can go, Jamie.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I love Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you don't love Sega, you probably have something wrong with your head.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, this is good news for people, is that Sega Superstars Tennis will be a week early.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was supposed to be on March 20th, and it's going to be out a week before that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you have minigames, and basically it's Virtua Tennis.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has achievements on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're named after older Sega games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can play as a bunch of the Sega geeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, actually, it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: No real clear answer on what exactly he's working on.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to be competing, obviously, with World of Warcraft and it's unavoidable that the social and massively multiplayer games have become important.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, I don't know, very vague on what he's working on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, new multiplayer game, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: What it is, no idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't he like retire from the industry or something and he opened up his restaurant?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, he just went and bought a pizza time theater, which was Chuck E. Cheese and Showtime.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: He had also a project anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: They joke though in the article that it's massively multiplayer online pong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that would be possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the drug is called Levaquin.
[SPEAKER_03]: I looked it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I just realized it's non-formulary.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I paid so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I have to get my doctor to try to prescribe me something that I wasn't paying too much money for.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I just had to get that out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares about Ponguy's MMO?
[SPEAKER_03]: Although Chuck E. Cheese is kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you been to a Chuck E. Cheese lately?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're really horrible now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a big theater room.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was this room that looked like a foyer to the bathroom that had glowing walls and shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It had hands and feet on the walls that would clap, and it had a party room with hippopotamus chickens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you ever been to Bullwinkle's in the Bay Area?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the old school Chuck E. Cheese's.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how big goal ankles of a chain they are, but you know
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess Rocky and Rowling aren't that popular.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of want to go check it out now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see if they're still even open.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, as always, John's Incredibly Shitty Dita.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I like some of their pizza.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a funny name.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a bad place.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I really like having rides inside of the place.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing I like seeing inside a place is Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, I haven't seen any yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you live in some places, they have been popping up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And over at Wired.com, they did a pretty lengthy...
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not both?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not though?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or do the old one on the Xbox, one on the Playstation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's always fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I missed the old Times Unlocked stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I've told this story before.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to work for an Amco arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when we had Tekken 3, it would be like, who's next?
[SPEAKER_04]: And have an outline of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And because I was keeping up with the overseas releases, I would come back and tell my boss who was next.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I found that they switched the order for
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope that they're going to have release characters in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do something like that, so you sort of have to guess who it is or anticipate something that would add a little bit more excitement to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, some new characters are already being spotted in Street Fighter 4 arcade machines that are out there in the wild in the testing region.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Sagat and Balrog have now shown up in the game, but only as bosses, like old school Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: You cannot select them on the main select screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And by Balrog, it's who we have in Vega over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure, because I believe it is Boxer Balrog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because one of these machines, I believe, is in North America, and that's where they gave this information from.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was looking at the little video.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're right, it's the US version.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_03]: There are some restaurants outside of California.
[SPEAKER_03]: One in Wilsonville, Oregon, Cary, North Carolina, Richmond, Virginia, Miamisburg, Ohio, and Irving, South Carolina.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a cool place.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, just wanted to say really quickly, all those screenshots you can see in Street Fighter 4, they all seem like they're in that upgraded version of the Chun-Li stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just so you know, there are some other battle locations out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's what's showing up.
[SPEAKER_03]: A drive-in at night, a beautiful bay in South Asia, and an inland jungle in South America.
[SPEAKER_03]: So some more battle regions are showing up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was looking at the movie that's up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Cybot vs. NGS and just watching how fluid it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really looks like it captured a lot of the old feel of the older games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll definitely be checking this out when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Arcade and console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I'll tell you something that I'm not at all excited about.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Road Rash.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I hate Road Rash.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my husband loves Road Rash.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: There has been a little bit let out that the Electronic Arts CEO is talking about doing another Road Rash, which is basically a game where you're on motorcycles beating each other up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like we had that scene in Final Fantasy 7, where you go and beat people up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, get a Road Rash, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, someone actually let a few things slip about it coming out, and that was actually Skid Row Sebastian Bach.
[SPEAKER_04]: At a classic metal show, he said that one of his recent songs is going to be in, and to quote, actually said, it's a super heavy song, it just got picked up for some video game, Road Rage or Road Rash or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, who would have thought that, like, a big scoop in gaming would have come from Sebastian Bach?
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um, EA actually said, um, uh, that Road Rash is not currently in development.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Road Rage, that's a whole different story.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, Sebastian Bach gets props for me because he was red.
[SPEAKER_04]: He did do a good job.
[SPEAKER_03]: By Nazis.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation Store as well from Capcom and looks like it's going to be available for 800 Microsoft points or $10 or just $10 in real money on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't heard too much about this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't look that great, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tread them, I believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be a special place in hell for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently, here's what's happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's this YouTube floating around, and there's this kid who got so excited because on Christmas Day, he opened up his presents under the tree, and he got an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: But unfortunately, here's what happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox 360 just was a box that was stuffed with clothes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the kids got clothes in an Xbox 360 box.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, there is video.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is so cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually haven't even watched it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It makes you want to cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Poor kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: He opens up the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a core system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you anyways, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm going to open it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's so excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is so wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Darketsuya in chat says, I forget which blog, but they suggested a pile of parenting books shaped like a car.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we wonder why our kids end up so screwed up in school.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fucked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I don't know if you've heard about the news on this, Engadget, they've offered to find the kid and they're going to give him a real Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: If he gets emancipated.
[SPEAKER_03]: I threw the last part in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fucked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: This kid's going to be in the news later on after playing the Xbox 360, later on he's going to kill his parents in the middle of the night because, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: You're fucked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she's like, oh, I can't afford an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet you're an asshole enough to go out there and find an empty Xbox 360 box to fill clothes with.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they put it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's just fucked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft says, man, those parents are douches.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frisbee says, look at me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a big man.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can laugh at my own kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, you're being awfully quiet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you've got a comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Disgusting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think there's anything at all funny about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is why we have kids that are just like, go to school and do dumb shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because their parents teach it to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, what's a kid gonna think?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: My parents are assholes.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what you're gonna think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless they just punked him with this and then like, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm wondering, is that maybe there's a second half where he actually got the Xbox later that none of us are seeing, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's all I have to say on that story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's just
[SPEAKER_04]: Penny Arcade Expo 10
[SPEAKER_04]: is going to be August 29th through 31st, 2008 with the DigiPen Institute of Technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're looking for 10 independent developers that want to do their games by attendees and media and publishers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's actually a panel of 50, I guess,
[SPEAKER_04]: The industry top people who will be selecting 10 submissions they consider are going to be the best based on gameplay and length factor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's also going to be one that the audience gets to vote on, an audience choice award.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the whole idea of bringing some independent stuff to the forefront.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Props to these folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would love to go to Penny Arcade Expo someday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe this will be my year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we're going to open up the Skype line very soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first, one more story.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know this story is going to come as a shock to people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this seriously breaking?
[SPEAKER_03]: A study has been done that shows men like video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shocking!
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely shocking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because this study, research that has been done by
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought men like fixed cars and went to baseball games and that's what men did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always thought video games were like a female thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doesn't Oprah bring video games on her show and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, but it says, you know, apparently...
[SPEAKER_03]: 34 Americans showed that among males, overall console gaming came in third behind using the internet and watching TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might add the internet and TV for both watching porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Among males 12 to 34, console gaming came in first and then dropped dramatically in older demographics.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be playing games until I die.
[SPEAKER_03]: The research shows women overall would rather talk on the phone, watch a DVD, listen to music, or read a book before playing console games.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is an odd spike among 24-year-old females for console gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Three web-based games did better with females, particularly among women of mature age.
[SPEAKER_03]: No real shocking revelations, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft in chat says, LOL stereotypes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Son of Pat says, where was masturbation on the list?
[SPEAKER_03]: That must have been number four.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that just isn't included with all the topics.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to understand, I do everything alphabetically, so it's Matt and then masturbation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Janai says, read a book, read a book.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking that, you know, there's probably a lot of women out there who like video games too, and I think there's also a lot of men who don't like video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that might be a shock for some people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we are going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR using Skype or Zones Radio, but first, we have some voicemails to catch up on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes when we're not live, some of the folks who like to listen to our podcast and so on, they like to leave us voicemails.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we want to get some of those out of the way real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to start with this one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't have a thing on your forums, but I'm known as Vaginator on the PlayStation Network, and I'm also known as Deere on Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just want to say, yes, guys, that's a great show.
[SPEAKER_00]: I kiss it every week.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I did have a couple questions to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: First of all, if you've ever seen any kind of rumors as to a sequel to Final Fantasy XI and could you provide any details if you know any?
[SPEAKER_00]: Secondly, I heard that Survival was a really great game and what not.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had something like 20 million players give or take.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the thing is though, I want to play it, but I don't have the PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is there any chance in hell that you'll be coming to consoles anytime soon?
[SPEAKER_00]: Specifically, PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_00]: If you don't, it'll be great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because right now my MMOs are really limited.
[SPEAKER_00]: Any advice you guys have would be great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much for the voicemail.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I'm thinking that where you're getting the impression that developers are working on the sequel is because it has come out that the people behind Final Fantasy XI, that team, is working on another MMO, but it hasn't been said what it is they're working on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think a lot of people are assuming it's Final Fantasy XI too, but I honestly think if they are going to make another MMO, it's not going to be Final Fantasy XIV or any of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they may make
[SPEAKER_03]: A new MMO with some of the same concepts.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would it sell as well without the Final Fantasy name?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: A Kingdom Hearts MMO?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's nothing out there concrete at this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can probably betcha that they'll try to crank at least one more expansion out of Final Fantasy XI before it's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know some people said this last one that came out, the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Not the time one, not Treasures of Otter again, but the one that just came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why can't I remember the name?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wings of the Goddess?
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wings of the Goddess.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of people said this is the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd think if they did like 12 expansions for EverQuest, they could get at least one more out of this, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least to hold the Final Fantasy XI fans over until the real sequel comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing concrete is that anything you hear out there is speculation alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: One more voice mail for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, it's Missy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Wednesday, and I'm waiting for my mom at work, so I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, I got the TFP script stuff for the holiday, so I thought I'd call, test it out, maybe be the first.
[SPEAKER_04]: I ordered a modem.
[SPEAKER_04]: It hasn't shipped yet, but it's shipping from Memphis, so when it does, it should get to me quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I miss you guys, plus, oh, and guess what I did on Sunday since I couldn't listen?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't have any questions up at the clock, even though it was 8 my time, so I ran an episode in my playlist and listened to it like I was listening to it live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't really recall the episode number of it,
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he had the reverse cage match in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should never happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure many of you know what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of paranoid that somebody's going to eject my computer while I'm not looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to go ahead and say bye, and with luck I should see y'all live Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_03]: Couple comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma says, sounds like she's walking and talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: SJ100 Matt says, is Misty the first PSP Sky caller?
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe she is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was trying to be number one, but I had the wrong... You got beat!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's definitely one reason I wanted to play that, is because that would be the first PSP call we've gotten.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I think that's really neat that she puts on the old episodes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do need to release more of the old episodes.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those projects I'll never get to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's open up the skyline for all y'all.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's now wide open for everybody to call in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio or our phone number 1-877-GAME-OL
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go ahead and take a call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi everyone, Tom's Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nah, just chilling right here recovering from the hickeys I got from clubbing last night.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that's besides the point.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just wanted to, you know, probably point out, you know, the whole clusterfuck that's basic, you know, that Nintendo has created as a result of their attempts to create an online multiplayer game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it got bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's bad enough when people, like, they have to wait in front of, like, 10, 20, 30 guys outside of Nintendo World every morning just to get to school a week.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, you know, you take it home, you realize that, you know, there's barely an online experience to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what about the children, Daku?
[SPEAKER_03]: What about the children?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's playing to the Disney vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the Soccer Mom vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: But who's buying weed, Zach?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's Soccer Mom?
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's your demographic.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they're playing the Disney card because, you know, think about what would happen if someone were to catch them off guard by trying to do something that allowed the other players to basically curse in a madness tangent like they did on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_00]: It would be a shitstorm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fox News for example would just spin the shit out of the Wii's image.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their eyes are being raped by the hideous voice chat inside Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do these rape your children tonight on Fox?
[SPEAKER_00]: If you're basically playing Mario Kart or, you know, voice chat or anything like that, the only thing I worry about is ActHeft.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, you know, ActHeft just ruining the experience for everyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the same time, you know, it's like, put me
[SPEAKER_03]: with Nintendo saying, no communication between strangers, period.
[SPEAKER_03]: But with this whole friend code thing, you know, I would think that, you know, once you have a friend code thing, you should be able, if you want to say fucking shit, you should be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right, I mean, I don't know, I guess I kind of, you know, I kind of go, you know, kind of basically take the way, if not, you know, go
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, yeah, that might be one thing, but I don't know if it would be enough to fill the fears of the software market.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, quick question, Zach, a quick question, then we've got to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68 says, and he's quoting something you said earlier in chat, he says, you say that Xbox Live, they say, you know, N-I-G, blah, blah, blah, F-A, blah, blah, blah, and all that they say on Xbox Live, yet you bitch about Nintendo's online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not enough, what's the answer?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, I mean, look, think about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, you can mute, in Xbox Live, I know you can mute people, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: And even though Nintendo is basically doing the mute for you, you don't even have that option to decide whether they're, like, rude, obnoxious players.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my last question for you, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: As much as you or I may hate to admit it, is this change, is this revelation about the online thing and Mario Kart Online, is it going to affect sales?
[SPEAKER_00]: I doubt it, I mean, most people, you know, most people will even, I doubt that many people will even take advantage of all, you know, the online features anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, some will, but I think it's more important in that sense that some people will share amongst friends, you know, with, you know, with food and liquor and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not that the Wii is a social video game conference that's, you know, that's going to have that
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope you heard the bonus statement tonight, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was some very exciting news for you in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1877-GAME-OL, our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Actdeft in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Actdeft in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just fucking out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to talk about...
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Talk up in the bonus segment about the March Madness that DMN is organizing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and just so our podcast listeners know, because they don't always get to hear the bonus segment, because we do something bonus, DMN, one of our weeknight shows, I believe it is the shows on Wednesdays, the Insanest Hour, he is putting together the Top 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's doing this March Madness thing with the 64 games going face-off against each other.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the listeners submitted in their list.
[SPEAKER_03]: And during the bonus segment tonight, the
[SPEAKER_00]: You and Loki made a vote for one of the brackets.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was Ocarina of Time and Kirby Superstar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say that I'm with you, though not for the same reason, but just because I do think that Kirby Superstar is a better game than Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki and I made a controversial vote during the bonus segment of this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: We voted for Kirby Superstar over Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And both of us said it's because basically we both agree that Ocarina of Time is one of the most, by the gaming community in general, overrated games there is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I've tried playing it and I can't stand it.
[SPEAKER_03]: When Zelda went 3D for me, it just didn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even Wind Waker, or not Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wind Waker is fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Wind Waker and I like the
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like I think it's a bad game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care for the more mature-looking length.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like the 3D ones that are on the Nintendo 64, and I didn't really get into... And I just love the Super Nintendo ones so, so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one of my favorite games of all time, is Link to the Past.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, maybe it's more solid talking about...
[SPEAKER_03]: For me, Charity Superstar is the better game there because Charity Superstar is like many games in one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Many adventure games, also multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically, although the story in it, or the many stories in it,
[SPEAKER_03]: aren't as deep as Ocarina of Time, so you can have a better time playing it, and even replaying it, like Great Table Sense of Death is one of the games there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically an adventure game that you gotta find treasures.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's like 100 treasures you have to find, and it's very difficult to do it in one simple run.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to replay it again and again to get
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, but maybe you just want to admit that maybe a little bit you're just a Kirby fanboy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I do like Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's one of my favorite games of all time, but I just want to make that point that maybe Ocarina of Time is not that great of a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not all that in the bag of chips.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure there's...
[SPEAKER_03]: and we have ours and I'm sure many of you have been asked the emails we get this week about how we hate Ocarina of Time, which isn't true, we like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, different show port, different port.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to put it that way, then fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Actdeft, any other comments you have for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just, I want to say that I already got my ticket for Video Game Scribe, so in two weeks,
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care Actdeft, have fun at Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to give us a call, we'll take one more call, 877-GAME-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1-1
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a couple of things about the whole Nintendo Online thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't blame them for saying it like the preset text chat and all that, but when friends get together and play, it is the most rowdiness ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, really, if I'm going to be playing Mario Kart Online with my friends, I don't want to curse like a sailor.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me too, and the weird thing is that thanks to technology, I'm still going to do that, whether it be this whole Ventrilo thing, or the, I love the idea of, I think it was even Loki or a chatter that said this, you sign on to the Xbox 360, and do your chat on the 360, and then play the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: For me, I'll just bring my laptop next to the Wii, and I'll just put my headset on, and just like,
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it depends on the fact that they're a quote-unquote family company, family gaming console and stuff like that, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're scared shitless about online, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Janai in chat says, but it's more fun when it's multiplayer offline.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, I mean, honestly, when I get Mario Kart Wii, I'm going to be busy the whole time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta say though, Jani, sometimes that's not an option though.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, one of the beautiful things about the internet is that it brings people together.
[SPEAKER_03]: One reason I'm so obsessed with WoW to the point you guys make fun
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I get to play with some of my friends I don't see on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_03]: For instance, one of my closest friends lives in Kansas, so we play that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, we also have a guy in our guild who's from Idaho who's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, there's a bunch of local people on there, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we have a good time, you know, just laughing and playing the game and, you know, all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's, you know, a lot of our listeners, you know, we get to play games on DS sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I get to play with people in New York City and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, sometimes the Internet really helps fill in that void that we can't have people on the couch.
[SPEAKER_03]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, any other thoughts, Ranma, before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, a couple things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, remember what you said earlier about a Hello Kitty PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you had a thing for Batch Maroon.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is the Batsamaru thing, not a Hello Kitty thing, but I've just accepted the fact that people are just going to loop it all on the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when I say Batsamaru is Sanrio, they're going to just go, oh, you like Hello Kitty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus there's the whole fact that I have the toaster and the coffee maker, which doesn't help.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't make, like, if they came out with a Batsamaru toaster, I would sell that thing to my Hello Kitty one at a garage sale so quick and replace it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they just, they don't do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No love for paint ones.
No love.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's my, so that's my, they have the Hello Kitty.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I was surprised no one got me the waffle maker for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: So many people said they were going to give me the waffle maker.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was one of the things where I think no one wanted to buy it because they all thought everyone else was getting it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: And before I go, when I went to Capcom a couple of weeks ago, a couple of interesting things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, the game room.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a 32-inch HD TV set up.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's an Atari 7800 playing Mario Brothers?
[SPEAKER_03]: That is fucking hardcore.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I have to admit, I have to admit, when I was at the record store this weekend that also sells the old games, and I saw some of the games that they had on the 2600, like Combat and Warlords and all that stuff, I was like, man, how fun would it be just for one day to hook up the Atari 2600 games to the TV, the big HD TV, and just have a brawl?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, come over.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll hook up the 5200.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let Justin TV that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to actually have the 5200 hooked up, because even though the controllers broke really easily, I would totally love to get a Kix game going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want some epic kaboom.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want some HD kaboom.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to do that one weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think one weekend we need to just marathon the shit out of old school Atari games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't we do this?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about twice a month?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we can manage the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We pick an old console, hook that shit up, and play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're talking about my, you know, vault in my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if we can get the time, we can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have to bring over Clicovision and television?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's make it happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's not let this go the way the Super Mentor would think.
[SPEAKER_03]: We set a time, we set a date, and we do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bring over the Justin TV cam so the chatters can enjoy it too.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll point it at the TV and just go to town.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: When?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... Okay, we can't set a time right now because we have to consult our calendars, but Ranma, you're in charge of bitching at us until it happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do it in early April.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to wait that long?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so Ranma, you stay on our asses until it happens, alright?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: We gotta let you go, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_00]: Relax, go to your room, change your underwear, and go back to play, okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: Relax.
[SPEAKER_00]: The line was like going all over the place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you had to go to rock and roll, but everybody was there to play Brawl.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is being clear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Each 500 copies per se.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You were looking at Brawl's target audience at that place.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, a lot of people that go to anime cons are excited about Brawl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most of them are Nintendo fanboys.
[SPEAKER_03]: But still, I mean, you've got people my age going that's over four.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be a huge dollar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not doubting you on that, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: This call's going on for very, very long.
[SPEAKER_03]: But thank you so much as always.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, this is getting to seven minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to keep them at four minutes now.
[SPEAKER_03]: One more call, we're wrapping up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, how far are we in the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my God, almost two hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we've got to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just part B. Because the bonus, our bonus statement tonight was 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 9.30 here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to end this shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that being said, quickly, Loki, any last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I have last-minute stories for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, LEGO MMO, we know and love that they
[SPEAKER_03]: You Don't Know Jack has become part of Yahoo Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Resident Evil Zero is coming to the Wii in Japan to support the NQ thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: A Finnish company...
[SPEAKER_03]: Game Studio, has filed papers to trademark Pwnage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, they're trying to trademark Pwnage.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, they can put it on shirts and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, the PlayStation Store is apparently going to be overhauled in April.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to look more like the Thing Store, which, you know, a little different, a little bit easier to navigate, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll look for that in April there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Initial D Arcade Stage 4 is headed to PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a game I'm going to be importing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I learned my lesson the first time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did the other Initial D games come out on consoles?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think they ever did.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they had an Initial D on the PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a PSP one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lastly, to piss off people even more,
[SPEAKER_03]: There's even a sketch of a Spartan done by the Rooster Teeth guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, his 360 died and has a free ring, so he sent it in to get fixed.
[SPEAKER_03]: He even, you know, took precautions of asking them, hey, you know, can you send this back to me in the same case?
[SPEAKER_03]: If not, you know, can you make sure you put the new case on the new system?
[SPEAKER_03]: That kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, he gets it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: His serial number is mapped.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would they do that in the first place?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you rub something off?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's just being a dick, is what that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know one that also didn't make a cut.
[SPEAKER_03]: The singing store is also going to be getting 67 songs in the next update, which I believe is supposed to happen in April as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: No problem with those 67.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tired.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is wine is good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plum wine was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is I'm still working on that 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still being done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, after our amazing February of fail, we hope March has been a good month to you guys so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was a good show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do think it was a good show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you everybody for tuning in and supporting us and supporting independent radio and independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know we only do this every week for you guys that continue to support us.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please, you know, we don't charge or any of that stuff for the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you like what you hear, just tell two friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: Help spread the word of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that will keep us motivated to come back next week where there will be more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And until then, I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's DarkSakra.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_05]: For more information on our live and contact programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week!
[SPEAKER_04]: you've been listening to the Orange Lounge Radio Lost episode now for my shameless plug www.marathongamer.com thanks for tuning in guys