[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, March 30th, 2008, Gamers4Hackers get the SmackDown from Microsoft, Rockband is announced for the Wii, and is another PSP redesign on the way?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Roar.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, I'm scared.
[SPEAKER_01]: Roar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things going good for you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fairly decently.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: We got the announcement about, you know, I had to make decisions about what the hell's going to happen with the show, the station going offline.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not the show, but the station going offline in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somehow I did the math wrong when I looked at the calendar.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought tonight was the last show on Life is Five, but it's actually next Saturday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or next...
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently I still can't read a calendar.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's next Sunday is going to be the last show on Life's Easy Five.
[SPEAKER_05]: I somehow missed that there was one more week in March.
[SPEAKER_05]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here we are on March 30th.
[SPEAKER_05]: April 6th will be the last show on LifeEasyFive.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then April 13th, something else, which we'll get to in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: The future of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about that in a little bit, but I wouldn't want to get away from how we usually start things off with.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very Ragnarok-ing, as usual.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I turned on my DS to play some Final Fantasy VI, and then turned it off promptly, because I ran out of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, and we were going to be able to get another pinball machine, but that fell through.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which pinball machine?
[SPEAKER_02]: Attack from Mars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I like that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan and Will to buy it, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Big Bang Bar, the Uber Rare Table, what pinball table would you like to own more than anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I actually have a pan list of a couple.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, one of them would actually be, um, Black Knight 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we have actually a Black Knight right now that we're borrowing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, oh god, I know what this is called.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, um, it's one that's like an airplane theme, like a jet theme.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had it, um, at Pentagogo, and it was, um, the whole game was like nothing but ramps.
[SPEAKER_02]: WorldCupSoccer94
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the machine to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have the one I want.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the husband's not allowed to sell that ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have the other one that I really like, which is Twilight Zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So those two were up there for my two favorite tables.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually are still trying to get me a Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost bought the TARDIS out of a Doctor Who on eBay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember, like,
[SPEAKER_04]: A Tommy machine wouldn't be bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a giant pinball on top.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the Jurassic Park pinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the one I was like, because the big dinosaur came down and ate your ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: But my favorite table ever was that in the family game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a Simpsons pinball party.
[SPEAKER_02]: That machine's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my God, is that one hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dan got rid of my Rocky and Bullwinkle, which I really liked.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Stern is bringing out a new Indiana Jones table.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I mentioned that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The market's still there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There definitely is still a market for pinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fun, and there's still rabid fans for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're getting off base.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone's playing Klonoa 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone in chat's playing Klonoa 2, and that game's fucking awesome and very depressing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what would bring pinball back is if they made a way to make it competitive against a couple teams.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually had sort of like a cocktail machine that had two sides on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, at Classic Gaming Expo, and I think I've seen it there, and at Pentagogo, they have the versus tables, but those are, they're not very fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to join our chat room so Jamie can have random outbursts at the games you're playing this week, chat.orangeloungeradio.com is the place to go do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meanwhile, Loki, I'm thinking you're going to bring us back to console games with your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week I played Crisis Core, so that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's definitely a lot different than, say, your typical Final Fantasy RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure if it's too similar to 12.
[SPEAKER_04]: The combat system's sort of real-time, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: You run around and you kind of mash buttons, but it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very linear so far, but like I said, I'm not that far in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if it continues the way it is, it's a very linear game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's fun so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love the cutscenes, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cutscenes are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I've also played Saints Row, actually the single player, because I'm trying to finish it before Grand Theft Auto 4 comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Almost done with the game, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on the last third.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then I played just some weird stuff that we'll be probably getting into later like that Romjack Fail and Tetroid 2012.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Tetris and Silent Hill with Arkanoid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to see this because when Loki says it's Tetris meets Silent Hill I'm like what the hell is that supposed to mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's weird though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: And then that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I may have played a little bit of Brawl in there, too, at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cool thing, though, because mainly this entire week I've been busy trying to get that stupid 360 working, the second one that went down, and finally fixed it, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, at a certain point, it's always when I just say, okay, fuck it, it's not going to work ever again, I'm just going to go all out and, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we have one more to go, but this one was a lot easier because I bought a replacement warranty sticker, so I'm going to slap that on there and put the old case back on there and send it to Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one, no work involved.
[SPEAKER_04]: So far, three out of six have broken, but I fixed two out of the three, so that's not bad so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is there anything else to report?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully we'll have some cool stuff to show Justin.TV later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of Justin.TV, we do have a webcam feed of our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of crap tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wi-Fi is kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I've played the game a million times, but it's still one of my favorites from, you know, way back yonder.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was playing like Root Beer Tapper, Tempest, and some of the other things on Xbox Live that are, you know, they're not like scream up and down and shout and type wonderful games, but, you know, they are classics.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some of them, I don't even like the upgraded versions of some of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't think I like the upgraded version of Tempest nearly as much as the original.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know if it's just like, I can't see as much of what's going on or what have you, but
[SPEAKER_05]: I got like some old achievements that for some reason I never got.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I also checked out that new release, Tikal or Tikal, Tikal, whatever that new puzzle game is on Xbox Live this week, which is OK.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like Tetris meets Luminous, sort of like you have to make the little blocks that you do in Luminous, but you make them with Tetris shaped pieces in different colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not just two colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like four different colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But yet, I don't believe this game is a PopCap game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe it's made by somebody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, the game itself has nothing to do with Zuma.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the games themselves are completely separate, except for the fact they're both puzzle-ish games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have that other one, too, that's just like kind of Zuma, or the same tribal thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was, um... Not Crystal Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was, um... Oh, Miss, uh, Magnetica.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not like Zuma.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about the tribal thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an Xbox Live Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, uh, Jewel Quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jewel Quest, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Jewel Quest is like bejeweled with one little twist to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I didn't end up really buying the full version of it because the demo gives you a really good taste of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't keep justifying these little $5 and $10 purchases for games I'm not going to play more than a couple times.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some days I do wish Xbox Live would switch to that model of you just pay...
[SPEAKER_05]: Tickle Tickle
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Tickle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like Tickle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gerardimo says Tickle.
[SPEAKER_05]: A mashup of good puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did you expect it to be decent?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I like puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I would say it's decent.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just didn't wow me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the first time I played Luminous, I was like, this game is the shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It didn't wow me, but it wasn't horrible either.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other thing I did during my gaming week, you know I'm like, I think I mentioned this a couple weeks ago on the show, I've been really late to the Steam bandwagon, you know, on the PC, getting Steam and checking that out, which is kind of like,
[SPEAKER_05]: X-Fire meets Xbox Live meets an online-type store kind of thing on your PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: I downloaded that a couple weeks ago, and I finally bought a game this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the game I bought was Portal, because Loki finally took his copy of the Orange Box back a little while ago, and I was very sad I couldn't play that on an Xbox 360 anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the only game in there I was really, really missing and wanting to play again was Portal.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big difference.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know this is like a classic debate, but it's not something I often think about because I do most of my gaming on console and, you know, World of Warcraft on the PC and a couple other things here and there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't often think about this, but there really is a world of difference between keyboard and mouse and two analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I actually do a lot better with a keyboard and mouse than I do analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's a classic debate.
[SPEAKER_05]: People say, this is better, this is better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might actually be a little better at Halo if I could use a keyboard and mouse in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yes, I know I could get Halo 2 and Vista, but I don't have Vista.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can also get one of the, they have the T-Mix Acuter stuff that you can buy that you can hook up a keyboard and mouse and do it that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do like how you actually fire the portal gun with a PC, your left or right click.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a little bit more intuitive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of like the feel of it on the PC a little better than I did on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, the Xbox 360, I could still play that on my big screen TV, and it was loud, and it was nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this one, whereas I have a widescreen monitor out here, it's not very big, but it's still pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, same game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know we love Portal here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have a lot to say about the game, but just kind of making that transition was very interesting because it's the exact same game, just playing it two different ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think I actually do a lot better with the mouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think part of what Jamie said has a lot to do with that, just the way you control the firing and just the movement is different and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It took me a minute to get used to moving, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: because sometimes with the whole WASD, I think if you hit two of them at the same time, it gets confused.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little unlike World of Warcraft, which also does a WASD, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing I will say about the difference on there too, just for perspective, I get more motion sick watching it on a TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it because it's just bigger, and so more of your vision is taken up by the images?
[SPEAKER_01]: That could possibly be it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I was watching on a widescreen laptop before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ross Steel UT in chat says Street Fighter would be an atrocity on a keyboard and mouse yeah I remember an old actually I had Street Fighter 2 Turbo Super Duper whatever it was the last big one they did they had a computer version of it on CD that had Redbook audio for the different stages like redone music and so yeah I had that on the PC and I played it on the keyboard and it's just not the same it's just not the same and then I go way way back and I think about Stick Fighter
[SPEAKER_04]: Stick Fighter is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody ever play Stick Fighter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that game back in the day?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've never played Stick Fighter, it's got to be out there on the internet somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one of those like back in the shareware days.
[SPEAKER_05]: You probably have to get a slowdown program to make it work okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine it's like way, but Stick Fighter was a Street Fighter 2 clone, but it used nothing but stick figures.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they actually stole voice samples out of the game in some of the later versions.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into tonight's housekeeping since we're done with our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get into housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know the question on everybody's mind is, okay, we dropped that bombshell last week that Orange Lounge Radio is going to be closing its doors as a live 24-hour-a-day, 7-day-a-week station as of April 12th.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, April 3rd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, no, April 12th is our last broadcast today.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to kind of thank everybody that sent us emails this week and sent us private messages and all of that sort and posts on forums and things with suggestions for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I got told to check out about 10 different websites.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple people actually offered to host a streaming thing for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't able to do a lot of research on that, but I think that's very cool that people would do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: but ultimately we decided to take things in a different direction and it was kind of the first thing that came it was the first idea that we had here at Orange Lounge Radio to do with the future of the show and um and first let me say this as well chat it's not April Fool's okay it just so happens live 365 you know if you've listened to the show long enough you know we freaking hate April Fool's Day okay so the last thing we would do is do something crappy like that for April Fool's Day this is not an April Fool's joke okay so um
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I lost my train of thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn you, chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was I saying?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the first idea that came to our minds is the one we decided to go with.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so we emailed some people and did some talking and looks like everybody's on board.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is what's going to happen, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting April 13th, that's episode number 275 of our show, we will now be officially a part of allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are going to merge, essentially, some of our shows from our station with the operations they have over at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in a way, I've been kind of joking all week long, it's creating a Voltron of independent podcasting, and that's kind of what I really believe in what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because while we could have set up our own feed and taken one of these offers to set up our own thing and run our own music feed and live thing,
[SPEAKER_05]: Music and all that stuff takes a long time to set up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more than just putting MP3s at random, trust me for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, it's kind of like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Why would we want to do that and run this whole separate thing when there's this perfectly established station going on over there that we already have a good relationship with because our show's been syndicated over on the network?
[SPEAKER_05]: We know the people there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We like the people over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're kind of something different-ish on the network.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a type of show they don't have otherwise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why go run off and do our own thing when we can instead come together and form...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: and there's the fact that you can listen to it on your PSP now.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you check out allgames.com on your PSP and I believe it's in the... It's one of the preset stations in the PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a good thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The more and more I kind of think about it, the more I think this is like the right idea for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here also, I have no announcements at this time as far as our other shows go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of Travis Donovan and DMN.
[SPEAKER_05]: However...
[SPEAKER_05]: We are in talks to have that be a part of the merge, and they didn't say no.
[SPEAKER_05]: So right now that's all in limbo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have nothing further to say at this time, but that is exciting that some of our other stuff will probably go over there as well if everybody's happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it'll be good, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's going to be a great thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else you guys want to add?
[SPEAKER_04]: I got nothing to add.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing to add?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: I like pastrami.
[SPEAKER_05]: You like pastrami?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we're not going to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we might do some aesthetic type changes with this move.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we might take the opportunity to clean up our album art, maybe do a different audio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we might make some small aesthetical changes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But as far as the content that you're actually going to hear in the show, nothing's going to change in that regard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Macquarie and Jamie, there will be more pastrami.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But honestly, you're not going to have to change your subscription or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're still going to get the podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like nothing ever happened for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've never listened to us live, it's going to be like nothing ever happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I hate to say it, even though the sound may be in higher quality, the show will not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, the show will not be in higher quality.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is there anything else to add?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else we should say?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm out of soda.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's about it
[SPEAKER_05]: I need it easier than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bookmark it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what else to tell you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zlatan asks, will it be 30 seconds behind like Live 365?
[SPEAKER_05]: I do not think the buffer will be as great because I think we're having to say, because right now we send from my computer to Live 365 who encodes it to their server.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's going to be as much of a delay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there will still be a delay, but that's inevitable because of the encoding process, but it won't be like 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be an hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, BlackWolf, Bobby BlackWolf is in chat helping to clear the air right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: He actually says it still will be 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just inevitable, I mean, because it's buffer and all that stuff, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ross Steel, UT, says, fuck that, bring BlackWolf on and make fun of him.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just might do that, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we love Bobby, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby has actually been very instrumental in making this happen, so we love Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, that's another really good thing is because when we're live on Sunday nights...
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby's show airs at 5 o'clock and he says that he's going to keep his show to an hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe occasionally he'll run over, but very little.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the nice thing is that instead of having music as a lead-in, we're going to have a really good quality show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's almost like being on a real television network where you have a quality show as a lead-in to your show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I think the listeners are really going to benefit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're all going to benefit because we'll get some of Bobby's people, he'll get some of our people.
[SPEAKER_05]: That all goes into the Voltron of independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like when they have heroes on and then they have Chuck and then everyone turns the TV off when Chuck comes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm hoping it doesn't go like that, but maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Will it blend?
[SPEAKER_05]: It may indeed blend.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: WetWeToo in chat says, as usual, OLR is the gamer tech podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever happened to OLR Food Network?
[SPEAKER_05]: OLR Food Network is still here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pastrami, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yum.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: With cheese and grilled onions.
[SPEAKER_02]: And no burger!
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so mad.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they also have talk radio that plays throughout the day, which I think is highly entertaining.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you never know what might happen in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going to free all of us up to kind of be working towards a more common goal now and working on, you know, kind of the visibility of the same radio station.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a good thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, I'll shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll stop talking about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're beating this topic into the ground.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into tonight's gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: A few tracks that will be available for, I guess, fans of Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, included in these are Make It, Uncle Salty, Draw the Line, No Surprise, and Sweet Emotion.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's going to be, I guess, 40 plus songs in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: 60% of it, of course, I guess, will be devoted to Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, actually, I saw like...
[SPEAKER_04]: The way they kind of have it set up is neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be doing different sets, I guess, follow their career a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they'll have two songs that are openers that are from a different band, and then they'll have three Aerosmith songs, maybe like a bonus song or something like that, and they're going to have different sets set up like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: As long as it's better than Guitar Hero Rocks the 80s, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it will be, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Steve Tyler's Lips
[SPEAKER_05]: and those big ol' lips are on the cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that going to be enough, do you think, to sell this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The easiest way to decide if you want this game or not is to wait until they get down to the point where they announce the entire soundtrack to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then just, okay, is that something that you want or not?
[SPEAKER_04]: My guess is they're not going to have download content for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably just going to be, you know, these songs and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, I mean, why would they cut into their Guitar Hero 3 download content?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, of course, is still going to be going on until Guitar Hero 4 comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of these music games are really starting to milk it to the point of getting sick of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, we'll be getting to some other stuff later like SingStar, which... I'm thinking part of the reason that makes this so alluring is that it looks like they're just using the same damn engine from Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's updated a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The engine itself is actually upgraded a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Define a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The graphics are a little bit better, animations are recaptured and they're a lot smoother.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stuff like that, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's basically Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gerardimo in chat, chat.orange.com, suggests Guitar Hero ABBA mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd be down with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But do they use any real guitar?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but you know, they have an opening for a drummer, so there might be Drum Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I had to laugh, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to love this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to laugh because on the trailer, you know how they have all the little logos of the different people that have products in the game and stuff like that, and Gibson was on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, oh, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the irony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ironic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very ironic.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Ray Yane.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we'll hear more about Guitar Hero Aerosmith in the future, I'm sure, as we get closer to the release date.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another game we're hearing more and more about is Ninja Gaiden 2, which looks bloody fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Emphasis on bloody.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks wonderful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ninja Gaiden 2, if you want to see all that blood, the demo is going to be coming in May.
[SPEAKER_05]: May is going to be the delivery of the Ninja Gaiden 2 demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is according to Microsoft's Ninja Gaiden 2 website.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently there's also supposed to be some exclusive content beginning on April 15th.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if it's anything like previous exclusive content, it's probably crappy gamer picks and crappy themes and maybe some cool looking trailers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ninja Gaiden Hi-Rez
[SPEAKER_05]: PENNY ARCADE ADVENTURES ON THE RAINSLICK PRECIPICE OF DARKNESS
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a price out for it now, $19.95, which would be about half that numeric value in pounds for our UK listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's just for the Windows, Mac, and Linux version of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be released on Linux, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is an Xbox Live Arcade version that will have a simultaneous launch, no price released yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Five to ten hours of playing for you, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that they were saying that the Xbox Live Arcade version was going to be $20, which I thought was kind of surprising, seeing as they haven't really had a game that was spent $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think most was like Luminous with $15 and stuff, but $20 for that game is really expensive.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is a little steep.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game better be epic as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: For $20.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I'm going to pay that much money, I'll just get it on Windows.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, yeah, I was going to say, you know, $20 is kind of the average.
[SPEAKER_05]: $19.95 is what you pay for a low-budget Windows game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So is it really that obscene of a price on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: But as long as the game is quality, that's what's important.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know it has a great tie-in, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know a lot of gamers who don't love Penny Arcade, or at least like and respect it a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you know it's going to be at least the quality there, it's just the question of, but will it be, it's kind of like that question, will it blend?
[SPEAKER_05]: Will it blend into a game?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now a game that we're probably not going to get over here, unfortunately, Raiden Fighters Aces has gotten a demo on the Japanese Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX Live Accounts
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there was, back in the day on the PlayStation, there was just, for the first two write-in games, before these came out, there was a compilation on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see one that's all of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be a big compilation.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be a very big compilation.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what that compilation's called?
[SPEAKER_04]: MAME.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, the boards for the first three Raiden games have been intensely difficult for them to crack.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that they've only gotten... They haven't... As far as I know, they haven't cracked Raiden DX yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had that at our roundtable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, I like the electric one that latches on and does the swirly bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my favorite one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just need them all.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, talking about, you know, games coming from Japan and shooter games, you know, I guess somebody out there was just thinking to themselves, like, you know, we don't have enough shoot-em-up games on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need more.
[SPEAKER_05]: And luckily, though, one of the granddaddies of shoot-em-up games is on its way to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess we can make room for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can find room in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, we've been having rumors about this game for a couple weeks now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the latest one, I think last week we had the month nailed down as April.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this week, thanks to Japan's version of Xbox.com, we now know that the release date is set to be April 9th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, of course, all these types of things are always subject to change, and who knows, the Japanese website could have been wrong, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: It does look pretty likely it's going to be out in early April rather than later, which isn't a bad thing because Ikaruga is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess we can make room for one more shooter if it's Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I would rather see than Ikaruga?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, in other...
[SPEAKER_02]: News as far as games to be out, and this is actually more of a leak from the ESRB, and this would be also for Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Darwinia is supposed to be coming out, and it actually was confirmed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually listed as Darwinia Plus, Survival of the Flat, which is, okay, from what I'm understanding on here, it's a multiplayer version, Multiwinia, Survival of the Flattest.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's fairly interesting, and we've had a lot of people tell us about this game, that it's supposed to be really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's actually a demo out for Windows, Mac, and Linux right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quiltipo in chat says, Screw Darwinia, I want Darwin Awards the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that just pain on PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds sort of like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, Darwinia, I've heard nothing but good things about Darwinia.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's kind of neat that these little games are getting this more massive distribution.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm assuming from the whole plus in the name, there's going to be a lot of extra features, which probably will, you know, be justifying the cost of it on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I look forward to an easy way to check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if anyone wants to check out the demo, go to introversion.co.uk slash Darwinia.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can download the demo there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: No interest from me whatsoever, but hey, I know a lot of people liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played it once, and I know it has a rabid fan base because of its quirky sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, if you're looking forward to it, I would say probably going to see it in November.
[SPEAKER_05]: How highly anticipated do you think this game is?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, one thing I also know about Banjo-Kazooie is it's been a long time since there's been a game in this series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they teased it at E3 last year, but that's probably the last we've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they need some good family games, I guess, because Viva Pinata's not that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, no offense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's people that love Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the wrong people that Microsoft thought were going to get into Viva Pinata got into Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they should take a note from it that they need a good sim game on the Xbox 360, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Then, what they should do, though, Viva Pinata, though, it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Gold Banjo in chat says Banjo Kazooie is awesome, that's what my screen name is named after
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft has been going through and finding people who have been cheating in games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doing save game hacks.
[SPEAKER_05]: How do people cheat their gamerscore?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you ought to know this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why would I know this stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I know you would know this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently there's some workarounds that they can actually do where it hacks their actual profile that you don't even need to play the game to get the achievement points from.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what they're really cracking down on, is stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you can't do the save stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have that stupid digital rights management thing that they threw in there to fuck everybody over with everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: That stopped people from save swapping and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not all the games worked with save swapping, so it was very unreliable stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: So now these folks basically get the scarlet question mark, or it's more the orange question mark on their profile that labels them as a cheater.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait because, you know, I'm not too optimistic on Microsoft in picking people that cheat, and I have a feeling they're going to make some mistakes in there, and they're going to pick people that, like, did not cheat, and they're going to mark them as cheaters, and that's going to have a whole backlash thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I would just ban these people from Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why aren't they just doing that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they seem to do that with everything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand why they just have to... Making examples of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no problem with them making examples out of them, but I have a feeling that they're going to get some people that really didn't cheat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why's it got to be an orange question mark?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's wrong with orange?
[SPEAKER_05]: You got a problem with orange, Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why's it got to be an orange question mark?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jerks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's kind of a gold orange.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't think at the same time Microsoft is like running rampant accusing everybody of being a witch, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Witch!
[SPEAKER_05]: Cheetah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Burn the cheetah!
[SPEAKER_05]: We found a witch, may we burn her?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think Microsoft is running through the village accusing everybody of being a witch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they just targeted some of the high profile people like
[SPEAKER_05]: Strip Club, GJ, you know that guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just know him because he actually messaged me once because I got DDR Universe the day it came out and I was playing it like all day long and I had like 500 gamerscore and I must have had one of the higher gamerscores out of anybody that day because he messaged me and he was like, how was the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it good?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it easy to get the gamerscore?
[SPEAKER_05]: So I remember him because I laughed my ass off when I saw I was getting this message from him and I heard he was one of the people that got caught with this and sure enough, yes he is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost have 10,000 gamer points.
[SPEAKER_05]: No thanks to my friend playing Rock Band for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's not cheating in the sense of Microsoft cheating.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sire Ran says, how do you know it's a cheater?
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like one!
[SPEAKER_03]: They turned me into a Yaris.
[SPEAKER_03]: Turned me into a... I got better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Strip Club DJ made me play Yaris.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's punishable by death.
[SPEAKER_05]: Burn him!
[SPEAKER_03]: How do you know they're a cheater?
[SPEAKER_03]: Build a game out of them!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I know, which is a very broad term.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what we're parrying here, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should be, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, a, uh, a Goomba hunt.
[SPEAKER_05]: It should be a release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, how about that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I got some release dates right here, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I have four.
[SPEAKER_02]: And two of them are the same game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Baroque on the first for PS2 and Wii and Kingdom 2 Bloodshot on Xbox 360 and PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now how can she predict the future about all these games coming out in the UK?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because she's a witch!
[SPEAKER_02]: Witch!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's because I have reliable sources.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reliable witch sources!
[SPEAKER_02]: I looked into my cauldron and lit some charcoal and read it in the smoke.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I want the Witch Hunt joke to die now before it gets too old.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be a wiki on it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the OLR wiki more than anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, as is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Loki, what's going on in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a whole lot of good stuff, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this time around we get some crap, including...
[SPEAKER_04]: Rafa Nadal, Tennis on the DS I think that came out already, but eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably a GameStop exclusive, but that's okay, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Octomania got delayed, I guess, a week or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's now coming out on the Wii, $19.99 for Puzzle Game, and it has online, so that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's Atlus, you gotta support Atlus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, let's see, Monochemia, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: Alchemist of Al Rivas, and that's a new Koei RPG for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a game called Toy Shop, which is coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's like a sim Toy Shop game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see here, Call of Duty 4, Game of the Year Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's coming out on the 1st as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just a re-release of Call of Duty 4 with the downloadable map pack, or token for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you don't have it yet, that's probably the way you want to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: and let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also World Championship cards on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, Eye of Judgment, Nintendo Wii,
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a very slow week in Japan as far as the next-gen systems go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, on the PlayStation 2, you get Pro Yaku Spirits 5 comes out, which is another baseball simulator game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's that, I suppose, to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's see if there's anything on the handhelds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surely there's got to be something on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, there's really not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, on April 3rd, there is some stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: One High Ten Fun by Igaizu Zunikakuru DS Detective Conan
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a new game coming out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this game coming from a group called FonFon is the publisher for this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kuchan no Shiwase Kantan Oryuri Recipe comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it looks like a cooking game or it could be, I don't think it's cooking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this is actually like a virtual cookbook.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like it has like 300 recipes in a little virtual cookbook.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were supposed to release something like that out here, but they never did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you can import this one, except I hope you can read Japanese or it's really not going to do you a lot of good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then you probably aren't going to be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Star Ocean Second Evolution comes out on the Sony PSP from Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so that would probably be one of the bigger releases in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, you've got to really wait until next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a lot of big releases in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it's a slow week all around, but probably because we're kind of in a little bit of a slow period until we get into, like, the summer games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we'll see a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Out of curiosity, real quick, before we get into the next story, because Summer Games reminded me, there's the Olympics this year, yet outside of Mario and Sonic at the Olympics, I haven't heard of a lot of, like, Beijing video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, it seems like every year there's an Olympics.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some horrible games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega is putting out an Olympics game in June.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beijing Olympics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is one coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it coming on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: No Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, maybe they don't want it to interview with Mario and Sonic at the Olympics one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about that, but there is one coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you giggling about over there, dare I ask?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at the listener profiles on our wiki, and while Steel U teases, great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop picking on him.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't want to pick on him, but I just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Did not expect it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was like, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gerardimo said, Sky, why is that bad?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not necessarily bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just curious.
[SPEAKER_05]: And usually these Olympic games are fucking horrible anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm just curious because I was surprised I haven't heard a lot about tie-in games when the Beijing Olympics are kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to hear something weird?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally off topic here, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week, there's a game, or not next week, but the week after next, there's a game on the DS coming out called Plushies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That reminds me of, like, furries.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want my ferret, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let the jokes begin.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want my ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want the ferret?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We might be able to make that happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: But not unless you read us more news.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have some news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony has said they're sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: We already knew they were sorry, but they've also apologized, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: they now have some updates to the PS3 store and one of them is Gran Turismo 5 Prologue which for the UK is $24.99 with UEFA Euro 2008 demo and Unreal Tournament 3 for free and Turok Map Packs for $1.99 and the Eye of Judgment Bio Rebellion card set for $6.99 also PS1 Realfishing
[SPEAKER_02]: has been added for $3.49 to PS3 and PSP stores.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also trailers on the PS3 store for Everybody's Golf World Tour, Eye of Judgment...
[SPEAKER_02]: GT5 Prologue, Dark Sector, and Dynasty Warriors 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Sony said, we sorry, poo, poo on us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somehow I don't think they phrased it quite like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, to quote, as previously mentioned, we unfortunately experienced some last-minute technical difficulties and weren't able to publish the new content as planned.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, we have been working hard to resolve these issues and are pleased to be able to let you know that basically they're all live on the UK store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this is specific, by the way, to the UK store.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, the Gran Turismo 5 Prologue Pal is out, so if you want to play an extended demo, go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, also in the U.S., they made some announcements of upcoming stuff, not necessarily anything coming out right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: But late April, we're going to be getting the Pixel Junk Monsters Encore, which is an expansion pack to, of course, Pixel Junk Monsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Early May, we'll be getting Echo Chrome, and in May sometime, Elefunc.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then late May or early June Wipeout HD so that's pretty cool they had some pretty interesting videos for Wipeout some Omega Pack or something that got released had some really trippy kind of like cartoony tracks I don't know so definitely check those out if you own Wipeout Pulse on the PSP it should be on the Playstation Store you can download those okay some other fun stuff
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby said he didn't need to make one creative change to our show, and that is that no more ferret.
Ferret, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: The batteries are going to die in that thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know that we've had that thing for as long as we've been doing this show?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a mascot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those batteries are going to die someday.
[SPEAKER_02]: The ferret is eternal.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they won't.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't understand, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can rip them open and put new batteries in.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how I got those other ones to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you have to fucking tell her how to do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know how to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could smile and nod and say, yes, Rob, the ferret will die.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, you have to say, oh, we can give it a lobotomy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, there's almost a bald spot now from where I've been pressing it in the same spot.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's ferret abuse.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, are we a video game podcast?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was getting confused.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I was going to get into a story.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're the food and ferret cast.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then you had to mention Bobby and it halted the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, they like to innovate with each new release that they're coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is something very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they're actually going to incorporate into Grand Theft Auto 4 is real-world music downloads.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to be tied in with Amazon.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the way this works is in the game, you can actually call an in-game service called Zit on your mobile phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you get text messages with song and artist names.
[SPEAKER_04]: as well as an email if you're a member of the Rockstar Social Club and then when you download tracks or whatever they're going to be about 89 cents to 99 cents and they'll actually of course they're DRM free because they're MP3s but I guess you can download them in game and you'll also get them in the real world so that's pretty cool that you'll be able to download some music
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody by the nickname of Beatmania Slot Machine in our chatroom says, Orange Ferret Foodio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I misunderstood this a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The way this works is the soundtrack for the game, so the music actually inside the game, not additional music.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you hear a song you like on the radio or something like that, you can dial that service in the game and then get the MP3 sent to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have to make a comment to Beatmania Slot Machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually not a slot machine, it's Apache Slot
[SPEAKER_05]: But we'll get to that later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't spoil the upcoming news stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't spoil them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I assume since this is an Xbox 360 game and a PS3 game that you'll be able to put your own music in there anyway, so that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aren't they doing this in real cars, too?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or at least I know there's that whole cell phone thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't there a commercial on TV for Verizon or something where you hold up your cell phone and it will recognize the song and download it for you or something like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there's stuff like that out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not physically taking the money out of your wallet and handing it to somebody or your purse or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not handing it to somebody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Therefore, it's so much easier to make these stupid impulse buys.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think this whole feature, while it's interesting and kind of cool, I guess, for a video game, is kind of capitalizing on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know there are going to be a lot of people that buy this game, and there's going to be a lot of people that are going to be like, Ooh, I like this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Click!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I just spent a dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's just a dollar.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I hate about iTunes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I click 20 times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, iTunes is almost the same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I was saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I hate about iTunes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially since it's on my damn phone!
[SPEAKER_05]: I've gone how many years without buying a damn thing on iTunes until I got my phone?
[SPEAKER_02]: and then I probably... I'm still okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've probably only bought like 25 songs total.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's that convenience.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're such a lazy society.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's not necessarily a... Like, I'm not saying like, oh, you're bad or, you know, oh, you're... But it's just kind of where we are.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's more putting the temptation in there because honestly, and this is how me personally I am, I believe that the things worth having are worth working for.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like I'm putting a giant cookie.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, I got it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm putting a giant piece of pastrami in your hands.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not that big on pastrami.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted pastrami today, so I got pastrami.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Press button, get pastrami.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I put a big bottle of Goldschlager in your hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like Goldschlager.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I say, well, goddammit, what is something you like?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what I want.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like sushi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, sushi.
[SPEAKER_05]: I put a big piece of sushi in your hand, and I say, hold on to this for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, if you eat that, you can eat it, but it will cost you a couple bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you're going to go, gulp.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're like, oh, it's just a couple bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gulp.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, here, hold this piece too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like hotel rooms at, you know, more upscale.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, obviously they don't have it at Motel 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: But like, you know, the more upscale type motels, they'll have all the candy and shit sitting out right there on the table.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's like, you know, hey, if you open it, two bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a terrible thing if you brought kids on the trip.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know what I do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I go to a grocery store down the street and buy me a bottle.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what you gotta do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, sorry, tangent.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are we without our tangents?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just going to say I want a service on Xbox Live where I can pay for a pizza with Microsoft Points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Slash pizza?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why shouldn't I be able to get... Wait!
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet that type of stuff is only a matter of time away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to be able to stop, pause my game for a second, order a pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I could just call up a pizza place and play the game at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking about integration, so why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: But once you get sick of pizza, I mean, I worked at a pizza place.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't get sick of pizza.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why I love internet TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, because me and every, I've made it perfectly clear, I hate being a slave to my television.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate having to, and you know, I don't see any money of paying for a DVR when I can just go online and watch whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to hear something that's going to be really bad?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait till Spore comes out and they have that service where you can create your character and then get a figurine of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, that looks awesome!
[SPEAKER_04]: Figuring, figuring, figuring!
[SPEAKER_04]: And they deliver this giant crate of figures for your house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, I actually would do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, I also go back and have drawn fan art of my PSO character in the past.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll do it too, and I like crappy things made by me, that's why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey everybody, pay me 20 bucks and I'll draw your RPG character.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have another thought you were trying to finish, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love this comment from RossDLUT in regards to the pizza being sold on Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then the pizza would be DRM protected and you'd not be able to eat it if something went wrong before it got delivered.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember what I was saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I was saying is that as long as you have a computer near you, anything is convenient.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because like I was saying, I don't watch TV, but I'll watch whatever I can on the internet and do all of my other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go out and get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Better yet, you order like Pizza Hut or something like that because, you know, they're kind of affiliated with, I know, I know, I'd prefer Roundtable, but that's regional and, you know, Pizza Hut, they did the whole affiliation with, you know, Xbox and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you order like a Pizza Hut pizza and they have a card from Microsoft Points taped to the top of the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that'd be cool, like, you know, 500 points or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pizza Hut Outfit Pizza in Game
[SPEAKER_04]: That's integration.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to hire us as marketing consultants.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to bring a soundboard with us to all games.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: You think Bobby would love that, if we take a soundboard with us to all games?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: And hey, Gerardimo, Papa John's got me through college.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need an actual soundboard first.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll work on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't want to go crazy with it, because I don't want to go crazy with a soundboard, but sometimes it's just too good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow, sorry, back to video gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, I wouldn't say this is gaming news, Morris, it is gaming rumor, that is big, big rumor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently the achievements for Grand Theft Auto 4 have hit the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two different websites have posted the 50 different achievements that are supposed to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the achievements are supposed to include things like hidden packages, doing types of stunt jumping, completing certain mission, beating minigames.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the other features, though, are a little weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's some sample achievements.
[SPEAKER_05]: Manhunt will get you 15 gamerscore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Complete the most wanted side missions from the police computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Warm coffee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Successfully date a girl to be invited into her house.
[SPEAKER_05]: If that's true, that's a pretty bold achievement.
[SPEAKER_05]: Warm coffee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let sleeping rock stars lie.
[SPEAKER_05]: 10 gamers score.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kill a rock star developer in a ranked multiplayer match.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's been a couple games that have things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kill the creator or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they kind of sound legitimate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's legit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The gamer...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: We kind of knew a lot of that stuff was coming, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, Grand Theft Auto 3 and Vice City had a lot of that video stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be awesome, and when this game comes out, I'll just have to become a hermit for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice knowing you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, a lot of people, you know, have been waiting, you know, for the Gran Turismo 5 prologue, but they're going to have to wait even longer for the actual thing, because they're saying it's still about a year away.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want any type of Gran Turismo 5 at all, your best bet is to get the Glorified demo on April 17th.
[SPEAKER_04]: My problem with the fact that this game is a year away is, assuming that they're using the same engine, and I hope to God that they're not by the time we get around to that, it's going to be so outdated.
[SPEAKER_04]: By that time, you're going to have Forza 3 and so many other games that do what they do a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of not worth it at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why does it take them so long to model cars when, you know, fucking Project Gotham and all these other games, you know, have cars that look good as well, and they're well modeled.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand what's taking them so long to get this game done.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like everyone seems to be doing it a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a quote Hippo asks in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, why the hell do these Gran Turismo games take so damn long?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it take that long to sample engine noises?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the game looks good, don't get me wrong, but it's just, it's not that much better than, like, Project Gotham or Forza, I mean, or even there's, like, Grid coming out that looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, I don't see what, you know, they're putting a lot of time in, you know, it's kind of like Duke Nukem Forever type, I mean, not so bad, but, you know, Duke Nukem Forever, they're putting all this effort and time into it, and then by the time it comes out, it's just going to be kind of, it'll be good, but it won't be, like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa, awesome!
[SPEAKER_04]: Gran Turismo 5 I'm sure will be really big for PlayStation, but will it really be that big of an achievement?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't understand why it's taking them so long for this game when Microsoft and other companies can push out these games really quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just my thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's just kind of
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP Slim
[SPEAKER_04]: After all, they were talking that it was going to be a 10-year life cycle for this portable system, so I can see them making some more revisions, but I think it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of sucks for people that bought the Slim and the original and stuff like that, now they have to buy a third one.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have this system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, by the way, it hasn't released yet, but we're already doing a revision on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're like, I'm just going to wait until the new one comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then no one bought it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I got to wonder, like, you know, Nintendo kind of does the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, but at the same time, I mean, here's the only difference between, I think, the DS Lite and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PSP Slim, it limits you to what options you have available for you when you're playing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's certain applications that you cannot use on the fatter PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, the newer PSPs have more RAM and other stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: In short, the battery life.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the battery life is just the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I think a little bit more improved.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the fact is that... Well, your friend's wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: So they have, you know, the DS Lite, it basically is a bit slimmer and has a brighter screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, most things that run on the DS Lite will also run on the original DS as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not anything that says, okay, you have to have this version of the hardware in order to be able to play this.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my only thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, there were three different versions of the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was that first one that wasn't backlit.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was the second one that came out that was backlit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there was the real miniature one that could go on like your keychain.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a micro.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the Game Boy Advance, the SP, and the micro.
[SPEAKER_05]: The SP was on, and then the micro, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The micro got me through many a line.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the micro didn't do very well overall.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only problem it sucked for is playing... RPGs or anything with text?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, even text wasn't so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was playing any type of shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's inevitable they're going to need to update the system since they're not going to just come out with the PSP 2 yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that kind of still sucks for someone that just bought the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should be used to it by now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure this PSP 3000 will be unhackable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Completely unhackable in any way.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, let's move on to another Sony-related story, and that has to do with a much-anticipated title, Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: The pre-order DVDs are shipping, and they come with that Metal Gear Online beta keys, and it does announce that the beta is going to begin on April 21st.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can download the Metal Gear Online beta on April 17th, so I guess they're giving a little bit of time so that maybe the servers don't all get hammered at once, which probably isn't a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: May 5th is when the beta runs until.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that actually isn't a whole lot of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I forgot I downloaded, well I haven't quite downloaded it yet, but I'm in the Battlefield Bad Company beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I hear wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I still haven't got a chance to play it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hopefully next week I'll be able to talk about it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was another one that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be very curious to hear from some of our listeners who are in on this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't ordered this because I don't really follow Metal Gear Online quite rapidly, but I'd be really curious to hear from some of our fans how this goes, how the online beta is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure there will be plenty of YouTubes and all that stuff, but I like to hear the first-hand experiences.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well for our listeners in Europe there actually may be an 80 gigabyte PlayStation 3 out by this summer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now there's only the 40 gigabyte version but there is a little bit of talk going around that indicates there is going to be an 80 gigabyte model coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so far Sony isn't really doing a good job at saying no about it so maybe it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: and there's actually no comment if it's going to even be backwards compatible or anything else good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to guess and say it probably will be as backwards compatible as the 80s over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now my question for Europe is, do you want it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, do you really want it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here would be my thing for Europe, okay, they just announced that they're going to release the 80 gig system there and I mean, they're kind of doing a new one for us with the Metal Gear Solid bundle and I know the same thing in Japan but
[SPEAKER_04]: If you just wait a few more months, I will bet you anything in the fall they will announce yet another SKU.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, just like we were talking about before with the PSP and stuff, just wait a little longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because unless there's something you really need to play right away, you can probably wait a few more months for the better games to be coming out towards the falls.
[SPEAKER_04]: And by that time you can get probably a newer system with better features for either the same price or less.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that would be my recommendation.
[SPEAKER_04]: another game you should definitely wait on buying is Eye of Judgment and actually the Eye of Judgment expansion has been having some delays coming to retail and the reason for this Sony says is transportation issues so they're having some problem I guess getting it from Wizards of the Coast to retailers
[SPEAKER_04]: I've Judgment, Byleth, Rebellion 2 Trading Cards
[SPEAKER_04]: and they have yet to set a new launch date for the software and cards but plan to do so in the near future.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone can buy the expansion because there's not a lot of people that own the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if anyone at Wizards of the Coast has heard of the Loki bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does anyone really care?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of our listeners seem to care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Wizards of the Coast couldn't give a rat's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eye of Judgment plus Let's Ride Friends Forever equals Tingle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cheeseburger's a reminder that we also get to count the sales of Let's Ride Friends Forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, all five of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, one more story for you guys, this segment, before we get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And those of you guys that remember the good old days of OLR, you can appreciate this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And something that was alluded to a little bit earlier, there is now a Pichi slot machine, which really kind of looks like a slot machine to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, oh, I was going to play the video for you guys, but it just got the smackdown taken off of YouTube.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got another one.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Video doesn't do very good over the radio anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But basically what happens, I watched it earlier, it looked like a slot machine to me, like one of those more video slot machines you'd see in the casinos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, when the slots come down, when certain symbols come up, you play like a Beatmania bonus game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you use the buttons on the thing to control Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what, there's something else that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not the only game that's gotten a...
[SPEAKER_04]: Ridge Racer
[SPEAKER_05]: Foxhunt Foxhunt
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: I bring up slot machines and all that because you know Konami makes a lot of slot machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even the ones you see over here, they make quite a few of those slot machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like another business of theirs we never really talk about.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I see many of their franchises go into those slot machines and Apache slots.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's Classic Game of the Week
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is actually one of my favorite RPGs ever, except honestly, it's actually one of the few that I've played quite a bit through in Japanese, until I had a little problem playing through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is Grandia, which is one of the pinnacle, I would say, of Sega Saturn role-playing, you know, for their RPG series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also...
[SPEAKER_02]: It did have quite a few sequels, one of them notably being Grandia 2 that was on Dreamcast that I remember bringing up on the show years ago because I thought it was cool that my Japanese save file worked on the US version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I was like, I put it and I was like, where am I?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what anybody's talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, Grandia is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: and so it'll follow with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a word of warning, the camera works so much better in the Saturn one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also get much more of the playfield open than you do with the PlayStation one, which is actually, the 3D looks better in the Saturn one, which is completely baffling to me, you know, since the Saturn didn't have, you know, that tremendous of a 3D processor.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also have a compass to show you where you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get treasure chests inside.
[SPEAKER_02]: A fun story to it, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also have skill points that you use to learn your abilities.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you have a rotational roster for your characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can pick different ones to have in.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are different types of weapon classes, like swords, maces, whips.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you actually learn your magic as you go through the game by recovering these mana eggs.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: The combat system though is what I like best.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you played Evolution, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Evolution is another game art title.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the way that the combat works in here is that it's on...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you can... It's like in Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see the enemies on the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they see you, they'll rush towards you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, you know, you can try to avoid them and they'll run into you, but then when you're in combat, it goes overhead.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it has...
[SPEAKER_02]: I look at it more of as initiative-based, you know, like if you were playing D&D or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everybody has their own sort of speed that their initiative moves at.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you'll have your slower characters taking longer, your faster ones being faster.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you choose your attacks as you're going through.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then when that turn comes up, they'll hit and then the enemy will go back and forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have to say it's fairly more realistic than the turn-based style for Final Fantasy games, if you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Rob, you're watching it, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've always heard a lot about this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just one of those games I just never got around to playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, there were a lot of games, especially this was the period when I was in college, so I didn't play a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was kind of the one time in my life when I wasn't as into video games as I was the rest of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it looks like a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I want to say a sequel of Grandia's is available on GameTap, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say, like, Grandia 2 is on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grandia 2 was a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then there was a Grandia 3 and I think a Grandia Extreme, which I haven't played the latter ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Grandia is probably up there in my list.
[SPEAKER_02]: This would actually, I even like this better than Final Fantasy VII and Final Fantasy VI, if that's an indication of how much I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The way I got my Saturn version was very fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because at the time I got my Saturn version, they were going for about $80 to $100 a piece.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought one for $15 that said the discs were damaged.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like I'll just rip them and re-burn them, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so, I, I, this is at Anime Expo, probably the last year I went, and I was going in to watch the Utena movie, and ended up just sitting out in the hall waiting for it to be over, and as I sat and tried to clean the discs, um, I realized that it was, the discs weren't scratched, they actually had stuff on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I cleaned off the discs, it was just like, it looked like, like hot glue.
[SPEAKER_02]: And cleaned it all off, and lo and behold, I had perfect copies for 15 bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And like I said, this did have a PlayStation release that is not nearly as good.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, the only way you can play it in English is on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I warn you, it is highly, highly censored.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially the part where they go in the bar.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's really, really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I say give it a try.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, your classic game of the week, boys and girls, Grandia.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is a series I know a lot of people really have a lot of love for so I'm sure that's not going to be disputed by many as a classic game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, real quick though, I do have the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Grandia 2 and Grandia 3 and then the spin-offs were Grandia Digital Museum which is basically a bunch of artwork and voice files and stuff that went with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grandia Parallel Trippers and Grandia Extreme and Grandia Online which I'm going to play Grandia Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well that's going to bring part A of our show to a close, but hey, stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're listening to us live, we're going to be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for you podcast folks, there's still more Orange Lounge Radio to come this week, so stay tuned to our podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be right back after this with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.