[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight, March 16th, 2008, Tetris and Bomberman are WiiWare bound, E-Amuse hits the DDR scene in North America, and are the rumors about a Blu-ray drive on the 360 true?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello everybody out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: We are that program on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_00]: My name is Rob Roberts, here with you every week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also here with you every week, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you, Ms.
[SPEAKER_00]: Summers?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm completely enamored with what I'm looking at.
[SPEAKER_00]: What are you looking at, pray tell?
[SPEAKER_04]: A melodica.
[SPEAKER_00]: A melodica.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are you shopping for musical instruments online tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did last week's techno didgeridoo inspire you to come up with an underappreciated instrument of your own?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I actually have, there's a few instruments that I personally want to own myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of them is a melodica, which is like a keyboard, but you play it like with the mouthpiece.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so it sounds sort of like a harmonica, but not quite.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also want an auto-harp.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I used to play auto-harp when I was little.
[SPEAKER_00]: What about kazoo?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is kazoo not satisfying to anyone anymore?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that the problem?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_00]: My wife auto-harps.
[SPEAKER_00]: Say hello to the smartass over there, Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: So your wife auto-harps, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's nice to know.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have to tell her to complain at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: She just does it on her own.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a joke in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And how are you otherwise this week, Techmaster Loki?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are you shopping for any musical instruments of your own?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just checking.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, well, let's get into how we always start off the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: First, let me introduce the chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's several people in chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of a smaller turnout, though, on the live stream than I've seen in recent weeks.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is there something else going on tonight I'm not aware of?
[SPEAKER_00]: No more Grammy Awards, no Oscars, no Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_00]: What else?
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go outside night?
[SPEAKER_00]: See Patty's Eve?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, maybe people are camping out outside the bars waiting for 6 a.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, who knows?
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyhow, we'll work with what we've got and also our little contingent over on Justin.TV on our feed there, which by the way, brand new addition to our Justin.TV arsenal.
[SPEAKER_00]: We now have a video capture card, so when we bring you clips of games, we'll actually, instead of having to point the camera at the TV, the little getaway, we'll actually be able to run the feed from the TV.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's very exciting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Happy, happy, happy.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stern is releasing a new Indiana Jones pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Dan said he'd even be willing to sell Creature of the Black Lagoon to obtain it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's going to be expensive, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: A new machine?
[SPEAKER_00]: A brand new machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys are crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he said he might even let go of Simpsons Pinball Party.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ragnarok Scrabble
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't go on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_00]: Facebook has a very Scrabble-like game.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, I think they got in trouble for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually an application called Scrabulous, is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you can play Scrabble with friends on Facebook, basically.
[SPEAKER_00]: And as much as Facebook kind of bugs me, I do like being able to play Scrabble with friends online.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's the same one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was something that was linked to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was doing the solitaire mode on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm pretty sure you have to be a Facebook member to use Scrabulous, so it was probably something different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a Facebook, but the last thing I actually did with it was through my phone when one of my friends in Mississippi found me in Facebook somehow and friended me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Jamie, I was just going to mention, I saw this earlier today and I thought of you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter 4, they're taking pre-orders on it right now for $2,590 with an $880 deposit.
[SPEAKER_02]: for the arcade hardware.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, for the machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, for the game?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: So.
[SPEAKER_00]: But what kind of machine do you have to put that in?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, normally the machines are $23,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, it's probably, you know, but, I mean, come on, 2DX?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, shit, that's just like a computer with like an HD screen attached to it and a sound system.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, most of these things nowadays, you can probably hook it up to a TV and build your own control panel for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's too sophisticated.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just have to be able to run the... Well, let me know if you end up doing that, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty hardcore, but then again...
[SPEAKER_00]: Street Fighter IV Network ID Card vs. Communication Kit
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I only have $3,000 to throw around.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course I don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably wouldn't spend it on Street Fighter 4 because I suck at Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I would do if I had that much money?
[SPEAKER_04]: Make a down payment on a house and move.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd need more than $3,000 for a down payment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was thinking the cost of the cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: $23,000, that would cover it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, this week I didn't play a whole lot, I just played basically N+, a few lunches I played that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fun, you know, it's just like N, and I think I'm like on the 10th level, but there's like 5 or 6 stages per level, so some of them are pretty hard, but that's N. And then the rest of the time I've been playing Smash Bros., but I've just basically been doing the Space Emissary mode, which...
[SPEAKER_02]: is varying levels of cool and crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, sometimes I'm just like, oh, this is pretty good level design, and then some other times it's just like, uh, I don't know, this is pretty dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, overall, I'm still playing it, and I'm only halfway through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, a little over halfway through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but, other than that, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_00]: How was M+, overall?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what some folks in chat are asking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, and plus, I like it, but I mean, it's not too different than just the regular N, except for the fact that, I don't know, different levels, that's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, well, uh, moving on to my gaming week, um, you know, I've actually been kind of sick this week, which you would think would make me want to stay home and play a lot of games, but it kind of, eh, I don't know, it kind of,
[SPEAKER_00]: Sucked my will to do a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been having these weird pains all over my side.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't want to get into all the nasty details about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, doctors don't even know what it is, and I've taken medication that have caused now side effects, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_00]: It kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yeah, I didn't play a lot of games because of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did play a few things, very random stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of the things I played were very random.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played Phantasy Star 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: I decided to download on Virtual Console quite randomly, and I checked that out, and that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: and, uh, although, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Phantasy Star 2 wasn't quite as cool as Final Fantasy, but it was different.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was one of those games, because I never had a Genesis growing up, so it was kind of one of those games I missed.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, it's kind of neat, though, now that I've played Phantasy Star online to kind of see some of the history of the Phantasy Star universe and see where a lot of that stuff has come from, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, uh, let's see, what else have I checked out?
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, World of Warcraft, as always, you know, Addict and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see, what else have I played this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm totally drawing a blank.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually skipped out on Lost Odyssey this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I checked out Brain Challenge, that new Xbox Live Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it looked dumb.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_00]: The minigames were kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_00]: The minigames were just kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just...
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess if you don't have Brain Age on the DS or I don't know, the whole novelty of these brain training games is really worn off.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's face it, the market's been really oversaturated.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess this is the only type of it available on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you must have a minigame collection for your very own on the Xbox 360, then you can go ahead and check that out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But honestly, it's really nothing to scream about.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that would be that.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's really it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so this week they officially announced that Super Mario Kart Wii will be coming to the US on April 27th.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is two days before Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, I mean, people on the Wii, they don't get Grand Theft Auto 4, so you get Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: No cars being stolen in this game, but, you know, it's still pretty violent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, some other cool stuff that you'll, of course, get the Wii wheel with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it will also be sold separately on the side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they're going to have 32 different courses up to 12 players online and media integration, 10 battle arenas and of course support for a bunch of different control methods much like Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I plan on picking them both though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I noticed some of the retro levels are making an appearance in Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of them are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: IGN actually had some footage of five levels that they had in their pre-release copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what you call it, Alpha or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've got Course 4 from the Super Nintendo Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's pretty awesome looking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then they had a remake of the Block Fort from Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although it looks a little different, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just a direct remake of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got a bunch of additional stuff on there, but it's still blocked for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then... Let's see what else was there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the ones I didn't play, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had one from the Game Boy Advance one, which I don't remember any of the battle modes in the Game Boy Advance one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's also some from Double Dash and the DS one.
[SPEAKER_02]: But to be honest, Double Dash is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Jaded says, between that and Brawl, I can say goodbye to my bank account.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm probably going to mispronounce this name, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_00]: Queltippo, I think that's how you say it, Queltippo, says the Wii wheel is about as useful as jamming the Wiimote into a giant pretzel.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can do that, too, as long as the pretzel is sideways.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually use a pretzel as a Wii steering wheel.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should do that on the show, that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, one thing that's not delicious... Mmm, yummy!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we can also do the Wii Cinnabon and alternate controller methods.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be sticky.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of messy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could use a hamburger bun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's circular.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, one thing that's not coming, though, to Mario Kart Wii is snaking.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know I'm very happy about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, according to the official Nintendo magazine in the UK, snaking is gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've changed how the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Boosting is done, I guess, around corners and no longer will you be able to speed boost by waggling the controls left and right as you power slide.
[SPEAKER_02]: This has, I guess, been scrapped and now your speed boost is determined by how long you can hold the slide.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure someone will find a different way to do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure it will be exploited one way or another.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, hey, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, now, you know how our chat room works, and a little joke comes up, and then everybody exploits it best they can.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've got Wii Churro, Wii Tortilla, Wii Hot Dog Bun.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd actually kind of use Wii Hot Dog Bun, I guess, for Mario Kart controls.
[SPEAKER_00]: What else did I want to read here?
[SPEAKER_00]: SSJ100Matt says, Mario Kart Wii looks like it's ripped from the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_00]: I kind of hope not, because the arcade version, I don't know, it just doesn't have that same feel to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: The arcade version feels...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, Mario Kart Wii isn't the only thing to get excited about this year if you're a Nintendo fan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Reggie Fils-Aimé is dropping some hints that there's a big holiday game coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, I mean, obviously every company's got to have their big holiday game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It will be revealed at this year's E3.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, he mentioned this in an interview with Jeff Keighley on Game Trailers TV.
[SPEAKER_00]: He says that the second half of 08's lineup will be announced at E3, which will probably include this year's big holiday title.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_00]: Some things that Reggie was asked about.
[SPEAKER_00]: The orchestra conductor demo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember that thing you saw at the very first E3 where we showed up?
[SPEAKER_00]: Which was the last E3 most of us went to.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, with music.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, who...
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't know if that's actually going to be a full game yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, we did hear about that Wii music game, but there was never any word if the conductor thing was a part of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, well, they asked him, Reggie, point blank about this, and Reggie said, who knows, maybe that's one of the things we'll talk about at E3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of dodging the question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_00]: He also dodged a question about Donkey Kong Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: No thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, Donkey Kong Bunga Blast sucked enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need another Donkey Kong game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Reggie did say that all the E3 releases, or actually, sorry, post-E3 releases will be, quote, maximizing all of our key franchises.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you can bet it's going to be either like an F-Zero game, the Animal Crossing game, which most people are speculating.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would bet it's the Animal Crossing game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be their big holiday title.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what I think.
[SPEAKER_00]: And what other big franchises have they still got to milk?
[SPEAKER_00]: Kirby.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ever really milked Kirby on the Wii yet, have they?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: They did milk Kirby on the DS, but not yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think there's going to be some type of Animal Crossing that will have some nifty little online feature that's going to make everybody want it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I say Animal Crossing Wii is their big title.
[SPEAKER_00]: They better fucking release Excite Truck 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: What if F-Zero was kind of Excite Truck-ish?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, that's like saying wipeouts, you know, like Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Crossing, not really for the hardcore gamers, but that sounds feasible that they would do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And every single Animal Crossing game I've ever heard of has always come out around that time of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, that'd be my guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: And because they're whores like that and they would want to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now, especially once we get to that point in, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Horse Candidate Kid Icarus
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's coming, but I don't think that's going to be it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a feeling it's going to come back.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it just worked so well in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, you watch some of those cinematics and play some of those stages, and you're like, God damn, they could put out a Kid Icarus game on the Wii and it would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or as Actdeft says in chat, Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario RPG, that would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: D.Va and Chad says, Microsoft took all the DK platformer game rights after they purchased Rare.
[SPEAKER_00]: Odd1 says, yeah, it's probably Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_00]: They said at the end of the anime movie that it'd be coming.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's also kind of one of those obvious things.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, someday there will be another Zelda game and another Mario game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wish, though, that Nintendo would come up with a new franchise.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm all down with that, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they should come up with a new franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's nice, you know, that we get a new Mario game, a new Metroid game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's like, you know, you take all the surprise out of things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we know that there's going to be... Every time you're going to put out a new system, there's obviously going to be a Mario game and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, it's like with...
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess there's always going to be a new Ratchet and Clank and that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, to be fair, Nintendo does seem to put out a few original IPs that do rather well.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, let's see, they had the Donkey Kong Bongo game, Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_00]: They had, what else?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm trying to think of the GameCube era that came out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess not Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's possible for them to come up with some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, they've done it before.
[SPEAKER_00]: WarioWare?
[SPEAKER_00]: Was that on GameCube?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, that started on Game Boy Advance, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_00]: That was fun on GameCube, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_00]: It was pretty fun on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, I mean, they're capable of churning out some new stuff once in a while when they really want to.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wii Sports 2!
[SPEAKER_00]: We're gonna whore that franchise like a bitch.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, let's... Wii Sports is kind of a new IP, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: That could be a holiday title, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why not Wii Sports 2?
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, Soccer Moms Across America would eat that shit up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're gonna whore it like a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trademarking that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, well, we'll see at this year's E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, for things that we said we would stop and wait and see on, it looks like Manhunt 2 is getting a UK release after all.
[SPEAKER_04]: According to the BBFC, they have no alternative but to give the 18 certificate to it, because basically, I guess they were overruled.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually a twice...
[SPEAKER_04]: Rejected, and it went up for review again, and they said, okay, we have to.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they finally just caved?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually the Video Appeals Committee gave their own review, and so because they've decided it should come out, it's going to come out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess I'm not too surprised by this, but what kind of makes me think that maybe they finally decided to let it come out is maybe they saw what happened in America is that the game came out and nobody cared because the game kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_00]: Blurring, crazy lighting gone
[SPEAKER_02]: whatever too bad the game sucks and you know it's not worth playing do we have any I know we don't have a whole lot of overseas listeners that listen live but are any of our overseas listeners planning on purchasing this game overseas I bet I'm going to hear a lot of no's you don't want it do yourself a favor but there's no release date announced for it yet if you want to see something like if you want to play a game kind of like that I guess and more fun maybe try the Godfather game and maybe no more heroes or just wait for something better
[SPEAKER_00]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even better.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something better.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something better, the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: That could be the new Nintendo IP.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something better.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're gonna buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we may be getting WiiWare in May, but of course Japan being super awesome and everything, they get it March 25th.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're gonna be launching with quite a few games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now they've got, of course, some of these...
[SPEAKER_02]: Okiraku Ping Pong Wii Word Puzzle Mojipitan Sakusaku Animal Panic
[SPEAKER_02]: by Konami, 4,000 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Soldier... What?
[SPEAKER_02]: 4,000 points?
[SPEAKER_02]: 1,000 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought you said 4,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ain't worth buying that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Soldier R by Hudson for 800 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Life as a King, Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles for 1,500 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Angel Solitaire by G-Mode for 500 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dr. Mario and Baculus Extermination...
[SPEAKER_02]: 4,000 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds painful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imbaculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody's Pokemon Ranch for 1,000 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Longpuss by Genki for 1,000 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of looking forward to the service.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be interesting to see what kind of games are on there.
[SPEAKER_00]: When are we supposed to be getting that here?
[SPEAKER_00]: Did they say May?
[SPEAKER_00]: It was like May...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess maybe that's a stupid question because, you know, a lot of games that you might buy on the PC and stuff don't have a lot of those types of frills, especially the casual type games.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think now in this day and age, part of the charms of, you know, having the online connections and online gaming is getting to somewhat compete with friends.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't like the way that Nintendo handles their online, especially the friend stuff, the friend codes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's got to go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, when the service actually launches in Japan, which is very, very soon...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, well, in the meantime, we do know some more details about some of the other games that will be coming out on the WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of them is Tetris.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tetris Online will be coming on the WiiWare, and you can play it with up to six players.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm guessing since it's called...
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm assuming, yeah, some of these games are going to be online, which is a little better now.
[SPEAKER_00]: So if you need another version of Tetris, you'll be able to play that on the Wii very soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: One thing I want to point out, though, based on some of these screenshots I'm looking at that's kind of cool, I'm looking at one particular two-player mode, and it looks like the wells aren't separated.
[SPEAKER_00]: It actually looks like the wells are combined into one giant well.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm not sure if there's a two-player mode where maybe both players play one giant board at the same time.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: A different spin on a well-known formula.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, it looks like this game might bring some new things to the table, which is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just asked about why I would need these types of games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Puzzle Fighter Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: With, like, Street Fighter 4 characters.
[SPEAKER_00]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_00]: RossDLUT comments in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Chat.OrangeLuncher.com Ooh, Tetris.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's so new and independent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, in a way, if you think about the history of Tetris, it actually is a very independent game at its roots.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, I mean, I get the point.
[SPEAKER_00]: Obviously, it's not that anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are still playing fucking Pac-Man Championship Edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just Pac-Man with neon lights.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's all it fucking is.
[SPEAKER_00]: But Pac-Man Championship Edition is kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's something about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not just neon lights and rave music.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, all they need to do now is come out with the Pac-Man DS system and all you whores will buy it like nothing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dark Tetsuya comments in the chat room that Rob, they actually had that mode that I'm describing there on Tengen Tetris.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember the Forbidden Tetris on the NES many years ago?
[SPEAKER_00]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That got cut up on a licensing debacle?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be even a better name for this online version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forbidden Tetris.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have Tengen Tetris.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you own Forbidden Tetris.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want Tangram Tetris.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fascinating.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whatever happened to the really shitty Tetris knockoffs we got?
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember when Tetris got really popular in the early 90s or so?
[SPEAKER_00]: We got tons of just shitty, shitty ripoffs.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had Word Triss and Hat Triss and Face Triss.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Blast Triss was real.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well Triss.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tetris 2 Bomb Bliss.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blastrous was fun because you could shoot things.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shooting always makes things better, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: It was a SuperScope game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was what made it cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, enough reminiscing, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, something else that is cool, and this is particularly cool for me, because I love Hudson, and they're bringing us a real Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay, it's for WiiWare, and it actually is a real Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we're talking about
[SPEAKER_04]: Up to eight players in one game.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least that's what Famitsu says.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be out in Japan in June, so hopefully we'll get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not too long, I hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Bomberman!
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, Bomberman Act Zero?
[SPEAKER_04]: as in piece of shit Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: And maybe that kind of just ruined Bomberman for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like it's like watching your childhood get raped right in front of your eyes.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still regularly break out the Super Nintendo and the Multitap and play, you know, Bomberman 2, Super Bomberman 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm thinking more of the recent Xbox Live one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember how they had a Bomberman come out on Xbox Live and it was pretty faithful to the original?
[SPEAKER_00]: I just, my resounding reaction to the game was, meh.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is an actual... Hudson.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Hudson!
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen, Hudson.
[SPEAKER_02]: We play Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_02]: On every system that's ever been made, ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then some.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you release four versions of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that it might seem like a good idea to release a lot of these each year, because, you know, you need money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm reading something else on here on the actual Famitsu article and from what I can see you can actually play as your me as a character in this game oh in that case I gotta buy that
[SPEAKER_00]: I sense that comment has a hint of sarcasm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, I'm just trying to pick out what I can actually read on this.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is kind of cool, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that is an interesting feature.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I mail away for an actual bomb piece of plastic that I can put on my Wii remote so that I can pretend I'm the real Bomberman?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, somebody is in your fan club in chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Somebody is on your side here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Odd1 in chat says, Bomberman is like Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_00]: I only want more, dammit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, you know that if I really like a game, I tend to like the entire series of it, no matter how much repetition it has.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: which I'll get into later in the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's my suggestion, though, for how to make Bomberman a little more appealing to people like me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Forbidden Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's on to something.
[SPEAKER_00]: and Blood Effect.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm working on the wrong side of gaming.
[SPEAKER_00]: I shouldn't be bitching about games like I do on the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: I should be making games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Show of hands in chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Forbidden Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_00]: Y or N. Here's what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a small bit of innovation and it's ripping a little bit off of Taito, but who cares.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bomberman mixed with Rampage.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're blowing up cities and you're fighting each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who doesn't want that?
[SPEAKER_02]: People like blowing things up, but they want a little bit more than just blowing up little cartoon characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to take out, like, cities.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like Rampage.
[SPEAKER_00]: We need to quit our damn jobs and start a gaming company.
[SPEAKER_00]: You are on a goldmine here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bomberman mixed with Rampage.
[SPEAKER_00]: Genius.
[SPEAKER_00]: Forbidden Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who doesn't like to blow up cities full of innocent people?
[SPEAKER_00]: In games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Only in game form.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not in real life.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just in game form.
[SPEAKER_00]: Great stress reliever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bomber Rampage.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: POPPING BUBBLE WRAP
[SPEAKER_00]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know... I have bubble wrap at my desk.
[SPEAKER_00]: How about the real thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I like popping real... Honestly, this reminds me of when I went to Barnes & Noble like ten years ago and found a big, thick book full of fat bubble wrap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not joking, and it was called Stress Relief Book.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not kidding.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are we sure there's not more to this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, maybe it just looks like it's a bubble wrap popping game, but maybe there's more to it that we just don't know about yet?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, with this bad translation thing gone wrong?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's put out by Namco Bandai.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Pac-Man's going to come out and eat it.
[SPEAKER_00]: For less than that, though, I could go to See's Candies because we all know the best part of See's Candy is that you get the little bubble wrap with everything you buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: is that only in California?
[SPEAKER_00]: I think so well then you know what I had never heard of C's until I moved here okay the national and international people can just deal for a minute here California only for a minute here it's like getting something in the mail the best part of C's candy is that you get a little piece of bubble wrap in the pack with the candy I mean think about it for ten bucks I get a little box of candy and not only do I have real bubble wrap to pop but I also have wait for it
[SPEAKER_00]: Candy!
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the best part though.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's 40 levels that you'll be able to play and of course it features vibration feedback.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and in fact they have a little link here on asovision.com slash puttyputty.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can watch a little movie of this stupid little bubble wrap thing which, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're like,
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: I forgot, every time you go into seas, they actually give you a free sample.
[SPEAKER_00]: Free is the best part.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see, Queltippo, who has a name I'm probably still mispronouncing in chat, says, Will it be like Gal's Panic, and after you pop the bubble wrap, you see a naked girl?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this has a picture of tea.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, hooray, a picture of tea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, this is great, I want one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it looks like this website sells them in five different colors.
[SPEAKER_02]: White, blue, pink, orange, and black.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, we can sell orange ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want one to annoy people at work with.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally going to get one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, let's talk about more incredibly awesome games that you can be spending your money on in the near future.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a new game that is coming out on the DS, and it's called Babysitting Mania.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually a game that you can play on the...
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Find out if you're the ultimate babysitter.
[SPEAKER_00]: What if you didn't expect was 20 of the craziest houses you've ever imagined being... And if the babies don't behave, then they get beat mania.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, now.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's not cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but apparently they're porting that to the DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's money in them DSs.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if one person buys it, they'll make back their budget.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the same Bill the Cat because, you know, we're coming up on election season and I used to vote for Bill the Cat.
[SPEAKER_00]: And plus, Bill the Cat in the game would actually be kind of cooler, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: He'd just walk around spitting on things and hacking up hairballs and then getting drunk with, I guess, hot naked chicks or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, Big the Cat is definitely going to be in it and it's, of course, being put out by BioWare and...
[SPEAKER_04]: People, basically, the co-founder who they were interviewing, Ray, is it pronounced Musica, I guess?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, you know, they actually asked him, you know, well, a lot of people don't like these characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, well, the whole point is to make you attach an emotion to the character and dislike is an emotion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, he says that all the characters are going to be really pivotal to the game, and it's not like a whole bunch of little mini-games, but something that's fully interactive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess... I don't know how I feel about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually thought that Big's part of the game was the most annoying part of Sonic Adventure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here, Froggy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should stop making retarded Sonic characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Amy was cool because she walked around smacking stuff with a hammer.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Knuckles, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mecha Sonic, really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can I take the show on a completely random, unrelated tangent for just a minute?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what you're preaching.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the best thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you were talking about Build the Cat, I started thinking about all these comic book cats, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm like, oh, then there's like Felix the Cat and there's all these other cats, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Felix the Cat is great, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then I thought about Garfield and that made me think about Garfield minus Garfield.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have you seen this cartoon?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're more funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because Garfield's not funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: But if you take out Garfield, it's actually really funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's this blog.
[SPEAKER_00]: All the ones with normal.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's this blog all about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Garfield-Garfield.tumblr.com Whatever happened to our website of the week segment?
[SPEAKER_04]: It became the classic video game of the week segment.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: We need to just for a minute here.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm hijacking the website of the week segment.
[SPEAKER_00]: My website of the week is garfield-garfield.tumblr.com Check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's hilarity.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe you'll link it in the chat room for people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll do that for you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, live listeners.
[SPEAKER_00]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's your completely random off-the-subject tangent for tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, uh... No, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Network problems, random tangents, sickness.
[SPEAKER_00]: This show has it all tonight, I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just gonna... Before you broke off on that whole Garfield thing, I was starting to say that Sonic and his friends are kind of reminding me, like, Godzilla and the other monsters, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they had the staple monsters that they made, and then they just started getting ridiculous with the monsters, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it will actually track how much you're exercising throughout the day or how much you're jiggling, I guess, and then track your progress throughout the DS title.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not sure if they also have some exercises or something that talks you through, but I guess that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: WTF L-O-L
[SPEAKER_00]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: Somebody in the room will write a challenge on their DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, for instance, the screenshot I'm looking at says, Draw Panda Bear.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then within a time limit, everybody else in the room has to draw... It sounds like Pictionary to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then everybody votes on the winner, and then you go to the next challenge.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: At first, this sounded cool, because it reminded me a lot of Apples to Apples, where you would do something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then I just started looking at this and thinking about it,
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't you do this already in PictoChat?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, couldn't you, I don't know, do the exact same thing just with like a little egg timer?
[SPEAKER_00]: Or better yet, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's how you can play LOL without even a Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's called Pen and Paper.
[SPEAKER_00]: What do I need to do this?
[SPEAKER_00]: You would actually need to get some pens and some paper.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can I use any type of pens or certain pens will work for this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Probably a pen that would show up.
[SPEAKER_00]: You wouldn't want to use a pink pen because that's kind of hard to see unless you want to go for LOL value.
[SPEAKER_00]: But make sure you have a pen.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the paper, it could be lined paper or grid paper or blank paper.
[SPEAKER_04]: If people do insist on having it in a virtual environment, open Canvas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you can network on open canvas and everyone can draw on the same picture.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, what do we need to do to get the word out about this pen and paper?
[SPEAKER_00]: That Yahoo chat thingy with the draw board is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or freaking Oikaki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think you're onto something with this pen and paper.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Look, think of what OLR Productions has come up with in the scope of just a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have Forbidden Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have the pen and paper version of LOL, which we can totally undercut these guys putting it out on DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: And remember, we're the ones that thought of LaserCats the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: True.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_00]: EA's going to buy us tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_00]: And how we'll sell.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's have T in chat says, pen and paper is the wave of the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, how about the wave of the future that is actually not necessarily in ours anytime soon?
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess who else is getting Wii Fit before us?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_00]: How about, I don't know, what's a country we don't hear about very often in the news?
[SPEAKER_00]: How about... Slovakia?
[SPEAKER_00]: How about the country of Chad in Africa?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is Chad getting the game before we are?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but they're getting it in Australia.
[SPEAKER_00]: Chad ruined our elections.
[SPEAKER_00]: Same thing, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Chad, Australia, what's the difference?
[SPEAKER_04]: Australia's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love Australia, of course I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we did get Priscilla, Queen of the Desert from them.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of my favorite movies ever is Muriel's Wedding, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Olivia Newton-John.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actdeft hit the nail on the head.
[SPEAKER_00]: Without Australia, you would never have The Dingo Ate My Baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: You would never have that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or the Didgeridoo Techno.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's take a moment to salute our Australian fans and their history.
[SPEAKER_00]: Their great history.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you, Australia.
[SPEAKER_04]: From OLR.
[SPEAKER_00]: So see, Australia, because of their greatness and contributions to culture, they get the game a little early.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought that was very nice of Nintendo to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyway, they're getting it on May 8th.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting ours on May 19th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be coming out for $150 Australian, which is, the equivalence is 140 here, or 91 Euro.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already sold over a million.
[SPEAKER_00]: Our dollar went to shit, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Our dollar really, really went to shit sometime in the past couple years, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, if it gets any worse, we're going to have to start calling it pesos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, I could go to Europe, and I could work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could go to Europe like people from Mexico come here to earn money and come back rich.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, like I was saying, it's already sold over a million units in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out on April 25th in Europe for £69.99 in the UK and €89.99 everywhere else in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're getting it on the 19th of May.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that gets the whatever award for me, but
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations, Australia.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've beat out Europe and America.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kudos to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're just trying to make it fair, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kirpok can ask a question.
[SPEAKER_00]: What is the capital of Australia?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sydney?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the most common mistake.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just like, but like, see, I can, it's Canberra.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Canberra.
[SPEAKER_00]: But here's the thing is that, but you could do the same thing is that like quick Australian listeners.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's the capital of Florida?
[SPEAKER_00]: How many of you said Miami?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Tallahassee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Miami is the capital of where old folks go to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Miami is also the capital of cocaine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_00]: Love Miami.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: When have you been to Miami?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I went to their airport once on my way to Jamaica.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have been to Miami thousands of times thanks to the power of television.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually been to Miami once, and I was two years old.
[SPEAKER_00]: And SSJ100Matt has a perfect example.
[SPEAKER_00]: You ask people what the capital of California is, hello, we live there, and most people don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you say Los Angeles, then you need to get your head out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, wait a minute, you said Sydney was the capital of Australia.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get your head out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't live there, so I have an excuse.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or get your ass out of your head, because it's Australia.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get it upside down?
[SPEAKER_00]: And the toilet flush backwards?
[SPEAKER_00]: What the hell happened to tonight's show?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just not right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to keep going then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a game that's coming out here in May pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty psyched about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Blastworks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Originally it was Tamiki Fighters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course now it's been... It's very little like Tamiki Fighters now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still the same kind of concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's kind of neat about it though is you'll actually... Of course the game has about 20 different levels you can play and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And plays a little bit like Katamari meets a really intense shooter game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now you'll be able to design completely new ships...
[SPEAKER_02]: New levels, new enemies, new AI patterns, and new bullet patterns.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, completely customizable, and you can share all this content over WeConnect24, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So some of the levels, I guess, they were just showing off to, like, Joystick, for example.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them looked like the environment was made out of paper, and you're actually flying a paper airplane and fighting other paper airplanes and origamis, enemies, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So really cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus the game itself also has unlockable versions of Tumiki Fighters and some of the other games made by Kenta Cho.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you're interested in checking out Tumiki Fighters, it's actually available for free on his website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just do a search for Tumiki Fighters and definitely check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is slated to come out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: in May, and I can't wait to check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think this is going to be one of those games that a lot of people aren't going to know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of those under-the-radar games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it going to be one of those under-the-radar costs, where it's only $20, or do we know a price point on this yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: If I remember correctly, I think it was like $39.99.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's kind of your typical wheat.
[SPEAKER_00]: One step below your AAA Wii titles, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, I think the value's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if it was just going to be a straight port of Tamaki Fighters, it might be a little high, but with all the, like, user-created stuff, I mean, you can get pretty crazy with this game, so... Alright, it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very good gaming story to bring us back from our Capitals of the World discussion.
[SPEAKER_00]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Loki's always working hard for OLR, isn't he?
[SPEAKER_00]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, definitely, there's...
[SPEAKER_02]: GameTrailers.com GameTrailers.com
[SPEAKER_00]: But actually this will be the entirety of Japan is getting these releases.
[SPEAKER_00]: This week in gaming on March 19th, they are getting on the Xbox 360 Armored Core for Answer, Army of Two, Blazing Angels 2, Need for Speed Pro Street, Sengoku Mosu 2, and that's quite a few Xbox 360 games for one week.
[SPEAKER_00]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Odd1 in chat says this is his favorite part of the show, Rob butchering the Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why I read them, because I can't pronounce any of them.
[SPEAKER_00]: PlayStation 3, I can pronounce Armored Core, that's easy enough.
[SPEAKER_00]: PlayStation 3 also gets Armored Core, also gets Arm Eve 2, also gets Blazing Angels 2, but gets another game, Folk Soul...
[SPEAKER_00]: you might just know that as folklore but that's actually getting a price reduction that's already been out there it's just a price reduction also getting a price reduction on PlayStation 3 Resistance Ridge Racer 7 which I can't pronounce and Mobile Suit Gundam Target Insight all getting price reductions this week
[SPEAKER_00]: and, uh, cheaper games is never bad news.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, on the Nintendo Wii, speaking of price reductions, Bomberland Wii is moving into the best, but some new games coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Spider-Man 3 just now coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would suggest you just pass on that, but maybe you want to pick up the House of the Dead 2 and 3 with the Wii Zapper, um, also being sold independently there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, Dekasporta also coming out on the Nintendo Wii in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Moving on to the PlayStation 2, uh,
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing really new coming out there, just some price reductions on the Godfather and Kamiwaza.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something to look forward to next week is the Metal Gear Solid collection, if you're looking out for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's check out the handhelds.
[SPEAKER_00]: Moving on to the Nintendo DS, Bangayo Spirits comes out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_00]: Cho Naketsu, Koku Kunio-kun, Dodgeball comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is going to be a fun week for Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Coming out from Konami, Kachishima Kosaku DS, Dekuru Otoko no Love and Success.
[SPEAKER_00]: SimCity DS 2 also comes out from EA on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: And quickly glancing at the PSP,
[SPEAKER_00]: To see if there's anything of note for you guys in Japan on there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Biohazard Trilogy Box.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that's the movies.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, not the games.
[SPEAKER_00]: But if you want that on your PSP, you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, a port of Need for Speed Pro Street.
[SPEAKER_00]: And since Skype was recently released in Japan, I believe we covered that on last week's news, the PSP microphone is finally hitting the shelves this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want Kunio-kun Dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you can import it from one of your favorite import retailers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or if you wait a few months...
[SPEAKER_04]: I have some releases for you guys On the 20th
[SPEAKER_04]: CSI Crime Scene Investigation Hard Evidence on Wii Mystery Dungeon Sharon the Wanderer on DS Ratchet and Clank Size Matters Sega Superstars Tennis on a bunch of stuff
[SPEAKER_04]: Spinout, Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas 2 on Xbox 360 and PS3, Victorious Boxers Challenge, and then we've got some games on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles, Ring of Fate, we have Offroad for PS2, PC, and PSP, Samurai Warriors 2, Extreme Legends, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very surprised no one mentioned Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles Ring of Fate in their gaming weeks because I heard the game came out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of my friends picked it up and have been raving about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like Crystal Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't either, but the DS version doesn't look quite like the GameCube one, so it might be worth a look.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just curious.
[SPEAKER_00]: How about Chatters?
[SPEAKER_00]: Chatters, any of our Chatters pick it up?
[SPEAKER_00]: Post your reviews real quickly.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll read some of them in a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the US, we're getting a few things that are pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: This week, of course, Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas 2 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega Superstars Tennis coming out on almost everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, and the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Metal Gear Solid Essentials Collection is coming out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to relive some of those older Metal Gear games before number 4 comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Condemned 2 Bloodshot on PlayStation 3, apparently a week late.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot Shots Golf Out of Bounds on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lost in Blue 3 on the DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm still shocked that they actually got a third game in that series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't be surprised if we see a fourth one either.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're whoring that thing to death.
[SPEAKER_02]: SingStar 90s Edition is going to be coming out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Samurai Warriors 2 Extreme Legends on PlayStation 2 and Xbox 360 via download.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Worms of Space Oddity on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantasy Aquarium on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go Pets Vacation Island on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which looks really weird and kind of stupid looking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pro Evolution Soccer 2008 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That one also is a week late.
[SPEAKER_02]: George of the Jungle on PlayStation 2 Wii and the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation 3 version of Karaoke Revolution American Idol is finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That totally delayed for about a month now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe that's it next week though the week after next I should say and I can't wait for this Crisis Core Final Fantasy 7 for PSP alright well moving on talking about something recently hitting the US DDR you remember DDR?
[SPEAKER_00]: our whole show used to be our whole show used to be about DDR
[SPEAKER_00]: and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And DDR is still going.
[SPEAKER_00]: DDR, obviously, you know, we get phone calls from folks on Skype once in a while.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why don't you love Bomani like you used to?
[SPEAKER_00]: Then we have to say, because it hasn't changed.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, anyhow, actually, DDR is changing a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: E-Amusement, you've heard of this before, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: E-Amusement is a system they have in Japan, where you basically have these little cards.
[SPEAKER_00]: Picture, y'all know, if you've been to the arcades, y'all know Initial D, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: How you have the cards.
[SPEAKER_00]: Picture something like that, but on a DDR machine, where you can kind of save your high scores, but it's also hooked into the internet, and so you can have these global leaderboards and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_00]: The E-Amusement system, finally, after all these years, is hitting America.
[SPEAKER_00]: And this is coming from an official Konami website, ddronlinecommunity.com is their website, and it's got the Konami logos and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: They are announcing that Naperville, Illinois, of all places, because when I think of arcade gaming, I think of Naperville, Illinois.
[SPEAKER_00]: But this must be one hella good arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: Brunswick Zone is the arcade that's going to be getting the EMU system.
[SPEAKER_00]: And come to think of it, this is an arcade that usually does a lot of the beta tests for DDR, so I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just kind of funny that, you know,
[SPEAKER_00]: Ground Zero for TDR Evolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure because I don't know too much about Benson, but maybe it's close to one of Benson's distribution centers or something like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just guessing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brunswick makes me think of bowling.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, I think Brunswick did make bowling stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made bowling pins.
[SPEAKER_00]: They might do entertainment stuff, you know, in other places.
[SPEAKER_00]: But anyhow, and as Konami says on the site, it's the new online service which connects arcade locations in North America via the internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Arcade players can compete with each other, review their ranking, tournament results, save the play data, and more.
[SPEAKER_00]: Konami will expand this new level service nationwide with Brunswick Bowling and Billiards.
[SPEAKER_00]: So coming to a bowling alley near you.
[SPEAKER_00]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now my question is, is this enough to make you interested in DDR again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_00]: I say not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of miss the old internet ranking that we had back in the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, that was old school.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, I mean, besides the fact that I do miss DDR a little bit for the nostalgia value, here's the reason why I don't think this is exactly the kick in the butt in the community that DDR's kind of needed for about, oh, four years now, is that the internet's already been doing this long before Konami decided to officially endorse it.
[SPEAKER_00]: This has been going on since like 4th Mix.
[SPEAKER_00]: What are those tracking sites for DDR?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, they've come and gone.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's how long those things have been around.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, didn't a long time ago, and it was built in the 4th Mix, they had a code that you could write down that you could go onto the website and plug it in, and there's your internet rankings.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: And then somebody could challenge you if they thought you were lying about your score.
[SPEAKER_00]: Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: GS68 says VJ Army.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, like that, but DDR.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was one for DDR they had.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's what they need to do, and this would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, you could have certain teams or whatever that you...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess associate yourself with I don't know how many different colors or whatever and then you could say like you play different arcades around the country or the world or whatever and you kind of capture them and they become like blue or whatever or red or whatever your color is and then kind of like remember how they had with Soul Calibur?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now here's the thing, you're talking about making DDR a more competitive game, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what I've been saying for five years on this program that DDR's needed to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is innovation sitting in there in the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just make DDR more competitive as opposed to cooperative game.
[SPEAKER_00]: You could make a whole new game out of it and really kick some butt in the franchise, but nobody's listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: What they need to do, and I'm not sure who's in charge of the DDR games, is they need to get someone new in charge of the DDR games.
[SPEAKER_00]: DDR Recall, says Actdeft, was the name of what I was trying to think of earlier.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyhow, so those of you that are still playing DDR, and I know we have a lot of DDR fans on the list.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not trying to knock DDR.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, obviously, it's still a great game because it keeps you physical and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, if I had the money and a room, I'd be buying a machine for my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd still be playing it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just frustrates me that they won't innovate the damn game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't have time to make it down to arcades anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll say it one more time.
[SPEAKER_00]: If anybody happens to be listening, and I know we have folks on the inside that listen to this show once in a great while.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nuke your code, build something from the ground up, innovate in the process.
[SPEAKER_00]: Watch money flow in.
[SPEAKER_02]: And stop, for the love of God, I know that you like doing these other modes like the fitness mode and that kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't need to go that crazy with this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I think they've made it too user-friendly, too simple, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think you need a training mode in every single DDR game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know I didn't need a training mode to play the damn game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I learned just fine by playing the damn game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there is more news out there that will make iPhone owners happy, including myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are going to be some game releases, including Pac-Man and Galaga.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that makes me very happy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also... Sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: and Zuma and Peggle, which I don't really give a crap about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just care about Pac-Man and Galaga.
[SPEAKER_00]: Peggle is really awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, thank God!
[SPEAKER_02]: I can play Pac-Man!
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if you play with your finger.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can't you play pretty much all these games on the iPod anyway?
[SPEAKER_00]: Including Peggle?
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is actually one of the better systems.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think the iPod was made for Peggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: From what I hear, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, Bejeweled, you have to kind of cycle through all the, like,
[SPEAKER_02]: Gems and stuff using the little, whatever the fuck they call that thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Touch wheel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Touch wheel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gay wheel, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole screen is touch screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you should just be able to poke whichever one and then poke the one next to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Bejeweled would be good on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that would work pretty well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised they haven't put Bejeweled on the DS yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they really...
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck, put a PopCap collection on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Watch how much that sells.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what else would work out?
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what other games would work really well on the iPhone?
[SPEAKER_00]: New things.
[SPEAKER_00]: New games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Things that haven't been thought of yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: New stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have this game that we would like to pitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Pen and Paper.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use the iPhone as paper and you can write stuff with your stylus, which is the pen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, and here's one.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's based off a popular Saturday Night Live sketch and you have cats and they have lasers attached to their heads.
[SPEAKER_00]: And where you touch on the screen, you shoot lasers at dogs and people.
[SPEAKER_00]: And sometimes other laser cats in multiplayer mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just had a random thought pop into my head.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually had a different video game experience this week, but that was watching the Family Guy Star Wars special.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did it feel like a game or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they were going into an asteroid field and it was asteroids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, apparently the Chinese Olympics website has been accused of game piracy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um,
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they have been stealing some Flash games that they feature on the website and kind of changing them just a little bit, but they're still blatantly stealing them.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to the creator of these Flash games, Kaden Batrick, who noticed some very similar similarities with different games like FUA Fights, The Olympic Clouds, which is very similar to his Snow Day game that he has.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, there are some other ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: that were also very similar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, you know, these have been removed from the Olympic sites as of last Monday, but there's still a couple games that are on there that may be stolen from some other websites as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, as if we didn't need more reasons to say the Olympics suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: Odd1 has an interesting comment in chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: It says, wait, aren't most Flash games rip-offs of each other or classic games?
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously, the Flash arena is rife with IP theft and copying.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, they are, but this I think was blatant.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, just like, if you made a Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: game, but instead you changed it to, I don't know, a female chicken or something like that, that would be a blatant rip-off of Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know, you called it like Chick Sisters or something like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wasn't that the PETA game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes, that was.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, blatant ripoff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not really, though, because the level design was totally different.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it was crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: I get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Made me hungry for chicken, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And really, who goes to the Chinese Olympics website to play Flash games?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, are people that bored?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well...
[SPEAKER_00]: We're just about done with part A tonight, but first off we have to read about our stupid person of the week.
[SPEAKER_00]: And actually, I don't know, this isn't so much stupid as it's just kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't really know how else to say it, so let's cue some music to read this very sad story.
[SPEAKER_00]: A 15-year-old boy in the Austin area of Austin, Texas got killed, gunshot wound to the head.
[SPEAKER_00]: The boy was playing a video game and his friend just shot him in the head.
[SPEAKER_00]: 13-year-old shooter.
[SPEAKER_00]: 13 years old shoots his 15-year-old friend in the head over a video game, I suppose, is what the story is trying to say.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because they do make a mention at the very end of this story.
[SPEAKER_00]: The boys were playing a video game.
[SPEAKER_00]: The game was called God of War.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yes, because there's tons of gun violence in God of War.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you so much to these kids.
[SPEAKER_00]: for giving Gamers Everywhere a wonderful name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where were the parents?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where?
[SPEAKER_02]: Out buying more ammo, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I don't see how... There's no way they're going to be able to tie that to the game because there's no fucking guns in God of War.
[SPEAKER_02]: At all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's not funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just kids shooting each other.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and Last Blade II.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really exactly when the exact time frame is in Japan, because there's references to the Shinsengumi, to fighting for the Shogun, so I would assume it's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And from what I can tell from the characters in the game, it's sort of right around that transitional period.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's really just, you've got people who use different weapons.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the guys who worked on...
[SPEAKER_04]: Guilty Gear actually helped develop this game, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's really, really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've also got your choice of using power or speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can have a stronger, slower character.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can have someone who's weaker but faster.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, you've got your attacks and combos that incorporate all of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I just really think that it's a very nice game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the other things that it brought into it was a deflect where you could block a move and then you would be able to instantly attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I thought that was a pretty neat function as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Last Blade was the first SNK game to bring in super cancels into its gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you've got desperation moves, super moves, all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just really, really a fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The series is fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the thing I like about the music is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty, I guess, almost on the classical end.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the things I really liked about it, and this is going to sound kind of cheeseball, is that when you go into each stage, you sort of have a little cutscene in the top corner that sets up the area you're playing in.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it's really cool, not just for the story, the characters themselves, but the environments in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say there was... I'm trying to remember the character that I played the most because I played the one who dressed up as her brother.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't remember the character.
[SPEAKER_00]: You played a cross-dresser?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say there was another game that's out there that sold one point... It was Kojiro, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: 0.18 million now for Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, well there you have it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight's classic game of the week, The Last Blade.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just the whole damn series.
[SPEAKER_00]: On every platform.
[SPEAKER_00]: Neo Geo, Dreamcast, there's one on Dreamcast, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe that there were PS2 versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to say that there were, but of course the Dreamcast one was like, beautiful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, so we'll say the Dreamcast version then, because you're such a Dreamcast fan.
[SPEAKER_00]: really everything alright so check that out The Last Blade that's going to bring our part A to a close tonight so we're going to take a break and we'll be back though never fear with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio