[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio for this Part B of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the things coming to Xbox Live, like Darwinian, some Ikaruga, and the Penny Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we're going to get into some Wii news, and we'll start off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, if you didn't listen to Part A, then you're a witch!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you're a witch!
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, damn you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming to the Wii, and this is, ooh, big shock here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock Band was announced for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be getting the special edition, otherwise known as the one with all the instruments.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that is coming to, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Retailers June 22nd for the small sum of $170.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's almost the price of a Wii console.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, there are a few things you should know about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: For one, the drum is white.
[SPEAKER_07]: And number two, it's going to contain five bonus songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's only because there are absolutely no downloads for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: PlaySation 2
[SPEAKER_07]: and it will come with a powered USB hub, much like the Xbox 360 release.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you really, I mean, honestly, people out there, did you really think that Rock Band on the Wii was going to have download content?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, did you really think that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because where would they put it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only other thing they could do is already have it on the disc and then you, you know, download little unlock codes, but that would piss people off even more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it would piss people off.
[SPEAKER_07]: The thing I would, I don't know, maybe download it to SD memory cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really, I think that's what it's going to take, you know, somehow make your own file formats, because I know that Nintendo has their stupid block set up for game saves and stuff like that, but it doesn't necessarily mean programs have to use that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if you look at it, you know, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: has its own save data, you know, Excite Truck and Endless Ocean use MP3s, so who's to say that you couldn't make some sort of, like,
[SPEAKER_07]: Dream on on all that stuff, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just dream on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, I was choking on toast.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, honestly, what my honest reaction though was when I heard that news about Rock Band being on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually, I was like, I thought it was already on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because seriously, Rock Band's on like every system, just like Guitar Hero and all this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I thought Rock Band was already on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I, of course, did not make that my system of choice because I knew it wouldn't have the download songs and I knew it wouldn't be probably quite the graphical quality of the other versions.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait until they shoehorn it onto the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure that's just a matter of time, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be insane.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would have to use Wi-Fi, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could do the drums with the stylus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tap, tap, tap, tap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that would work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe make use of that Guitar Hero expansion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably not, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: You would have a separate guitar that wouldn't be compatible with the other one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just you wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if singing is more your thing, it could be very soon that a SingStar-type clone is coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like it's called JoySound.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently Hudson is making this game called JoySound.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be something you can actually get on WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll download this JoySound thing and you get it from a server that's being exclusively set up for that, whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the trick with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Instead of having to pay for individual songs, you subscribe to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're hoping to release it this summer in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to have 20,000 songs available at launch, 1,000 more every month.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they have that, I'm sorry, but that's sad for SingStar, especially when they're touting that they're going to have this huge long thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, actually, here's the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Hudson that's putting it up there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So imagine, if you will, they could do something like this and brand it with Karaoke Revolution, and boom, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bring that over to the U.S.,
[SPEAKER_06]: But with 20,000 songs, I can't help but think it's just going to be like MIDI songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like the quality of the songs is going to be really crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: MP3s, I mean, they could do it that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that wouldn't be that hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually think it's kind of a neat setup and it's a different way of trying to do things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, it all depends on price.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember Iridium very vaguely, but I did play that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're fighting aliens and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it apparently has elements from Gradius and Defender and a few others that are on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's actually 500 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_09]: And before I forget to mention, International Karate is also 500 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really curious how those Commodore 64 games are going to translate over on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really curious to check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the other game that is out is Cruisin' U.S.A.,
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a Nintendo 64 game for a thousand Wii points.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, well, it's Cruisin' USA.
[SPEAKER_09]: It probably still controls just as badly, and it's still just as weird as it was before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, was it Cruisin' USA?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to remember Cruisin' USA on Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember it was very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68 says I wouldn't buy Cruisin' USA for even 100 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no, I'm thinking, I'm sorry, I'm thinking of Rush the Rock.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rush the Rock was okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had that on Nintendo 64, and no, that wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cruisin' USA, no, that probably wasn't very good either.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cruisin' World was a lot better.
[SPEAKER_07]: California Speed, not very good either.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, all the games made by Midway that were racing...
[SPEAKER_07]: Not very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hydro Thunder.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Hydro Thunder.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Thunder games are good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hydro Thunder was brilliant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can only play that game in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't play it on console.
[SPEAKER_06]: No way.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had it on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: No way way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll tell you what, it sucked on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sucked ass on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Japan, you're going to be able to get one of the games that Jamie's been super excited about for a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rondo of Blood or Dracula X Rondo of Blood is coming to the Japanese Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that is the Turbo Duo version.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word on how much it's going to cost you, but I mean, hey, that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And unfortunately, I don't think we're going to see it come over here because that would mean it would need to be localized and no one wants to spend any time on something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you can play the Japanese version, awesome!
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, all the cutscenes had a text on them.
[SPEAKER_09]: All they'd have to do is just translate the text and not worry about the dialogue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's still effort, and you remember they don't want to put effort into these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is true, and so that wouldn't be that hard, but once again, it takes a little bit of effort to change all the text.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, isn't the PSP version all graphiced up, too?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, but don't they have the original one on there too?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do they?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they have, I think the original one, wasn't it Dracula X?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's not the new Rondo, or the... Yeah, while these guys get Dracula X Rondo of Blood, you know what we'll get on US Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_09]: The stupid, crappy...
[SPEAKER_09]: Pooh version.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it came out over here as Dracula X on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought it was our Castlevania V. No, because the Dracula X series doesn't necessarily fall in with the actual Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only there was a Castlevania V. No, there was a Castlevania V, I swear to God.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did get a Castlevania V, but it wasn't Dracula X. Castlevania V, in fact, I do believe it was re-released with the Castlevania Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm fairly positive that it was not Dracula X. Then you're right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I must be crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could have sworn it was Castlevania V we got here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because there was Super Castlevania IV and I don't remember what after that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Castlevania V came out on PlayStation if I'm remembering right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or no.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Castlevania 64. 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: That does not exist.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Castlevania 64 does not exist.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not worth losing sleep over.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does not exist to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's dead to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dead to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: And to DarkTetsuya, technically Dracula XX was Nocturne in the Moonlight, which we got over here as Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, some other systems games are making its way to the Virtual Console on the Nintendo Wii very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Sega Master System, and we mentioned this a couple shows ago, but now it is official.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are making their way to the North American Virtual Console, and they're going to cost 400 points a game, so it makes it the cheapest system of any of them out there, because it's only going to be 4 bucks a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: The NES games are 5 bucks a pop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two of the first games that are going to be coming out that should be out soon, that probably means any week now, Wonder Boy and Fantasy Zone are going to be the first two that come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fantasy Zone, of course, was one of the classic games of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Fantasy Zone's a good game, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I don't know if the Sega Master System port of it's my favorite, but, you know, it is, for four bucks, probably not a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, we'll see what other types of Sega Master System games show up very soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to correct myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Symphony of the Night was X2.
[SPEAKER_09]: XX was the Super Nintendo release in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too confusing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn them for releasing completely different games over here in the US than they did over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn the man.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just should have brought it out over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was so... Well, I've had it on this show before.
[SPEAKER_09]: We hooked it up through the old setup.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, very few people remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was years ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: And did screen captures and everything through the webcam.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was the whole German intro and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I like fantasy, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, another wonderful, wonderful game is going to be remade for WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that is going to be one of the best pinball simulating games ever is Alien Crush.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can actually download Alien Crush right now and play it on virtual console.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's really, really, really happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: So far, there's only, of course, note for it being out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we could get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really hope that we do, because hopefully Hudson loves us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although, honestly, I would prefer to have Devil's Crush myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: What happens to... Because I have the original Alien Crush, so I guess I'm just going to have to have two.
[SPEAKER_09]: What I'm understanding from this screen capture I'm seeing on here...
[SPEAKER_09]: is that instead of the top-down view, you actually have a slightly more diagonal overhead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of like more traditional, or I shouldn't say more traditional, more newer.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, our speak grammar good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: The current types of pinball games look like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're looking at it from an angled view, like you would be more accurately.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like an actual table.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's more of an actual table layout.
[SPEAKER_09]: but Alien Crush is still pretty sexy.
[SPEAKER_09]: He played a whole crap load of Alien Crush.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, I think he played that game for an entire day once.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I still meant to bring over my Turbo Duo so he could play Devil's Crush at the time, but now it's out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and now he's not my roommate anymore, so, tear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe he'll get a Wii at some point, though, and buy the game to relive those memories all over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, one thing he's not going to have made available to him is one of the brand new features to Club Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is a memory card that you can get, an SD memory card, 128 megs worth of music from different Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And some of the songs that they have on there, of course, songs from Super Mario Sunshine, Donkey Kong Jungle Beat, Catch Touch Yoshi, that's kind of a weird name,
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendogs, Mario Kart Double Dash, Legend of Zelda The Wind Waker, Pikmin 2 and Super Mario Brothers and of course Club Nintendo is exclusively Japanese and they get all sorts of cool stuff including classic controllers that look like Super Famicom controllers and DS games for the Game & Watch stuff and that stupid Tingle balloon fight game
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is an official Nintendo product.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yet we know Nintendo kind of hates the SD card.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this thing is so weird to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't say they hate the SD card.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they put damn SD... But they just use it for the weirdest stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, the most obvious things, like extra storage, they don't use it for.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this... I mean, like... What would you really use this on?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, custom songs?
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can play these songs in Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoopee!
[SPEAKER_06]: How many people remember Excite Truck?
[SPEAKER_06]: You and who else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Me!
[SPEAKER_06]: And who else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nelly!
[SPEAKER_06]: KU, your wife, and who else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I can't help it if Excite Truck is the greatest racing game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Until Excite Truck 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sooner than later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well guess what kind of story I've got for you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, when you hear that music, you know something really tragic has happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that is that another person has been killed over video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or at least that's what the media wants you to believe.
[SPEAKER_06]: A 15-year-old boy was killed by his 18-year-old friend William Suarez because he refused to hand over the video game he was playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what did Suarez do?
[SPEAKER_06]: He whipped out a .32 caliber Smith & Wesson from his waistband, not Mommy and Daddy's closet, not under the bed.
[SPEAKER_06]: He whipped it out from his waistband and shot his 15-year-old friend in the head.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is this world coming to?
[SPEAKER_06]: The killer is 18 years old.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's been charged with manslaughter, illegal possession of a firearm, assault with a dangerous weapon, and discharging a firearm within 500 feet of the dwelling.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why manslaughter?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I would think murder, if anything, because he intended to kill him.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about a bullet wound to the head?
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll scare him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just give him the chair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just give him the chair already.
[SPEAKER_06]: A quote from the article, witnesses told authorities that Suarez then put the gun down on the kitchen counter and began saying, this just didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: So kind of like he went crazy or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, here's the question, did video games really have anything to do with this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yet, here are the headlines that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Family, game led to teen's murder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video game linked to fatal shooting in Brockton.
[SPEAKER_09]: More like Psycho killed Kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'd be the same thing as if he had a Furby a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or a Tickle Me Elmo or whatever the fuck it was called.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what they need to do to this kid?
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to burn him.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because he's a witch!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, he's much, much worse than that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Being a witch is not bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Being a psycho murderer is.
[SPEAKER_07]: You see, I thought he had two lives and so that's why I didn't know he would be dead forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you News Media, by the way, for...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm blowing this story completely out of proportion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bitch, come back on Imagine Babies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not laughing at that, I swear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it really isn't funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it makes me angsty.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know after those types of stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know this part of the show is coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: The F-Use of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And an F you to the ferret?
[SPEAKER_09]: The ferret had to get a few things out from being stuck in your closet for how long?
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to... Well, I don't really want to say F you to California Burger because really all I wanted was the pastrami.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they didn't give me the burger that was supposed to go with the pastrami.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I feel deprived of meat.
[SPEAKER_09]: So F you to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And F you to my lack of fundage for the presents.
[SPEAKER_09]: A big FU poopy ball to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: FU to money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, money is just FU to lack of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: FU to people who drive big trucks that can't figure out where in the lane they're supposed to be because, you know, for some reason when people need to make a left turn, they start heading towards the right and cutting into my lane and then they make their left turn because their truck's too big.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not my fault you bought a big truck.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't mean you have to run me off the road.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU of the week goes to the fact that I'm about to enter my fourth week of having pains that float around my abdomen, my back, my stomach, and no one knows what's wrong with me still.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a blood test on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still waiting on the results.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going for Alien Chess Popper.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, I hope not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I guess that would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if I'm going to go, let's go out with a bang like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: But
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you have the special?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: This might still make people angsty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, but I didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_09]: GameStop is not going to be carrying Game Boy and Game Boy Color stuff, games, systems, crap that goes with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hoping to have it all wiped out by the end of April.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't know they were still carrying Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not angsty about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised they still got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you can always go to GameCrazy for that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: or playing trade or any other mom and pops out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or buy yourself a freaking Game Boy Advance and get with the times already.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there were some really, really good games that were old Game Boy and Game Boy Color games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But those old games will work on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_09]: They will.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if they're not going to be selling the games, you have to go to the little trader places.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yet, I do have to admit, one of the cutest Game Boys I ever had.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why I gave it to my sister.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the stupidest thing I ever did.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I had a Game Boy Color that when you turned it on, it had a little Pikachu around the power thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so it looked like his cheeks lit up because the power was on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it was Pichu, not Pikachu, but you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had a pink Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_06]: How girly.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is me who isn't like the uber girly girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just...
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted a pink one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I wanted them because they were hard to get.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mine was clear and has no backlight.
[SPEAKER_09]: We put a backlight in mine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had to use those stupid little reading light things that would clip to the top so you could actually see the screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had a friend put an afterburner in mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think you're just happy about having a chance to take apart something technological.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you may not be able to get Game Boy and Game Boy Color games, but one game you will be able to get probably pretty soon is the sequel to 50 Cent Bulletproof.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_07]: 50 Cent to Blood in the Sand.
[SPEAKER_07]: And my god, is it shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically, if I remember the premise of it correct,
[SPEAKER_07]: Fitty goes to the Middle East to perform for somebody and the promoter doesn't have the money to pay him so instead of paying him money he pays him in a diamond encrusted skull which gets stolen by I can only assume terrorists and then it's up to Fitty to get the skull back.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkTetsuya says, please tell me this is an early April Fool's Day joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm afraid it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost kind of want to agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do bring up an interesting point, Loki, is that if it's almost like self-parody or something, it's actually kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think he's trying to make it out like, dude, it's 50 Cent fighting terrorists.
[SPEAKER_07]: How much more American do you need?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, he shits red, white, and blue.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how American it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you know, no more taking on gangbangers.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's now time to take on terrorists.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hurrah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's... And people will buy it!
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the first thing I thought of when I heard there was a sequel to this game is I thought, you mean Bulletproof 1 sold enough copies to necessitate this?
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I just... I wanted to make sure I have the correct, um... What was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: The, uh... The correct name for all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think...
[SPEAKER_07]: I am pretty positive that was the actual plot to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if this is trying to be like, you know how some movies are so bad they're actually kind of good, like Showgirls?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is going to be like the Showgirls of video gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so bad, it's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: You are a whore.
[SPEAKER_09]: You made me sit down and watch that movie and I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess Bulletproof sold, it was a multi-million dollar, or multi-million copy selling game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember it selling more than one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's buying it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blend the Sand is something more exotic, more Hollywood blockbuster.
[SPEAKER_07]: This game sets 50s character against a cabal of international gangsters on a far-flung, bullet-ridden adventure.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's inspired by Three Kings meets Lock, Stock, and Two Smoking Barrels.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's definitely a crime story.
[SPEAKER_07]: The developer credited 50 with pushing the game's creators to consider novel locations and said that MC played a big part in crafting the game's still-secret story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I guess the game will run on the Unreal 3 engine because every other fucking game on the face of the earth runs on the...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not a lot of games out there for the urban market and stuff like this does do really well actually so it's just crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Even this?
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it sounds like that they're actually putting some effort into the game because, I mean, the first one was pretty cinematic.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this one, you know, being that it's on the Unreal 3 engine and stuff like that, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to see how it looks.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, the whole thing sounds ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: as the months will go on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: But I imagine the shirts will be more expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should try GameStop.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I know I hate to push GameStop, but I mean... Or other game box stores.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, gaming chains.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or, I don't know, allow them to be purchased on their website from independent retailers out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be the way to do it, I would think.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, only a few.
[SPEAKER_06]: Depressing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, hey, we got some spam in the interim as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_09]: And another couple emails.
[SPEAKER_09]: So actually, I might just be generous and read the two new ones that came in as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: So starting off, this one says, Hi, all.
[SPEAKER_09]: First, sorry for not contacting you before, but I've been listening to your show via iTunes podcasts for about 18 months.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big fan of DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: And wouldn't like to miss hearing her every week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So on that note, have you ever looked into using, I guess it's ustream.tv, stickcam.com with chat, plus storage for shows and have been used by Leo Laporte for TWIT TV?
[SPEAKER_07]: This week in tech.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, basically, it lists a whole bunch of other things, but as we've announced earlier in the show, we've got our plan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and Ustream TV, actually, we actually have a channel on Ustream TV, we just never used it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, we were originally going to go with Ustream TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: We made a last-minute decision to switch to Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was after the Operator 11 fallout because I remember we were using them for a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'd actually created the Ustream TV account with the intention of going over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was something about Justin TV I just liked a little better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I think I like the way that fans could go in and cut out the highlight clips and you could upload things to YouTube and import things from YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: I felt Justin TV had a little more of the functionality.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Ustream seemed a little too big for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a lot more interactive, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I like Justin TV a little more.
[SPEAKER_06]: We prefer cozy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a little more cozy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, just to continue with the email, also TalkShoe.com does a live audio broadcast with chat room, but it needs to be downloaded first order to use the live server, and you can also record the shows as you do them, which are available in the show archive.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope that helps.
[SPEAKER_09]: If not, sorry and hope you find a solution soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the best, Steve in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, hopefully you'll be pleased with the earlier news about our solution.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're pretty excited about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Voltron!
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is pretty much sort of what we had kind of thought already.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, gentlemen and lady.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just watched Dead Fantasy 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you guys have seen the first one.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's nothing compared to the second.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think that it's amazing that someone could do this in their spare time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've looked at it several times now and can't help but wonder what DarkSakura thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I haven't seen it yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know she loves her fighting games in Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Monty Ohm has said that there are at least five more in the series.
[SPEAKER_09]: I won't spoil it for those who haven't seen it yet, but I've got a few questions.
[SPEAKER_09]: With the latest surprising characters, who do you think might make an appearance next?
[SPEAKER_09]: And finally, which side will win in the end?
[SPEAKER_09]: Seems the Final Fantasy team has an unfair advantage by using both weapons and magic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be surprised if they win, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lastly, I don't have the time to listen to the show live, but I've always downloaded the podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: It seems that there are always regular live listeners to support the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you guys can find a suitable alternative to Live 365, then how about a fundraiser?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it sounds a bit corny, but I've come to like the show very much and would hate to see any changes that would cripple the community that has grown around it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would be... I'll...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd be more than willing to donate money to keep the show going, and I'm sure most of the live listeners would as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for getting me through a rough day.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's from Recymo.
[SPEAKER_09]: And to be honest, we disagree with what Live 365 is doing, and it's more or less the point that we don't want to support what they're doing, no matter if we can afford it or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoa, the FU music came in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, where the hell is that music going?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's appropriate, so it's alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, again, thank you for the wonderful offer.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, we have another plan that we think will help actually grow our community a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Jamie, here's a little sneak peek of Dead Fantasy 2, which shows the... It's basically... I did watch some of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's just one giant fanboy orgasm in real form.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's... What is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's just special effect after special effect after...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I'm going to watch that one again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see dead or alive people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, well, it's Dead or Alive characters versus Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just one giant fanboy orgasm.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Riku just got thrown in that clip there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, sorry, I know that makes for horrible radio, but I wanted to show Jamie a little clip of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's completely awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we got an email from HeroAntagonist, which was a link, and it said, this seemed like something you'd want to see if you haven't already.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a bizarre twist between DDR Beatmania and a slot machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have something for him, that is, if he's still listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure if you've seen this yet, but on YouTube there's a blind gamer who goes by the nickname
[SPEAKER_09]: Geniuses Corruption, who has played through Zelda Ocarina of Time, Zelda Twilight Princess, and Castlevania Circle of the Moon, and posted videos of his conquests.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can see his page.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, again, Geniuses Corruption, geniuses being plural.
[SPEAKER_09]: Given that he has proven he is blind through the front page video of him beating a boss blindfolded, it just goes to show that even blind gamers can play video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: To Ranma of India, you are not alone.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are other gamers out there who were born blind and they play video games, so can you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's from GS68.
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game he was playing in... Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I lost the link.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh...
[SPEAKER_09]: I closed it, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he was playing through a GameCube game and doing fairly decently.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cheeseburger sent us a giant ASCII finger that says to live 365.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was very nice ASCII art.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was very impressed.
[SPEAKER_09]: J-Rod emailed one of the two that we got recently.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi OLR crew, love the show, keep up the awesome job.
[SPEAKER_09]: What I was writing about was concerning deeper characters and themes in video games and how long you think it will be before we actually start seeing this type of stuff in games.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are recently seeing a much greater character portrayal and writing with emotions like love with games like Mass Effect and others.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like to see deep and mature storylines involving other things and emotions that are quote too hot for video games to deal with like racism, sexism, homosexuality and various other things.
[SPEAKER_09]: American History X and Schindler's List are very powerful and well done films that deal with very mature subjects and are in good taste.
[SPEAKER_09]: It seems like companies such as Rockstar putting out games like Manhunt are actually setting us backwards when it comes to being taken seriously compared to other forms of entertainment like movies and books.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is this email sponsored by Olive Garden, home of the never-ending salads and breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a really good thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Japanese games have been doing it for a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would love to play these types of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it would be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, you only really see it in the occasional role-playing game that has the more mature themes, but I think it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't think they'd sell well is the unfortunate thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Hollywood, you can make a big budget movie, lots of special effects and explosions.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can make a big budget movie, or you can make a small budget movie that costs a lot less to make.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: A, doesn't get a lot of exposure, and B, usually the indie stuff is innovating on different types of gameplay, not necessarily new themes in game formats that we've already seen, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because when you talk about exploring those types of themes, well, you can't really do a lot of that in a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're talking about types of games that are really involved with story, so that's basically RPG and those types of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't see a lot of really...
[SPEAKER_06]: polished indie efforts in those realms, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think that's why you're right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be a long time, unfortunately, before we see something like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what it's going to take is it's going to take video games getting even bigger and bigger so that more and more money and there's more budgets for different types of experiments and try things.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think it would be great to have some of those things you mentioned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, like I said, quite a few games have come out overseas that
[SPEAKER_09]: dealt with deeper topics, but we won't get them over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last email from Mr. D. Big wave from across the pond to Sky, DarkSakura, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a UK listener who occasionally listens live and am as I write this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I must be crazy since the show starts about 1 to 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_09]: here, but I often find myself not getting a lot of sleep during the early hours of Monday morning due to having frequent uni deadlines.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your show keeps me going, so thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, DarkSakura's talk of Grandia reminded me of something I've been thinking about previously, memorable RPG moments.
[SPEAKER_06]: My memory of... Damn, that was fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you just brought up Grandia like an hour ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's instant gratification.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: My memory of Grandia is really patchy, and I found the crossing of the wall that marks the end of the world to be very memorable.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are your most memorable RPG scenes?
[SPEAKER_09]: To stop right there...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's one of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, the whole ghost ship part in Grandia I thought was really just awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to be cliche, but come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole, you know who... Well, the opera in 6, but the you know who dies in Final Fantasy 7 was really emotional and a really big step in games at that time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to be cliche, but that really is the one that comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was really emotional for me too, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: You emotionally overjoyed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I cheered so loudly, and I was like, yes!
[SPEAKER_09]: and I still to this day have my card with the stupid Hobag's death saved on it because I laughed my ass off and I spent the whole time screaming at Jenova so I can get to that part and watch the death.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give an answer that maybe the guy wasn't looking for, but I'll kind of take it in a different direction.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to say games like World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you do things with your guild, like for instance, I have a guild of mostly people I know offline.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have maybe a handful of OLR listeners in there, but not a few.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I've plugged it like a million times, I guess you all don't want to play WoW with us.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: See if I care.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, we have this guild on there and we're currently raiding Karazhan because we finally have enough people who are level 70 to start doing some of the 10-man raids.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'll tell you what, when we finally get the strategy down to beat one of the bosses, such as Maiden of Virtue, was one of those bosses where like the first couple times we went in there and did it, oh my god, she was so tough.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then we were finally able to overcome that and beat her.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were like so happy and like so excited because we really accomplished something, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, not like, oh my gosh, I'm going to run out naked through the streets.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there definitely is that emotion of, hey, look, we accomplished this together.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kind of a different type of answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not necessarily a scripted thing, but working together towards a common goal.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still laughed my ass off in Final Fantasy VII, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I laughed.
[SPEAKER_09]: to continue with the email personally mine are the Bridge Battle and Shining Force Escaping Midgar in Final Fantasy 7 and the aforementioned Wall at the End of the World in Grandia the Shining Force thing probably doesn't seem all that interesting to most people but that was my first RPG at age 6 in 1993 oh I feel old so it's got a special place in my heart speaking of sentimental games it'd also be cool to know what games are particularly special to you and why keep up the great show Mr. D
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as games that are special to me, Super Street Fighter 2 on Super Nintendo because it was my very first Super Nintendo game that was mine and not my brother's on my Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It belonged to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Special games...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't think of a whole lot that, like, Super Metroid, I suppose, would be one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because I think it's the really greatest game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have to, maybe I would go all the way back to the Atari 2600 and say things like Spider-Man, because those are some of my earliest gaming memories right there, so those games are definitely special.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have, you know, sorry, this really makes me feel old, but I remember being, you know, little, like a first grader,
[SPEAKER_09]: and going next door to my friend's house and playing their Odyssey 2 and playing... I want to say it was like a Lord of the Rings game or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: You play either as a fighter, a wizard, a changeling, or something else.
[SPEAKER_09]: And playing... What was that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Casey Munchkin's Crazy Chase that got sued for being like Pac-Man, which I actually still have a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know...
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess I kind of have good memories of that, but I also have good memories of playing Kix in elementary school.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll tell you what game I used to freaking love that's very special to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an old-ass computer game called Rogue.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you ever played this game, but you control a little happy face looking thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was all done in ASCII graphics, but it was an actual game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think like Epyx or somebody put it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you play this little ASCII happy face that went around through these tunnels.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were exploring, you know, like a dungeon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And creatures were giant capital letters that would, like a B for bat would attack you and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds like quite a number of the old MUDs I used to have.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was old school, but great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, also, I have to say, when I was in second or third grade, we had a Clicca Vision.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for me, it was always playing Venture and Mousetrap, which I suck at Venture now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, I guess it's like really a lot, because there's certain games that I would be playing at a time that I'd attach to certain things that were going on in my life at the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, like, I think it's entirely hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan was trying to, I guess, catalog things that had happened in his life
[SPEAKER_09]: and, um, he was doing a lot of it by sort of what he was playing at that time and what grade he was in.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that, you know, honestly, that's sort of how I correlate a lot of stuff happens to me too, because I'll remember, oh, this happened, and at the time I was playing this.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I have that kind of memory attachment, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, you're awfully quiet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot of special video games for you?
[SPEAKER_06]: He's looking at porn.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not looking at porn, I'm looking at news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gal's Panic is not a special game to you?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No more emails?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we have one particular attachment.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, our names are attached to.
[SPEAKER_09]: OLR the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: The text game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yes, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: The OLR text game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Put that on our wiki, people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you still get a copy of that?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got to be available somewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I've got it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, if you want to email us, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we're going to get to the Skype line very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have some gaming news first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there was a rumor going around that Def Leppard was going to be in Guitar Hero 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it actually ended up turning out that wasn't exactly true.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was during an interview with the band on the radio show Rock Align.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I guess Caller asked why none of their songs have been featured in Guitar Hero or Rockman.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, their guitarist, Phil Cullen, replied, revealing at least three of their hits would be featured in Guitar Hero 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock of Ages, Animal, and, of course, Photograph.
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem is, though, it actually isn't going to be featured in Guitar Hero 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually download content that's going to be coming out soon for Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: There will be Def Leppard songs, just not in Guitar Hero 4, at least not those songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will be Def Leppard.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, I was thinking, we just had a story a couple weeks ago that really made us think that arcades were dying.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we kind of already kind of knew that sadly arcades are dying and they're just not what they used to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, I think we had another story about, didn't we have the story last week about Namco's doing something with the Wii in their arcades or something, trying to like integrate all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we talked about it last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess somebody else has faith in arcade games because apparently Signature Devices, they're hardware and software developers, they have sent word out that they are putting final touches on a new four-player arcade game that will, quote, include several well-known comic book and television superheroes.
[SPEAKER_06]: As to who those are, that's still a mystery.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could be anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it could literally be anything from the Marvel DC world all the way to heroes from NBC, although I kind of doubt that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it's kind of interesting that all hope is not dead yet for arcades and depending on what names are attached to this game because you know well known quote unquote you know that could be Dora the Explorer as a hero to some and I don't know if that's going to be the one that gets people to come back so hopefully it's the right thing we'll hopefully get more information on that in the coming weeks
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, how about some other news then?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Capcom!
[SPEAKER_09]: As in Capcom's Gamers Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they're letting people who are not the press go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except they're only letting five of them go.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, basically, five lucky people are going to be able to get in and they're actually calling it Captivate 08.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is, I guess, kind of an interesting name.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're lucky, you get to get in and play with everybody else.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, um, basically, um, I don't really see, though, anything on here about how it actually is accomplished.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you have to write them, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a little thingy, email them, saying why you think you should be able to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they pick a winner out of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, there's actually a link on there afterwards that you basically said it, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beg!
[SPEAKER_07]: That still sucks, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get one and sell it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you should enter the contest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't tell them you do this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just tell them, you know, oh, I grew up on Mega Man and I love Capcom and Street Fighter is so memorable to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Write something really cheesy and maybe they'll pick you.
[SPEAKER_06]: They get to go anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not a cool lie to them like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not lying.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you've got to say that you're part of an independent podcast and that they don't give the little guy a fair shake and then you make them feel bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they don't care, then you say, well, fuck, your Mega Man games lately have sucked, so what do I care?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's say you enter it and then you lose because they say, oh, well, you know, you're a podcaster.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, then that's a double standard because then they're saying, oh, but podcasters and people like that aren't supposed to come to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So make up your mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't make any sense, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Podcasters and people in the media aren't supposed to come to their media event?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're not, you know, IGN or anything, so that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to play Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was it Star Force, Zerker X, you know, Sauron or Ninja?
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll all be on YouTube the day after anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just bitter like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the Gamer Day events we have gone to in the past have been kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, all two of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is kind of thrilling to be there, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Konami was the only ones that invited us and then they moved away.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, oh, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, there's a game out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is free to play, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to go to some stupid gamer's day to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game called Tetroid 2012.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a mashup of Tetris and Arkanoid.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, I think a little bit like Silent Hills, especially if you listen to some of the soundtrack for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really trippy.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's free to download.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually available on... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come over to the website.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a 111 meg download too, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of music and sound effects in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the website to go check it out, it's entity.be slash entity.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there's some links to the games that they make.
[SPEAKER_07]: They made, of course, this game and then, I guess, a remake of Tempest.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you're a fan of Tempest, you can check that out as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: I heart Tempest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might have to check that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does it go Super Zapper Recharge?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, but it's very trippy looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Before this, though, from what I remember, I guess that they used to do, like, demo scene stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, all the, like, encoding graphic little demos and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it is a very trippy-looking game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was looking at that Tetroid 2012 a little bit ago, and it definitely looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you charge up with, like, a little special meter, and then when you hit the special button, it flips the whole screen upside down, and then you turn into, like, you know, Arkanoid mode or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to admit, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: So hopefully we'll check that out a little later.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least maybe I'll download that and check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might be Link and you're in the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: world and you're trying to stab at asteroids.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then all of a sudden you're Pac-Man and you're in Arkanoid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It randomly changes your characters too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So sometimes you will have the really crappy Space Invaders ship and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of them can only shoot in one direction and you have to basically play them like their respective games.
[SPEAKER_06]: IndieGames.com
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the best name ever, Funk Monkey.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I made Polychromatic Funk Monkey a tile-based platforming game about building maps for tile-based platforming games.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Polychromatic Funk Monkey, the eponymous monkey of funk brings order and rhythm to his chaotic land arranging the blocks he finds into towering staircases and bridges in the sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like a riot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there's another game called Fishy Fishy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this might be one of my new favorite developers.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's
[SPEAKER_09]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can get them on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I will send an email this week and see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he'll have to wait because I'm not doing anything special for Life365, so maybe we can have him on our debut all games episode.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to say, though, I watched someone play through a whole game of Romchek fail.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was cracking up the entire time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Romchek win.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Win for reals.
[SPEAKER_09]: So guess what?
[SPEAKER_09]: We have more news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Paramount is going to be getting into games.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are going to be doing mobile, handheld, casual games because they make money.
[SPEAKER_09]: And a lot of them are talking about tie-ins between their movie franchises and these games.
[SPEAKER_09]: So hey, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the other thing I bet happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: Paramount realized, writer's strike, loss of money, people aren't going to the movies like they used to, video games, money machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would you do?
[SPEAKER_07]: They also may have realized, hey, Sony, Warner, Vividi, they're all in games as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Vivendi?
[SPEAKER_07]: Vivendi.
[SPEAKER_07]: You said Vinvidi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fusion of Vivendi and Invidia.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vinvidia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Vivendi, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and Disney or Buena Vista.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all in games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, why not them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_07]: One game that they're not making, but you can get for dirt cheap, at least this week in Steam, has been offering Prey for $4.95.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week and only.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, apparently if you listen to this on podcast, you've missed out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless you bought this already.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, uh,
[SPEAKER_07]: Get it now, because you only have a few hours left before this deal is up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Pray, for those who may not remember, was a 3D Realms game, not Duke Nukem Forever, and involved you, a Native American, to be basically abducted onto a ship where there's a bunch of weird, crazy shit, and you can never die.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can die in the very early levels if you're not good at first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_06]: I died once in the early levels because I'm horrible at first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played it on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not bad, and it has a beautiful soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has an absolutely gorgeous soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's from the guy who did Oblivion and Guild Wars and all that, so you know the music's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game itself, kind of a little short.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember it kind of just ended suddenly, but definitely made way for a sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: So give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're already getting a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you're just a little quiet, but maybe that's our studio mic.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just trying to... Just trying to go through, you know... It kind of sucks that you have to ditch Live 365, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it kind of sucks they had to double their rates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, you are really quiet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you get closer to your microphone?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just us.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're coming through really quiet on the thing.
Perfect, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: So it sucks we have to leave Life 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me see, I was going to get Rainbow Six Vegas, but what I read is that Ubisoft's not doing their job and trying to get the shit out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: all the bugs on the PS3 and 360 that are making me jittery.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just making me nervous right now before I even buy the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said it was Rainbow Six Vegas 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: 2, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you played Rainbow Six Vegas 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like the Tom Clancy games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have some folks on my Xbox Live list though that have been playing nothing but that lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're lucky enough to do the crap that the current bugs that haven't been fixed yet
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you actually buy the game or were you just worried about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just read it on Kotaku, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just read it from other folks that the PS3 version of the servers were basically just getting really flaky and just not connecting through games.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 360 version was about the same with very noticeable glitches and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm waiting right now, so I'm getting paid tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully, if there's a patch coming out very soon, that's all I need for me to actually go down to GameStop and buy the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, is there anybody in chat at our chatroom, chat.orangelaunchradio.com, that maybe has some suggestions on this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, is it worth buying it now, or should you wait for a patch, or what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, yeah, Loki doesn't play those games, I don't think Jamie's played it, and I have not played it, so I'm kind of curious if anyone in our chat...
[SPEAKER_06]: has anything to say about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's part of the beauty of doing this live with the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: When we are not familiar with it, hopefully somebody else is.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else is on your mind, Zaku, while we wait for some comments?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I don't like to bring up Bomani that much, but EMUs, by now you've probably heard it's already rolling out on somewhat of a national level, although it's in one arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we covered the one arcade a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has it rolled out to more yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, no unlocks so far, so I'm not sure whether, you know, at this rate if we're trying to catch up to Japan in terms of unlocking the games, by the time they're done, we'll be done in like, what, October, November, at that rate?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they've only got one arcade working on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we got a response about Vegas 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ross2UT says, Well, I got my version of Rainbow Six Vegas 2 exchanged for the 360, and it's fine, aside from the odd frame rate drop, which never becomes unplayable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Online co-op is absolutely amazing, especially as you actually go through the story this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like a fairly favorable review.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Zaku, anything else before we let you go and take some more calls?
[SPEAKER_02]: Any plans on finding a good replacement for Live 365 that won't involve paying royalties up the ass?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, listen to Part A. We are going to be merging with AllGames.com and doing our show live on their feed, and you won't have to register or any of that stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, in terms of the radio station, that's done for good, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as the 24-hour day, 7-day-a-week feed, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not going to be operating it on Life 35 anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Instead, we're going to be trying to come together with other independent podcasters to create a Voltron network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Will you still be able to play the music eventually?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing is changing on our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything is staying the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to be kept in the loop just like everyone else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just got in right now, just playing my 360 up until like an hour ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, check out part A when it goes up later tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's all the details?
[SPEAKER_06]: All righty?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you'd like to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's take another call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been reading the comments for this one story and thinking about how PC gaming is dying.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a lot of comments saying about how PC gaming is not dead and how PC gaming is inferior to consoles and crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_00]: They got me wondering, I mean, aside from the games, what do consoles have on PCs?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, and then, like, there's some people talking about how, like, keyboard and mouse, like, goes great with, like, how, like, there should be keyboard and mouse support for every PS3 game, among other things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think there's a lot of truth to that whole PC gaming is dying.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's that when a game comes out on the PC and the console, the console tends to do a little better.
[SPEAKER_06]: But come on.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what I'm focusing on.
[SPEAKER_06]: But look at a game like World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's huge.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's only on the PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're not going to hear... I'm not exactly talking about PC games dying.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just talking about a lot of people saying how PC gaming is superior to console gaming and...
[SPEAKER_00]: How PC can do everything for your homework or browsing the internet and you don't have to buy $500 consoles every few years, just upgraded PCs.
[SPEAKER_00]: With that said, what do consoles have on PCs besides the games on them?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Those that remember when the Commodore 64 was out in this country and it did very well in Europe as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one reason the Commodore 64 did so great is because not only did the Commodore 64 have a monitor it would hook up to, but it also would hook up to your TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was a pretty big deal to have a home computer that actually was on your TV as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think there really is just that convenience of having it in your living room.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, even games that normally go on consoles, like 2D platformers and scrolling shooters, I mean, there are... I mean, there are, like, free games that they can download on their PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, like, look at Cave Story and, just for Dark Tetsuya, La Milana.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, those are great platforms, but they're not on consoles.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, they're for the PC, and they're free.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I can't name any free console games or free indie console games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give you one, and I hate to say it, but Yaris.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there was also Aegis Wing and a few of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: A very, very few handful available on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to see more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to see a subscription-based available service or some more free perks on the consoles here and there, but
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very easy in comparison to just fire up a coding program and a C++ compiler or whatever language you want to program in and make your game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's kind of the difference is that it's more accessible to make stuff indie-wise on the PC than it is for consoles who have a very closed authoring format.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well GS68, do you have anything else you want to share or ask us tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I love the ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's on camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad it's not on the camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my ferret headgear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I wear the ferret on my head for a little bit on the cam?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know if Justin TV is working right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been very terrible at checking that chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's DJ Ranma S from Anime Jam Sessions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, hello, DJ Ranma S from Anime Jam Sessions.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much, and that was me that told you that we were doing a live feed of OLR from Anime Boston.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it actually happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Partially.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we got there, we started setting up, I started the feed, and I'm like, okay, where's the power?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the power?
[SPEAKER_04]: I see other dealers, other vendors with power.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I go over to the convention head, center head to get power.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like 119 for the full weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're like  This is a long no answer, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: So it was like, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we ended up having the feed a little bit on Friday and for about a couple of hours on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Were you here for the announcement?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that was a heck of a show to be listening to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was having a WrestleMania 24 party, but I did hear the announcement about where OLR is heading off to.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is, I actually know somebody that probably would have kept you guys going for 24-7.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got a lot of great offers along those types of lines, but we're excited about the powers of Voltron.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what else is on your mind, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to basically give you guys a basic con rap of anime Boston, and believe it or not, you want to know what most popular items in the dealer's room was?
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy VII related material.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goji is always the number two item sold at dealers rooms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dolphins.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet there were some though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did see a couple.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I give up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo merchandise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Almost every single vendor had all kinds of Super Mario Brothers or standard Nintendo merchandise that was selling like hotcakes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, was WYSIWYG there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, they were.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are the big culprits for the Nintendo goods, plus they sell Pocky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they weren't selling Pocky at this con, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sad!
[SPEAKER_04]: They can't, because when your convention is in a convention center, according to the contract, you're not allowed to sell food.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that sucks, because I bought every burger at Faname last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: is that that candy hamburger stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: yes the candy hamburger I love that stuff that stuff is really good well that stuff is fine but you got people you can't sell like Pocky or Ramenade and stuff like that that you can't sell lame yeah yeah I know I know it's kind of crazy though but me and my crew we're trying to figure out like a way around that well good luck to you how was the con?
[SPEAKER_06]: otherwise good times?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number one problem was the long, long, long, long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I mention long lines for registration?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: That seems to be the problem with a lot of anime cons is long registration lines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but at most cons, it's like you wait no more than an hour to get your badge.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were people that were waiting anywhere between 5 and 11 hours for their badges.
[SPEAKER_06]: 11 hours to get a badge?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I'm not kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got to be fucking kidding me.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's crazy talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they printed them out on these machines and the machines broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's only four people on registration and the lines were going forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone posted a link.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did a parody of Still Alive to Still in Line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think, and I've been suggesting this for a while now, for conventions they should take the old E3 approach and mail your pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: or just don't make fancy fucking badges
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Bulk rate, I guess, would be available for business.
[SPEAKER_09]: But have them print it out and, you know, you pay like X amount extra to have, you know, your badge mailed to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I actually know a couple of people that are like reg, throwing heads at worked reg.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they say it just doesn't work that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wouldn't work out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wouldn't be all that cost effective.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's the paying a little extra.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that was the only method that someone wants to avoid the long line, then just say, well, I will pay another $5 for postage and you can mail it to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what some cons are doing now, they're offering like two-year badges, three-year badges, lifetime badges, and pre-con night.
[SPEAKER_04]: The thing is, not everybody's going to come up Thursday night for a convention, so to give that option, and a lot of people still do it, but the difference is you show up Thursday, you get your badge under 15 minutes tops.
[SPEAKER_09]: AX did the day before thing, and it was just as much of a, pardon the expression, clusterfuck as it is doing day of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, if you're not there by 10 a.m., you're basically SOL.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we've got to wrap up, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely some lessons learned for anybody thinking about throwing on a convention in the near future, but any last-minute thoughts for our folks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Three links I posted in the chat room, pictures from my website.
[SPEAKER_04]: One picture is a cart, a facial looking like World 1-1 from Super Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the last two pictures is the old man from The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one says, it's dangerous to go alone, take this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the second one says, Dodongo dislikes smoke.
[SPEAKER_06]: I figured you'd get a kick out of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I'm looking at the picture.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know this is horrible radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there actually is somebody dressed up holding a big old poster board that says it's dangerous to go alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But where's the sword?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the cannon.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you go to DJRanmas.net and click on Gallery, you'll see all the pictures from Anime Boston 08.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like 320 shots I took.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Ranma, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: One more call and we're going to call it a night.
[SPEAKER_06]: 877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And while we wait for a call, Loki, any quick last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I've been gathering stories this entire time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we got one more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love cutting you off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: The ferret's going to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been hanging out in your chat room trying to calm everybody's fears.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, about like, OMG, we're going to have to suddenly change everything we're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm kind of like, have you ever listened to the other shows on allgames.com?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would we have to change other than maybe I'll have to bring on a soundboard?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you'll have to get rid of the ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the ferret.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're going to put a big picture on our, big thing on our site, you know, saying, hey, you know, Orange Signs Radio is coming in, we're going to get, like, Tingle, and we're going to Photoshop Loki's head on it, and that's going to be your new logo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, these are all the type of editorial decisions that are being made for us now.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's as close as you'll ever get.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll go buy Eye of Judgment again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go ahead, Neil.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many copies are we up to?
[SPEAKER_06]: We haven't had an update in a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I want you to look it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: The listeners demand to know this.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's new in your gaming world, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_06]: What types of stuff have you been playing lately and enjoying?
[SPEAKER_03]: Believe it or not, recently I've picked up, I got an old retro Japanese RPG kick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I recently started playing the original Suikoden again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was mainly because somebody wrote me on my PS3 saying, why don't you ever play games on your PS3?
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm playing Suikoden.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're playing a PS1 game on your PS3, nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Leading the All Games Radio team.
[SPEAKER_06]: I stopped running that app a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if I get a PlayStation 3, Bobby, we will work together, this Voltron of podcasts, to cure cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because only Voltron can cure cancer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's where we're at right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're still at .18 million.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the problem is it's not tracking the UK sales.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I can guarantee that they're not any more than the US sales.
[SPEAKER_07]: So even if the number were doubled, you would still not be to where you need to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very sad to hear that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sad to hear that.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, they only sold, was it week 10, which I guess was last week, they sold 8,627 units in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now how about copies of Let's Ride Friends Forever?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even think that's on here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think they're even tracking that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll get back to you on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, please do.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not tracking it because it's just too many.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It blew sales through the roof.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, any other things that our listeners ought to know about this whole all games transition or anything they should know about allgames.com and why it's the place for OLR?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, for one, no more ads if you try to listen to the live stream and no more funky players that you have to click through things to get to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You go to allgames.com or you go to allgamesradio.com
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be very easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a higher quality, no more MP3 Pro.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we don't plan to have you guys change anything music-wise or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know a lot of people are like, well, what about the music and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: And Rob, you know that I'm willing to talk to you about that and maybe even doing a music block from your library or even just merging your library of music into ours during the 24-7 stream.
[SPEAKER_03]: and bring in some of your other talk programs over.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I'm not keeping this only to the Sunday night thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's part of, you know, why it was a good idea is that, you know, it's not just, you know, that All Games is sucking this show up and tearing it away from what we had.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it is kind of like a, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think one way when we were kind of talking about it was that it's now the resources of the three of us that make this show happen and some of the other people behind OLR are now troops in the allgames.com universe and can work towards building good ideas there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it's going to be great because I know everybody over there has got ideas and Lord knows we have ideas of our own.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just going to keep going from there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a new chapter.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll send the camera crew up there for Loki and the Tingle outfit and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be awesome whenever that sells a million copies.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be at PAX.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I will say this, you know, because I know you're thinking about coming up to PAX.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're actually trying to do something really big at PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: In terms of live streaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kropotkin and Hendrix are actually coming out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kropotkin's coming out from the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that is big.
[SPEAKER_03]: Flying to PAX.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we've got a couple of our, I think, you know, Chatterbox is always up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Evil Avatar, it's their 10th anniversary for evilavatar.com, so they're doing a big thing as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, Evil Avatar Radio is one of our affiliates and stuff, so we're planning on doing some big stuff at PAX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'd love to see you guys represented with or without the Tingle outfit, but I think the Tingle outfit would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's mid-August, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Last weekend in August.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually Labor Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which means, well, it's the same weekend as DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, for you especially.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I chose PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, PAX is more gaming anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: DragonCon's a little more D20s and stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: DragonCon's more, you know, let's all fawn over Joss Whedon and everything he's touched.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joss!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, DarkSakura might choose to go there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't phrase it that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Josh is the man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely, I haven't been to PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely, I like what I'm hearing, and we'll have to see what we can do to make that happen, especially if it's a long weekend and it's that far off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't see why at least I can't get up there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully, if the monies work out, we can get everybody up there somehow.
[SPEAKER_06]: We might be able to make it work.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have to get the wife to agree to let Loki go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might actually be able to go because we do our game conferencing at my work,
[SPEAKER_06]: E3 E3
[SPEAKER_03]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's a lot of stuff that E3 didn't have.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's way more community oriented and it's basically what people thought E3 was.
[SPEAKER_03]: People who've never been to E3, it's what they thought it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like it's going to be a ton of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll definitely have to make that happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only reason I didn't go last year, the only thing that stopped me from going last year is that my BFF from college got married that exact same weekend and she said if I did not go to her wedding I would be killed.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this year no one's getting married that I know of.
[SPEAKER_03]: No weddings.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do kill them.
[SPEAKER_06]: No weddings.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or don't plan it during PAX because I want to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be doing live streaming from there, and so we'd love to have you guys as part of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what we can do, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Bobby, we've got to let you go because we're going to wrap this show up before it's getting really late for you guys out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kill the ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll try.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we look forward to being partnered up with you on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be a lot of fun on April 13th.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's D-Day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always enjoy hearing from Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we're going to close up the Skype line now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're running a little long here in Part B, which is okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can go as long as we want, and we'll get to continue to go as long as we want on all games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not scheduling anything after us.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, but Loki did want to get to some last-minute stories, so I suppose we should get those out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I have a ton of them now, thanks to you cutting me off all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll just go down the list then of all the wonderful stuff, whether it be important or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: SOCOM Confrontation comes out on the PSN, or the PlayStation Network, September 16th.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it'll be a great addition to, I guess, the SOCOM series.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, yeah, look forward to that in the fall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another game coming in the fall, Far Cry 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's coming to consoles or at least Xbox 360 and PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: as well as PC no word on exactly when but fall-ish area Madden turns 20 this year and Madden 09 will be coming out August 12th as well as a collector's edition which will feature exclusively NFL Head Coach 09 which I'm glad because that game sucks or at least looks like crap I know the first one didn't sell very well for me and I don't want to push this one so awesome and let's see here
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a rumor about what Sega will be showing off at their Gamers Day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of the stuff rumored in there, a brand new Knights game and also a new Eternal Arcadia game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some other stuff, of course, a preview for Sonic Unleashed, which I think we've all seen that anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoopsie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a game called The Crucible, Evil Within.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope that's not based off the book.
[SPEAKER_06]: and... You know where I want to go with this and I'm just biting my tongue.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that is too funny that they are actually thinking about putting a game about witch trials out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Witch!
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's based on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't write that, folks.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't write it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Super Monkey Ball for the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tentative.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, Samba de Amigo on the iPhone?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: We.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's coming out this summer, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember we talked a little bit a while back about that homebrew game being made, Super Mario Fusion, that's going to have levels featuring Mega Man and Halo and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they have a new video up now that shows one of the new suits you can get from Mario, which is a Mega Man suit with all the sound effects and stuff from Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also apparently a Halo Spartan suit that you can get from Mario as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So looking for that game when that comes out eventually.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a rumor that some DS-like colors are coming to the UK soon, including green, ice, blue, and red.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm not surprised because Nintendo likes to put out a ton of different colors of these things.
[SPEAKER_07]: A French retailer is listing Grand Theft Auto 4 for the DS, although that might be a misprint, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here...
[SPEAKER_07]: EchoChrome's coming to the US like we said, I think sometime in April for $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right now you can actually download on the PlayStation Store R-Type Command if you want to play a demo of that for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's that one that's like a RTS R-Type game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another game coming out in April, Happy Tree Friends False Alarms coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be...
[SPEAKER_07]: XBOX Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_07]: 3-4 player multiplayer tag battles and single player standard driller single player quest driller 100 puzzles so that's kind of neat let's see here and that's it alright that was a lot of last minute stories there's a lot of late breaking stuff tonight or just stuff we were too lazy to get to otherwise and I'm going to post this in chat room it's a wallpaper featuring portal you know their portal warning signs it's funny
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we'll check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to bring us to the end of our show, except we've got one more thing to do, and that's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is, why did I go out and get the ferret?
[SPEAKER_06]: I could have just told her that I lost it forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm nice, that's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm super nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could have kicked you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is I want to get to playing some more games this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a lot on my plate and a lot that I haven't gotten to yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And hopefully we'll get some curling action going on after the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: on JustinTV.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's something you kind of have to learn.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'd be pretty pissed off if I didn't have a high-def TV and I was trying to do video out on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently it works for UMD movies, but why they can't implement that for the composite cables is beyond me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well that's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to us and downloading and supporting independent radio and independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, if you like what you hear, just tell a couple people you know about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how we will slowly take over the world with our friends at the Voltron of podcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next week for the last show on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, honestly, for most of you folks that listen on the podcast forum, you're going to be like, what changed?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: So,
[SPEAKER_01]: that's going to do it though for this week so until next time we'll see you here on Orange Lounge Radio you've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production for more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com see you next week